<tv date="20260715164900 " generator-info-name="TV5-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV5-Source-EPG"><channel id="465032">
    <display-name lang="US">AMC HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464745">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO East</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465201">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO Drama</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465255">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO Hits</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465104">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO Zone HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465302">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO West</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465284">
    <display-name lang="US">MGM+ Hits HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465261">
    <display-name lang="US">MGM+ HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464850">
    <display-name lang="US">MoreMax HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465332">
    <display-name lang="US">Paramount+ with Showtime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465402">
    <display-name lang="US">Showtime 2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464890">
    <display-name lang="US">SHO x BET HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9315">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Cinema Select</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464979">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Comedy HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464893">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Encore HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465242">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Encore Family SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465115">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Cinema HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465109">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Kids HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464973">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Encore Westerns SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465397">
    <display-name lang="US">The Movie Channel Extra HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9304">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Utsav GOLD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260715154500 +0000" stop="20260715184500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Die Hard With a Vengeance</title>
    <desc>Detective John McClane (Bruce Willis) is now divorced, alcoholic and jobless after getting fired for his reckless behavior and bad attitude. He is called back into action, however, when a cryptic terrorist (Jeremy Irons) takes New York City hostage in a lethal game of "Simon Says" and refuses to speak with anyone but McClane. Teaming up with a street-savvy electrician named Zeus Carver (Samuel L. </desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260715184500 +0000" stop="20260715211500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Beekeeper</title>
    <desc>One man's brutal campaign for vengeance takes on national stakes after it's revealed he's a former operative of a powerful and clandestine organization known as Beekeepers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260715211500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wrath of Man</title>
    <desc>Mysterious and wild-eyed, a new security guard for a cash truck surprises his co-workers when he unleashes precision skills during a heist. The crew is left wondering who he is and where he came from. Soon, the marksman's ultimate motive becomes clear as he takes dramatic and irrevocable steps to settle a score.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716021500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beverly Hills Cop</title>
    <desc>After his childhood buddy is murdered while visiting Detroit, rebellious cop Axel Foley (Eddie Murphy) follows the leads to Beverly Hills, Calif., under the auspices of a vacation. He checks in with old friend Jenny Summers (Lisa Eilbacher) and starts to believe her boss, art dealer Victor Maitland (Steven Berkoff), might somehow be involved in the murder. However, Lt. Bogomil (Ronny Cox) of the B</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716021500 +0000" stop="20260716041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beverly Hills Cop II</title>
    <desc>The hard-nosed Detroit cop returns to Los Angeles to help solve another case. This time he must direct his efforts towards unraveling the Alphabet Crimes, a series of robberies committed by leather-jacketed punks. The investigation puts him on the trail of an illegal arms dealer and his hit lady.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716041500 +0000" stop="20260716061500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caddyshack</title>
    <desc>Danny Noonan (Michael O'Keefe), a teen down on his luck, works as a caddy at the snob-infested Bushwood Country Club to raise money for his college education. In an attempt to gain votes for a college scholarship reserved for caddies, Noonan volunteers to caddy for a prominent and influential club member (Ted Knight). Meanwhile, Danny struggles to prepare for the high pressure Caddy Day golf tourn</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716061500 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beverly Hills Cop</title>
    <desc>After his childhood buddy is murdered while visiting Detroit, rebellious cop Axel Foley (Eddie Murphy) follows the leads to Beverly Hills, Calif., under the auspices of a vacation. He checks in with old friend Jenny Summers (Lisa Eilbacher) and starts to believe her boss, art dealer Victor Maitland (Steven Berkoff), might somehow be involved in the murder. However, Lt. Bogomil (Ronny Cox) of the B</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Walking Dead</title>
    <desc>Every story and battle from the first half of the season comes crashing together in this action-packed, emotional mid-season finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Freedom to Leave the House! Inogen Portable Oxygen</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716113000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Car Repair Secrets!</title>
    <desc>Save thousands on car repairs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716123000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Protect Your Family From Identity Theft</title>
    <desc>Every 5 seconds there's a victim of identity theft; LifeLock helps alert you, restore your identity, and reimburse lost funds—leading the way in protecting families every day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Three Stooges</title>
    <desc>The boys unwittingly re-enlist under their old sergeant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716133000 +0000" stop="20260716163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fifth Element</title>
    <desc>The Earth is about to be destroyed by a huge ball of fire racing toward the planet. Cornelius, an old monk, knows how to stop the burning sphere with the help of Korben Dallas, a taxi driver and former secret agent and a woman named Leeloo.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716163000 +0000" stop="20260716193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">White House Down</title>
    <desc>Capitol police officer John Cale has just been denied his dream job of protecting President James Sawyer as a member of the Secret Service. Not wanting to disappoint his young daughter with the bad news, Cale takes her on a tour of the White House. While he and his daughter are there, a heavily armed paramilitary group attacks and seizes control. As the nation's government dissolves in chaos, only</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716193000 +0000" stop="20260716223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Die Hard</title>
    <desc>New York City policeman John McClane is visiting his estranged wife and two daughters on Christmas Eve. He joins her at a holiday party in the headquarters of the Japanese-owned business she works for. But the festivities are interrupted by a group of terrorists who take over the exclusive high-rise, and everyone in it. Very soon McClane realizes that there's no one to save the hostages -- but him</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260716223000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Die Hard 2</title>
    <desc>A year after his heroics in L.A., detective John McClane (Bruce Willis) is mixed up in another terrorist plot, this time at Washington Dulles International Airport, where he is waiting for his wife (Bonnie Bedelia). That same night, South American politico and drug profiteer Ramon Esperanza (Franco Nero) is arriving in U.S. custody. McClane takes action when a treasonous ex-colonel (William Sadler</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464745" start="20260715154400 +0000" stop="20260715164800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>Alicent risks everything to fulfill her end of the bargain; Rhaenyra must decide whether the Iron Throne is worth the cost.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260715164800 +0000" stop="20260715174500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>Rhaenyra, driven by her faith in Alicent, prepares to take King's Landing while the Triarchy sets sail to confront Corlys at the Gullet.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260715174500 +0000" stop="20260715185100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260715185100 +0000" stop="20260715203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dead of Winter</title>
    <desc>A grief-stricken widow stops by a remote cabin after getting lost on the back roads of Minnesota in the middle of winter. She soon finds herself in a desperate fight for survival as she encounters a murderous couple holding a young woman hostage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260715203000 +0000" stop="20260715212900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Burning Man grows from an anti-establishment group in San Francisco, founded by Larry Harvey in the 1980s, to a multi-million-dollar event with thousands of attendees and the backing of billionaire tech donors; first-time Burners look forward to the experience, while repeat attendees and organizers prep for the unpredictable as COVID-19 threatens the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260715212900 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Marty Supreme</title>
    <desc>Marty Mauser, a wily hustler with a dream no one respects, goes to hell and back in pursuit of greatness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716003700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>Larry crashes a party in Boston Harbor; Joe McCarthy airs his grievances on the senate floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716003700 +0000" stop="20260716014300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716014300 +0000" stop="20260716033300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Long Walk</title>
    <desc>Teens participate in a grueling high-stakes contest where they must continuously walk or be shot by a member of their military escort.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716033300 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Us</title>
    <desc>Accompanied by her husband, son and daughter, Adelaide Wilson returns to the beachfront home where she grew up as a child. Haunted by a traumatic experience from the past, Adelaide grows increasingly concerned that something bad is going to happen. Her worst fears soon become a reality when four masked strangers descend upon the house, forcing the Wilsons into a fight for survival. When the masks </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716062900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Burning Man grows from an anti-establishment group in San Francisco, founded by Larry Harvey in the 1980s, to a multi-million-dollar event with thousands of attendees and the backing of billionaire tech donors; first-time Burners look forward to the experience, while repeat attendees and organizers prep for the unpredictable as COVID-19 threatens the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716062900 +0000" stop="20260716073500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716073500 +0000" stop="20260716081100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>Larry crashes a party in Boston Harbor; Joe McCarthy airs his grievances on the senate floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716081100 +0000" stop="20260716095000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Miss You, Love You</title>
    <desc>A blunt, grieving widow is forced to plan her husband's funeral with a total stranger: her estranged son's assistant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716095000 +0000" stop="20260716113400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The LEGO NINJAGO Movie</title>
    <desc>The battle for NINJAGO City calls to action young Master Builder Lloyd, aka the Green Ninja, along with his friends, also secret ninja warriors. Led by Master Wu, as wise-cracking as he is wise, they must defeat the evil warlord Garmadon, who also happens to be Lloyd's dad. Pitting father against son, the epic showdown tests these fierce but undisciplined modern-day ninjas as they learn to check t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716113400 +0000" stop="20260716135800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aquaman</title>
    <desc>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, the city of Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people -- and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur, Orm's half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne. With help from royal counselor Vulko, Arthur</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716135800 +0000" stop="20260716160400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aquaman and the Lost Kingdom</title>
    <desc>After failing to defeat Aquaman the first time, Black Manta wields the power of the mythic Black Trident to unleash an ancient and malevolent force. Hoping to end his reign of terror, Aquaman forges an unlikely alliance with his brother, Orm, the former king of Atlantis. Setting aside their differences, they join forces to protect their kingdom and save the world from irreversible destruction.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716160400 +0000" stop="20260716171000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716171000 +0000" stop="20260716181000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Burning Man grows from an anti-establishment group in San Francisco, founded by Larry Harvey in the 1980s, to a multi-million-dollar event with thousands of attendees and the backing of billionaire tech donors; first-time Burners look forward to the experience, while repeat attendees and organizers prep for the unpredictable as COVID-19 threatens the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716181000 +0000" stop="20260716195300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rover</title>
    <desc>In the near future, mankind's greed and excesses have pushed civilization to the breaking point. Society is in decline, and the rule of law has disintegrated. Hardened drifter Eric (Guy Pearce) wanders across this dangerous and desolate landscape. When thieves steal Eric's car -- and only remaining possession -- they leave behind Rey (Robert Pattinson), a wounded comrade. Eric forces Rey to help h</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716195300 +0000" stop="20260716202900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>Larry crashes a party in Boston Harbor; Joe McCarthy airs his grievances on the senate floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716202900 +0000" stop="20260716213500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716213500 +0000" stop="20260716231300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Evil Dead Rise</title>
    <desc>A reunion between two estranged sisters gets cut short by the rise of flesh-possessing demons, thrusting them into a primal battle for survival as they face the most nightmarish version of family imaginable.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464745" start="20260716231300 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dumb Money</title>
    <desc>Everyday people flip the script on Wall Street and get rich by turning GameStop into one of the world's hottest companies. In the middle of everything is Keith Gill, a regular guy who starts it all by sinking his life savings into the stock. When his social media posts start blowing up, so does his life and the lives of everyone following him. As a stock tip becomes a movement, everyone gets wealt</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465201" start="20260715154400 +0000" stop="20260715164000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>An unfortunate development finds George's new rail station under threat; Marian continues to see Mr. Raikes despite Agnes' warnings.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260715164000 +0000" stop="20260715173700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>In the aftermath of a tragedy, George agrees to help Bertha; a visit has a lasting impact on the staff of Russell house.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260715173700 +0000" stop="20260715182500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Bertha, Marian, Aurora, and Peggy make an overnight trip to see Clara Barton speak; Gladys' desired beau is invited to dinner.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260715182500 +0000" stop="20260715192000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>As George fights to protect his public image, Agnes' status quo is disrupted; Armstrong intensifies her campaign against Peggy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260715192000 +0000" stop="20260715200700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>As Edison's illuminating electricity demonstration sparks conversation, George prepares for a legal battle, and Bannister plots revenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260715200700 +0000" stop="20260715205700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Peggy reveals the truth about her past; George's day in court arrives; Marian considers her romantic future.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260715205700 +0000" stop="20260715215900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Marian's grand plan is threatened; Bertha and Mrs. Astor lock horns over Gladys' debut; Peggy is stunned.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260715215900 +0000" stop="20260715225900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Agnes shares news of her nephew Dashiell's imminent arrival in New York; Bertha decides to back the new Metropolitan Opera House.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260715225900 +0000" stop="20260715235300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>George delivers a final decision to Oscar; Peggy is welcomed back into the Van Rhijn household by all but one; Marian meets a new match.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260715235300 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>A surprise guest attends Bertha's fundraiser; Ada organizes a luncheon for Mr. Forte; Peggy presses Mr. Fortune about Tuskegee.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716005000 +0000" stop="20260716014300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Bertha angles for position with a visiting Duke; with Marian's help, Ada continues to see Mr. Forte; Peggy travels to Alabama.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716014300 +0000" stop="20260716024100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>After sharing her news, Ada questions moving ahead without Agnes' support; Peggy experiences the dangers of the South.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716024100 +0000" stop="20260716033700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>As George heads to Pittsburgh to deal with the potential strike, Bertha learns that the Duke will return for the Metropolitan Opera's opening night; Bannister tries to retrieve an incriminating letter from the Russell house.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716033700 +0000" stop="20260716043100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>As New York celebrates a historic event, Bertha reconsiders her loyalty to the Met while Marian has doubts about her future.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716043100 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>The staff questions its future at Rhijn's house, just as Peggy questions her future at The New York Globe; Marian confesses her true feelings to Dashiell; the opera war reaches its climax.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716062300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>George has ambitious plans to build a railway line between New York, Chicago and Los Angeles, but his plans are met with resistance; Bertha is busy preparing for the Duke's arrival.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716062300 +0000" stop="20260716071700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Amid their domestic quibbles, Agnes and Ada welcome the Scotts into their home; Bertha and George disagree about Gladys's future.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716071700 +0000" stop="20260716081600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>George negotiates with the Duke.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716081600 +0000" stop="20260716091600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Bertha deals with unwanted rumors in the press and the surprise arrival of her sister Monica.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716091600 +0000" stop="20260716101300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Gladys adjusts to her changed circumstances; Larry runs into a familiar face; Peggy gets an opportunity from an old colleague.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716101300 +0000" stop="20260716111400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Marian has doubts.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716111400 +0000" stop="20260716121300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Mrs Astor discusses the future of her Newport ball with Bertha; Larry receives disturbing news; Mrs Kirkland gets information about Peggy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716121300 +0000" stop="20260716132200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gilded Age</title>
    <desc>Bertha finalizes the guest list for the ball and faces the consequences; Dr. Kirkland makes a decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716132200 +0000" stop="20260716150700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wuthering Heights</title>
    <desc>In this adaptation of the classic Emily Brontë novel set in 19th-century England, wealthy young Cathy Earnshaw (Merle Oberon) shares a loving bond with Heathcliff (Laurence Olivier), a poor childhood friend who now works in her stables. Unfortunately, things become complicated when the affluent Edgar Linton (David Niven) decides to pursue Cathy, and Heathcliff leaves out of resentment. Though Heat</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716150700 +0000" stop="20260716161300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716161300 +0000" stop="20260716191000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Batman</title>
    <desc>Batman ventures into Gotham City's underworld when a sadistic killer leaves behind a trail of cryptic clues. As the scale of the perpetrator's plans become clear, he must bring justice to the abuse of power and corruption that plagues the metropolis.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716191000 +0000" stop="20260716204400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Curse of La Llorona</title>
    <desc>In the 1970s Los Angeles, the legendary ghost La Llorona is stalking the night -- and the children. Ignoring the eerie warning of a troubled mother, a social worker and her own kids are drawn into a frightening supernatural realm. Their only hope of surviving La Llorona's deadly wrath is a disillusioned priest who practices mysticism to keep evil at bay.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716204400 +0000" stop="20260716230200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sinners</title>
    <desc>Trying to leave their troubled lives behind, twin brothers return to their Mississippi hometown to start again, only to discover that an even greater evil is waiting to welcome them back.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260716230200 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465255" start="20260715153000 +0000" stop="20260715163100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Burning Man grows from an anti-establishment group in San Francisco, founded by Larry Harvey in the 1980s, to a multi-million-dollar event with thousands of attendees and the backing of billionaire tech donors; first-time Burners look forward to the experience, while repeat attendees and organizers prep for the unpredictable as COVID-19 threatens the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260715163100 +0000" stop="20260715184400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Welcome Table</title>
    <desc>Investigation into the impact of the ecological disaster on everyday people's lives by looking at the intersection of climate and immigration.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260715184400 +0000" stop="20260715194600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260715194600 +0000" stop="20260715214000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Meg</title>
    <desc>Previously thought to be extinct, a massive creature attacks a deep-sea submersible, leaving it disabled and trapping the crew at the bottom of the Pacific. With time running out, a visionary oceanographer recruits rescue diver Jonas Taylor to save the crew and the sea itself from an unimaginable threat -- a 75-foot-long prehistoric shark known as the Megalodon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260715214000 +0000" stop="20260715233600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Meg 2: The Trench</title>
    <desc>Jonas Taylor leads a research team on an exploratory dive into the deepest depths of the ocean. Their voyage spirals into chaos when a malevolent mining operation threatens their mission and forces them into a high-stakes battle for survival. Pitted against colossal, prehistoric sharks and relentless environmental plunderers, they must outrun, outsmart and outswim their merciless predators.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260715233600 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Burning Man grows from an anti-establishment group in San Francisco, founded by Larry Harvey in the 1980s, to a multi-million-dollar event with thousands of attendees and the backing of billionaire tech donors; first-time Burners look forward to the experience, while repeat attendees and organizers prep for the unpredictable as COVID-19 threatens the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716003500 +0000" stop="20260716011200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>Larry crashes a party in Boston Harbor; Joe McCarthy airs his grievances on the senate floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716011200 +0000" stop="20260716025800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">How to Make a Killing</title>
    <desc>Disowned by his obscenely wealthy family, Becket Redfellow will stop at nothing to reclaim his inheritance, no matter how many relatives stand in his way.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716025800 +0000" stop="20260716033500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>Larry crashes a party in Boston Harbor; Joe McCarthy airs his grievances on the senate floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716033500 +0000" stop="20260716055000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lee Cronin's The Mummy</title>
    <desc>The young daughter of a journalist disappears into the desert without a trace. Eight years later, the broken family is shocked when she's returned to them. However, what should be a joyful reunion soon turns into a living nightmare as she starts to transform into something truly horrifying.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716055000 +0000" stop="20260716075000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deadpool 2</title>
    <desc>Wisecracking mercenary Deadpool meets Russell, an angry teenage mutant who lives at an orphanage. When Russell becomes the target of Cable -- a genetically enhanced soldier from the future -- Deadpool realizes that he'll need some help saving the boy from such a superior enemy. He soon joins forces with Bedlam, Shatterstar, Domino and other powerful mutants to protect young Russell from Cable and </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716075000 +0000" stop="20260716085200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716085200 +0000" stop="20260716101500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Water</title>
    <desc>Daniel (Daniel Travis) and Susan (Blanchard Ryan) embark on a tropical vacation with their scuba-diving certifications in tow. During a group dive, the two separate themselves from the others to dive a little deeper. An incorrect head-count suggests the entire group has returned, so the boat departs. When the pair surfaces, they make out a vessel in the distance, but it does not immediately set in</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716101500 +0000" stop="20260716114600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGruber</title>
    <desc>In the decade since his fiancée was killed, an Army Ranger, Green Beret and Navy SEAL rolled into one has sworn off fighting crime, preferring instead to rock his mullet as a man of peace. But when his sworn enemy, Dieter Von Cunth, steals a nuclear warhead, only MacGruber and his crack team of experts are equal to the task of bringing the villain to justice.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716114600 +0000" stop="20260716135900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Equalizer</title>
    <desc>Robert McCall (Denzel Washington), a man of mysterious origin who believes he has put the past behind him, dedicates himself to creating a quiet new life. However, when he meets Teri (Chloë Grace Moretz), a teenager who has been manhandled by violent Russian mobsters, he simply cannot walk away. With his set of formidable skills, McCall comes out of self-imposed retirement and emerges as an avengi</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716135900 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Equalizer 2</title>
    <desc>Robert McCall's mysterious past cuts especially close to home when thugs kill Susan Plummer, his best friend and former colleague. Now out for revenge, McCall must take on a crew of highly trained assassins who'll stop at nothing to destroy him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716174900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Equalizer 3</title>
    <desc>Since giving up his life as a government assassin, Robert McCall finds solace in serving justice on behalf of the oppressed. Now living in Southern Italy, he soon discovers his new friends are under the control of local crime bosses. As events turn deadly, McCall becomes their protector by taking on the mafia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716174900 +0000" stop="20260716184900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716184900 +0000" stop="20260716200900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bang My Box: The Robin Byrd Story</title>
    <desc>Explore the rise of a boundary-pushing, sex-positive, cable-access pioneer who became an accidental AIDS-era lifeline and First Amendment fighter; at 70, with 600 shows behind her, she considers her place in the history she created.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716200900 +0000" stop="20260716214800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Greenland 2: Migration</title>
    <desc>In the aftermath of a comet strike that decimated most of the planet, the Garrity family must leave the safety of their Greenland bunker to traverse a shattered world in search of a new home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716214800 +0000" stop="20260716224700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Burning Man grows from an anti-establishment group in San Francisco, founded by Larry Harvey in the 1980s, to a multi-million-dollar event with thousands of attendees and the backing of billionaire tech donors; first-time Burners look forward to the experience, while repeat attendees and organizers prep for the unpredictable as COVID-19 threatens the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465255" start="20260716224700 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pillion</title>
    <desc>A timid man is swept off his feet when an enigmatic, impossibly handsome biker takes him on as his submissive.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465104" start="20260715152400 +0000" stop="20260715160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When I Knew</title>
    <desc>Men and women tell their stories of the moment they knew they were gay.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260715160000 +0000" stop="20260715181500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Lord of the Rings: The War of the Rohirrim</title>
    <desc>A sudden attack by Wulf, a ruthless Dunlending lord, forces Helm Hammerhand and his people to make a daring last stand in the ancient stronghold of the Hornburg. Finding herself in an increasingly desperate situation, Helm's daughter, Héra, must lead the resistance against a deadly enemy who's intent on total destruction.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260715181500 +0000" stop="20260715201800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alien: Covenant</title>
    <desc>Bound for a remote planet on the far side of the galaxy, members (Katherine Waterston, Billy Crudup) of the colony ship Covenant discover what they think to be an uncharted paradise. While there, they meet David (Michael Fassbender), the synthetic survivor of the doomed Prometheus expedition. The mysterious world soon turns dark and dangerous when a hostile alien life-form forces the crew into a d</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260715201800 +0000" stop="20260715222200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prometheus</title>
    <desc>The discovery of a clue to mankind's origins on Earth leads a team of explorers to the darkest parts of the universe. Two brilliant young scientists lead the expedition. Shaw hopes that they will meet a race of benevolent, godlike beings who will in some way verify her religious beliefs, while Holloway is out to debunk any spiritual notions. However, neither the scientists nor their shipmates are </desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260715222200 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fackham Hall</title>
    <desc>Eric Noone begins a forbidden romance with Rose Davenport, the lady of the house at a posh English manor. When an unexpected murder occurs, Eric gets framed, leaving Rose and her family's future uncertain.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716012300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">This Is Spinal Tap</title>
    <desc>"This Is Spinal Tap" shines a light on the self-contained universe of a metal band struggling to get back on the charts, including everything from its complicated history of ups and downs, gold albums, name changes and undersold concert dates, along with the full host of requisite groupies, promoters, hangers-on and historians, sessions, release events and those special behind-the-scenes moments t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716012300 +0000" stop="20260716024700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spinal Tap II: The End Continues</title>
    <desc>Documentarian Marty DiBergi follows estranged Spinal Tap bandmates David St. Hubbins, Nigel Tufnel and Derek Smalls as they search for a drummer and prepare for a reunion concert in New Orleans. Joined by music royalty Paul McCartney and Elton John, Spinal Tap wrestles with their checkered past to put on a show they hope will solidify their place in the pantheon of rock 'n' roll.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716024700 +0000" stop="20260716043300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">How to Make a Killing</title>
    <desc>Disowned by his obscenely wealthy family, Becket Redfellow will stop at nothing to reclaim his inheritance, no matter how many relatives stand in his way.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716043300 +0000" stop="20260716060800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">They Will Kill You</title>
    <desc>A woman answers a cryptic ad for a housekeeping job at a luxurious yet foreboding New York City high-rise. Upon arrival, she discovers residents have vanished without a trace for decades, fueling whispers of a satanic cult lurking in the shadows.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716060800 +0000" stop="20260716075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pillion</title>
    <desc>A timid man is swept off his feet when an enigmatic, impossibly handsome biker takes him on as his submissive.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716075500 +0000" stop="20260716093300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Good Day to Die Hard</title>
    <desc>New York City cop John McClane (Bruce Willis) arrives in Moscow to track down his estranged son, Jack (Jai Courtney). McClane thinks his son is a criminal, so it comes as a shock when he learns that Jack is actually working undercover to protect Komarov (Sebastian Koch), a Russian government whistleblower. With their own lives on the line, McClane and Jack must overcome their differences in order </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716093300 +0000" stop="20260716110100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Martin Lawrence: You So Crazy</title>
    <desc>Filmed at a sold-out Majestic Theater in Brooklyn, N.Y., comedian Martin Lawrence delivers his first full-length stand-up special. Harking back to Eddie Murphy, the leather-clad comic riffs on drugs, jail, his impoverished upbringing with his mother and his luck -- or lack thereof -- with women. He also speaks at length about racism and the Rodney King ruling and subsequent riots. Lawrence even of</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716110100 +0000" stop="20260716123200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Day the Earth Blew Up: A Looney Tunes Movie</title>
    <desc>Porky Pig and Daffy Duck become Earth's only hope when their antics at the local bubble-gum factory uncover a secret alien mind-control plot. Faced with cosmic odds, they must save their town and the world while not driving each other totally loony.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716123200 +0000" stop="20260716135800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Year One: A Political Odyssey</title>
    <desc>Following the Biden administration's efforts to reshape U.S. foreign policy and national security during his first year in office.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716135800 +0000" stop="20260716153300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Revolution on Canvas</title>
    <desc>Sara Nodjoumi investigates the disappearance of more than 100 "treasonous" paintings by her father, Iranian artist Nickzad Nodjoumi.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716153300 +0000" stop="20260716171100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Architecton</title>
    <desc>A hypnotic, propulsive odyssey through the foundations of the modern world, following mountains as they are turned into concrete and buildings as they are turned into rubble.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716171100 +0000" stop="20260716203200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Brutalist</title>
    <desc>Escaping postwar Europe, a visionary architect arrives in America to rebuild his life. On his own in a strange new country, a wealthy industrialist recognizes his talent -- but power and legacy comes at a heavy cost.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716203200 +0000" stop="20260716223700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mummy</title>
    <desc>The Mummy is a rousing, suspenseful and horrifying epic about an expedition of treasure-seeking explorers in the Sahara Desert in 1925. Stumbling upon an ancient tomb, the hunters unwittingly set loose a 3,000-year-old legacy of terror, which is embodied in the vengeful reincarnation of an Egyptian priest who had been sentenced to an eternity as one of the living dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465104" start="20260716223700 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mummy Returns</title>
    <desc>Ten years after the events of the first film, Rick and Evelyn O'Connell are settled in 1935 London, where they are raising their son. When a chain of events finds the corpse of Imhotep resurrected, the O'Connells go on a desperate race to save the world from unspeakable evil and to rescue their son before it is too late.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465302" start="20260715154100 +0000" stop="20260715161700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>Larry crashes a party in Boston Harbor; Joe McCarthy airs his grievances on the senate floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260715161700 +0000" stop="20260715173800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open Water</title>
    <desc>Daniel (Daniel Travis) and Susan (Blanchard Ryan) embark on a tropical vacation with their scuba-diving certifications in tow. During a group dive, the two separate themselves from the others to dive a little deeper. An incorrect head-count suggests the entire group has returned, so the boat departs. When the pair surfaces, they make out a vessel in the distance, but it does not immediately set in</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260715173800 +0000" stop="20260715184400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>Driven by her faith in Alicent, Rhaenyra positions herself to take King's Landing while the Triarchy sails to take on Corlys in the Gullet.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260715184400 +0000" stop="20260715194800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>Alicent risks everything to fulfill her end of the bargain; Rhaenyra must decide whether the Iron Throne is worth the cost.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260715194800 +0000" stop="20260715204500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>Rhaenyra, driven by her faith in Alicent, prepares to take King's Landing while the Triarchy sets sail to confront Corlys at the Gullet.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260715204500 +0000" stop="20260715215100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260715215100 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dead of Winter</title>
    <desc>A grief-stricken widow stops by a remote cabin after getting lost on the back roads of Minnesota in the middle of winter. She soon finds herself in a desperate fight for survival as she encounters a murderous couple holding a young woman hostage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Burning Man grows from an anti-establishment group in San Francisco, founded by Larry Harvey in the 1980s, to a multi-million-dollar event with thousands of attendees and the backing of billionaire tech donors; first-time Burners look forward to the experience, while repeat attendees and organizers prep for the unpredictable as COVID-19 threatens the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716002900 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Marty Supreme</title>
    <desc>Marty Mauser, a wily hustler with a dream no one respects, goes to hell and back in pursuit of greatness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>Larry crashes a party in Boston Harbor; Joe McCarthy airs his grievances on the senate floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716033700 +0000" stop="20260716044300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716044300 +0000" stop="20260716063300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Long Walk</title>
    <desc>Teens participate in a grueling high-stakes contest where they must continuously walk or be shot by a member of their military escort.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716063300 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Us</title>
    <desc>Accompanied by her husband, son and daughter, Adelaide Wilson returns to the beachfront home where she grew up as a child. Haunted by a traumatic experience from the past, Adelaide grows increasingly concerned that something bad is going to happen. Her worst fears soon become a reality when four masked strangers descend upon the house, forcing the Wilsons into a fight for survival. When the masks </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716092900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Burning Man grows from an anti-establishment group in San Francisco, founded by Larry Harvey in the 1980s, to a multi-million-dollar event with thousands of attendees and the backing of billionaire tech donors; first-time Burners look forward to the experience, while repeat attendees and organizers prep for the unpredictable as COVID-19 threatens the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716092900 +0000" stop="20260716103500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716103500 +0000" stop="20260716111100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>Larry crashes a party in Boston Harbor; Joe McCarthy airs his grievances on the senate floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716111100 +0000" stop="20260716125000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Miss You, Love You</title>
    <desc>A blunt, grieving widow is forced to plan her husband's funeral with a total stranger: her estranged son's assistant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716125000 +0000" stop="20260716143400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The LEGO NINJAGO Movie</title>
    <desc>The battle for NINJAGO City calls to action young Master Builder Lloyd, aka the Green Ninja, along with his friends, also secret ninja warriors. Led by Master Wu, as wise-cracking as he is wise, they must defeat the evil warlord Garmadon, who also happens to be Lloyd's dad. Pitting father against son, the epic showdown tests these fierce but undisciplined modern-day ninjas as they learn to check t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716143400 +0000" stop="20260716165800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aquaman</title>
    <desc>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, the city of Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people -- and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur, Orm's half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne. With help from royal counselor Vulko, Arthur</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716165800 +0000" stop="20260716190400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aquaman and the Lost Kingdom</title>
    <desc>After failing to defeat Aquaman the first time, Black Manta wields the power of the mythic Black Trident to unleash an ancient and malevolent force. Hoping to end his reign of terror, Aquaman forges an unlikely alliance with his brother, Orm, the former king of Atlantis. Setting aside their differences, they join forces to protect their kingdom and save the world from irreversible destruction.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716190400 +0000" stop="20260716201000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716201000 +0000" stop="20260716211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Man Will Burn</title>
    <desc>Burning Man grows from an anti-establishment group in San Francisco, founded by Larry Harvey in the 1980s, to a multi-million-dollar event with thousands of attendees and the backing of billionaire tech donors; first-time Burners look forward to the experience, while repeat attendees and organizers prep for the unpredictable as COVID-19 threatens the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716211000 +0000" stop="20260716225300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rover</title>
    <desc>In the near future, mankind's greed and excesses have pushed civilization to the breaking point. Society is in decline, and the rule of law has disintegrated. Hardened drifter Eric (Guy Pearce) wanders across this dangerous and desolate landscape. When thieves steal Eric's car -- and only remaining possession -- they leave behind Rey (Robert Pattinson), a wounded comrade. Eric forces Rey to help h</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716225300 +0000" stop="20260716232900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life, Larry and the Pursuit of Unhappiness</title>
    <desc>Larry crashes a party in Boston Harbor; Joe McCarthy airs his grievances on the senate floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465302" start="20260716232900 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of the Dragon</title>
    <desc>The story of the Targaryen civil war with King Viserys I Targaryen's children battling for control of the Iron Throne.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465284" start="20260715150500 +0000" stop="20260715164500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Barbarella</title>
    <desc>Barbarella (Jane Fonda) roams 41st-century space with her blind guardian angel, Pygar (John Phillip Law).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260715164500 +0000" stop="20260715182000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">There's Something Wrong With the Children</title>
    <desc>Margaret and Ben take a weekend trip with two longtime friends and their two young children. Ben soon suspects something sinister is afoot when the kids start behaving strangely after disappearing into the woods overnight.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260715182000 +0000" stop="20260715201500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Of Mice and Men</title>
    <desc>Itinerant worker George (Gary Sinise) reflects on the time he spent traveling with Lennie (John Malkovich), a huge childlike man. The two men drift through California during the Great Depression, looking for work. After they find jobs on a ranch, Lennie develops an infatuation with the owner's daughter-in-law (Sherilyn Fenn). However, when George and Lennie are handed an opportunity to own part of</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260715201500 +0000" stop="20260715222500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Raging Bull</title>
    <desc>The story of a middleweight boxer as he rises through ranks to earn his first shot at the middleweight crown. He falls in love with a gorgeous girl from the Bronx. The inability to express his feelings enters into the ring and eventually takes over his life. He eventually is sent into a downward spiral that costs him everything.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260715222500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">September 5</title>
    <desc>During the 1972 Munich Olympics, an American sports broadcasting crew finds itself thrust into covering the hostage crisis involving Israeli athletes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716025500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aviator</title>
    <desc>Billionaire and aviation tycoon Howard Hughes (Leonardo DiCaprio) is a successful public figure: a director of big-budget Hollywood films such as "Hell's Angels," a passionate lover of Hollywood leading ladies Katharine Hepburn (Cate Blanchett) and Ava Gardner (Kate Beckinsale), and an aviation pioneer who helps build TWA into a major airline. But in private, Hughes remains tormented, suffering fr</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716025500 +0000" stop="20260716044500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Whiplash</title>
    <desc>Andrew Neiman (Miles Teller) is an ambitious young jazz drummer, in pursuit of rising to the top of his elite music conservatory. Terence Fletcher (J.K. Simmons), an instructor known for his terrifying teaching methods, discovers Andrew and transfers the aspiring drummer into the top jazz ensemble, forever changing the young man's life. But Andrew's passion to achieve perfection quickly spirals in</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716044500 +0000" stop="20260716065500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roofman</title>
    <desc>After escaping from prison, former soldier and professional thief Jeffrey Manchester finds a hideout inside a Toys "R" Us, surviving undetected for months while planning his next move. However, when Jeffrey falls for a divorced mom, his double life starts to unravel, setting off a compelling and suspenseful game of cat and mouse as his past closes in.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716065500 +0000" stop="20260716084000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hour of the Gun</title>
    <desc>While the Earp brothers may have won the gunfight at the O.K. Corral, they didn't escape unscathed for long. Seeking revenge over their fallen comrades, members of the Clanton gang go after the Earp family, gunning down both Virgil and Morgan Earp. But they don't succeed at getting Wyatt (James Garner). Now it's his turn to seek revenge. With Doc Holliday (Jason Robards) by his side, Wyatt forms a</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716084000 +0000" stop="20260716090500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unprotected Sets</title>
    <desc>Mohanad is living the American dream; as an immigrant from the no-fly country of Libya, his observations about American life are razor sharp; while many comics perform for the love of the spotlight, Mohanad is performing for survival.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716090500 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Westies</title>
    <desc>The Westies' fragile deal with the Italians unravels after a reckless kidnapping; Flanagan is released from Bellevue and rejoins Roarke's crew, Keenan is pulled onto an FBI task force, and Bridget receives a dangerous assignment from an IRA contact.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716105500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Westies</title>
    <desc>Roarke and the Westies hide the body of a dead Italian mobster and stage crimes to cover up the murder before Gotti retaliates; Polk pressures Keenan to dig into Sweeney's Mafia ties, while Bridget uncovers more of Cahill's plot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716105500 +0000" stop="20260716132000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Irma La Douce</title>
    <desc>This entertaining comedy finds disgraced former police officer Nestor Patou falling for beautiful Parisian prostitute Irma La Douce. Though Nestor becomes Irma's pimp, he can't stand the idea of her being with clients, so he devises a way to keep her all to himself. This scheme leads to plenty of trouble, however, and soon Nestor is forced to avoid his old law-enforcement peers in an attempt to st</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716132000 +0000" stop="20260716144500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hostile Border</title>
    <desc>Deported to Mexico, a young woman (Veronica Sixtos) forms a dangerous alliance with a smuggler (Roberto Urbina) to try and return to the United States.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716144500 +0000" stop="20260716155500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alive</title>
    <desc>Following the conflicts in Iraq and Afghanistan, injured veterans turn to adaptive athletics to heal their physical and emotional battle wounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716155500 +0000" stop="20260716172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Invasion of the Body Snatchers</title>
    <desc>In Santa Mira, California, Dr. Miles Bennell (Kevin McCarthy) is baffled when all his patients come to him with the same complaint: their loved ones seem to have been replaced by emotionless impostors. Despite others' dismissive denials, Dr. Bennell, his former girlfriend Becky (Dana Wynter) and his friend Jack (King Donovan) soon discover that the patients' suspicions are true: an alien species o</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716172000 +0000" stop="20260716184500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Deep House</title>
    <desc>While diving in a remote French lake, two YouTubers who specialize in underwater exploration videos discover a house submerged in deep waters. Their dive turns into a nightmare when they discover the house was the scene of atrocious crimes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716184500 +0000" stop="20260716202500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Keep</title>
    <desc>A stranger (Scott Glenn) fights timeless evil in a Romanian castle occupied by a Nazi captain (Jürgen Prochnow).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716202500 +0000" stop="20260716220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mercy</title>
    <desc>In the near future, an advanced AI judge tells a captive detective that he's on trial for the murder of his wife. If he fails to prove his innocence within 90 minutes, he'll be executed on the spot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260716220500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Annihilation</title>
    <desc>Lena, a biologist and former soldier, joins a mission to uncover what happened to her husband inside Area X -- a sinister and mysterious phenomenon that is expanding across the American coastline. Once inside, the expedition discovers a world of mutated landscapes and creatures, as dangerous as it is beautiful, that threatens both their lives and their sanity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260717000000 +0000" stop="20260718000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Westies</title>
    <desc>The Westies' fragile deal with the Italians unravels after a reckless kidnapping; Flanagan is released from Bellevue and rejoins Roarke's crew, Keenan is pulled onto an FBI task force, and Bridget receives a dangerous assignment from an IRA contact.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-17</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465261" start="20260715152500 +0000" stop="20260715170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Poltergeist II: The Other Side</title>
    <desc>The Freelings have escaped their haunted house, which is now being studied by paranormal investigators, including shaman Taylor (Will Sampson). When Taylor realizes that the Beast, masquerading as the Rev. Kane (Julian Beck), knows where young Carol Anne Freeling (Heather O'Rourke) now lives, he goes to warn the family that their daughter is in danger again. To protect Carol, her father, Steve (Cr</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260715170000 +0000" stop="20260715184000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Carrie</title>
    <desc>High school can be tough for many teenagers, but for Carrie White (Chloë Grace Moretz), it's especially hellish. A shy and awkward teen being raised by a religious zealot (Julianne Moore), Carrie is frequently the target of bullies. But Carrie has a secret talent: She can make things move with her mind. One fateful night, an especially cruel prank at her senior prom pushes her over the edge, and C</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260715184000 +0000" stop="20260715201500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Clockstoppers</title>
    <desc>Until now, Zak Gibbs' greatest challenge has been to find a way to buy a car. But when he discovers an odd wristwatch amidst his father's various inventions and slips it on -- something very strange happens. The world around him seems to come to a stop, everything and everybody frozen in time. Zak quickly learns how to manipulate the device and he and his quick-witted and beautiful new friend, Fra</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260715201500 +0000" stop="20260715221000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Annihilation</title>
    <desc>Lena, a biologist and former soldier, joins a mission to uncover what happened to her husband inside Area X -- a sinister and mysterious phenomenon that is expanding across the American coastline. Once inside, the expedition discovers a world of mutated landscapes and creatures, as dangerous as it is beautiful, that threatens both their lives and their sanity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260715221000 +0000" stop="20260715230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Westies</title>
    <desc>The Westies' fragile deal with the Italians unravels after a reckless kidnapping; Flanagan is released from Bellevue and rejoins Roarke's crew, Keenan is pulled onto an FBI task force, and Bridget receives a dangerous assignment from an IRA contact.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260715230500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Westies</title>
    <desc>Roarke and the Westies hide the body of a dead Italian mobster and stage crimes to cover up the murder before Gotti retaliates; Polk pressures Keenan to dig into Sweeney's Mafia ties, while Bridget uncovers more of Cahill's plot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Transformers: The Last Knight</title>
    <desc>Humans are at war with the Transformers, and Optimus Prime is gone. The key to saving the future lies buried in the secrets of the past and the hidden history of Transformers on Earth. Now, it's up to the unlikely alliance of inventor Cade Yeager, Bumblebee, an English lord and an Oxford professor to save the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716023500 +0000" stop="20260716044500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Spy Who Loved Me</title>
    <desc>In a globe-trotting assignment that has him skiing off the edges of cliffs and driving a car deep underwater, British super-spy James Bond (Roger Moore) unites with sexy Russian agent Anya Amasova (Barbara Bach) to defeat megalomaniac shipping magnate Karl Stromberg (Curt Jurgens), who is threatening to destroy New York City with nuclear weapons. Bond's most deadly adversary on the case is Strombe</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716044500 +0000" stop="20260716064500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">From Russia With Love</title>
    <desc>Agent 007 (Sean Connery) is back in the second installment of the James Bond series, this time battling a secret crime organization known as SPECTRE. Russians Rosa Klebb (Lotte Lenya) and Kronsteen are out to snatch a decoding device known as the Lektor, using the ravishing Tatiana (Daniela Bianchi) to lure Bond into helping them. Bond willingly travels to meet Tatiana in Istanbul, where he must r</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716064500 +0000" stop="20260716074000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Westies</title>
    <desc>The Westies' fragile deal with the Italians unravels after a reckless kidnapping; Flanagan is released from Bellevue and rejoins Roarke's crew, Keenan is pulled onto an FBI task force, and Bridget receives a dangerous assignment from an IRA contact.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716074000 +0000" stop="20260716083500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Westies</title>
    <desc>Roarke and the Westies hide the body of a dead Italian mobster and stage crimes to cover up the murder before Gotti retaliates; Polk pressures Keenan to dig into Sweeney's Mafia ties, while Bridget uncovers more of Cahill's plot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716083500 +0000" stop="20260716100500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Visitor</title>
    <desc>When Robert and his wife move to her childhood home, he discovers an old portrait in the attic of a man who looks just like him. He soon travels down a frightening rabbit hole as he tries to discover the true identity of his mysterious doppelgänger, only to realize that every family has its own terrifying secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716100500 +0000" stop="20260716113500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Smurfs</title>
    <desc>When evil wizards Razamel and Gargamel take Papa Smurf, the Smurfs embark on a mission to the real world to save him. With help from some new friends, they must discover what defines their destiny to save the universe.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716113500 +0000" stop="20260716131000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ordeal by Innocence</title>
    <desc>A 1950s U.S. scientist (Donald Sutherland) probes the murder of a British friend's (Christopher Plummer) wife (Faye Dunaway).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716131000 +0000" stop="20260716144000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I'm Gonna Git You Sucka</title>
    <desc>Jack Spade (Keenen Ivory Wayans) comes home to the ghetto and finds his brother dead from a gold chain overdose. With the help of his hero, John Slade (Bernie Casey), and a team of washed-up crime fighters, Spade declares vengeance on Mr. Big (John Vernon), the white crime leader responsible for selling gold chains on the streets. But Spade realizes that he must take matters into his own hands to </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716144000 +0000" stop="20260716163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fame</title>
    <desc>At New York's High School of Performing Arts, students (Asher Book, Kristy Flores, Paul Iacono) from all walks of life get the chance to hone their skills as singers, actors, dancers and more. Over four years, these young men and women will see if they truly have the dedication and talent to achieve success, while still juggling regular schoolwork, feelings of self-doubt and budding romances.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716163000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hot Pursuit</title>
    <desc>Straight-arrow policewoman Cooper (Reese Witherspoon) is excited and thrilled about her next assignment. Her task is to escort Daniella Riva (Sofía Vergara), a wisecracking Colombian beauty, from San Antonio to Dallas so both she and her husband can testify against a drug lord. Plans go awry when Mr. Riva gets ambushed, leaving Daniella a widow. Cooper and her witness must now use their wits to es</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716195000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fire Inside</title>
    <desc>The story of Claressa "T-Rex" Shields, a boxer from Flint, Mich., who trained to become the first woman in her country's history to win an Olympic gold medal in the sport.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716195000 +0000" stop="20260716220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rain Man</title>
    <desc>When car dealer Charlie Babbitt (Tom Cruise) learns that his estranged father has died, he returns home to Cincinnati, where he discovers that he has an autistic older brother named Raymond (Dustin Hoffman) and that his father's $3 million fortune is being left to the mental institution in which Raymond lives. Motivated by his father's money, Charlie checks Raymond out of the facility in order to </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260716220500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wonder</title>
    <desc>Born with facial differences that, up until now, have prevented him from going to a mainstream school, Auggie Pullman becomes the most unlikely of heroes when he enters the local fifth grade. As his family, his new classmates, and the larger community all struggle to discover their compassion and acceptance, Auggie's extraordinary journey will unite them and prove you can't blend in when you were </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260717000000 +0000" stop="20260718000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stand by Me</title>
    <desc>After learning that a stranger has been accidentally killed near their rural homes, four Oregon boys decide to go see the body. On the way, Gordie Lachance (Wil Wheaton), Vern Tessio (Jerry O'Connell), Chris Chambers (River Phoenix) and Teddy Duchamp (Corey Feldman) encounter a mean junk man and a marsh full of leeches, as they also learn more about one another and their very different home lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-17</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464850" start="20260715153900 +0000" stop="20260715172100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Switch</title>
    <desc>Neurotic Wally Mars has one bright spot in his life: his friendship with Kassie. When Kassie announces her intention to become pregnant using a sperm donor, Wally thinks he will be the lucky guy, but Kassie has someone else in mind. While drunk at Kassie's insemination party, Wally substitutes his sperm for the donor's, then passes out, remembering nothing. Seven years later, Wally meets Kassie's </desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260715172100 +0000" stop="20260715191600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spare Parts</title>
    <desc>With the help of their high school's newest teacher (George Lopez), four Hispanic students form a robotics club. Although they have no experience, the youths set their sights on a national robotics contest. With $800 and parts scavenged from old cars, they build a robot and compete against reigning champion MIT. Along the way, the students learn not only how to build a robot but something far more</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260715191600 +0000" stop="20260715210300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Contagion</title>
    <desc>When Beth Emhoff returns to Minnesota from a Hong Kong business trip, she attributes the malaise she feels to jet lag. However, two days later, Beth is dead, and doctors tell her shocked husband that they have no idea what killed her. Soon, many others start to exhibit the same symptoms, and a global pandemic explodes. Doctors try to contain the lethal microbe, but society begins to collapse as a </desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260715210300 +0000" stop="20260715224200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stoker</title>
    <desc>India Stoker's (Mia Wasikowska) world comes crashing down when her father (Jacki Weaver) dies in a car accident. Adding to the girl's emotional turmoil is the sudden arrival of Charlie (Matthew Goode), an uncle whom she never knew existed. Charlie moves in with India and her unstable mother (Nicole Kidman), and soon India begins to suspect that this charming and mysterious man has ulterior motives</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260715224200 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">X-Men: First Class</title>
    <desc>In the early 1960s, during the height of the Cold War, a mutant named Charles Xavier (James McAvoy) meets a fellow mutant named Erik Lehnsherr (Michael Fassbender). Despite their vastly different backgrounds -- Charles grew up with a wealthy family, while Erik lost his parents at Auschwitz -- the two become close friends. As the world teeters on the brink of a nuclear war, Charles and Erik with ot</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716005400 +0000" stop="20260716024900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Atomic Blonde</title>
    <desc>Sensual and savage, Lorraine Broughton is the most elite spy in MI6, an agent who's willing to use all of her lethal skills to stay alive during an impossible mission. With the Berlin Wall about to fall, she travels into the heart of the city to retrieve a priceless dossier and take down a ruthless espionage ring. Once there, she teams up with an embedded station chief to navigate her way through </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716024900 +0000" stop="20260716044700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tomb Raider</title>
    <desc>Lara Croft is the fiercely independent daughter of an eccentric adventurer who vanished years earlier. Hoping to solve the mystery of her father's disappearance, Croft embarks on a perilous journey to his last-known destination -- a fabled tomb on a mythical island that might be somewhere off the coast of Japan. The stakes couldn't be higher as Lara must rely on her sharp mind, blind faith and stu</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716044700 +0000" stop="20260716062300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Transporter Refueled</title>
    <desc>Frank Martin is living a less perilous lifestyle, or so he thinks, transporting classified packages for questionable people. Things get complicated when femme fatale Anna and her three accomplices orchestrate a bank heist and the kidnapping of Frank's father. It's all part of a grand plan to take down the human trafficker who victimized her years earlier. Now a pawn in her vengeful scheme, the for</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716062300 +0000" stop="20260716084000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rock</title>
    <desc>FBI chemical warfare expert Stanley Goodspeed (Nicolas Cage) is sent on an urgent mission with a former British spy, John Patrick Mason (Sean Connery), to stop Gen. Francis X. Hummel (Ed Harris) from launching chemical weapons on Alcatraz Island into San Francisco. Gen. Hummel demands $100 million in war reparations to be paid to the families of slain servicemen who died on covert operations. Afte</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716084000 +0000" stop="20260716102800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trap</title>
    <desc>A man and his teenage daughter realize they're at the center of a dark and sinister event while watching a concert.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716102800 +0000" stop="20260716121700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nanny McPhee Returns</title>
    <desc>Enigmatic Nanny McPhee arrives on the doorstep of a harried mother, Isabel Green, who is trying to raise her kids and tend to the family farm while her husband is away at war. Isabel has her hands full of not only her own three, but also with her sister's spoiled pair. With no time to lose, McPhee uses magic to instill in the children five important lessons.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716121700 +0000" stop="20260716135100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beasts of the Southern Wild</title>
    <desc>Six-year-old Hushpuppy lives with her father, Wink, in a remote Delta community. Wink is a stern taskmaster, but he is preparing his young daughter for the end of the world. When Wink falls mysteriously ill, nature seems to fall ill with him. Temperatures rise, the ice caps melt, and fearsome prehistoric beasts called aurochs run loose. Rising waters threaten to engulf their community, sending Hus</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716135100 +0000" stop="20260716154300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mountain Between Us</title>
    <desc>Stranded on a mountain after a tragic plane crash, two strangers must work together to endure the extreme elements of the remote, snow-covered terrain. Realizing that help is not on the way, they embark on a perilous journey across hundreds of miles of wilderness, pushing each other to survive and discovering their inner strength.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716154300 +0000" stop="20260716171300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destroy All Monsters!</title>
    <desc>Scientists face Godzilla, Rodan, Mothra and more obscure Japanese monsters sent by she-aliens.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716171300 +0000" stop="20260716183300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For All Mankind</title>
    <desc>Directed by Al Reinert and with music scored by Brian Eno, "For All Mankind" provides a testament to NASA's Apollo program of the 1960s and '70s. Composed of actual NASA footage of the missions and astronaut interviews, the documentary offers the viewpoint of the individuals who braved the remarkable journey to the moon and back. While compiling the material for the film, Reinert went through more</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716183300 +0000" stop="20260716200400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lord of the Flies</title>
    <desc>Amidst a nuclear war, a plane carrying a group of schoolboys crash lands on a deserted island. With no adult survivors, the boys are forced to fend for themselves. At first, they cooperate, but when they split into two separate camps -- one led by the pragmatic Ralph (James Aubrey) and the other by militaristic Jack (Tom Chapin) -- their society falls into disarray, leading to a disturbing examina</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716200400 +0000" stop="20260716220200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mississippi Masala</title>
    <desc>After Mina's Indian family is ousted from their home in Uganda by dictator Idi Amin, they relocate to Mississippi to start a new life. Mina falls for Demetrius, a young carpet cleaner, despite the protestations of their families over their racial difference. The families and their surrounding communities begin to feud, putting even more pressure on the couple's romance. Having to choose between fa</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260716220200 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Twin Peaks: Fire Walk With Me</title>
    <desc>In the folksy town of Deerfield, Wash., FBI Agent Desmond (Chris Isaak) inexplicably disappears while hunting for the man who murdered a teen girl. The killer is never apprehended, and, after experiencing dark visions and supernatural encounters, Agent Dale Cooper (Kyle MacLachlan) chillingly predicts that the culprit will claim another life. Meanwhile, in the similarly cozy town of Twin Peaks, he</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465332" start="20260715141500 +0000" stop="20260715161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Daniela Forever</title>
    <desc>After his girlfriend dies in an accident, a grieving man joins a sleep trial that allows him to rebuild his life with her through the use of lucid dreams.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260715161500 +0000" stop="20260715183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Trade Center</title>
    <desc>Two Port Authority officers, Sgt. John McLoughlin (Nicolas Cage) and Officer Will Jimeno (Michael Peña), become trapped in the rubble of the World Trade Center after going in to help people escape from the buildings during the terrorist attacks of Sept. 11, 2001.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260715183000 +0000" stop="20260715203500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sahara</title>
    <desc>Seasoned adventurer Dirk Pitt (Matthew McConaughey) sets out for the African desert with his sarcastic companion (Steve Zahn) in search of a ship rumored to have vanished long ago, the main draw being the treasure supposedly hidden within the lost vessel. When the daring duo come across a beautiful scientist (Penélope Cruz) who is juggling an escape from a warlord and a mission to stop the spread </desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260715203500 +0000" stop="20260715223500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Out of the Furnace</title>
    <desc>Steelworker Russell Baze works a dead-end job and holds tight to his sense of family, duty and loyalty. Rodney Baze, Russell's brother, returns home after serving in Iraq and, with his debts piling up, becomes entangled with a vicious crime lord. Soon afterward, Rodney disappears mysteriously. The police fail to solve the case, so Russell -- feeling he has little left to lose -- puts his life on t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260715223500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masterminds</title>
    <desc>An armored-car driver (Zach Galifianakis) helps a flirty co-worker (Kristen Wiig) and her friends pull off a heist, then finds himself holding the bag after they double-cross him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716001500 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Last Vegas</title>
    <desc>Aging pals Billy (Michael Douglas), Paddy (Robert De Niro), Archie (Morgan Freeman) and Sam (Kevin Kline) have been best friends since childhood. When Billy finally proposes to his much-younger girlfriend, all four friends go to Las Vegas to celebrate the end of Billy's longtime bachelorhood and relive their glory days. However, the four quickly realize that the intervening decades have changed Si</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716034000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Vacation</title>
    <desc>Remembering fond, childhood memories of his trip to Walley World, Rusty Griswold surprises his wife and two sons with a cross-country excursion to America's favorite fun park. Following in his father's footsteps, Rusty and the gang pack up the car and hit the road for some much-needed family bonding. Soon, the promise of fun turns into one misadventure after another for the next generation of Gris</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716034000 +0000" stop="20260716051500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Boys</title>
    <desc>Invited to his first kissing party, 12-year-old Max asks his best friends Lucas and Thor for some much-needed help on how to pucker up. When they hit a dead end, Max decides to use his father's drone to spy on the teenage girls next door. When the boys lose the drone, they skip school and hatch a plan to retrieve it before Max's dad can figure out what happened.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716051500 +0000" stop="20260716070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Staten Island Summer</title>
    <desc>Danny and Frank work as lifeguards for the summer and make plans to throw the wildest party of the season.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716070500 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seven Psychopaths</title>
    <desc>Boozy writer Marty (Colin Farrell) is a man in search of a screenplay. He has a catchy title but no story to go along with it. Marty has a couple of oddball buddies, Hans (Christopher Walken) and Billy (Sam Rockwell), who make a living by kidnapping rich people's dogs, then returning them and collecting the reward. However this time, the fur flies when Hans and Billy kidnap the beloved pooch of a </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ring</title>
    <desc>It sounds like just another urban legend -- a videotape filled with nightmarish images leads to a phone call foretelling the viewer's death in exactly seven days. Newspaper reporter Rachel Keller (Naomi Watts) is skeptical of the story until four teenagers all die mysteriously exactly one week after watching just such a tape. Allowing her investigative curiosity to get the better of her, Rachel tr</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Snag</title>
    <desc>A lone wolf's quiet existence gets shattered when he learns that the woman he once loved and thought was dead is alive and being held captive by ruthless gangsters. Now, to take on this dangerous criminal organization, he must seek out allies and storm into a world of violence to rescue the love of his life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716123000 +0000" stop="20260716140500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Last Stop in Yuma County</title>
    <desc>Stranded at an Arizona rest stop, a traveling knife salesman gets thrust into a high-stakes hostage situation by the arrival of two bank robbers who will stop at nothing to protect their ill-begotten fortune.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716140500 +0000" stop="20260716161000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Not Without Hope</title>
    <desc>Four friends face disaster when their boat capsizes in the Gulf of Mexico. Battling massive waves, sharks, dehydration and hypothermia, they cling to hope as Capt. Timothy Close and his Coast Guard crew launch a daring rescue through a raging storm to save them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716161000 +0000" stop="20260716175000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cut</title>
    <desc>Given one last shot at glory, a former boxing champion has just six days to make weight for a title fight. His obsession soon leaves him at the mercy of a notorious trainer who takes every last ounce from his mind, body and soul.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716175000 +0000" stop="20260716194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scream 4</title>
    <desc>It has been many years since the Ghostface Killer cut a deadly path through the town of Woodsboro. In order to get over the trauma of those horrific events, Sidney Prescott (Neve Campbell) has written a self-help book. She returns to Woodsboro for her book tour, and reconnects with old friends Gale Weathers (Courteney Cox) and Sheriff Dewey (David Arquette). However, Sidney's arrival also sparks t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716194500 +0000" stop="20260716213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kickback</title>
    <desc>A documentary following the decades-long crusade of investigative journalist Andrew Jennings to expose corruption inside FIFA, football's sole governing body and the largest sports organization in the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716213000 +0000" stop="20260716233500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Not Without Hope</title>
    <desc>Four friends face disaster when their boat capsizes in the Gulf of Mexico. Battling massive waves, sharks, dehydration and hypothermia, they cling to hope as Capt. Timothy Close and his Coast Guard crew launch a daring rescue through a raging storm to save them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260716233500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacksaw Ridge</title>
    <desc>The true story of Pfc. Desmond T. Doss (Andrew Garfield), who won the Congressional Medal of Honor despite refusing to bear arms during WWII on religious grounds. Doss was drafted and ostracized by fellow soldiers for his pacifist stance but went on to earn respect and adoration for his bravery, selflessness and compassion after he risked his life -- without firing a shot -- to save 75 men in the </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465402" start="20260715154500 +0000" stop="20260715175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Expendables 3</title>
    <desc>Years ago, Barney Ross co-founded the Expendables with Conrad Stonebanks. After Stonebanks became an arms dealer, Ross was forced to kill him -- or so he thought. Now, Stonebanks is back, and he's on a mission to end the Expendables. Ross decides that the way to fight old blood is with new blood, so he assembles a team of younger, faster, more tech-savvy recruits. The battle to topple Stonebanks b</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260715175500 +0000" stop="20260715194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Expend4bles</title>
    <desc>Armed with every weapon they can get their hands on, the Expendables are the world's last line of defense and the team that gets called when all other options are off the table.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260715194500 +0000" stop="20260715215000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheech &amp; Chong's Last Movie</title>
    <desc>Cheech Marin and Tommy Chong discuss their lifelong friendship and popularity as a comedic duo. Features interviews, sketches and never-before-seen footage spanning their five-decade career.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260715215000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Terminator: Dark Fate</title>
    <desc>In Mexico City, a newly modified liquid Terminator -- the Rev-9 model -- arrives from the future to kill a young factory worker named Dani Ramos. Also sent back in time is Grace, a hybrid cyborg human who must protect Ramos from the seemingly indestructible robotic assassin. But the two women soon find some much-needed help from a pair of unexpected allies -- seasoned warrior Sarah Connor and the </desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Expendables</title>
    <desc>Mercenary leader Barney Ross and his loyal men take on what they think is a routine assignment: a covert operation to invade the South American country of Vilena and overthrow its dictator. But, when they learn that the job will be a suicide mission, they must choose redemption or the destruction of their brotherhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716014500 +0000" stop="20260716033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Expendables 2</title>
    <desc>Mercenary leader Barney Ross (Sylvester Stallone), Lee Christmas (Jason Statham) and the rest of the Expendables team reunite when Mr. Church (Bruce Willis) hires them for a seemingly easy job. But things go terribly wrong, compelling the mercenaries to seek revenge for a comrade's murder. With the odds against them, Barney and his team are hell-bent on payback and cut a path of destruction throug</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716033000 +0000" stop="20260716054000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Expendables 3</title>
    <desc>Years ago, Barney Ross co-founded the Expendables with Conrad Stonebanks. After Stonebanks became an arms dealer, Ross was forced to kill him -- or so he thought. Now, Stonebanks is back, and he's on a mission to end the Expendables. Ross decides that the way to fight old blood is with new blood, so he assembles a team of younger, faster, more tech-savvy recruits. The battle to topple Stonebanks b</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716054000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Expend4bles</title>
    <desc>Armed with every weapon they can get their hands on, the Expendables are the world's last line of defense and the team that gets called when all other options are off the table.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chi</title>
    <desc>The South Side of Chicago carries daily danger, and the smallest and simplest of decisions can have life or death consequences for the residents. Life continues as the kids prep for school and their parents shuffle off to work. The young adults of the area are trying to scrape a living for themselves, while the elders sit on their front porches and observe the goings on. The South Side has the pot</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716102000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Borg vs. McEnroe</title>
    <desc>It's the summer of 1980, and Björn Borg is the top tennis player in the world, dominating the sport both on and off the court. A powerful and rigorously disciplined player, there is only one obstacle in his pursuit of a record-breaking fifth Wimbledon championship: the highly talented but ferociously abrasive young American John McEnroe. With three days until the tournament begins, Borg trains rel</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716102000 +0000" stop="20260716120500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The First Wives Club</title>
    <desc>Despondent over the marriage of her ex-husband to a younger woman, a middle-aged divorcée plunges to her death from her penthouse. At the woman's funeral, her former college friends (Bette Midler, Goldie Hawn, Diane Keaton) reunite for the first time in nearly 30 years. When the three discover the reason for their friend's suicide, they realize that all of their ex-husbands have taken them for gra</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716120500 +0000" stop="20260716134000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aeon Flux</title>
    <desc>In the 25th century, the Earth's population has dwindled to a surviving five million following a devastating virus that almost resulted in the extinction of all human life 400 years earlier. Confined to one city-state, a group of rebels, led by Handler (Frances McDormand), seeks to destroy the oppressive government -- first, by assassinating a high-ranking chairman (Marton Csokas). Tasked with thi</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716134000 +0000" stop="20260716151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Río</title>
    <desc>Captured by smugglers when he was just a hatchling, a macaw named Blu never learned to fly and lives a happily domesticated life in Minnesota with his human friend, Linda. Blu is thought to be the last of his kind, but when word comes that Jewel, a lone female, lives in Rio de Janeiro, Blu and Linda go to meet her. Animal smugglers kidnap Blu and Jewel, but the pair soon escape and begin a perilou</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716151500 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lara Croft: Tomb Raider</title>
    <desc>This live action feature is inspired by the most successful interactive video-game character in history -- Lara Croft. Beautiful and brainy, Lara is the heroine of Eidos Interactive's phenomenally successful "Tomb Raider" game series. It is one woman's fearless quest crisscrossing the globe, in an amazing attempt to save the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Untouchables</title>
    <desc>After building an empire with bootleg alcohol, legendary crime boss Al Capone (Robert De Niro) rules Chicago with an iron fist. Though Prohibition agent Eliot Ness (Kevin Costner) attempts to take Capone down, even his best efforts fail due to widespread corruption within the Windy City's police force. Recruiting an elite group of lawmen who won't be swayed by bribes or fear, including Irish-Ameri</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716203500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Extract</title>
    <desc>The owner of a factory that produces flavor extracts, Joel Reynold (Jason Bateman) seems to have it all, but really doesn't. What's missing is sexual attention from his wife, Suzie (Kristen Wiig). Joel hatches a convoluted plan to get Suzie to cheat on him, thereby clearing the way for Joel to have an affair with Cindy (Mila Kunis), an employee. But what Joel doesn't know is that Cindy is a sociop</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716203500 +0000" stop="20260716221500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Buddy Games: Spring Awakening</title>
    <desc>Faced with their biggest challenge yet, the gang sets out to honor a lost pal, only to find themselves in the middle of where it all began -- spring break. They soon learn their old school ways of partying can hardly compete with today's generation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260716221500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Without a Paddle</title>
    <desc>After their friend Billy (Anthony Starr) dies, Tom (Dax Shepard), Jerry (Matthew Lillard) and Dan (Seth Green) go on a camping trip to honor his memory. The campsite, however, has special significance. Billy believed famous airplane hijacker D.B. Cooper hid money in the area, and his friends aim to find it. Unfortunately, they are not prepared for the adventure. After falling over a waterfall, the</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260717000000 +0000" stop="20260718000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masterminds</title>
    <desc>An armored-car driver (Zach Galifianakis) helps a flirty co-worker (Kristen Wiig) and her friends pull off a heist, then finds himself holding the bag after they double-cross him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-17</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464890" start="20260715143500 +0000" stop="20260715163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pretty Red Dress</title>
    <desc>The story of Travis, Candice and their daughter, Kenisha, and their relationships with the same red dress.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260715163000 +0000" stop="20260715180500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aurora: A Love Story</title>
    <desc>Kenny and Giselle are set to marry on a beach in Puerto Rico. Giselle disappears on the day of the ceremony, setting off a wild chain of events that unearths secrets, lies and betrayal, and threatens to destroy the fairy-tale love story.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260715180500 +0000" stop="20260715203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fences</title>
    <desc>Troy Maxson makes his living as a sanitation worker in the 1950s Pittsburgh. Maxson once dreamed of becoming a professional baseball player, but was deemed too old when the major leagues began admitting black athletes. Bitter over his missed opportunity, Troy creates further tension in his family when he squashes his son's chance to meet a college football recruiter.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260715203000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Down to Earth</title>
    <desc>When amateur comedian Lance Barton (Chris Rock) finds himself at Heaven's door, he is convinced there has been a mistake. Miraculously he is right. Since returning to his own body is not an option, a heavenly agent places him into the corpse of a rich Manhattan mogul who has just been murdered by his wife -- until a more suitable replacement can be found. Ironically, it is as this new person that </desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trading Places</title>
    <desc>Upper-crust executive Louis Winthorpe III (Dan Aykroyd) and down-and-out hustler Billy Ray Valentine (Eddie Murphy) are the subjects of a bet by successful brokers Mortimer (Don Ameche) and Randolph Duke (Ralph Bellamy). An employee of the Dukes, Winthorpe is framed by the brothers for a crime he didn't commit, with the siblings then installing the street-smart Valentine in his position. When Wint</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Eddie Murphy Raw</title>
    <desc>Recorded in front of a live audience in New York City, this film features actor/comedian Eddie Murphy performing a scathing comedy routine. Eddie's uncle (Samuel L. Jackson) and other family members are lampooned in sketch segments, while Murphy largely sticks to stand-up, riffing on fellow black comedians, marriage and various racial and ethnic stereotypes, among many other topics. The concert is</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716023000 +0000" stop="20260716040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Star Trek: Section 31</title>
    <desc>Emperor Philippa Georgiou faces the sins of her past after joining a secret division of Starfleet that's tasked with protecting the United Federation of Planets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716040500 +0000" stop="20260716054500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Regarding Us</title>
    <desc>After losing her teaching career in the Catholic school system, a transgender woman has a profound impact on the lives of two children, one with two fathers in marital strife, and the other a recent transplant from a conservative household. When the children form a unique bond, new questions and old prejudices erupt.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716054500 +0000" stop="20260716074500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trading Places</title>
    <desc>Upper-crust executive Louis Winthorpe III (Dan Aykroyd) and down-and-out hustler Billy Ray Valentine (Eddie Murphy) are the subjects of a bet by successful brokers Mortimer (Don Ameche) and Randolph Duke (Ralph Bellamy). An employee of the Dukes, Winthorpe is framed by the brothers for a crime he didn't commit, with the siblings then installing the street-smart Valentine in his position. When Wint</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716074500 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">16 Shots</title>
    <desc>A Chicago police officer is charged with murder after the shooting of Laquan McDonald.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716111500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Silent Planet</title>
    <desc>Serving a life sentence alone on a distant planet, an aging convict must confront his past when a new prisoner arrives and forces him to remember his life on Earth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716111500 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Up in the Biz</title>
    <desc>Celebrity interviews and rare archival footage provide insight into the life and legacy of hip-hop icon Biz Markie.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716141500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Resurgence: DeMarcus Cousins</title>
    <desc>A documentary following DeMarcus Cousins while he recovers from an injury that has been a career death sentence for some NBA players; featuring exclusive interviews with teammates, coaches and NBA insiders.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716141500 +0000" stop="20260716160500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Virtuosity</title>
    <desc>A former cop who has been imprisoned for murdering the psychopath who killed his family, Parker Barnes (Denzel Washington) is recruited to test out a new virtual-reality program where the goal is to apprehend a computer-generated being called SID 6.7 (Russell Crowe), who has been modeled on hundreds of deranged criminals. When SID manages to escape into the real world, Barnes must capture or destr</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716160500 +0000" stop="20260716181500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Manchurian Candidate</title>
    <desc>Years after his squad was ambushed during the Gulf War, Major Ben Marco (Denzel Washington) finds himself having terrible nightmares. He begins to doubt that his fellow squad-mate Sergeant Raymond Shaw (Liev Schreiber), now a vice-presidential candidate, is the hero he remembers him being. As Marco's doubts deepen, Shaw's political power grows, and, when Marco finds a mysterious implant embedded i</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716181500 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Violent Heart</title>
    <desc>Long-buried secrets threaten to tear a couple apart.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260716214000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Run</title>
    <desc>Smugglers, the police, locals and tourists get drawn into a dangerous web of survival, sacrifice and shifting loyalties as Europe faces a surge in migration.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716214000 +0000" stop="20260716231000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parallel</title>
    <desc>Following the journey of Vanessa, a grief-stricken woman who mysteriously finds herself navigating between parallel spaces.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260716231000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Virtuosity</title>
    <desc>A former cop who has been imprisoned for murdering the psychopath who killed his family, Parker Barnes (Denzel Washington) is recruited to test out a new virtual-reality program where the goal is to apprehend a computer-generated being called SID 6.7 (Russell Crowe), who has been modeled on hundreds of deranged criminals. When SID manages to escape into the real world, Barnes must capture or destr</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="9315" start="20260715150500 +0000" stop="20260715165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">LifeHack</title>
    <desc>Kyle and his friends hack for fun, pranking online scammers. Seeking a bigger thrill, they target a billionaire's cryptocurrency..</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260715165000 +0000" stop="20260715190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">M3GAN 2.0</title>
    <desc>Two years after M3GAN's rampage, her creator, Gemma, resorts to resurrecting her infamous creation to take down Amelia, a military-grade weapon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260715190000 +0000" stop="20260715212000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Conjuring: Last Rites</title>
    <desc>Paranormal investigators Ed and Lorraine Warren take on one last terrifying case involving mysterious entities they must confront.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260715212000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Him</title>
    <desc>A young athlete descends into a world of terror when he's invited to train with a legendary champion whose charisma curdles into something darker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Weapons</title>
    <desc>When all but one child from the same class vanish on the same night, a community is left questioning their disappearance. Twisted horror.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716011500 +0000" stop="20260716025000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Last Deal</title>
    <desc>A veteran sports agent races to secure a final lucrative contract for his star client, as both their careers and lives hang in the balance. Starring Danny Dyer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716025000 +0000" stop="20260716043500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Borderline</title>
    <desc>A bodyguard protects a pop superstar and her athlete boyfriend from a determined stalker in 1990s Los Angeles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716043500 +0000" stop="20260716061000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Safe House</title>
    <desc>Six federal agents in hiding after the LA terror attack grow suspicious of each other as they realise the perpetrator could be among them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716061000 +0000" stop="20260716075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Ordinary Heist</title>
    <desc>Inspired by the 2004 Northern Bank robbery, two feuding bank employees are forced to execute Ireland's biggest heist after criminals kidnap their families.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716075500 +0000" stop="20260716094000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">LifeHack</title>
    <desc>Kyle and his friends hack for fun, pranking online scammers. Seeking a bigger thrill, they target a billionaire's cryptocurrency..</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716094000 +0000" stop="20260716112500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Plague</title>
    <desc>A socially awkward tween endures the ruthless hierarchy at a water polo camp as his anxiety spirals into psychological turmoil over the summer. Language/sex/mature themes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716112500 +0000" stop="20260716131000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icefall</title>
    <desc>A game warden captures a poacher only to discover he's aware of the location of a plane carrying millions of dollars frozen in a lake. Sky Original with Joel Kinnaman.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716131000 +0000" stop="20260716145500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Ordinary Heist</title>
    <desc>Inspired by the 2004 Northern Bank robbery, two feuding bank employees are forced to execute Ireland's biggest heist after criminals kidnap their families.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716145500 +0000" stop="20260716171500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Conjuring: Last Rites</title>
    <desc>Paranormal investigators Ed and Lorraine Warren take on one last terrifying case involving mysterious entities they must confront.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716171500 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sisu: Road To Revenge</title>
    <desc>Returning to his house, a one-man army comes up against his family's killers and sets out for revenge. Finnish action sequel with subtitles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716204000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nobody 2</title>
    <desc>Suburban dad Hutch, a former lethal assassin, is pulled back into his violent past after a home invasion, setting off a chain of events.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716204000 +0000" stop="20260716225500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Weapons</title>
    <desc>When all but one child from the same class vanish on the same night, a community is left questioning their disappearance. Twisted horror.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9315" start="20260716225500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Last Deal</title>
    <desc>A veteran sports agent races to secure a final lucrative contract for his star client, as both their careers and lives hang in the balance. Starring Danny Dyer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464979" start="20260715151400 +0000" stop="20260715171400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Another Happy Day</title>
    <desc>A woman (Ellen Barkin) attends her son's wedding at the estate of her ex-husband (Thomas Haden Church).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260715171400 +0000" stop="20260715184700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Twice Upon a Yesterday</title>
    <desc>Victor Bukowski cheats on girlfriend Sylvia Weld, who rebounds and gets engaged to Dave Summers. Wishing he could undo his error, Victor happens upon two otherworldly trash collectors, who send him back in time. He uses the opportunity to woo Sylvia again, while making sure that an attractive woman catches Dave's eye. But his attraction to a waitress, Louise, could ruin Victor's plan to right thin</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260715184700 +0000" stop="20260715203500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Morning Glory</title>
    <desc>Newly hired as a producer on a national morning-news program called "Daybreak," Becky Fuller (Rachel McAdams) decides to revitalize the low-rated show by bringing in legendary anchorman Mike Pomeroy (Harrison Ford). Pomeroy, however, refuses to do puff pieces like celebrity gossip and fashion, and clashes with his co-host (Diane Keaton). Meanwhile, Becky's romance with a colleague begins to unrave</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260715203500 +0000" stop="20260715220100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hi-Life</title>
    <desc>An out-of-work New York actor enlists friends and strangers to help him get the $900 he owes a bookie (Charles Durning).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260715220100 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Another Happy Day</title>
    <desc>A woman (Ellen Barkin) attends her son's wedding at the estate of her ex-husband (Thomas Haden Church).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716000100 +0000" stop="20260716014400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Evolution</title>
    <desc>Chaos ensues when a meteor hits the Earth carrying alien life forms that give new meaning to the term survival of the fittest.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716014400 +0000" stop="20260716033200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Morning Glory</title>
    <desc>Newly hired as a producer on a national morning-news program called "Daybreak," Becky Fuller (Rachel McAdams) decides to revitalize the low-rated show by bringing in legendary anchorman Mike Pomeroy (Harrison Ford). Pomeroy, however, refuses to do puff pieces like celebrity gossip and fashion, and clashes with his co-host (Diane Keaton). Meanwhile, Becky's romance with a colleague begins to unrave</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716033200 +0000" stop="20260716051300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">High School</title>
    <desc>The day after high-school senior Henry Burke (Matt Bush) smokes his very first joint, his principal (Michael Chiklis) institutes a mandatory drug test for all students. Since he'll lose his college scholarship if he fails the drug test, Henry forms a half-baked plan. He teams up with his stoner pal Breaux (Sean Marquette) to steal some prime weed from a drug dealer named Psycho Ed (Adrien Brody), </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716051300 +0000" stop="20260716071000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Words and Pictures</title>
    <desc>An art teacher and English teacher have a competition and allow students to vote on the importance of words and pictures.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716071000 +0000" stop="20260716084600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Novocaine</title>
    <desc>Steve Martin is a prosperous dentist, secure in his neatly ordered existence and happily engaged to his ambitious dental hygienist. But when an alluring new patient steps into his life, this ordinary man discovers how little control he has over his world as he is drawn into a maelstrom of sex, drugs and murder. Edgy and unpredictable, "Novocaine" also stars Kevin Bacon and Scott Caan and marks the</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716084600 +0000" stop="20260716102100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Krystal</title>
    <desc>A sheltered young man joins Alcoholics Anonymous to get closer to the woman of his dreams, a former hooker and stripper named Krystal.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716102100 +0000" stop="20260716115600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Death on Long Island</title>
    <desc>Curmudgeonly author Giles De'Ath (John Hurt), a widower with a marked distaste for modern popular culture, attempts to buy a ticket for a film adaptation of an E.M. Forster novel, but instead finds himself watching a tacky teen sex comedy. Yet when the beautiful Ronnie Bostock (Jason Priestley) appears on the movie screen, Giles finds himself caught in a whirlwind of unanswered questions about bot</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716115600 +0000" stop="20260716135300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Words and Pictures</title>
    <desc>An art teacher and English teacher have a competition and allow students to vote on the importance of words and pictures.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716135300 +0000" stop="20260716154400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The School of Rock</title>
    <desc>Overly enthusiastic guitarist Dewey Finn (Jack Black) gets thrown out of his bar band and finds himself in desperate need of work. Posing as a substitute music teacher at an elite private elementary school, he exposes his students to the hard rock gods he idolizes and emulates -- much to the consternation of the uptight principal (Joan Cusack). As he gets his privileged and precocious charges in t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716154400 +0000" stop="20260716172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cake</title>
    <desc>A travel writer (Heather Graham) improves her love life when she becomes an editor for her father's wedding magazine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716172000 +0000" stop="20260716185200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Stoned Age</title>
    <desc>A pair of '70s-era drug-befuddled buddies tries to cash in on the abundance of women at an unbelievable party.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716185200 +0000" stop="20260716202900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Burger</title>
    <desc>Teen misfits (Kel Mitchell, Kenan Thompson) at a modest burger joint face competition from a hamburger emporium across the street.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716202900 +0000" stop="20260716220400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Death on Long Island</title>
    <desc>Curmudgeonly author Giles De'Ath (John Hurt), a widower with a marked distaste for modern popular culture, attempts to buy a ticket for a film adaptation of an E.M. Forster novel, but instead finds himself watching a tacky teen sex comedy. Yet when the beautiful Ronnie Bostock (Jason Priestley) appears on the movie screen, Giles finds himself caught in a whirlwind of unanswered questions about bot</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716220400 +0000" stop="20260716235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The School of Rock</title>
    <desc>Overly enthusiastic guitarist Dewey Finn (Jack Black) gets thrown out of his bar band and finds himself in desperate need of work. Posing as a substitute music teacher at an elite private elementary school, he exposes his students to the hard rock gods he idolizes and emulates -- much to the consternation of the uptight principal (Joan Cusack). As he gets his privileged and precocious charges in t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260716235500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Words and Pictures</title>
    <desc>An art teacher and English teacher have a competition and allow students to vote on the importance of words and pictures.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464893" start="20260715153400 +0000" stop="20260715174700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baby Boy</title>
    <desc>The story of Jody (Tyrese Gibson), a misguided, 20-year-old African-American who is really just a baby boy finally forced-kicking and screaming to face the commitments of real life. Streetwise and jobless, he has not only fathered two children by two different women-Yvette (Taraji P. Henson) and Peanut (Tamara LaSeon Bass) but still lives with his own mother. He can't seem to strike a balance or f</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260715174700 +0000" stop="20260715194900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Looper</title>
    <desc>In a future society, time-travel exists, but it's only available to those with the means to pay for it on the black market. When the mob wants to eliminate someone, it sends the target into the past, where a hit man known as a looper lies in wait to finish the job. Joe (Joseph Gordon-Levitt) is one such hired gun, and he does his job well -- until the day his bosses decide to "close the loop" and </desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260715194900 +0000" stop="20260715213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Fortune</title>
    <desc>A well-meaning but inept angel named Gabriel meddles in the lives of a struggling gig worker and a wealthy venture capitalist.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Never Let Go</title>
    <desc>When an unspeakable evil takes over the world, the only protection for a mother and her twin sons is their house and strong bond. Needing to stay connected at all times, even tethering themselves with ropes, they must cling to one another and never let go. However, when one of the boys questions if the evil is real, the ties that bind them together are severed, triggering a terrifying fight for su</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260715231500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wedding Ringer</title>
    <desc>Socially awkward Doug Harris is two weeks from marrying the gal of his dreams, but he has a problem: He doesn't have any groomsmen for the occasion. Desperate and running out of time, Doug calls upon Jimmy Callahan, owner and operator of Best Man Inc., a company that provides attendants for friendless grooms. As Doug tries to pull off the con, a bromance unexpectedly blossoms between Jimmy and him</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716024400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">About Last Night</title>
    <desc>While out with loudmouthed pal Bernie (Kevin Hart), Danny (Michael Ealy) meets successful businesswoman Debbie (Joy Bryant), who's as leery of relationships as Danny is. However, Danny and Debbie both feel the pull of undeniable attraction, and they end up spending the first of several nights together. The two try to make a success of being a couple despite warnings from Bernie and Joan (Regina Ha</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716024400 +0000" stop="20260716044600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Looper</title>
    <desc>In a future society, time-travel exists, but it's only available to those with the means to pay for it on the black market. When the mob wants to eliminate someone, it sends the target into the past, where a hit man known as a looper lies in wait to finish the job. Joe (Joseph Gordon-Levitt) is one such hired gun, and he does his job well -- until the day his bosses decide to "close the loop" and </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716044600 +0000" stop="20260716062700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Strangers: Chapter 2</title>
    <desc>After learning that one of their victims, Maya, is still alive, three masked maniacs return to finish the job. With nowhere to run and no one to trust, Maya soon finds herself in a brutal fight for survival against psychopaths who are more than willing to kill anyone who stands in their way.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716062700 +0000" stop="20260716083900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blood Ties</title>
    <desc>An ex-con (Clive Owen) tries to pull away from a life of crime, but the temptation proves too strong, bringing his already-strained relationship with his policeman brother (Billy Crudup) to the breaking point.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716083900 +0000" stop="20260716114100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Casino</title>
    <desc>In early-1970s Las Vegas, low-level mobster Sam "Ace" Rothstein (Robert De Niro) gets tapped by his bosses to head the Tangiers Casino. At first, he's a great success in the job, but over the years, problems with his loose-cannon enforcer Nicky Santoro (Joe Pesci), his ex-hustler wife Ginger (Sharon Stone), her con-artist ex Lester Diamond (James Woods) and a handful of corrupt politicians put Sam</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716114100 +0000" stop="20260716132200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Confidence</title>
    <desc>In this glossy neo-noir caper, expert grifter Jake Vig (Edward Burns) inadvertently crosses volatile crime boss the King (Dustin Hoffman) and, to make it right, he must agree to con banker Morgan Price (Robert Forster). He assembles his team, including Lily (Rachel Weisz) and Gordo (Paul Giamatti), but things get complicated fast with the arrival of Special Agent Gunther Butan (Andy Garcia), who h</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716132200 +0000" stop="20260716145500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mo' Money</title>
    <desc>After petty criminal Johnny (Damon Wayans) falls for the lovely Amber (Stacey Dash), he decides to stop breaking the law and gets a gig at his crush's workplace in order to get closer to her, thus proving that he's a stand-up guy. Soon, he learns that going straight doesn't pay very well, so he decides to nab a company credit card and show off his newfound wealth to Amber. Unfortunately, a blackma</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716145500 +0000" stop="20260716163500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Neighbors</title>
    <desc>A young couple suffering from arrested development are forced to live next to a fraternity house after the birth of their newborn baby.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716163500 +0000" stop="20260716181100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Neighbors 2: Sorority Rising</title>
    <desc>Life is good for Mac Radner (Seth Rogen) and pregnant wife Kelly (Rose Byrne) until the unruly sisters of Kappa Nu move in next door. As the loud parties threaten the sale of their home, the couple turn to ex-neighbor and one-time enemy Teddy Sanders (Zac Efron) for help. Now united with the former college student, the trio devises schemes to get the wild sorority off the block. Unfortunately, the</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716181100 +0000" stop="20260716211300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Casino</title>
    <desc>In early-1970s Las Vegas, low-level mobster Sam "Ace" Rothstein (Robert De Niro) gets tapped by his bosses to head the Tangiers Casino. At first, he's a great success in the job, but over the years, problems with his loose-cannon enforcer Nicky Santoro (Joe Pesci), his ex-hustler wife Ginger (Sharon Stone), her con-artist ex Lester Diamond (James Woods) and a handful of corrupt politicians put Sam</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716211300 +0000" stop="20260716232700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dreamgirls</title>
    <desc>Deena (Beyoncé Knowles), Effie (Jennifer Hudson) and Lorrell (Anika Noni Rose) form a music trio called the Dreamettes. When ambitious manager Curtis Taylor Jr. (Jamie Foxx) spots the act at a talent show, he offers the chance of a lifetime, to be backup singers for a national star (Eddie Murphy). Taylor takes creative control of the group and eventually pushes the singers into the spotlight. Howe</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464893" start="20260716232700 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mo' Money</title>
    <desc>After petty criminal Johnny (Damon Wayans) falls for the lovely Amber (Stacey Dash), he decides to stop breaking the law and gets a gig at his crush's workplace in order to get closer to her, thus proving that he's a stand-up guy. Soon, he learns that going straight doesn't pay very well, so he decides to nab a company credit card and show off his newfound wealth to Amber. Unfortunately, a blackma</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465242" start="20260715154800 +0000" stop="20260715173400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">You Again</title>
    <desc>Marni is shocked to learn that her brother is marrying her school bully from the past. When she tries to expose her, things do not go as planned.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260715173400 +0000" stop="20260715190200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Treasure</title>
    <desc>An old sea captain helps three young friends solve the 30-year-old case of a missing lighthouse keeper.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260715190200 +0000" stop="20260715202000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Barkers: Mind the Cats!</title>
    <desc>A family of dogs decides to go on a holiday.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260715202000 +0000" stop="20260715215300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Against the Wild</title>
    <desc>Two siblings and their dogs become lost in the wilderness and combine their skills to survive.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260715215300 +0000" stop="20260715232600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Against the Wild: Survive the Serengeti</title>
    <desc>Two kids and their dog have to survive in the African bush after their plane crashes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260715232600 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joey &amp; Ella</title>
    <desc>A mysterious diamond causes a baby kangaroo named Joey to grow quickly and gain the power of speech. When two bumbling thieves try to retrieve the magical gem, a teen and her new boyfriend try to get Joey to safety before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716005600 +0000" stop="20260716023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Centurion: The Dancing Stallion</title>
    <desc>Ellissia adopts a white stallion to train in the art of Mexican horse dancing. As she starts teaching the handsome but previously abused Centurion, Ellissia falls critically ill, which keeps her from competing in a celebrated equestrian event. Under the watchful eyes of her father, new ranch hand Danny steps in as trainer, hoping to win the competition - and, perhaps, Ellissia's heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716023500 +0000" stop="20260716042100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">You Again</title>
    <desc>Marni is shocked to learn that her brother is marrying her school bully from the past. When she tries to expose her, things do not go as planned.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716042100 +0000" stop="20260716054600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Adventures of Jurassic Pet</title>
    <desc>A young boy tries to protect his pet dinosaur, Albert, from a scientist who is determined to conduct nefarious experiments on him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716054600 +0000" stop="20260716071100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Adventures of Jurassic Pet 2: The Lost Secret</title>
    <desc>An adventurous teenager and an orphan must save their town from a group of criminals while trying to get a baby dinosaur back home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716071100 +0000" stop="20260716085100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Best Friend</title>
    <desc>A free-spirited girl from the city feels out of place when her family moves to the country. Thankfully, she meets a telepathic horse that can give her the companionship and advice she'll need to succeed in her new home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716085100 +0000" stop="20260716093700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega 3: The Great Wolf Games</title>
    <desc>Coach Humphrey must assemble a ragtag team of underdogs after an unexpected accident puts many of the alpha wolves out of commission.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716093700 +0000" stop="20260716102300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega: The Legend of the Saw Tooth Cave</title>
    <desc>When Runt sneaks off to explore a haunted cave, he finds a wolf who has been driven from her pack and tries to help her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716102300 +0000" stop="20260716110700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega: Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Kate and Humphrey take their pups to Alfred Creek Falls for a vacation, where they find themselves embroiled in a cross-country chase after mad wolf trappers spot them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716110700 +0000" stop="20260716115300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha &amp; Omega: The Big Fureeze</title>
    <desc>Wolf pups Stinky, Claudette and Runt venture out into a blizzard to save their parents. They're joined by a sleepy bear cub and a feisty porcupine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716115300 +0000" stop="20260716124100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega: Dino Digs</title>
    <desc>After Kate, Humphrey, and their three pups are forced to relocate their den, they discover Amy, a friendly raptor who came to life after being uncovered during a big dig.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716124100 +0000" stop="20260716132600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega: Journey to Bear Kingdom</title>
    <desc>Stinky, Runt and Claudette spring into action when rogue wolves threaten the royal bears. With courage, wits and help from their wild friends, the alpha and omega wolves rise to protect the queen and princess and save their forest home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716132600 +0000" stop="20260716145600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Dog Who Saved Summer</title>
    <desc>After their dog Zeus ruins a party, George takes him to an obedience school run by a no-nonsense instructor. When Zeus manages to fail every test, he seeks help from a trainer with special techniques.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716145600 +0000" stop="20260716162400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chestnut: Hero of Central Park</title>
    <desc>Two adopted sisters try to conceal a puppy in a New York building where dogs are prohibited.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716162400 +0000" stop="20260716180400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Best Friend</title>
    <desc>A free-spirited girl from the city feels out of place when her family moves to the country. Thankfully, she meets a telepathic horse that can give her the companionship and advice she'll need to succeed in her new home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716180400 +0000" stop="20260716193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fly Me to the Moon</title>
    <desc>Nat the fly loves listening to his grandfather (Christopher Lloyd) tell stories of adventures from his youth. Desperate to experience some derring-do of his own, Nat convinces two of his friends to stow away on Apollo 11. The high-flying trio have the adventure of a lifetime when they must prevent a Russian bug (Tim Curry) from sabotaging the mission.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716193000 +0000" stop="20260716201600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega 3: The Great Wolf Games</title>
    <desc>Coach Humphrey must assemble a ragtag team of underdogs after an unexpected accident puts many of the alpha wolves out of commission.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716201600 +0000" stop="20260716210200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega: The Legend of the Saw Tooth Cave</title>
    <desc>When Runt sneaks off to explore a haunted cave, he finds a wolf who has been driven from her pack and tries to help her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716210200 +0000" stop="20260716214600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega: Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Kate and Humphrey take their pups to Alfred Creek Falls for a vacation, where they find themselves embroiled in a cross-country chase after mad wolf trappers spot them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716214600 +0000" stop="20260716223200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha &amp; Omega: The Big Fureeze</title>
    <desc>Wolf pups Stinky, Claudette and Runt venture out into a blizzard to save their parents. They're joined by a sleepy bear cub and a feisty porcupine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716223200 +0000" stop="20260716232000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega: Dino Digs</title>
    <desc>After Kate, Humphrey, and their three pups are forced to relocate their den, they discover Amy, a friendly raptor who came to life after being uncovered during a big dig.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260716232000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alpha and Omega: Journey to Bear Kingdom</title>
    <desc>Stinky, Runt and Claudette spring into action when rogue wolves threaten the royal bears. With courage, wits and help from their wild friends, the alpha and omega wolves rise to protect the queen and princess and save their forest home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465115" start="20260715155100 +0000" stop="20260715173800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape From Pretoria</title>
    <desc>Sentenced to a South African prison for 12 years, anti-apartheid activist Tim Jenkin and his fellow inmates devise a daring plan to escape.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260715173800 +0000" stop="20260715190500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bending All the Rules</title>
    <desc>A businessman (David Gail) and a disc jockey (Bradley Cooper) woo a free-spirited photographer (Colleen Porch).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260715190500 +0000" stop="20260715204400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Groomsmen</title>
    <desc>Blue-collar Paulie (Edward Burns) prepares for fatherhood and his forthcoming wedding to Sue (Brittany Murphy) by hanging out with his groomsmen. Brother Jimbo (Donal Logue), cousin Mike (Jay Mohr) and his pals fill the reunion with drinking, boys-will-be-boys antics and a few unexpected personal confessions. But, when the bonding devolves into accusations and regret, Paulie has to decide whether </desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260715204400 +0000" stop="20260715221500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Broken Vows</title>
    <desc>A troubled man spirals into a rage after he is rejected by a woman he seduced.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260715221500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Lucky Ones</title>
    <desc>Stuck at a closed airport while on leave from Iraq War service, soldiers Colee Dunn (Rachel McAdams), Fred Cheaver (Tim Robbins) and T.K. Poole (Michael Peña) decide to carpool to get to their far-off destinations. Colee wants to visit with her late fiancé's family, while wounded T.K. longs to see his future wife and Fred, needing fast cash to send his son to college, is headed for a casino. Durin</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716000900 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bonjour tristesse</title>
    <desc>At the height of summer, 18-year-old Cécile is relaxing by the French seaside with her father and falling in love with her new boyfriend. However, the arrival of her late mother's enigmatic friend soon turns her world upside down.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716034300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Details</title>
    <desc>Seemingly blind to the actual cracks in his marriage, a doctor (Tobey Maguire) blames a family of destructive raccoons for the problems in his home life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716034300 +0000" stop="20260716053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Macbeth</title>
    <desc>After murdering King Duncan (David Thewlis) and seizing the throne, Macbeth (Michael Fassbender) becomes consumed with guilt and paranoia as the tyrannical ruler of Scotland.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716053700 +0000" stop="20260716072400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Family Fang</title>
    <desc>An actress and her brother investigate the mysterious disappearance of their parents, two performance artists known for their hoaxes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716072400 +0000" stop="20260716090100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mistress of Spices</title>
    <desc>A woman (Aishwarya Rai) who harnesses magic powers from spices falls for a hunky architect (Dylan McDermott).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716090100 +0000" stop="20260716103700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dedication</title>
    <desc>When children's author Henry Roth (Billy Crudup) loses his longtime illustrator, his publisher sends him a new artist, Lucy (Mandy Moore). He is a tangle of neuroses and nastiness, and he does everything he can to alienate her, even though he must deliver his latest book in less than a month. Secretly Henry begins to fall in love with Lucy, and at the same time, her ex-boyfriend returns to try to </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716103700 +0000" stop="20260716115700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Frenemy</title>
    <desc>Two drifters (Matthew Modine, Callum Blue) in Los Angeles leave behind a trail of murdered women.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716115700 +0000" stop="20260716134200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Asher</title>
    <desc>Asher is a former Mossad agent turned gun-for-hire, living an austere life in an ever-changing Brooklyn. Approaching the end of his career, he breaks the oath he took as a young man when he meets Sophie on a hit gone wrong. In order to have love in his life before it's too late, he must kill the man he was, for a chance at becoming the man he wants to be.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716134200 +0000" stop="20260716151600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chronic</title>
    <desc>David, a meticulous and efficient home care nurse working with terminally ill people, develops close relationships with his patients. In his private life David is awkward and reserved, which leads to him needing his patients as much as they need him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716151600 +0000" stop="20260716165900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Details</title>
    <desc>Seemingly blind to the actual cracks in his marriage, a doctor (Tobey Maguire) blames a family of destructive raccoons for the problems in his home life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716165900 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Conclave</title>
    <desc>Cardinal Lawrence has one of the world's most secretive and ancient events, participating in the selection of a new pope. Surrounded by powerful religious leaders in the halls of the Vatican, he soon uncovers a trail of deep secrets that could shake the very foundation of the Roman Catholic Church.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716210800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Queen of Spain</title>
    <desc>Eighteen years after fleeing Nazi Germany, Spanish film actress Macarena Granada becomes a major Hollywood star. She returns to Spain to play Isabella I of Castile, surrounded by showbiz hype.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716210800 +0000" stop="20260716225500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Family Fang</title>
    <desc>An actress and her brother investigate the mysterious disappearance of their parents, two performance artists known for their hoaxes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465115" start="20260716225500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chronic</title>
    <desc>David, a meticulous and efficient home care nurse working with terminally ill people, develops close relationships with his patients. In his private life David is awkward and reserved, which leads to him needing his patients as much as they need him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465109" start="20260715151900 +0000" stop="20260715164700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wings</title>
    <desc>A young aircraft fighter pilot trains with a flying legend in the hope that he can win a prestigious air show competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260715164700 +0000" stop="20260715181000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wings: Sky Force Heroes</title>
    <desc>After his recklessness causes a comrade's death, a firefighter (Josh Duhamel) quits the brigade and goes to work in a coal mine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260715181000 +0000" stop="20260715193800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Gobie</title>
    <desc>While snowboarding, Little Gobie and his pet dragon BeBe get into an accident. BeBe gets injured, Little Gobie looks for help from Santa Claus.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260715193800 +0000" stop="20260715210800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Adventures of A.R.I.: My Robot Friend</title>
    <desc>A teen tries to save a friendly robot from a ruthless CEO who wants to turn it into a dangerous weapon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260715210800 +0000" stop="20260715223800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joey &amp; Ella</title>
    <desc>A mysterious diamond causes a baby kangaroo named Joey to grow quickly and gain the power of speech. When two bumbling thieves try to retrieve the magical gem, a teen and her new boyfriend try to get Joey to safety before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260715223800 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Return to Wickensburg</title>
    <desc>Mr. Hexenmeister has escaped from prison, and once again threatens Wickensburg. A race against time to find an ancient orb, capable of destroying the entire town, before it falls into the wrong hands.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716000700 +0000" stop="20260716015100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">H Is for Happiness</title>
    <desc>An optimistic 12-year-old girl hatches scheme after scheme to make her mother, father and uncle happy again.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716015100 +0000" stop="20260716031900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wings</title>
    <desc>A young aircraft fighter pilot trains with a flying legend in the hope that he can win a prestigious air show competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716031900 +0000" stop="20260716044200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wings: Sky Force Heroes</title>
    <desc>After his recklessness causes a comrade's death, a firefighter (Josh Duhamel) quits the brigade and goes to work in a coal mine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716044200 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unstable Fables: Tortoise vs. Hare</title>
    <desc>Defeated in a race, a frustrated hare (Jay Leno) challenges a slow tortoise (Danny Glover) to a rematch.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716072700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Turtle Tale</title>
    <desc>Rafi, Hank and Goliath, a trio of talking turtles, are living the good life at a Florida animal park. But when vandals kidnap Hank, it's up to Rafi and Goliath to find their missing friend.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716072700 +0000" stop="20260716084900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">C.I.Ape</title>
    <desc>Agent James Bond and a talking chimp embark on a dangerous mission to Wolfhound Island to stop Alpha Dog's plans for world domination.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716084900 +0000" stop="20260716102400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Grizzly Falls</title>
    <desc>After a grizzly bear abducts him during a hunting trip, a young boy forms an unexpected bond with the creature, while his father and a tracker embark on a dangerous mission to rescue him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716102400 +0000" stop="20260716115700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nacho Libre</title>
    <desc>Ignacio (Jack Black), or Nacho to his friends, works as a cook in the Mexican monastery where he grew up. The monastery is home to a host of orphans whom Nacho cares for deeply, but there is not much money to feed them properly. Nacho decides to raise money for the children by moonlighting as a Lucha Libre wrestler with his partner Esqueleto (Héctor Jiménez), but since the church forbids Lucha, Na</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716115700 +0000" stop="20260716134300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Young and Prodigious T.S. Spivet</title>
    <desc>T.S. is invited to the Smithsonian to receive an award for inventing a perpetual motion machine. Without telling any of his family, he boards a freight train heading to Washington, D.C., to attend the ceremony.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716134300 +0000" stop="20260716152000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mistress of Spices</title>
    <desc>A woman (Aishwarya Rai) who harnesses magic powers from spices falls for a hunky architect (Dylan McDermott).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716152000 +0000" stop="20260716164800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Dog the Champion</title>
    <desc>A girl (Dora Madison Burge) discovers that her grandfather's (Lance Henriksen) cattle dog has a natural talent for dog agility competitions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716164800 +0000" stop="20260716182300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Grizzly Falls</title>
    <desc>After a grizzly bear abducts him during a hunting trip, a young boy forms an unexpected bond with the creature, while his father and a tracker embark on a dangerous mission to rescue him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716182300 +0000" stop="20260716194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">C.I.Ape</title>
    <desc>Agent James Bond and a talking chimp embark on a dangerous mission to Wolfhound Island to stop Alpha Dog's plans for world domination.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716194500 +0000" stop="20260716212800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Heart Shakey</title>
    <desc>A widowed chef (Steve Lemme) and his daughter (Rylie Behr) move to Chicago, but a clause in their new apartment's rental agreement means that they will have to give up their beloved dog.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716212800 +0000" stop="20260716231400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Young and Prodigious T.S. Spivet</title>
    <desc>T.S. is invited to the Smithsonian to receive an award for inventing a perpetual motion machine. Without telling any of his family, he boards a freight train heading to Washington, D.C., to attend the ceremony.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465109" start="20260716231400 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nacho Libre</title>
    <desc>Ignacio (Jack Black), or Nacho to his friends, works as a cook in the Mexican monastery where he grew up. The monastery is home to a host of orphans whom Nacho cares for deeply, but there is not much money to feed them properly. Nacho decides to raise money for the children by moonlighting as a Lucha Libre wrestler with his partner Esqueleto (Héctor Jiménez), but since the church forbids Lucha, Na</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464973" start="20260715153200 +0000" stop="20260715170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hellgate</title>
    <desc>After the Civil War, ranch owner Gil Hanley helps a stranger in desperate need of medical attention. Soon he is questioned by Union soldiers about the stranger, who turns out to be an ex-Confederate soldier. Hanley, also an ex-Confederate, is unjustly convicted as a conspirator and sentenced to life in a brutal desert prison in New Mexico. After battling his tough cellmate and a sadistic guard, Ha</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715170000 +0000" stop="20260715175200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Maverick</title>
    <desc>Bart wins a ton of money through a poker game but when he offers aid to a stranger, he finds himself in the middle of a swindle.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715175200 +0000" stop="20260715184100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheyenne</title>
    <desc>Cheyenne springs a trap to catch the would-be assassins of Juarez and snags a killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715184100 +0000" stop="20260715195900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wagon Train</title>
    <desc>Cooper learns that his girlfriend Rose's (Annette Funicello) brother is a Brooklyn criminal.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715195900 +0000" stop="20260715211700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wagon Train</title>
    <desc>The Bancroft gang robs a family of emigrants of all their possessions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715211700 +0000" stop="20260715214400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tales of Wells Fargo</title>
    <desc>Hardie is called to investigate when a rash of robberies occurs at Leadville, but his arrival is less than auspicious when he's relieved of his wallet and gun by an old woman who robs the stage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715214400 +0000" stop="20260715221100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tales of Wells Fargo</title>
    <desc>Hardie's curious when a successful stage-line owner suddenly decides to sell out, at a very low price.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715221100 +0000" stop="20260715223700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lawman</title>
    <desc>Marshal Troop takes on a gang that is trying to free a dangerous killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715223700 +0000" stop="20260715230300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lawman</title>
    <desc>Troop faces a shoot-out when he takes on a vigilante committee.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715230300 +0000" stop="20260715232900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lawman</title>
    <desc>Troop and McKay are held captive by bank robbers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260715232900 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheyenne</title>
    <desc>Cheyenne tries to help a pregnant woman get a herd of cattle to town, then learns the man he shot in self-defense is her husband.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716001900 +0000" stop="20260716010900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheyenne</title>
    <desc>Cheyenne and Char, a young Lakota, search for a 10-year-old boy who disappeared.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716010900 +0000" stop="20260716015900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Maverick</title>
    <desc>In order to prove that crooks can't be trusted, Bart double-crosses a double-crosser.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716015900 +0000" stop="20260716024900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Maverick</title>
    <desc>Bret is forced to become sheriff after his horse renders the town bully unconscious.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716024900 +0000" stop="20260716041800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hellgate</title>
    <desc>After the Civil War, ranch owner Gil Hanley helps a stranger in desperate need of medical attention. Soon he is questioned by Union soldiers about the stranger, who turns out to be an ex-Confederate soldier. Hanley, also an ex-Confederate, is unjustly convicted as a conspirator and sentenced to life in a brutal desert prison in New Mexico. After battling his tough cellmate and a sadistic guard, Ha</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716041800 +0000" stop="20260716064800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brimstone</title>
    <desc>A frontier woman turns fugitive when she is wrongly accused of a crime she didn't commit and is hunted by a vengeful preacher.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716064800 +0000" stop="20260716082600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Town Called Hell</title>
    <desc>At the turn of the 20th century in Mexico, an outlaw leads a massacre of a small town. Soldiers and townspeople alike are killed, and, when a priest and his followers take refuge in a church, they too are ruthlessly offed. A decade later, the town is run by Don Carlos, and the murderous outlaw has changed his name and is now a local priest. When Elvira trots into the town, she offers a large rewar</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716082600 +0000" stop="20260716100400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Magnificent Matador</title>
    <desc>An aging matador (Anthony Quinn) faces fear as he loves a rich American (Maureen O'Hara) and guides his son (Manuel Rojas) in the bullring.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716100400 +0000" stop="20260716110200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stars Over Texas</title>
    <desc>Cowboys Eddie Dean (Eddie Dean) and Soapy Jones (Roscoe Ates) have come to the end of a tough cattle drive, but, instead of the rancher they were expecting, they're welcomed by his sister, young Terry Lawrence (Shirley Patterson). It seems that Terry's brother and one of his employees were wounded by gun-toting thugs. Eddie and Soapy realize that they'll need to get to the bottom of things, so the</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716110200 +0000" stop="20260716120100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Romance of the West</title>
    <desc>Eddie Dean (Eddie Dean), along with his sidekick, Ezra (Emmett Lynn), oversees the peaceful coexistence of the Native American tribes with the white settlers of Antelope Valley. The treaty that binds the two groups is threatened when some of the town leaders learn that the Native American land contains rich deposits of silver. Eager to oust the tribes and claim the silver, the town leaders try to </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716120100 +0000" stop="20260716132900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hellgate</title>
    <desc>After the Civil War, ranch owner Gil Hanley helps a stranger in desperate need of medical attention. Soon he is questioned by Union soldiers about the stranger, who turns out to be an ex-Confederate soldier. Hanley, also an ex-Confederate, is unjustly convicted as a conspirator and sentenced to life in a brutal desert prison in New Mexico. After battling his tough cellmate and a sadistic guard, Ha</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716132900 +0000" stop="20260716153700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">McLintock!</title>
    <desc>Aging rancher George Washington McLintock, a wealthy self-made man, is forced to deal with numerous personal and professional problems. Seemingly everyone wants a piece of his enormous farmstead, including high-ranking government men, McLintock's own sons and nearby Native Americans. As McLintock tries to juggle his various adversaries, his wife, who left him two years previously, suddenly returns</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716153700 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brother Outlaw</title>
    <desc>A man is framed for bank robbery, prompting his brother to spring him from jail. Their search for the real culprits ends in a violent confrontation with a famed gunfighter.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716175200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Maverick</title>
    <desc>Beau engages in a desperate struggle with Mexican bandits and Indians to find a lost gold mine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716175200 +0000" stop="20260716184100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheyenne</title>
    <desc>Cheyenne uses an old theatrical trick to pin down a confession from a clever murderer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716184100 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wagon Train</title>
    <desc>A woman (Diana Hyland) faces a death sentence after her married boyfriend is found murdered during a cross-country journey. Bradford Dillman also guest stars.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260716211800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wagon Train</title>
    <desc>A woman must protect herself and her daughter from a callous man.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716211800 +0000" stop="20260716214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tales of Wells Fargo</title>
    <desc>Hardie is sent to guard a shipment of old paper money being sent to San Francisco to be destroyed when he gets a tip that a robbery is planned.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716214500 +0000" stop="20260716221200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tales of Wells Fargo</title>
    <desc>Hardie meets a woman whose estranged husband is a wanted outlaw.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716221200 +0000" stop="20260716223800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lawman</title>
    <desc>A veteran lawman plans an ambush killing.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716223800 +0000" stop="20260716230400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lawman</title>
    <desc>Marshal Troop arrests a woman gunfighter.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716230400 +0000" stop="20260716233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lawman</title>
    <desc>Marshal Troop defends a woman who was in prison for murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260716233000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheyenne</title>
    <desc>After helping a wounded man into a Mexican town, Cheyenne discovers his patient is an escaped bank robber and murderer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465397" start="20260715151000 +0000" stop="20260715163500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Argument</title>
    <desc>When a couple argue about a party and neither will back down, they decide to re-create the evening to determine who is right.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260715163500 +0000" stop="20260715183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chasing Amy</title>
    <desc>Holden and Banky are best friends and authors of a popular comic book. Holden falls in love with Alyssa, who happens to be a lesbian. Holden's relationship with Alyssa strains his life-long friendship with Banky, and soon the relationship between Holden and Alyssa has problems when he cannot deal with her past.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260715183000 +0000" stop="20260715201000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teaching Mrs. Tingle</title>
    <desc>A hardworking and bright high-school senior, Leigh Ann (Katie Holmes) has her impending status as valedictorian jeopardized when her bitter history teacher, Mrs. Tingle (Helen Mirren), gives her a poor grade on a project. This antagonistic relationship quickly escalates until circumstances lead Leigh Ann and her friends Luke (Barry Watson) and Jo Lynn (Marisa Coughlan) to hold Tingle hostage in he</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260715201000 +0000" stop="20260715214000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Used to Go Here</title>
    <desc>A successful author finds herself deeply enmeshed in the lives of a group of college students after being asked to speak at her alma mater.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260715214000 +0000" stop="20260715231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kings of Summer</title>
    <desc>Three teenagers (Nick Robinson, Gabriel Basso, Moises Arias) carry out a plan to leave their dysfunctional parents, build a house in the woods and live off the land.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260715231500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Queen Bees</title>
    <desc>While her house undergoes repairs, fiercely independent senior Helen temporarily moves into a nearby retirement community, where she encounters lusty widows, cutthroat bridge tournaments and a hotbed of bullying "mean girls.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Bad Moms Christmas</title>
    <desc>Under-appreciated and overburdened moms Amy, Kiki and Carla rebel against the challenges and expectations of the Super Bowl for moms: Christmas. As if creating the perfect holiday for their families isn't hard enough, they'll have to do it while hosting and entertaining their own respective mothers when they come to visit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716024500 +0000" stop="20260716043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wedding Banquet</title>
    <desc>Hoping to stay in the country, a gay man proposes a green card marriage to a female friend in exchange for paying for her IVF treatment. However, things soon get complicated when his grandmother surprises them with plans for an extravagant Korean wedding banquet.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716043000 +0000" stop="20260716060500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Me</title>
    <desc>A buoy and a satellite meet online long after humanity's extinction. As they learn what life was like on Earth, they discover themselves and what it means to be alive and in love.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716060500 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Infernal Machine</title>
    <desc>Bruce Cogburn, a reclusive and controversial author of the famed book "The Infernal Machine," is drawn out of hiding when he begins to receive endless letters from an obsessive fan. What ensues is a dangerous labyrinth as Bruce searches for the person behind the cryptic messages, forcing him to confront his past and ultimately revealing the truth behind the book.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Grit</title>
    <desc>After an outlaw named Tom Chaney murders her father, feisty 14-year-old farm girl Mattie Ross hires Rooster Cogburn, a boozy, trigger-happy lawman, to help her find Chaney and avenge her father. The bickering duo are not alone in their quest, for a Texas Ranger named LaBoeuf is also tracking Chaney for reasons of his own. Together the unlikely trio ventures into hostile territory to dispense some </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716114500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monster Trucks</title>
    <desc>Looking for any way to get away from the life and town he was born into, Tripp (Lucas Till), a high school senior, builds a monster truck from bits and pieces of scrapped cars. After an accident at a nearby oil-drilling site displaces a strange and subterranean creature with a taste and a talent for speed, Tripp may have just found the key to getting out of town with a most unlikely friend.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716114500 +0000" stop="20260716131500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wild Thornberrys Movie</title>
    <desc>The Wild Thornberrys feature film finds one of America's favorite animated families going on wild adventures around the world. Now, 12-year-old Eliza is in Africa where she meets a mysterious shaman who grants her the power to talk to animals. But there's a catch -- if she reveals her gift she will lose it forever. One day Eliza discovers that poachers plan to kill an elephant herd with an electri</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716131500 +0000" stop="20260716151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Star Trek Generations</title>
    <desc>In the 23rd century, the Starship Enterprise is dispatched to the scene of a giant energy field about to engulf two ships. Capt. Kirk (William Shatner) averts calamity, but is exposed to the field and presumed dead. Years later, the Enterprise's new commander, Capt. Picard (Patrick Stewart), learns that one of the disaster's survivors, Dr. Soran (Malcolm McDowell), plans to enter the field by dest</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716151500 +0000" stop="20260716170500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Focus</title>
    <desc>Lawrence Newman (William H. Macy) is an ordinary man who doesn't want to stand out in a dangerous world. Then, unassuming Newman and his sexy, outspoken newlywed wife (Laura Dern) become caught up in a case of mistaken identity. Suddenly the unwitting focus of his neighbors' prejudice, Newman is faced with a choice - to go down as a coward or take a long shot at becoming the unlikeliest of heroes </desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716170500 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sense of an Ending</title>
    <desc>A business owner (Jim Broadbent) reunites with his first love (Charlotte Rampling) after a letter and a diary force him to confront the past.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716204500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Words</title>
    <desc>When shallow wannabe-writer Rory (Bradley Cooper) finds an old manuscript tucked away in a bag, he decides to pass the work off as his own. The book, called "The Window Tears," brings Rory great acclaim, until the real author (Jeremy Irons) shows up and threatens to destroy Rory's reputation. Cut to Clayton Hammond (Dennis Quaid), a writer whose popular novel "The Words" seems to mirror Rory's sto</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716204500 +0000" stop="20260716230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Talented Mr. Ripley</title>
    <desc>To be young and carefree amid the blue waters and idyllic landscape of sun-drenched Italy in the late 1950s; that's la dolce vita Tom Ripley (Matt Damon) craves- and Dickie Greenleaf (Jude Law) leads. When Dickie's father asks Tom to bring his errant playboy son back home to America, Dickie and his beautiful expatriate girlfriend, Marge Sherwood (Gwyneth Paltrow), never suspect the dangerous extre</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260716230500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Witness</title>
    <desc>An eight-year-old Amish boy witnesses a drug-related murder in a Philadelphia train station. The Philadelphia police captain discovers that the murderers are cops trying to squelch a corruption investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="9304" start="20260715142000 +0000" stop="20260715170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Guest Iin London</title>
    <desc>A young couple's life turns upside down when unexpected guests arrive from India. Chaos, humor, and emotion follow as family values clash with modern living in this relatable comedy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260715170000 +0000" stop="20260715200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Partner</title>
    <desc>Prem, a love guru who shares tips on dating women, helps his client, Bhaskar, woo his boss. However, he later falls for a single mother and tries to hide his profession.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260715200000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">De Dana Dan</title>
    <desc>Nitin and Anjali love each other but cannot marry because Nitin isn't rich enough to receive consent from her father.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Freddy</title>
    <desc>The lines between love and obsession blur in this romantic thriller packed with unpredictable twists and sharp turns.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260716020500 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chandni Chowk To China</title>
    <desc>A humble cook from Delhi believes he's the reincarnation of a Chinese warrior. Thrust into an epic adventure, he discovers courage, identity, and humor in this martial arts comedy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716080500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Patiala House</title>
    <desc>A victim Rishi Kapoor of British racial violence and profiling prevents his son Akshay Kumar from playing cricket for an English team. The film also stars Anushka Sharma.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260716080500 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Two Three</title>
    <desc>Laxmi, Pooja and Chandu get caught in gangster confusion and mistaken identities, creating nonstop comedy, action chaos and accidental crime entanglements.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716135000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bhoothnath</title>
    <desc>A friendly ghost befriends a young boy, teaching him courage and kindness. Their heartwarming bond helps heal a grieving family, blending humor, emotion, and a message about love beyond life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260716135000 +0000" stop="20260716163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Total Dhamaal</title>
    <desc>Six people encounter wild jungle animals and danger at every turn while racing against time to find a hidden stash of 500 million rupees.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260716163000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dhoom 3</title>
    <desc>A circus performer turns to crime to avenge his father's humiliation, facing off against a relentless cop. High-octane stunts, emotion, and revenge collide in this stylish action thriller.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9304" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mujhse Shaadi Karogi</title>
    <desc>Sameer, fast at losing his temper is re-located to Goa where he falls in love with Rani. But Sameer's new roommate Sunny, has some plans of his own.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
</tv>