<tv date="20260703232254 " generator-info-name="TV5-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV5-Source-EPG"><channel id="465032">
    <display-name lang="US">AMC HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464771">
    <display-name lang="US">AXS TV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="480608">
    <display-name lang="US">Cinemax Action</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486763">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Film4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486852">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">U and GOLD HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464745">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO East</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470372">
    <display-name lang="Canada">HBO Canada West HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464953">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO Comedy HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465201">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO Drama</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465255">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO Hits</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465104">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO Zone HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465302">
    <display-name lang="US">HBO West</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465212">
    <display-name lang="US">HDNet Movies</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464786">
    <display-name lang="US">INSP HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465284">
    <display-name lang="US">MGM+ Hits HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465261">
    <display-name lang="US">MGM+ HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464850">
    <display-name lang="US">MoreMax HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465332">
    <display-name lang="US">Paramount+ with Showtime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465402">
    <display-name lang="US">Showtime 2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464890">
    <display-name lang="US">SHO x BET HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464954">
    <display-name lang="US">Showtime Familyzone HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464877">
    <display-name lang="US">Showtime Extreme HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="494413">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Action</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="494411">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Cinema Comedy</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9124">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Drama HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9432">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Family HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="494412">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Greats</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="454796">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Cinema Hits HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9122">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">SkyPremiereHD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9531">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky ScFi/HorHD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9315">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Cinema Select</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9394">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Thriller HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464979">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Comedy HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465240">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Encore Classic</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464893">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Encore HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465242">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Encore Family SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465115">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Cinema HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465109">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Kids HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464973">
    <display-name lang="US">Starz Encore Westerns SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465397">
    <display-name lang="US">The Movie Channel Extra HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9304">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Utsav GOLD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260703213000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Back to the Future Part II</title>
    <desc>In this zany sequel, time-traveling duo Marty McFly and Dr. Emmett Brown return from saving Marty's future son from disaster, only to discover their own time transformed. In this nightmarish version of Hill Valley, Marty's father has been murdered and Biff Tannen, Marty's nemesis, has profited. After uncovering the secret to Biff's success -- a sports almanac from the future -- Marty and the Doc e</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465032" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Back to the Future</title>
    <desc>In this 1980s sci-fi classic, small-town California teen Marty McFly is thrown back into the '50s when an experiment by his eccentric scientist friend Doc Brown goes awry. Traveling through time in a modified DeLorean car, Marty encounters young versions of his parents, and must make sure that they fall in love, or he'll cease to exist. Even more dauntingly, Marty has to return to his own time and</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464771" start="20260703230000 +0000" stop="20260703233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Top Ten Revealed</title>
    <desc>We're ranking some of the epic songs of 1971; find out which songs from 1971 make our list as rock experts like John Oates, Lita Ford, Dee Snider and more count us down!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464771" start="20260703233000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Top Ten Revealed</title>
    <desc>Find out which Red Songs make our list as rock experts like Lita Ford, James Durbin, Sebastian Bach and more count us down!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464771" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Top Ten Revealed</title>
    <desc>Find out which Summer of Love songs make our list with rock experts like Dee Snider, Lita Ford, EG and more!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="480608" start="20260703232100 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Red Riding Hood</title>
    <desc>Young Valerie (Amanda Seyfried) feels torn between two men. She loves Peter, but her parents intend that she marry wealthy Henry. Valerie and Peter are going to run away together, but her sister is killed by a werewolf before they can put their plan into action. The villagers call on the help of Father Solomon (Gary Oldman), a famous monster hunter who warns that the beast takes human form by day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="486763" start="20260703221000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bad Boys for Life</title>
    <desc>Action-comedy starring Will Smith and Martin Lawrence. Just when Marcus is planning to retire, a vengeful drug lord's son shoots Mike. Can our dynamic duo beat the cartel.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="486852" start="20260703222000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bottom</title>
    <desc>Following a nasty incident with three children and a pitchfork on Hallowe'en, Eddie and Richie (Rik Mayall and Ade Edmondson) realise the cash potential of trick-or-treating.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464745" start="20260703231200 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">How to Make a Killing</title>
    <desc>Disowned by his obscenely wealthy family, Becket Redfellow will stop at nothing to reclaim his inheritance, no matter how many relatives stand in his way.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="470372" start="20260703215500 +0000" stop="20260703232500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crossword Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When Tess prepares for a crossword challenge against a supercomputer, the engineer behind it gets murdered, spurring her and Logan to seek answers before they become the next victims.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470372" start="20260703232500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Atomic Homefront</title>
    <desc>A major metropolitan area in the United States lies dangerously close to a large landfill containing radioactive waste and an escalating underground fire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464953" start="20260703225600 +0000" stop="20260703232700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Comeback</title>
    <desc>Valerie Cherish stars in a sitcom written by artificial intelligence, which presents her with bizarre challenges.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464953" start="20260703232700 +0000" stop="20260703235800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Comeback</title>
    <desc>Valerie finds herself alone amid a media meltdown after news of her AI written show is somehow leaked to the public; Val is further shocked to discover that a member of her team has not signed a NDA.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464953" start="20260703235800 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Comeback</title>
    <desc>Valerie tries to repair the damage caused by negative AI press and save Mark's reality show job by making an appearance on "Finance Dudes.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465201" start="20260703224200 +0000" stop="20260703235700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">We Are Who We Are</title>
    <desc>The friend group fractures even further over their hatred for Col. Wilson; Caitlin momentarily pauses her self-discovery journey and Danny fully commits to his; Richard's insubordination reaches a breaking point.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465201" start="20260703235700 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">We Are Who We Are</title>
    <desc>In honor of her last day in Italy, Caitlin and Fraser sneak off to catch a concert in Bologna; Fraser finally feels comfortable admitting a shocking secret about Mark and finds a new friend in Luca.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465255" start="20260703224100 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bang My Box: The Robin Byrd Story</title>
    <desc>Explore the rise of a boundary-pushing, sex-positive, cable-access pioneer who became an accidental AIDS-era lifeline and First Amendment fighter; at 70, with 600 shows behind her, she considers her place in the history she created.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465104" start="20260703232000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Strangers</title>
    <desc>Kristen (Liv Tyler) and James (Scott Speedman) are expecting a relaxing weekend at a family vacation home, but their stay turns out to be anything but peaceful. First, a mysterious and dangerous woman arrives at the door while James is out on an errand. When he returns, he accidentally kills his friend Mike (Glenn Howerton), mistaking him for an intruder. And then real danger does show up -- in th</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465302" start="20260703230700 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bang My Box: The Robin Byrd Story</title>
    <desc>Explore the rise of a boundary-pushing, sex-positive, cable-access pioneer who became an accidental AIDS-era lifeline and First Amendment fighter; at 70, with 600 shows behind her, she considers her place in the history she created.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465212" start="20260703211500 +0000" stop="20260703233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Navajo Joe</title>
    <desc>Proud warrior Navajo Joe (Burt Reynolds) is the only man left alive when outlaw Marvin Duncan (Aldo Sambrell) and his brutal gang destroy his village. Riding into a nearby town of white settlers, Joe announces his plans for vengeance, but the townspeople fear Duncan's retribution too much to stand behind him. In the course of his one-man battle against Duncan's small army for control of the town, </desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465212" start="20260703233000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Reason to Live, A Reason to Die</title>
    <desc>After surrendering Fort Holman to the Confederacy without there being a single shot fired, Col. Pembroke (James Coburn) faces public disgrace and a potential court-martial unless he's able to recapture the fort now held by the power-mad Maj. Ward (Telly Savalas). To help him on this mission, Pembroke enlists a ragtag bunch of condemned men who are promised their freedom should they survive. Despit</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464786" start="20260703230000 +0000" stop="20260703233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gunsmoke</title>
    <desc>A witness's refusal to testify means that an innocent cowboy will hang for killing a man in self-defense.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464786" start="20260703233000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gunsmoke</title>
    <desc>A belligerent young man tries to make a name for himself by challenging Matt to a street fight.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464786" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gun the Man Down</title>
    <desc>An outlaw is left by his cohorts and girlfriend to be captured after he is wounded during a heist. When he is released from prison, he tracks his old crew to a run-down town and plays a game of cat and mouse with them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465284" start="20260703215000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jennifer 8</title>
    <desc>After discovering his wife's adultery, Los Angeles detective John Berlin (Andy Garcia) relocates to recover and work alongside old friend Freddy Ross (Lance Henriksen) in the peaceful small town of Eureka, Calif. When a severed hand is found in a garbage dump, John realizes it belongs to a missing blind woman and connects it to six similar murders. Fearing the next to die will be Helena Robertson </desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465284" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Silence of the Lambs</title>
    <desc>Jodie Foster stars as Clarice Starling, a top student at the FBI's training academy. Jack Crawford (Scott Glenn) wants Clarice to interview Dr. Hannibal Lecter (Anthony Hopkins), a brilliant psychiatrist who is also a violent psychopath, serving life behind bars for various acts of murder and cannibalism. Crawford believes that Lecter may have insight into a case and that Starling, as an attractiv</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465261" start="20260703220000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Working Man</title>
    <desc>Levon Cade left behind a decorated military career in the black ops to live a simple life of working construction. However, when human traffickers kidnap his boss's daughter, his search to bring her home uncovers a world of corruption far greater than he ever could have imagined.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465261" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Protector</title>
    <desc>Nikki is a former war hero whose life gets shattered when her daughter is kidnapped by sex traffickers. Thrust into a criminal underworld while also being hunted by police and the military, she fights by any means possible to rescue her child.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464850" start="20260703215900 +0000" stop="20260703235400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Knox Goes Away</title>
    <desc>Diagnosed with a rapidly evolving form of dementia, a contract killer gets the chance to redeem himself by saving the life of his estranged son.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464850" start="20260703235400 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trap</title>
    <desc>A man and his teenage daughter realize they're at the center of a dark and sinister event while watching a concert.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465332" start="20260703220500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Quantum of Solace</title>
    <desc>Following the death of Vesper Lynd, James Bond (Daniel Craig) makes his next mission personal. The hunt for those who blackmailed his lover leads him to ruthless businessman Dominic Greene (Mathieu Amalric), a key player in the organization which coerced Vesper. Bond learns that Greene is plotting to gain total control of a vital natural resource, and he must navigate a minefield of danger and tre</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465332" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chi</title>
    <desc>The South Side of Chicago carries daily danger, and the smallest and simplest of decisions can have life or death consequences for the residents. Life continues as the kids prep for school and their parents shuffle off to work. The young adults of the area are trying to scrape a living for themselves, while the elders sit on their front porches and observe the goings on. The South Side has the pot</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465402" start="20260703221500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Daddy's Home</title>
    <desc>Brad Whitaker (Will Ferrell) is a kindhearted radio executive who wants to be the best possible stepfather to his wife's (Linda Cardellini) two children. When her freewheeling ex-husband, Dusty (Mark Wahlberg), breezes back into town, Brad's feeling of insecurity quickly develops into an inferiority complex. As Dusty demonstrates his flair for athletics, home repair and bad-boy charisma, Whitaker </desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465402" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Without a Paddle</title>
    <desc>After their friend Billy (Anthony Starr) dies, Tom (Dax Shepard), Jerry (Matthew Lillard) and Dan (Seth Green) go on a camping trip to honor his memory. The campsite, however, has special significance. Billy believed famous airplane hijacker D.B. Cooper hid money in the area, and his friends aim to find it. Unfortunately, they are not prepared for the adventure. After falling over a waterfall, the</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464890" start="20260703223000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Down to Earth</title>
    <desc>When amateur comedian Lance Barton (Chris Rock) finds himself at Heaven's door, he is convinced there has been a mistake. Miraculously he is right. Since returning to his own body is not an option, a heavenly agent places him into the corpse of a rich Manhattan mogul who has just been murdered by his wife -- until a more suitable replacement can be found. Ironically, it is as this new person that </desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464890" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boomerang</title>
    <desc>A cocky ad executive, Marcus (Eddie Murphy) has a reputation as a ladies' man. However, Marcus gets a taste of his own medicine when a merger finds him working under the beautiful Jacqueline (Robin Givens), who has a similarly cavalier attitude about romance. Marcus and Jacqueline become involved, but he is put off by her noncommittal approach to their relationship. Meanwhile, Marcus also begins t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464954" start="20260703220000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Indiana Jones and the Raiders of the Lost Ark</title>
    <desc>Dr. Indiana Jones, a renowned archeologist and expert in the occult, is hired by the U.S. Government to find the ark of the covenant, which is believed to still hold the Ten Commandments. Unfortunately, Hitler's agents are also after the ark. Indy and his ex-flame Marion escape from various close scrapes in a quest that takes them from Nepal to Cairo.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464954" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom</title>
    <desc>The second of the Lucas/Spielberg Indiana Jones epics is set a year or so before the events in Raiders of the Lost Ark. Indy needs to retrieve a precious gem and several kidnapped young boys on behalf of a remote East Indian village. This time he teams up with a night club singer and a 12-year old boy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464877" start="20260703220000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Assassin</title>
    <desc>When Cold War veteran Stan Hurley takes CIA black ops recruit Mitch Rapp under his wing, they receive an assignment to investigate a wave of random attacks on both military and civilian targets. After discovering a pattern of violence, Hurley and Rapp join forces with a lethal Turkish agent to stop a mysterious operative who wants to start a global war.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464877" start="20260704000000 +0000" stop="20260705000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shooter</title>
    <desc>A top Marine sniper, Bob Lee Swagger, leaves the military after a mission goes awry and disappears without a trace. Swagger is coaxed back into service after high-profile government officials convince him to help thwart a plot against the President of the United States. Swagger realizes he has been betrayed and becomes the target of a nationwide manhunt. Instead of hiding, he seeks revenge against</desc>
    <date>2026-07-04</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="494413" start="20260703225500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wonder Woman</title>
    <desc>Gal Gadot stars as an Amazon warrior princess who leaves her hidden island home to fight in the Great War.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="494411" start="20260703205000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beetlejuice Beetlejuice</title>
    <desc>A family tragedy woos Delia Deetz, daughter Lydia and rebellious teenage granddaughter Astrid back to the close-knit community of Winter River. Astrid accidentally opens a portal to the afterlife by summoning Beetlejuice three times. The mischievous demon ricochets between realms, wreaking havoc wherever he goes. Tim Burton's comedy sequel, starring Michael Keaton, Winona Ryder and Jenna Ortega.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="9124" start="20260703212500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">About Time</title>
    <desc>On learning he can time travel, Domhnall Gleeson tries to engineer the perfect relationship with Rachel McAdams. Romance from Richard Curtis. Strong language/sex/nudity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="9432" start="20260703223500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles</title>
    <desc>The ninja turtles emerge from the sewers below to protect New York from the villainous Shredder. Hit action fun with Megan Fox.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="494412" start="20260703220500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">National Lampoon's Vacation</title>
    <desc>Hilarious cross-country comedy starring Chevy Chase as accident-prone dad Clark Griswold whose well-planned family holiday quickly descends into chaos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="454796" start="20260703211500 +0000" stop="20260703235000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inglourious Basterds</title>
    <desc>American officer Aldo Raine leads a squad of soldiers into occupied France on a mission to kill as many Nazis as possible and spread fear through the Third Reich. They become involved in a Jewish resistance fighter's plan to blow up the premiere of a propaganda movie - due to be attended by Hitler himself. Quentin Tarantino's wartime adventure, with Brad Pitt, Melanie Laurent, Diane Kruger, Michae</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="454796" start="20260703235000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Alto Knights</title>
    <desc>Two rivals fight for control of a major crime family. Director Barry Levinson's drama based on true events, starring Robert De Niro, Cosmo Jarvis and Debra Messing.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="9122" start="20260703222500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Civil War</title>
    <desc>Action thriller set across a dystopian US, following a team of journalists as they race to the White House before a faction of rebels do.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="9531" start="20260703205000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Smile 2</title>
    <desc>Would it kill you to smile? Pop star Skye Riley faces increasingly terrifying events, leading her down a dark path into her past. Horror sequel.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="9315" start="20260703212000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Battle After Another</title>
    <desc>When their enemy resurfaces after 16 years, a group of ex-revolutionaries reunite to rescue the daughter of one of their own.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="9394" start="20260703224500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Firm</title>
    <desc>Young lawyer Tom Cruise becomes embroiled in his new firm's shady dealings. Sydney Pollack directs this gripping drama. Contains strong language and violence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464979" start="20260703215700 +0000" stop="20260703235000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">This Must Be the Place</title>
    <desc>At 50 years of age, former rock star Cheyenne (Sean Penn) still dresses the part and lives in Ireland off the royalties and dividends from smart investments. The death of his estranged father brings Cheyenne back to New York, where he discovers the old man had one obsession: to hunt down a Nazi war criminal (Heinz Lieven). Cheyenne decides to pick up the quest where his late father left off, and s</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464979" start="20260703235000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nacho Libre</title>
    <desc>Ignacio (Jack Black), or Nacho to his friends, works as a cook in the Mexican monastery where he grew up. The monastery is home to a host of orphans whom Nacho cares for deeply, but there is not much money to feed them properly. Nacho decides to raise money for the children by moonlighting as a Lucha Libre wrestler with his partner Esqueleto (Héctor Jiménez), but since the church forbids Lucha, Na</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465240" start="20260703231800 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wedding Ringer</title>
    <desc>Socially awkward Doug Harris is two weeks from marrying the gal of his dreams, but he has a problem: He doesn't have any groomsmen for the occasion. Desperate and running out of time, Doug calls upon Jimmy Callahan, owner and operator of Best Man Inc., a company that provides attendants for friendless grooms. As Doug tries to pull off the con, a bromance unexpectedly blossoms between Jimmy and him</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464893" start="20260703224500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Van Helsing</title>
    <desc>Famed monster slayer Gabriel Van Helsing (Hugh Jackman) is dispatched to Transylvania to assist the last of the Valerious bloodline in defeating Count Dracula (Richard Roxburgh). Anna Valerious (Kate Beckinsale) reveals that Dracula has formed an unholy alliance with Dr. Frankenstein's monster (Shuler Hensley) and is hell-bent on exacting a centuries-old curse on her family. Together Anna and Van </desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465242" start="20260703222000 +0000" stop="20260703235000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joey &amp; Ella</title>
    <desc>A mysterious diamond causes a baby kangaroo named Joey to grow quickly and gain the power of speech. When two bumbling thieves try to retrieve the magical gem, a teen and her new boyfriend try to get Joey to safety before it's too late.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465242" start="20260703235000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Dog Who Saved Summer</title>
    <desc>After their dog Zeus ruins a party, George takes him to an obedience school run by a no-nonsense instructor. When Zeus manages to fail every test, he seeks help from a trainer with special techniques.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465115" start="20260703224700 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Blueberry Nights</title>
    <desc>After her boyfriend of five years breaks up with her, Elizabeth (Norah Jones) consoles herself by consuming creamy confections at a sympathetic café owner's (Jude Law) eatery. She sets out on a road trip, supporting herself as a waitress along the way. Elizabeth meets a host of interesting characters on her journey, including an alcoholic policeman (David Strathairn), his unfaithful wife (Rachel W</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465109" start="20260703223200 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tarzan</title>
    <desc>Tarzan and Jane face a mercenary army dispatched by the evil CEO of Greystoke Energies.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="464973" start="20260703223600 +0000" stop="20260703232600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheyenne</title>
    <desc>Unwittingly, Cheyenne plays a part in a bank robbery.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464973" start="20260703232600 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheyenne</title>
    <desc>Indians go on the warpath when a newspaper woman decides to interview Chief Sitting Bull.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="465397" start="20260703210500 +0000" stop="20260703232500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Talented Mr. Ripley</title>
    <desc>To be young and carefree amid the blue waters and idyllic landscape of sun-drenched Italy in the late 1950s; that's la dolce vita Tom Ripley (Matt Damon) craves- and Dickie Greenleaf (Jude Law) leads. When Dickie's father asks Tom to bring his errant playboy son back home to America, Dickie and his beautiful expatriate girlfriend, Marge Sherwood (Gwyneth Paltrow), never suspect the dangerous extre</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465397" start="20260703232500 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Guns Up</title>
    <desc>After a job goes horribly wrong, a man who moonlights as a mob henchman has one night to get his family out of the city while keeping his dark secret hidden.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="9304" start="20260703200000 +0000" stop="20260704000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haseena Maan Jaayegi</title>
    <desc>Two mischievous brothers' pranks lead them into love and trouble. Their hilarious antics, mistaken identities, and romantic escapades make this a timeless family entertainer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-03</date>
  </programme>
</tv>