<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260720222859 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="FX.us">
    <display-name>US | FX East</display-name>
    <icon src="https://tlgrm.re/images/fx-us.png" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465105">
    <display-name lang="US">Fuse HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470910">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464774">
    <display-name lang="US">FYI Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465357">
    <display-name lang="US">FXX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465354">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486672">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486821">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV Quiz</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470474">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Much Music HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465080">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV - Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465113">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV2: Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260720163000 -0400" stop="20260720190000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Jason Bourne</title>
    <desc>It's been 10 years since Jason Bourne (Matt Damon) walked away from the agency that trained him to become a deadly weapon. Hoping to draw him out of the shadows, CIA director Robert Dewey assigns hacker and counterinsurgency expert Heather Lee to find him. Lee suspects that former operative Nicky Parsons is also looking for him. As she begins tracking the duo, Bourne finds himself back in action battling a sinister network that utilizes terror and technology to maintain unchecked power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260720190000 -0400" stop="20260720213000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ant-Man</title>
    <desc>Forced out of his own company by former protégé Darren Cross, Dr. Hank Pym recruits the talents of Scott Lang, a master thief just released from prison. Lang becomes Ant-Man, trained by Pym and armed with a suit that allows him to shrink in size, possess superhuman strength and control an army of ants. The miniature hero must use his new skills to prevent Cross, also known as Yellowjacket, from perfecting the same technology and using it as a weapon for evil.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260720213000 -0400" stop="20260721000000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ant-Man and The Wasp</title>
    <desc>Scott Lang is grappling with the consequences of his choices as both a superhero and a father. Approached by Hope van Dyne and Dr. Hank Pym, Lang must once again don the Ant-Man suit and fight alongside the Wasp. The urgent mission soon leads to secret revelations from the past as the dynamic duo find themselves in an epic battle against a powerful new enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721000000 -0400" stop="20260721023000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ant-Man and the Wasp: Quantumania</title>
    <desc>Ant-Man and the Wasp find themselves exploring the Quantum Realm, interacting with strange new creatures and embarking on an adventure that pushes them beyond the limits of what they thought was possible.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721023000 -0400" stop="20260721030000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim worries Cheryl will learn the truth about her engagement ring after she invites his old girlfriend (Crystal Bernard) to dinner.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721030000 -0400" stop="20260721033000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721033000 -0400" stop="20260721040000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>What's Your Injury Case Worth?</title>
    <desc>Legal professionals are standing by 24/7. Call now for a free case evaluation and learn what your injury case may be worth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721040000 -0400" stop="20260721043000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721043000 -0400" stop="20260721050000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721050000 -0400" stop="20260721053000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721053000 -0400" stop="20260721060000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Overwhelmed with IRS Debt? Keys to Resolving Tax Debt</title>
    <desc>See how one company is changing people's lives by helping them put their tax problems to rest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721060000 -0400" stop="20260721063000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Freedom to Leave the House! Inogen Portable Oxygen</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721063000 -0400" stop="20260721070000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721070000 -0400" stop="20260721100000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Logan</title>
    <desc>In the near future, a weary Logan (Hugh Jackman) cares for an ailing Professor X (Patrick Stewart) at a remote outpost on the Mexican border. His plan to hide from the outside world gets upended when he meets a young mutant (Dafne Keen) who is very much like him. Logan must now protect the girl and battle the dark forces that want to capture her.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721100000 -0400" stop="20260721123000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>21 Jump Street</title>
    <desc>When cops Schmidt and Jenko join the secret Jump Street unit, they use their youthful appearances to go undercover as high-school students. They trade in their guns and badges for backpacks, and set out to shut down a dangerous drug ring. But, as time goes on, Schmidt and Jenko discover that high school is nothing like it was just a few years earlier -- and, what's more, they must again confront the teenage terror and anxiety they thought they had left behind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721123000 -0400" stop="20260721153000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Aliens</title>
    <desc>After floating in space for 57 years, Lt. Ripley's shuttle is found by a deep space salvage team. Upon arriving at LV-426, the marines find only one survivor, a nine-year-old girl named Newt. But even these battle-hardened marines with all the latest weaponry are no match for the hundreds of aliens that have invaded the colony.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721153000 -0400" stop="20260721180000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Guardians of the Galaxy</title>
    <desc>Brash space adventurer Peter Quill finds himself the quarry of relentless bounty hunters after he steals an orb coveted by Ronan, a powerful villain. To evade Ronan, Quill is forced into an uneasy truce with four disparate misfits: gun-toting Rocket Raccoon, treelike-humanoid Groot, enigmatic Gamora, and vengeance-driven Drax the Destroyer. But when he discovers the orb's true power and the cosmic threat it poses, Quill must rally his ragtag group to save the universe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260721180000 -0400" stop="20260721210000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2</title>
    <desc>Peter Quill and his fellow Guardians are hired by a powerful alien race, the Sovereign, to protect their precious batteries from invaders. When it is discovered that Rocket has stolen the items they were sent to guard, the Sovereign dispatch their armada to search for vengeance. As the Guardians try to escape, the mystery of Peter's parentage is revealed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Funniest Pets and People is a solid half-hour of pure entertainment with a proven format featuring hysterical, fast-paced video clips submitted by viewers who share the funniest moments of their favorite Pets and People.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260720223000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Boy runs over a girl; birthday celebration; playing softball; fight in the mud; set falling; Doberman gives lady a ride on her chair.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Addiction: Michael Jackson</title>
    <desc>Family, friends and fellow musicians describe the life of the child prodigy turned king of pop Michael Jackson over his four-decade career, from his rise to fame to his later battle with tabloids.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721003000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Michael Jackson: Chase the Truth</title>
    <desc>Close friends, former staff and researchers paint an intimate portrait of pop star Michael Jackson's complicated world and put allegations of sexual abuse under the microscope.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Rayne wants to find out where Abel is spending his time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721023000 +0000" stop="20260721030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Amy wants to know why Jonathan is behaving childishly.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721030000 +0000" stop="20260721033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Lexi wants to know what's behind her beau's behavior.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721033000 +0000" stop="20260721040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Pierre wants to investigate his girlfriend after finding a bite mark on her rear-end.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721040000 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Manson Murders</title>
    <desc>A dive into the murders committed by the Manson Family in July and August 1969, including the brutal killing of Sharon Tate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Eagles: The Long Road</title>
    <desc>Paying tribute to the life and career of Glenn Frey, one of the main band members. Revisiting the achievements of one of the best-selling and most loved American rock bands of all time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721063000 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stevie Nicks: Wild at Heart</title>
    <desc>For decades, Stevie Nicks has fronted one of the most successful bands in history, resurrecting them from the ashes; even with the trials and tribulations of being a member of Fleetwood Mac, Stevie has remained a role model.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Women That Made Elvis</title>
    <desc>Taking a look at the women who influenced Elvis Presley's life, from his mother, Gladys, to his true love, Priscilla.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Jill wants to know why Rose constantly wants alone time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721093000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Leroy thinks his girlfriend is cheating while he's out of town for bodybuilding competitions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Nate thinks his girlfriend may be using him for his money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721103000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Christian wants to check up on Tata.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>A water boarder hits a buoy; cat plays with a tent.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721113000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Girl falling on the steps, ball dancing, baby plays with food, wheelbarrow race, cat being spun around on kitchen floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Funniest Pets and People is a solid half-hour of pure entertainment with a proven format featuring hysterical, fast-paced video clips submitted by viewers who share the funniest moments of their favorite Pets and People.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721123000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Boy runs over a girl; birthday celebration; playing softball; fight in the mud; set falling; Doberman gives lady a ride on her chair.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elvis Presley: The Final Hours</title>
    <desc>An examination of the last day of Elvis Presley's life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721143000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elvis &amp; the Memphis Mafia</title>
    <desc>Exploring Elvis' life through the eyes of The Memphis Mafia — a select group of friends he entrusted with his life — from the highs to the lows.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elvis: Death of the King</title>
    <desc>Elvis Presley's charisma and musical talent made him the king of rock, but his rock star lifestyle led to a downfall that was as swift as his rise.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Larry wants to know why his wife is acting peculiar.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721173000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Bridget risks breaking her heart to check up on Dwight.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Christian wants to discover why Celeste is so secretive.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721183000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Amber wants to know the reason behind Robert's constant showering and frequent haircuts.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Malibooty</title>
    <desc>Three buddies (Brian Hooks, Sticky Fingaz, J.T. Jackson) leave their Arizona town and head to California for a wild beach party.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Horses howl with a conductor; Lulu runs and jumps over people near fountain; three peacocks play ring around the Rosie.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721213000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>People in mud; fighting with pots and pans; dancers fall; acrobats fall.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>A cat's head is stuck; a hamster squeezes under a door; a chipmunk stuffs his face with hickory nuts.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721223000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Ball dancers fall; the rocket comes back; dancing baby; cat spun around on the floor; bicycle in the water.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Eagles: The Long Road</title>
    <desc>Paying tribute to the life and career of Glenn Frey, one of the main band members. Revisiting the achievements of one of the best-selling and most loved American rock bands of all time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a young woman dies a slow and painful death from an untreated infection, Cosgrove and Shaw suspect she was under the influence of a powerful cult; Price and Maroun put pressure on its members to find the cult's true mastermind.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a teen from a group home goes missing, the squad has only minutes to determine if he ran away or was abducted; Velasco suspects the system at large is to blame for letting children slip through the cracks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260721010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young boy seeks help when his sister doesn't come home from work; Benson and Carisi suspect a woman's assault was prearranged by a third party.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721010000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Sports Story: Aaron Hernandez</title>
    <desc>With Aaron behind bars, the women in his life are forced to face their new reality and make a difficult decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Sports Story: Aaron Hernandez</title>
    <desc>New lawyers and a second trial offer unexpected hope; Aaron's tortured mind struggles to withstand the weight of his deepest secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721030000 +0000" stop="20260721040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Sports Story: Aaron Hernandez</title>
    <desc>Young Aaron grows up with high aspirations and immense pressure for his football career; when tragedy strikes, his fate falls into new hands.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721040500 +0000" stop="20260721050500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Sports Story: Aaron Hernandez</title>
    <desc>Aaron faces college level competition on the field and distractions off of it; he learns that the rules work differently when you're a team asset.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721050500 +0000" stop="20260721060500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Sports Story: Aaron Hernandez</title>
    <desc>With Aaron behind bars, the women in his life are forced to face their new reality and make a difficult decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721060500 +0000" stop="20260721070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Sports Story: Aaron Hernandez</title>
    <desc>New lawyers and a second trial offer unexpected hope; Aaron's tortured mind struggles to withstand the weight of his deepest secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721070500 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate a hot case under cold conditions when a figure skating coach is found dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a murder at the shipping container port, Charlie and Rex partner with a Border Security officer to track down the mastermind behind a smuggling ring.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex pull apart the secrets of a local band when their lead singer is found dead on the beach.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>The clock is ticking as Charlie and Rex attempt to find a murderer before the victim can succumb to the poison slowly killing them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex are thrust into action when a popular social media star meets an untimely demise while livestreaming her wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Charlie and Rex head into the woods to track a missing photographer, a mysterious organization throws the investigation off its trail.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex pull apart the secrets of a local band when their lead singer is found dead on the beach.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721140000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>The clock is ticking as Charlie and Rex attempt to find a murderer before the victim can succumb to the poison slowly killing them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex are thrust into action when a popular social media star meets an untimely demise while livestreaming her wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Charlie and Rex head into the woods to track a missing photographer, a mysterious organization throws the investigation off its trail.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex pull apart the secrets of a local band when their lead singer is found dead on the beach.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>The clock is ticking as Charlie and Rex attempt to find a murderer before the victim can succumb to the poison slowly killing them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a young woman dies a slow and painful death from an untreated infection, Cosgrove and Shaw suspect she was under the influence of a powerful cult; Price and Maroun put pressure on its members to find the cult's true mastermind.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young boy seeks help when his sister doesn't come home from work; Benson and Carisi suspect a woman's assault was prearranged by a third party.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a young woman dies a slow and painful death from an untreated infection, Cosgrove and Shaw suspect she was under the influence of a powerful cult; Price and Maroun put pressure on its members to find the cult's true mastermind.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Cosgrove and Shaw investigate the murder of a physician whose politician wife suspects she was the intended target; Price and Maroun's case hangs in the balance when the defense calls one of the doctor's young patients to testify as a witness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A young boy seeks help when his sister doesn't come home from work; Benson and Carisi suspect a woman's assault was prearranged by a third party.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260722000000 +0000" stop="20260723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a high school principal busts a student for sexting, the SVU uncovers a sinister case of distribution concerning hundreds of underage students; Silva pleads for leniency for a suspect she believes is innocent.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Darrell defends his turf when the buyers descend upon Costa Mesa, Calif.; Ivy Calvin comes across a unique tool; Jarrod and Brandi seek store stock.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260720223000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders visit Laguna Niguel, Calif.; Jarrod and Brandi discover some toys; Ivy Calvin tries to climb out of a hole; Barry tries his luck on a safe.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260720233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Barry is visited by wrestling legend "Rowdy" Roddy Piper; Rene and Casey score a statue that could be worth thousands of dollars; Darrell uncovers cat-related items.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260720233000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers visit El Monte, Calif.; the Harris Brothers go into stealth mode; Jarrod and Brandi feel charitable; Darrell hopes a big pole will vault him to the top.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260721003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Rachael shows a new take on traditional pesto sauce with a base of herbs and charred onions, that pairs with a Mediterranean chicken salad.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721003000 +0000" stop="20260721010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Rachael shows how to make a white, quick cooking Ragù sauce that she serves over ribbony pappardelle pasta, cooked al dente style.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721010000 +0000" stop="20260721013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Rachael prepares deviled eggs with ham and cheese alongside beef and pork burgers with beets. John complements the meal with a Vodka Beet Fizz, a martini-style cocktail featuring muddled rosemary and a splash of club soda.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721013000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Rachael shows how to make Saganaki, a Greek favorite, with large shrimp, diced tomatoes, Kalamata olives and feta cheese sautéed in a large saucepan and served over toasted orzo topped with pistachios and pine nuts. John uses the feta brine from the Saganaki to craft a Dirty Greek Martini, a gin-based cocktail with dry vermouth, garnished with a feta-stuffed pepperoncini.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Instant Italian With Anna Gass</title>
    <desc>Anna proves that no two meatballs are alike as she reimagines her mother's beloved recipe into three unique dishes. A blend of beef, veal and pork forms the base for cozy meatballs in a blanket, delicate polpettini and crispy smashed meatball tacos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721023000 +0000" stop="20260721030100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Instant Italian With Anna Gass</title>
    <desc>Anna makes vegetables the star with two family-friendly dishes. She begins by roasting a whole cauliflower and serving it with a bright Italian salsa verde. She then turns broccoli into a creamy pesto for a pasta dish that's bold, hearty, and irresistible.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721030100 +0000" stop="20260721033100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Arroz con pollo or chicken and rice is a traditional Latin American dish loved by millions worldwide; Rachael shows how to make it quickly and easily so that it becomes a household staple.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721033100 +0000" stop="20260721040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>To celebrate her wedding anniversary, Rachael prepares her well-known beet risotto that's made with roasted beets, red wine, onions and ricotta salata; she also uses the rice leftovers to make flavorful arancini balls with peas and breadcrumbs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721040000 +0000" stop="20260721043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Rachael shows a new take on traditional pesto sauce with a base of herbs and charred onions, that pairs with a Mediterranean chicken salad.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721043000 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Rachael shows how to make a white, quick cooking Ragù sauce that she serves over ribbony pappardelle pasta, cooked al dente style.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Rachael prepares deviled eggs with ham and cheese alongside beef and pork burgers with beets. John complements the meal with a Vodka Beet Fizz, a martini-style cocktail featuring muddled rosemary and a splash of club soda.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721053000 +0000" stop="20260721060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Rachael shows how to make Saganaki, a Greek favorite, with large shrimp, diced tomatoes, Kalamata olives and feta cheese sautéed in a large saucepan and served over toasted orzo topped with pistachios and pine nuts. John uses the feta brine from the Saganaki to craft a Dirty Greek Martini, a gin-based cocktail with dry vermouth, garnished with a feta-stuffed pepperoncini.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721060000 +0000" stop="20260721063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Instant Italian With Anna Gass</title>
    <desc>Anna proves that no two meatballs are alike as she reimagines her mother's beloved recipe into three unique dishes. A blend of beef, veal and pork forms the base for cozy meatballs in a blanket, delicate polpettini and crispy smashed meatball tacos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721063000 +0000" stop="20260721070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Instant Italian With Anna Gass</title>
    <desc>Anna makes vegetables the star with two family-friendly dishes. She begins by roasting a whole cauliflower and serving it with a bright Italian salsa verde. She then turns broccoli into a creamy pesto for a pasta dish that's bold, hearty, and irresistible.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721070100 +0000" stop="20260721073100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>Arroz con pollo or chicken and rice is a traditional Latin American dish loved by millions worldwide; Rachael shows how to make it quickly and easily so that it becomes a household staple.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721073100 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rachael Ray's Meals in Minutes</title>
    <desc>To celebrate her wedding anniversary, Rachael prepares her well-known beet risotto that's made with roasted beets, red wine, onions and ricotta salata; she also uses the rice leftovers to make flavorful arancini balls with peas and breadcrumbs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers return to Huntington Beach, Calif.; Barry introduces kitsch king Charles Phoenix to the joys of an auction; Darrell loses his home-field advantage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721083000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders roll into La Habra, Calif.; Darrell squares off against a former professional fighter; Jarrod and Brandi meet a nerd; Barry relaxes with a famous golfing friend.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721093000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Protect Your Family From Identity Theft</title>
    <desc>Every 5 seconds there's a victim of identity theft; LifeLock helps alert you, restore your identity, and reimburse lost funds—leading the way in protecting families every day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721103000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joni Table Talk</title>
    <desc>Joni and guests tackle a wide range of relevant issues, controversial subjects and hard-hitting news topics with candor and wit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721113000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Marty's retreat leads to a surprise in his own backyard; Morgan builds to beat the dangers of the deep freeze; Tom hits the jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Tom defends his home against a wolf pack; Eustace attempts to turn trash into treasure; Jason goes on a mission to feed his family.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721140000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>A slip of an ax blade slices Morgan too deep; Marty targets a wolf pack on a killing spree; Tom digs out.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Morgan gets sidelined as he recovers and gets back on his feet; Marty fights to stay in the game; Eustace makes a critical trade to protect his future.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Marty doubles down on a new strategy to keep from losing more ground; Morgan and Margaret defend what's theirs; Jason's hunt for land becomes an ordeal.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>As winter approaches, Morgan battles a bear-infested island for a critical head start on the season; Montana's deadly wildfires catch Tom; Eustace wrestles with the aftermath of Preston's death; the Hawk clan prepares for an arrival.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>The bears keep Morgan on the run as he tries to secure his catch; Eustace struggles to get back to work without Preston; Jason and Mary prepare for their due date; Tom scales treacherous terrain; Jake readies his team to face down the lions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>In a risky bid to get out of the red, Marty fights to reclaim his long-abandoned turf; Morgan races to build a shelter in the snow and ice of subzero Alaska; Eustace gets a boost in horsepower; Jason and Mary brace for a home birth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Morgan gets a crash course in extreme winter flying; Marty battles a predator invasion; Tom faces a new wolf threat; Jake and his hounds hunt a rogue lion; Jason steps in to bring a new life into the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Tom takes the fight to the wolves; a lion chase claims a casualty; Morgan builds bigger; Eustace goes to battle to defend his land.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Marty brings in a record haul; Margaret's extreme flight training leaves her out in the cold; Tom puts his master craftsmen skills to work; Jake chases his next meal.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Tom returns to the field on a rescue mission; the deep freeze leaves Morgan and Margaret scrambling for water; Eustace takes on a risky payday in a bid to buy his neighbor's land; Jason's improvised engineering is a game-changer in the forge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260722000000 +0000" stop="20260723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Eustace battles a beast to bring home a bonus payday; lion chase dangles Jake's team on cliff edge; Marty gambles on the ice to make bank; Mike fights to survive the dangers of bear-infested Kodiak.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When Louise and Tina go to a Boyz 4 Now concert, Louise develops a crush on one of the singers; Gene enters a table-setting competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260720223000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Bob chaperones the kids' field trip; Louise gets lost in a closed rainforest exhibit at the museum.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260720233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When Brian thinks he has lost his chance at love, he goes in search of an old flame, only to discover he is the father of an unruly son.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260720233000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After terrorizing the neighbors with his new pet parrot, Peter accidentally kills his beloved bird; Chris goes with Brian to the vet and falls for an intern.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260721003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Brian tries to take it slow when he meets the girl of his dreams, but when Cleveland sweeps her off her feet, Brian vows to do whatever it takes to win her back.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721003000 +0000" stop="20260721010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When Peter searches every record store in Quahog for his favorite song, he runs into a familiar face and wants everyone to know he is friends with Jesus.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721010000 +0000" stop="20260721013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Brian and Stewie try to bring Mort back after he accidentally steps into a time machine, but things go from bad to worse when the three discover they are in Poland on the day of the Nazi invasion.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721013000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When Peter wins a year of unlimited gas, the Griffins go on a road trip to the Grand Canyon, but one of their own gets left behind.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After watching "Jackass," Peter and the guys film their own pranks; after Brian gets hurt, the family worries he is getting too old; Peter brings another dog home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721023000 +0000" stop="20260721030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter's boss, Angela (Carrie Fisher), sends him back to the third grade so he can meet the requirements for a promotion; Brian, Stewie and Frank Sinatra Jr. open a club in Quahog.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721030000 +0000" stop="20260721033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Bonnie gives birth to a baby girl named Susie; Joe borrows money from a bookie to pay for Bonnie's medical bills.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721033000 +0000" stop="20260721040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter takes part in medical experiments to make some extra money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721040000 +0000" stop="20260721043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Professor Farnsworth rescues the ship from the junkyard and joins a gang of street-racing punks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721043000 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>After being marooned on a distant planet, Fry is befriended by a young monster.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Fry and Leela try to get some privacy, but their romantic vacation goes very wrong.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721053000 +0000" stop="20260721060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Bender becomes a famous firefighter, but the crew suspects him of arson.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721060000 +0000" stop="20260721063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Bobby raises a protest over a soda machine at school to impress a girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721063000 +0000" stop="20260721070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Bobby is asked to be a cheerleader for the school's annual powder-puff football game; Peggy volunteers with the PTA.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721070000 +0000" stop="20260721073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>When Hank takes Bobby, Joseph and Connie to a water park, a group of surfer bullies approaches them; Bill becomes known throughout Arlen as the "Heat-Waver.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721073000 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Cotton volunteers to baby-sit Bobby so Hank and Peggy can go to an upscale restaurant, but he lands in a deathly situation when he visits the restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721083000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721093000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Overwhelmed with IRS Debt? Keys to Resolving Tax Debt</title>
    <desc>See how one company is changing people's lives by helping them put their tax problems to rest.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721103000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Morbius</title>
    <desc>Dangerously ill with a rare blood disorder and determined to save others from the same fate, Dr. Morbius attempts a desperate gamble. While at first it seems to be a radical success, a darkness inside of him is soon unleashed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721133000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spider-Man</title>
    <desc>"Spider-Man" centers on student Peter Parker (Tobey Maguire) who, after being bitten by a genetically-altered spider, gains superhuman strength and the spider-like ability to cling to any surface. He vows to use his abilities to fight crime, coming to understand the words of his beloved Uncle Ben: "With great power comes great responsibility.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spider-Man 2</title>
    <desc>When a failed nuclear fusion experiment results in an explosion that kills his wife, Dr. Otto Octavius is transformed into Dr. Octopus, a cyborg with deadly metal tentacles. Doc Ock blames Spider-Man for the accident and seeks revenge. Meanwhile, Spidey's alter ego, Peter Parker, faces fading powers and self-doubt. Complicating matters are his best friend's hatred for Spider-Man and his true love'</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>An exchange program sends Bart to France and an Albanian to Springfield.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721193000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer thwarts Bart and Lisa's efforts to bring the notorious babysitter bandit to justice.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Gene goes to baseball camp; Tina gets hooked on caffeine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721203000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Bob, Linda and the kids brave river rapids, squirrels and separation while on a camping adventure.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>The kids' Halloween adventure goes awry when Louise's friend Millie takes them hostage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721213000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Linda's attempt to spice up date night by signing up for flying lessons backfires when Bob refuses to go with her, and she ends up the target of a charming pilot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When Bob gets a job cooking at a frat house, he and the brothers find themselves in the middle of a prank war; the kids hatch a plan to invade the frat house.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721223000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Bob discovers his carefully prepared turkey was put in the toilet in an act of Thanksgiving sabotage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260721233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter cashes in an old raffle ticket and wins a golf outing with O.J. Simpson.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260721233000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Lois gets a job at Fox News but is fired when her expose on a liberal filmmaker implicates a conservative radio host.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260722000000 +0000" stop="20260723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>The Griffin family heads to the annual "Star Trek" convention, but Stewie gets angry when he can't ask his favorite cast members a question, so he builds a transporter and beams the cast to his bedroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>An ex-NYPD officer goes missing the day after she reveals to Danny her plans to make amends to the woman she and her partner wrongfully convicted years ago; Frank faces a dilemma when one of his peers refuses to retire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A vigilante posts a video online of a man, previously locked up for statutory rape, being beaten and burned alive; Lindsay encounters some personal and professional problems.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260721010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Lindsay's mother, Bunny, becomes a murder suspect when her boyfriend is shot; high school students overdose on drugs; Lindsay finds herself up against the review board.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721010000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A young bystander is shot during a difficult operation; Chief Lugo reviews the shootout and Halstead becomes a key player in the outcome.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A patrol officer becomes a suspect when a van explodes during a Chicago street festival; Burgess, who helped train the officer, is desperate to prove his innocence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721030000 +0000" stop="20260721040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The investigation into a murder of an illegal immigrant is hampered by the perception of police among the city's immigrant population.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721040000 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The investigation into a drug-related homicide is hampered by the neighborhood's no-snitch culture; Upton is asked about Ruzek's rough altercation with a suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A meth lab bust uncovers a scam in which children adopted from foreign countries are abandoned, then sold online; Atwater struggles with decisions about moving his siblings to a safer environment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721060000 +0000" stop="20260721070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>A family is killed, and the team searches for a drug dealer with a likely connection; Voight asks Vice Sgt. Sean McGrady for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721070000 +0000" stop="20260721073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Protect Your Family From Identity Theft</title>
    <desc>Every 5 seconds there's a victim of identity theft; LifeLock helps alert you, restore your identity, and reimburse lost funds—leading the way in protecting families every day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721073000 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721083000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joint Relief Revolution</title>
    <desc>Join Connie Craig-Carroll and health visionary Ken Meares as they uncover OmegaXL, the groundbreaking natural supplement transforming lives by tackling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721093000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nursing Home Nightmares 2026</title>
    <desc>This is a must-see program if you have a loved one in a nursing home; go behind the scenes and find out what really goes on when you're not there, and all that's wrong with today's nursing homes; you will learn exactly what you can do if you.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>A ring of thieves pulls off the heist of an armored car, killing two security guards and leaving the money behind; Danny must seek his ex-wife's help in the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>The abduction of a woman and the murder of her husband on their honeymoon becomes the case of the Five-0 team; Dr. Max Bergman (Masi Oka) recognizes similarities to a string of unsolved homicides.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>The man who murdered McGarrett's father resurfaces; Chin Ho's life is put in danger during a hostage situation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>McGarrett discovers new clues in his mother's murder when his sister is kidnapped.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721140000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>After a high-speed chase, the team makes a gruesome discovery; Chin Ho and his former fiancée awkwardly reunite.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Herrmann tries to rescue a toddler from a structure fire; Mills discovers unexpected news; Brett and Cruz's relationship reaches a critical juncture; Otis is surprised by some feelings that develop.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Members of Firehouse 51 transport victims of a gas leak to nearby Chicago Med; an armed patient claiming to be carrying a deadly airborne disease forces Chicago Med into lockdown.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Mills works to save the life of a driver injured in a car wreck; Casey harbors doubts about Jack Nesbitt; Hermann, Otis, Cruz and Chaplain Orlovsky ready their team for the peewee hockey championship.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>An apartment fire with connections to a rape and attempted murder leads to a joint investigation with the CPD and Sgt. Benson of the NYPD's Special Victims Unit; Dawson risks her life during a call.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Sgt. Voight encourages Lt. Casey to go undercover in order to obtain proof of Jack Nesbitt's shady dealings; tensions grow between Otis and Severide; Herrmann helps another member of the firehouse.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Lt. Casey ends up in danger as he continues to investigate Jack Nesbitt; Boden tries to create unity in the house; Cruz and Boden put their lives on the line to save their own when a warehouse blaze gets out of control; Dawson receives news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>During an undercover operation, Lt. Casey lands in very dangerous territory; Dawson's suspicions are confirmed; a new candidate (Steven R. McQueen) makes an unusual first impression; a protest hinders firefighters who are trying to battle a blaze.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Members of the firehouse are frustrated with their inability to help Chief Boden, whose job is on the line pending an internal investigation in the aftermath of a complicated call to a fire; Lt. Severide struggles to accept his smaller role and adjusts to the presence of Capt. Patterson, his new commanding officer; Dawson shakes things up on the work front and Casey attempts to find a crucial piec</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>When new evidence appears in the internal affairs investigation that will clear Chief Boden, a twist puts him right back in the thick of it; Brett and Chili try to save a stabbing victim from bleeding to death.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260722000000 +0000" stop="20260723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Members of the firehouse band together to help one of their own; Herrmann looks for a way to reopen Molly's; Severide struggles to deal with one of his toughest days as he looks into the arson investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260720214500 +0000" stop="20260720223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Peston</title>
    <desc>As the political temperature rises, join Robert Peston for a late-night political magazine show featuring big interviews with the country's leading politicians and topical guests.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260720223000 +0000" stop="20260720233500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Death</title>
    <desc>Crime drama series about two church-going couples in Texas. As their affair continues, Candy fears that she and Allan are at risk of breaking their first rule about it.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260720233500 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Debrief with Dan and ROG</title>
    <desc>Claire Thomas is joined by Dan Biggar and Ronan O'Gara to analyse the best of the action from round three of the Nations Championship.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721003000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shop on TV</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nobody's Fool</title>
    <desc>A game where it's not just about how smart you are, but how smart others think you are. Players must eliminate the worst performing player or they will lose half the prize pot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721030000 +0000" stop="20260721040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721040500 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dickinson's Real Deal</title>
    <desc>Newport plays host to the dealers' den. Karen Dalmeny lights up the den when she buys some arts and craft candle sticks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Morning Britain</title>
    <desc>News, current affairs and lively debate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">This Morning</title>
    <desc>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real-life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721123000 +0000" stop="20260721125500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Lunchtime News</title>
    <desc>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721125500 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dickinson's Real Deal</title>
    <desc>The Duke and his dealers set up in Blackburn - will local dealer Matt Taylor score with a football jersey, and can Alys Dobbie walk away with a pair of vintage boots.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721140000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern for the game show with only one question as Monz gets to open the red boxes and tries to beat the Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which three players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as Alex originally from Orpington, Izzy from London, Hothan from Scunthorpe and Iain from East Yorkshire hope that they can beat a Chaser together.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721173000 +0000" stop="20260721183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Evening News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721183000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inside The Langham: Britain's First Grand Hotel</title>
    <desc>Michel Roux hosts his year's biggest dinner, chef Oliver tackles a culinary crisis, and twin engineers Alan and Trevor light up the hotel.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Vanessa and Mack dig for other cases against Doctor Todd. With Robert still injured, Aaron offers Serena a job. Kev has a plan.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721193000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Lisa advises Kit not to put his career at risk for Sarah, Gary tries to reassure Maria, Todd covers up Christina's relapse, and Brody and Ryan's words give Dylan pause for thought.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Dark</title>
    <desc>After a third murder attempt fails, a new suspect emerges for DI Kennedy, and the return of a missing son sends shockwaves through his family.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News at Ten</title>
    <desc>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721213000 +0000" stop="20260721214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721214500 +0000" stop="20260721224500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase Around the World</title>
    <desc>The Chase Around The World sees Bradley and The Chasers escape the studio and challenge contestants in a bid to win £100,000. First up, it's the eternal city: Rome.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260721224500 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sorry, I Didn't Know</title>
    <desc>Axel Blake, Josh Jones, Fatiha El-Ghorri and Slim join host Jimmy Akingbola and team leaders Chizzy Akudolu and Eddie Kadi to take viewers on a tour of Black British history.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260720235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260720235500 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Here Come the Girls and Neil: Warwick Davis hosts the quiz as a team of five from Nottingham answer Top 10 list questions and attempt to top the Tenable Tower to win 125,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721005000 +0000" stop="20260721013500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the rapid and ruthless quiz as contestants Gareth and Chris, Sally and Les, and Annika and Robert take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721013500 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern as Richard steps up to play his game against the Banker and tries to take home a huge cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Going for glory this time are South London brothers Kevin and Ian, Bailey and his auntie Jo from Kettering, and siblings Kevin and Karen from Cumbria and Barnsley.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Warwick Davis hosts the quiz show as a team of five siblings answer Top 10 list questions as they attempt to win a big cash prize, but can they take home the money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721140000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Clarkson returns to the host's chair as six contestants vie for a place in the famous hot seat and try to walk away with one million pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the rapid-fire quiz as contestants Andy and Lorraine, Maisie and Andrew, and Carl and Ashley take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Alex joins Stephen Mulhern and gets his chance to open the iconic red boxes - he may be swayed by one of the Banker's offers, or resist for a shot at 100,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Seeking success this time are pals Jack and Isaac from Colwyn Bay, Lisanne and mum Carole from Lancashire, and mates Bryony and Alison from Peterborough and Chester.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Looking to Lingo all the way this time are civil partners David and Matthew from Cardiff, mates Claire and Kayleigh from Glasgow, and twins Saifo and Kakul from Hounslow.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Hoping to win big money this time are Edinburgh couple Douglas and Louise, Karen with her son James from Eastleigh and Sutton Coldfield, and pals Katie and Sophie from Aylesbury.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 1% Club Rollover</title>
    <desc>Lee Mack hosts a spin-off of the quiz where it doesn't matter if you're not usually good at quizzes as 100 contestants try to win a prize pot of anything up to 500,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260721235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260721235500 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Warwick Davis hosts the quiz show as a team of five siblings answer Top 10 list questions as they attempt to win a big cash prize, but can they take home the money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Watching an elephant looking for a friend and many more pranks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260720223000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>The masters of pranking are at it again, with gags including a breastfeeding nun, and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Marvel</title>
    <desc>Marvel ventures into new terrain with a little-known space fantasy title.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260721003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Jerry is challenged when Elaine's boyfriend insists it is impossible to rent a villa in the Tuscany region of Italy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721003000 +0000" stop="20260721010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>An uncontrollable wink creates problems for George and Kramer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721010000 +0000" stop="20260721013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Marge's rage against the new toll road system somehow leads to the discovery of a frozen mailman and his 40-year-old mail.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721013000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>After a pizza guy wakes up in the year 3000, he is befriended by a robot and one-eyed alien. Voices of Billy West, Katey Sagal and John DiMaggio. Guest voices: Leonard Nimoy and Dick Clark.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Universal Basic Guys</title>
    <desc>Mark goes medieval in an effort to bond with Darren; Tammy and Andrea test-drive an autonomous car.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721023000 +0000" stop="20260721030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Krapopolis</title>
    <desc>Aphrodite's Fertility Fest is here, and baby fever is at an all-time high; Ty tries to relax at a bathhouse, but it's proving difficult to let loose.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721030000 +0000" stop="20260721040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fear Factor USA</title>
    <desc>Teams of twins test their fear of bees, drop from a helicopter and escape from a submerged car. Host Joe Rogan.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721040000 +0000" stop="20260721043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Marge's rage against the new toll road system somehow leads to the discovery of a frozen mailman and his 40-year-old mail.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721043000 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>After a pizza guy wakes up in the year 3000, he is befriended by a robot and one-eyed alien. Voices of Billy West, Katey Sagal and John DiMaggio. Guest voices: Leonard Nimoy and Dick Clark.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Marvel</title>
    <desc>Marvel ventures into new terrain with a little-known space fantasy title.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721060000 +0000" stop="20260721063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Universal Basic Guys</title>
    <desc>Mark goes medieval in an effort to bond with Darren; Tammy and Andrea test-drive an autonomous car.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721063000 +0000" stop="20260721070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Krapopolis</title>
    <desc>Aphrodite's Fertility Fest is here, and baby fever is at an all-time high; Ty tries to relax at a bathhouse, but it's proving difficult to let loose.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721070000 +0000" stop="20260721073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>Videos making the countdown include some nervous bungee jumpers, fearless senior citizens and the least coordinated pole dancers on the planet.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721073000 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>Poorly placed chorus singers; killer animal impressions; the clumsiest dancers in show business.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Sneezing cats; calamitous canines; dumpster-diving bears; rascally raccoons; counting down the top ten critter crack-ups of the week.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721083000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Sneezing cats; calamitous canines; dumpster-diving bears; rascally raccoons.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fear Factor USA</title>
    <desc>Teams of twins test their fear of bees, drop from a helicopter and escape from a submerged car. Host Joe Rogan.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Watch a stuffed dog react to a real one and many more pranks from the masters of pranking.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721103000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include really fresh pork and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic Lars Callieou performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721113000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic John Ki performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic Mark Little performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721123000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic Kyle Radke performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Watch a stuffed dog react to a real one and many more pranks from the masters of pranking.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721133000 +0000" stop="20260721140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include really fresh pork and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721140000 +0000" stop="20260721143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic Lars Callieou performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721143000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic John Ki performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic Mark Little performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721153000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic Kyle Radke performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Watch a stuffed dog react to a real one and many more pranks from the masters of pranking.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721163000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include really fresh pork and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>This rowdy gang of four take a big gamble in the Cash Cab; they are full of enthusiasm and have some great answers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721173000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Alec, Ann and Jacqueline are bemused by the Cash Cab, but decide to give it a go; it's a tense ride.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Caught-on-camera videos that highlight the outrageous and wacky world of animals, hosted by comic Andy Woodhull.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721183000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Outrageous and wacky animal clips.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>Feeding wild bears; a family's reaction when monkeys attack; dolphin impressions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721193000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>Comfy hammocks falling apart, a high-powered flying lawn mower and outrageous office pranks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Marvel</title>
    <desc>Ant-Man's original writer and director, Edgar Wright, departs from the project months before filming, taking his department heads with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>After Bart steals a key from Principal Skinner's office and gets himself into hot water, Marge and Homer send him to a behavior modification camp.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721213000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Fry and Leela deliver a package to a lunar amusement park, and Bender finds romance with a farmer's daughter.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>A look at Jesus' thoughts on adult literature and many more pranks from the masters of pranking.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721223000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>In this episode, you will laugh at seeing an elephant get sick on a zookeeper and many more hilarious pranks from the masters of pranking!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Marvel</title>
    <desc>Ant-Man's original writer and director, Edgar Wright, departs from the project months before filming, taking his department heads with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260722000000 +0000" stop="20260723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Jerry tries to ensure that Elaine's houseguest (Jeremiah Birkett) doesn't sleep through the New York Marathon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>As Sheldon stresses about picking a wedding date, Amy tries to convince him he has a more laid-back side; Koothrappali and Stuart compete to win the heart of Bernadette's new co-worker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260720223000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Wolowitz and Sheldon bond over having disappointing fathers; Leonard is disturbed when his mother finds a new best friend in Penny.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260720233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Legendary "Jackass" Steve-O joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to prepare for the "Machine Uprising"; feeling the relief of "Beating Your Junk"; doing a little "Roofin' Off.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260720233000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Lolo Wood experiences the pain of a sudden bicycle stop in bike locks; seeing some real pain in virtual violence; finding out who's not leap frog material.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260721003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood celebrate a Special Kind of Love, arrest some Self-Service Outlaws and take a spin with Pedal Predators.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721003000 +0000" stop="20260721010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo reinvent the game in "Neobasketball," hang out with some alligators in "Gator Casual," and get intimate with the inanimate in "Lifeless Love.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721010000 +0000" stop="20260721013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo feel the sting of rejection in "Access Denied," fantasize about better bathrooms in "Bidet Dreamin'," and dig deep to unearth some "Cult Classics.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721013000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Grammy nominated singer, songwriter and actress Christina Milian joins to be amazed by some "Superhumans" and give some restaurants an "F-Rating.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood find out what happens when you don't seal that deck in Dropped by the Rot and meet folks who will never be Employee of the Month in Workin' Dumb.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721023000 +0000" stop="20260721030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Rocsi Diaz get some basketball bruises in "Hoop Damage," meet some eerily human-like bears in "Bear Guys" and witness secret haters in "It's a Setup.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721030000 +0000" stop="20260721033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Lolo Wood welcome The Challenge's Queen Kam Williams to watch couples fall for each other in Hurt Flirtin', get primal with some Mad Mamas, and make sure no one goes hungry.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721033000 +0000" stop="20260721040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo face danger with "Death Down Under," make friends with "Lung Buddies," and enlist the services of "Dyrdek, Dudley &amp; Brim.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721040000 +0000" stop="20260721043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo talk about their worst birthdays, the condition doctors call drunk feet, and how to know when it's time for a detail.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721043000 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob and Steelo are joined by special guest Rachel Wolfson to dig in.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo welcome TikTok star Griffin Johnson as they watch ball players get "Diamond Dusted," celebrate some "Spectacular Shepherds," and check out a bunch of "Frat Clowns.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721053000 +0000" stop="20260721060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Lolo Wood encounter some dogs who are hazardous for humans in "Kamikaze Canines" and feel the pain of failing to launch in "Ramp Stamped.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721060000 +0000" stop="20260721063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo let it out in "All the Rage," create new moves in "Dance Geniuses," and explore the latest men's fashion in "D-Strings.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721063000 +0000" stop="20260721070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood suffer a pain in the butt; while suffering from tail trauma, they meet some young wedding guests who are little wedding wreckers; they have fun with people who are also dancing.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721070000 +0000" stop="20260721073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood welcome Lioness's LaMonica Garrett to put on the fatigues for some "Not So Special Ops," saddle up for "Cowboy Camp Dropouts" and play some brutal basketball in "Slamball.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721073000 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob and Steelo welcome Carly Aquilino to get pulled over and scarred.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood see how encouraging children goes wrong in Parental Pressure; suffer slice heartbreak in Pizzagony and bust bones with Broken Dancing.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721083000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo join the animal resistance, judge a nitrous talent show, and premiere their action blockbuster, "The Disposables.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob Dyrdek, Steelo Brim and Lolo Wood meet some hard-headed people who could have used a helmet; Rob becomes a member of the party police; finding out about the power of petty in K.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721093000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Comedian Brendan Schaub joins Rob, Chanel, and Steelo to get medieval with "Modern Knights," celebrate to the extreme in "Power Fives," and get burned by some "Chaos Candles.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood take a foul in Red Down; failing to achieve Crew Coordination and seeing which couples are Worse Together.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721103000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Nina Agdal take a trip, hang out solo, and celebrate love "Ridiculousness" style.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob Dyrdek, Steelo Brim and Lolo Wood find out Steelo loves singing in the rain with rain pain, learn that not all kids are destined to be athletes in not sports kids, then see some substandard.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721113000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Foreigner frontman Kelly Hansen joins Rob, Chanel, and Steelo at a concert of Jukebox Zeros, experiencing firsts in Feels Like The First Time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Talking about the pain of taking "Ribshots"; the cruel fun of committing "Friend Abuse"; taking guidance in "Tips From Idiots.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721123000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Carly Aquilino take the game too seriously in "Adult League Intensity," reveal far too much in "Super Honest" and pick up some late night work in "Night Shift Nightmares.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob Dyrdek, Steelo Brim and Lolo Wood drop and pop right back up; turning the corner on chaos; celebrating the world's worst subway performers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721133000 +0000" stop="20260721140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>The Chainsmokers; "Biters"; "Stolen Mattresses"; "Teleporters.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721140000 +0000" stop="20260721143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo celebrate Oktoberfest in "Lederhosed"; welcoming unexpected guests in "Don't Answer"; experiencing some sweet and stern "Southern Mother'n.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721143000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Carly Aquilino hit the rapids with "Wack Yakers," figure out "Little Logic," and look for some "All Star Hiders.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo try to use some "Dumb-Chucks"; having a sip with a few "Grape Nuts"; finding out the price of "The Free-est Shipping.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721153000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood are joined by The Challenge star Cara Maria and watch hallway-free collisions in Brawls Without Halls, get pecked and panicked in Feather Heads and see workouts go wrong in Cross Unfit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo discover that shopping can be fun in "Market Mayhem," meet some handy "Multipurpose Friends," and get to cooking with "Dinner Time Dads.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721163000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob Dyrdek, Steelo Brim and Carly Aquilino shatter the hoop dreams of some Sloppy Ballers; they meow their way through some Cat Convos and marvel at the predictions coming true in Future Seers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Karrueche Tran cause damage when they try Golfin' at Home; they meet some construction workers, who are having fun in Job Site Jesters and witness the power of wind in Blowin'.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721173000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Pro-skateboarder Torey Pudwill joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to skate with some "T-Dubs," face the fur of "Forest Kings" and try living on a "Trash Based Diet.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>On this episode of Ridiculousness, Rob, Steelo, and Lolo Wood can't get back inside after a long night in DRUNKS AT THE DOOR, are sent into full-blown panic mode in NOT READY FOR FIRE, and give firm rejections in DEFINITELY NO.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721183000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood get taken down by some aggressive furnishings, change their tire creatively with some wheel substitutes, and fill up their ride with a lot of pain at the pump.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo witness some "Counterterrorism," live the "Jort Life" and see who's been "Getting Clocked.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721193000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Comic Gary Owen joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to try out some "Sackupuncture"; watch couples get lost in a "Love Bubble" and experience redheads reaching their boiling point in "Ginger Snap.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon and Koothrappali confide in Bernadette when they can't handle Amy and Wolowitz working together; Penny and Leonard learn a secret from an unlikely source about dealing with Sheldon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721203000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon auditions for the role of the new Professor Proton; Penny takes care of Halley when Bernadette and Wolowitz need bed rest.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon tries to keep his collaboration with Bert a secret; Penny and Bernadette coach Koothrappali on navigating his relationship with Ruchi.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721213000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Leonard and Wolowitz are furious when they learn Sheldon worked with the military behind their backs; Bernadette suspects Ruchi is trying to steal her job.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon tries to teach the guys a lesson after they cut him out of a potentially valuable investment; a seven-year-old video reveals a secret about Leonard and Penny's relationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721223000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon and Amy try to use math to eliminate wedding planning stress; Koothrappali "breaks up" with Wolowitz after realizing he is hurting his confidence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260721233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>During an interview for a job in Philadelphia, a manager gives Pam déjà vu; Dwight asks Angela to join him on a mission; Andy returns from his trip.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260721233000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>During an interview for a job in Philadelphia, a manager gives Pam déjà vu; Dwight asks Angela to join him on a mission; Andy returns from his trip.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260722000000 +0000" stop="20260723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Dwight takes a trip home for a Schrute funeral; Todd Packer tries to make up for a lifetime of bad behavior.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>Ton and Allen find a motorized railroad maintenance car from the 1960s and a pre-World War I Japanese semi-automatic pistol.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260720223000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>Ton and Allen face-off with a buyer who has shady bidding tactics; a custom-built monowheel; a rifle designed to ward off grave robbers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260720233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>Toni and Allen face competition in Glendale, Calif., where they find a 1940s Zildjian brand percussion cymbal and a pyrotechnics control board.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260720233000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>Ton and Allen go to Alaska and get an unwelcome reception from the local auctioneer; Ton and Allen find a powerful production handgun, two large seaplane pontoons and two Smith &amp; Wesson revolvers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260721003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>Allen &amp; Ton battle local buyers to get a WWII-era motor scooter and Polynesian tattoo tools.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721003000 +0000" stop="20260721010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>Ton and Allen go to a storage container auction in Pasadena, Calif., and have to contend with inexperienced buyers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721010000 +0000" stop="20260721013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>Thugs try to bully Ton and Allen out of an auction, but the guys fight back; a rare Bornean blowgun and special effects wire harness are found.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721013000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>The first ever model CD player; a classic 1951 jukebox; a rare Willie Mays baseball card.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>Ton and Allen fight it out with a local thrift store at a Brooklyn storage auction; a classic arcade redemption; a mid-century water cannon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721023000 +0000" stop="20260721030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auction Hunters</title>
    <desc>A vicious battle erupts with former employee Carolyn over a 1968 Corvette Stingray; Allen tests his ninja skills.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721030000 +0000" stop="20260721033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) finds size 22 basketball shoes underneath Fancy's (Garcelle Beauvais) bed while poking around her apartment. Guest stars: NBA players Kevin Garnett and Derek Fisher.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721033000 +0000" stop="20260721040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) finds himself competing with Cupid (guest star Gary Coleman) for Fancy's (Garcelle Beauvais) affections.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721040000 +0000" stop="20260721043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie and Fancy agree not to have bachelor and bachelorette parties, and then promptly begin planning wild blowouts.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721043000 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Helen and Junior bequeath the hotel to Jamie and Fancy as they announce their retirement from the business.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>Uncle Phil's and Will's geese are cooked when a Thanksgiving Day massage with two prostitutes lands them in the hoosegow.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721053000 +0000" stop="20260721060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>Uncle Phil's and Will's geese are cooked when a Thanksgiving Day massage with two prostitutes lands them in the hoosegow.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721060000 +0000" stop="20260721063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>Will plays matchmaker for Hilary and a doctor; Hilary reveals shocking news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721063000 +0000" stop="20260721070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>Will's encounter with a beautiful woman at the gym leaves his ego bruised; Ashley's job is too demanding.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721070000 +0000" stop="20260721073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>The neighborhood bully forces Marlon (Marlon Wayans) to marry his sister.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721073000 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>After performing an emergency delivery, Dee realizes she wants her own child and turns to Shawn, Marlon and Pops for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Grandma tricks Shawn and Marlon into spending time with her, so they decide to find her a boyfriend; Dee is frustrated at being single.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721083000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>When baseball player Kenny Lofton visits, Marlon and Shawn recall when the three of them were Little Leaguers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon lands a role in a play with singer Keith Sweat, and Shawn feels left behind when Marlon's play goes on tour.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721093000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) shares the stage with music star Keith Sweat (appearing as himself).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Jenelle and Barb come to an agreement; Briana receives surprising news from Luis; Leah enters the dating world; Aubree visits Adam; Jo pursues custody of Isaac.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Leah pushes Jeremy to spend more time with Addie; Chelsea reconsiders her visitation agreement with Adam's parents; Jenelle wants a special weekend with Jace.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Luis asks Briana a question before she goes into labor; Barb tries to make peace with Jenelle; Kailyn prepares for her graduation; Chelsea takes her family on a trip.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Kailyn graduates from college; a fight between Briana's family and Luis ruins Stella's homecoming; Leah takes another shot at motivational speaking; Jenelle shops for wedding dresses.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721140000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Briana rushes Stella to the hospital; Kailyn's vacation is threatened by court; Leah and Corey believe Gracie may need special attention; Chelsea tries to change Aubree's custody agreement.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Whitney is offered her dream job in New York; Lauren learns her parents are selling their house in Laguna Beach; Stephanie turns to Spencer for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721153000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Spencer and Heidi travel to Mexico to elope; Whitney takes a chance at her dream job in New York City.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Lauren and Heidi have a run-in; Spencer and Heidi deal with the fallout from the elopement; Justin surprises Audrina.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721163000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Heidi crashes Lauren's surprise birthday party; Spencer starts a fight.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Heidi returns home to Colorado; Lauren has words with Stephanie for bringing Heidi to her party; Spencer ends a long silence with Brody.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721173000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Heidi demands couples therapy after catching Spencer out with a bartender; Lauren risks her reputation to get Stephanie an internship at People's Revolution.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Audrina sets her sights on someone else to get over Justin; Heidi drags Spencer to couples therapy; Stephanie screws up at People's Revolution.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721183000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Audrina tries to get over Justin by hooking up with Brody; Heidi's ex-boyfriend visits.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Brody's girlfriend confronts Audrina about Hawaii; Heidi intercepts a text message from Stacie to Spencer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721193000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Justin confronts Audrina.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>Spencer tries to save his relationship by asking Heidi's father for her hand; Lauren must fire Stephanie.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721203000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hills</title>
    <desc>After Spencer apologizes, Lauren considers attending Heidi's wedding; Brody refuses to risk his relationship to save his friendship with Audrina; Stephanie confronts Kelly.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Chloe Trautman check out some "Ship Wrecks"; loving to hate on their "Frenemies"; celebrating some clips that are "Classic Florida.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721213000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>"The Flash" star Grant Gustin joins Rob, Steelo and Chanel to go for a jog in "Trash Flashes," find a felon friend in "Cellmates" and put tap-dancing skills to use in "Applied Tap.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Singer Madison Beer joins Rob, Steelo and Chanel to visit "Strong Island," experience the tech obsessed in "Cell Centered" and see the unique Pomeranian breed in "Puff Guys.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721223000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Comedian Brendan Schaub joins Rob, Chanel, and Steelo to meet duos with similar vibes in "Energy Matchers," have their food swapped in "Food Switcheroo," and get shamed by modesty.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260721233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Model Danielle Herrington joins Rob, Steelo and Chanel to teach the gang what it takes to be "Cover Ready" and check out cutting edge fashion in "NY Looks.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260721233000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Actress Karrueche Tran joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to find out "The Salon Gets Serious"; getting "Life Sync'd"; watching some suspenseful "Cliphangers.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260722000000 +0000" stop="20260723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>UFC star and MMA champ Paige VanZant joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to celebrate some "First-Time Fighters" and order takeout with some "Chef Messes.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-22</date>
  </programme>
</tv>