<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260610225743 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="FX.us">
    <display-name>US | FX East</display-name>
    <icon src="https://tlgrm.re/images/fx-us.png" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465105">
    <display-name lang="US">Fuse HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470910">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464774">
    <display-name lang="US">FYI Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464897">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Family</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465331">
    <display-name lang="US">Freeform HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465354">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465290">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467015">
    <display-name lang="US">WNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260610173000 -0400" stop="20260610200000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Iron Man 2</title>
    <desc>With the world now aware that he is Iron Man, billionaire inventor Tony Stark (Robert Downey Jr.) faces pressure from all sides to share his technology with the military. He is reluctant to divulge the secrets of his armored suit, fearing the information will fall into the wrong hands. With Pepper Potts (Gwyneth Paltrow) and "Rhodey" Rhodes (Don Cheadle) by his side, Tony must forge new alliances and confront a powerful new enemy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610200000 -0400" stop="20260610230000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Iron Man 3</title>
    <desc>Plagued with worry and insomnia since saving New York from destruction, Tony Stark (Robert Downey Jr.), now, is more dependent on the suits that give him his Iron Man persona -- so much so that every aspect of his life is affected, including his relationship with Pepper (Gwyneth Paltrow). After a malevolent enemy known as the Mandarin (Ben Kingsley) reduces his personal world to rubble, Tony must rely solely on instinct and ingenuity to avenge his losses and protect the people he loves.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260610230000 -0400" stop="20260611013000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Jason Bourne</title>
    <desc>It's been 10 years since Jason Bourne (Matt Damon) walked away from the agency that trained him to become a deadly weapon. Hoping to draw him out of the shadows, CIA director Robert Dewey assigns hacker and counterinsurgency expert Heather Lee to find him. Lee suspects that former operative Nicky Parsons is also looking for him. As she begins tracking the duo, Bourne finds himself back in action battling a sinister network that utilizes terror and technology to maintain unchecked power.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611013000 -0400" stop="20260611050000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Nightmare Alley</title>
    <desc>In the 1940s New York, down-on-his-luck Stanton Carlisle endears himself to a clairvoyant and her mentalist husband at a traveling carnival. Using newly acquired knowledge, Carlisle crafts a golden ticket to success by swindling the elite and wealthy. Hoping for a big score, he soon hatches a scheme to con a dangerous tycoon with help from a mysterious psychologist who might be his most formidable opponent yet.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611050000 -0400" stop="20260611053000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611053000 -0400" stop="20260611060000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>NEW! Shark PowerDetect with DuoClean Detect Technology</title>
    <desc>Meet the new Shark PowerDetect Upright Vacuum with features like DuoClean Detect Technology, self-cleaning brush roll and odor neutralizing, and you will be cleaning faster, smarter and better!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611060000 -0400" stop="20260611063000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>2026 Silver Eagle is here &amp; it is a once-in-a-lifetime coin!</title>
    <desc>Join your hosts Kevin Cash &amp; Cory Cady as we discuss the 250th Anniversary of America with the official "America 250" logo on a Silver American Eagle label; we are locking in orders for this iconic release, but coins are limited! Don't miss out!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611063000 -0400" stop="20260611070000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611070000 -0400" stop="20260611090000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Harold and the Purple Crayon</title>
    <desc>Inside his book, adventurous Harold can make anything come to life simply by drawing it. After he grows up and draws himself off the book's pages and into the physical world, he soon learns his trusty crayon can set off more hilarious hijinks than he thought possible. However, when the power of unlimited imagination falls into the wrong hands, it will take all of his creativity to save both the real world and his own.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611090000 -0400" stop="20260611110000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Garfield Movie</title>
    <desc>Garfield, the Monday-hating, lasagna-loving indoor cat, finds himself on a wild outdoor adventure when his long-lost father draws him into a high-stakes heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611110000 -0400" stop="20260611130000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ice Age</title>
    <desc>Twenty-thousand years ago, Earth was a wondrous, prehistoric world filled with great danger, not the least of which is the beginning of the Ice Age. To avoid a terrible frostbite, the planet's majestic creatures - and a few small, slothful ones - begin migrating south. The story revolves around sub-zero heroes: a woolly mammoth, a saber-toothed tiger, a sloth and a prehistoric combination of a squirrel and rat, known as Scrat.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611130000 -0400" stop="20260611150000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ice Age: The Meltdown</title>
    <desc>With global warming threatening their once-icy domain with widespread flooding, Manny (Ray Romano), Sid (John Leguizamo) and Diego (Denis Leary) set out to find a safe haven. Along the way, another mammoth (Queen Latifah), who thinks she is an opossum, joins the travelers on their perilous quest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611150000 -0400" stop="20260611170000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Tooth Fairy</title>
    <desc>Rough-and-tumble hockey player Derek Thompson (Dwayne Johnson) is a terror on the ice, earning the nickname "Tooth Fairy" by separating opposing players from their choppers. When Derek dashes the dreams of a young fan, he is quickly sentenced to serve time as a real tooth fairy, complete with wings and magic wand. Though he can't "handle the tooth" at first, Derek's new job helps him to slowly rediscover the dreams that he gave up long ago.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260611170000 -0400" stop="20260611190000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Night at the Museum: Secret of the Tomb</title>
    <desc>When the exhibits at New York's Natural History Museum start behaving strangely, Larry Daley (Ben Stiller) -- now the director of nighttime operations -- must find out the cause. He learns that the Tablet, which magically brings Teddy Roosevelt (Robin Williams), Jedediah (Owen Wilson) and the other exhibits to life at night, has started to decay. Larry, along with his son and museum friends, must travel to London's British Museum to learn how to prevent the Tablet's magic from disappearing.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260610223000 +0000" stop="20260610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>A boy teaches his dad how to rollerblade; a dog spins a man in a chair; a boy plays a violin and hula-hoops; a bird won't stay off a man's head.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260610230000 +0000" stop="20260611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jim Morrison's Final Chapter</title>
    <desc>Explore the life of Jim Morrison, the Doors frontman, and uncover the enigmatic details surrounding his untimely death in Paris at age 27.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611000000 +0000" stop="20260611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Willie Nelson: The Outlaw Country King</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611010000 +0000" stop="20260611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elvis Presley: Shook Up</title>
    <desc>Behind the glitz and glamour of rock 'n' roll royalty is the haunting tale of Elvis Presley; many question his moral fiber and notorious violent temper; devilish charm dressed in angelic white had friends and fans fooled for too long.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611020000 +0000" stop="20260611023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Brittany wants to find out why her boyfriend, Taylor, has become distant.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611023000 +0000" stop="20260611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Kesha wants to find out what's going on with Duke.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611030000 +0000" stop="20260611033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Lizet wants to know the truth about Nick.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611033000 +0000" stop="20260611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Nicholas is worried about his relationship with Ava.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611040000 +0000" stop="20260611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BKB 54: Mayhem in Manchester</title>
    <desc>Featuring Rolando Dy vs. Paulie Malignaggi, plus Javon Wright vs. Dan Gittens in bare-knuckle boxing action from Manchester, England.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611070000 +0000" stop="20260611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Student Sex Workers</title>
    <desc>Ella has been bullied out of her university after her peers discovered she was an award-winning porn star, and Akonne is a sports science student and a stripper who doesn't consider himself to be a sex worker.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611080000 +0000" stop="20260611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Women That Made Elvis</title>
    <desc>Taking a look at the women who influenced Elvis Presley's life, from his mother, Gladys, to his true love, Priscilla.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611090000 +0000" stop="20260611093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Allie falls for a handsome pilot who lives in her building. But when he disappears Allie is left heartbroken until he shows up again. Dorian goes on a date with a girl who has a Jekyll and Hyde-like personality.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611093000 +0000" stop="20260611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>In 1995, Tanya was on a double date driving through the mountains; the boys hunt down an elk and leave the girls stranded in the Utah wilderness; 19-year-old Sam dates a much older army veteran with a dark past and an insatiable sexual appetite.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611100000 +0000" stop="20260611103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>People who think their significant other is cheating on them hire a hidden camera crew to investigate their suspicions.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611103000 +0000" stop="20260611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Nicki Parsons fears her husband-to-be has developed a case of cold feet.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611110000 +0000" stop="20260611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Freedia: Queen of Bounce</title>
    <desc>Freedia lives it up in LA; Berto mixes things up with the dancers in New Orleans; Tootie snaps when she hears Freedia is bonding with the new dancers deep in the swamps of Louisiana.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611120000 +0000" stop="20260611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Freedia: Queen of Bounce</title>
    <desc>It's Mardi Gras in New Orleans and Freedia has finally earned a coveted spot in the main parade, but a visit by a mysterious voodoo priest unsettles her as she hears shocking predictions about her future.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Beatles: In the Life</title>
    <desc>The Beatles took the world by storm in the 1960s and are still the best-selling band of all time with 183 million sales worldwide.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611143000 +0000" stop="20260611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Killing John Lennon</title>
    <desc>A dramatic step-by-step breakdown behind the lead up to John Lennon's murder on Dec. 8, 1980.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611160000 +0000" stop="20260611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Willie Nelson: The Outlaw Country King</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611170000 +0000" stop="20260611173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Nadia Freeman discovers the reason behind her boyfriend's unbalanced behavior.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611173000 +0000" stop="20260611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Nia Deon learns her boyfriend has a wife.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611180000 +0000" stop="20260611183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Asia Jones worries her boyfriend is getting too much attention from a lady bartender.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611183000 +0000" stop="20260611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Byron Tut is betrayed by his girlfriend and his best friend.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611190000 +0000" stop="20260611203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Another Christmas</title>
    <desc>Kelly Brooks has given up on finding love during the holiday season until her childhood friend returns home for Christmas to win her heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611203000 +0000" stop="20260611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Dog on a beach goes around on his bottom; Molly dancing; Sandy and her sandbox.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611210000 +0000" stop="20260611213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Little girl breaks bowling ball, lazy dog plays keyboard, down the chair twice, man in tie plays world's smallest harmonica, amazing pool shot, photographer hit on sidelines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611213000 +0000" stop="20260611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Dance around the bottle, snake scares little girl, man on stilt falls down, dirt track driving.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611220000 +0000" stop="20260611223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Cat chasing Hot Wheel car; bulldog hates cars; dog runs and runs around bush.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611223000 +0000" stop="20260611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Anything goes with the comedic moments celebrating funny pets and people.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260611230000 +0000" stop="20260612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stevie Nicks: Wild at Heart</title>
    <desc>For decades, Stevie Nicks has fronted one of the most successful bands in history, resurrecting them from the ashes; even with the trials and tribulations of being a member of Fleetwood Mac, Stevie has remained a role model.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260610220000 +0000" stop="20260610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a successful Wall Street investor is murdered in his home, Shaw and Riley dig into his professional and personal lives to identify his killer; DA Baxter puts pressure on Price and Maroun to make sure his first case in office is a success.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260610230000 +0000" stop="20260611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When an assault at gunpoint is witnessed through a neighboring window, the squad scrambles to locate the victim to confirm she's safe; a threat to extort the victim's family leads to a shocking suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611000000 +0000" stop="20260611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson investigates a string of sexual assaults targeting local female psychiatrists; the squad celebrates a promotion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611010000 +0000" stop="20260611013500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires go on a mission to New Hampshire to retrieve Nandor, who has lost his mind.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611013500 +0000" stop="20260611021000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Laszlo's father's ghost returns to make amends; Nadja and Nandor deal with the shapeshifters who have moved in next door.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611021000 +0000" stop="20260611024000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Laszlo and Nandor try to exorcise the demon who had possessed their neighbor Sean.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611024000 +0000" stop="20260611031000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Colin and Nadja have a couples' night with an old friend, while Nandor and Laszlo battle the film crew that have invaded their neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611031000 +0000" stop="20260611034500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires go on a mission to New Hampshire to retrieve Nandor, who has lost his mind.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611034500 +0000" stop="20260611042000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Laszlo's father's ghost returns to make amends; Nadja and Nandor deal with the shapeshifters who have moved in next door.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611042000 +0000" stop="20260611045000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Laszlo and Nandor try to exorcise the demon who had possessed their neighbor Sean.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611045000 +0000" stop="20260611052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Colin and Nadja have a couples' night with an old friend, while Nandor and Laszlo battle the film crew that have invaded their neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611052000 +0000" stop="20260611055500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires go on a mission to New Hampshire to retrieve Nandor, who has lost his mind.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611055500 +0000" stop="20260611063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Laszlo's father's ghost returns to make amends; Nadja and Nandor deal with the shapeshifters who have moved in next door.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611063000 +0000" stop="20260611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Laszlo and Nandor try to exorcise the demon who had possessed their neighbor Sean.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611070000 +0000" stop="20260611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When Donovan ́s ex, a recovering addict, wakes up with blood on her hands and a dead roommate in her apartment, the team moves quickly, finding there ́s more to the story.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611080000 +0000" stop="20260611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a car accident leads Charlie and Rex to investigate reports of a strange blue light in the sky, they discover the truth is more science than fiction.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611090000 +0000" stop="20260611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex have a run-in with a wanted criminal, when his past catches up with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611100000 +0000" stop="20260611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate a hot case under cold conditions when a figure skating coach is found dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611110000 +0000" stop="20260611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a murder at the shipping container port, Charlie and Rex partner with a Border Security officer to track down the mastermind behind a smuggling ring.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611120000 +0000" stop="20260611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex pull apart the secrets of a local band when their lead singer is found dead on the beach.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex have a run-in with a wanted criminal, when his past catches up with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611140000 +0000" stop="20260611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate a hot case under cold conditions when a figure skating coach is found dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611150000 +0000" stop="20260611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a murder at the shipping container port, Charlie and Rex partner with a Border Security officer to track down the mastermind behind a smuggling ring.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611160000 +0000" stop="20260611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex pull apart the secrets of a local band when their lead singer is found dead on the beach.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611170000 +0000" stop="20260611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex have a run-in with a wanted criminal, when his past catches up with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611180000 +0000" stop="20260611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate a hot case under cold conditions when a figure skating coach is found dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611190000 +0000" stop="20260611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a successful Wall Street investor is murdered in his home, Shaw and Riley dig into his professional and personal lives to identify his killer; DA Baxter puts pressure on Price and Maroun to make sure his first case in office is a success.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611200000 +0000" stop="20260611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson investigates a string of sexual assaults targeting local female psychiatrists; the squad celebrates a promotion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611210000 +0000" stop="20260611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a successful Wall Street investor is murdered in his home, Shaw and Riley dig into his professional and personal lives to identify his killer; DA Baxter puts pressure on Price and Maroun to make sure his first case in office is a success.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611220000 +0000" stop="20260611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Shaw and Riley investigate the death of a comic after a subway altercation; when a suspect is arrested, Baxter insists they increase the charges despite Price's apprehension; at trial, a new witness comes forward to throw the case into question.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260611230000 +0000" stop="20260612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson investigates a string of sexual assaults targeting local female psychiatrists; the squad celebrates a promotion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260612000000 +0000" stop="20260613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A girl is shot and Cosgrove teams with Detective Jalen Shaw to track down her killer; Benson and Stabler assist and realize it's more than a typical homicide; McCoy and Price seek justice against an international crime ring; part 2 of 3.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260610220000 +0000" stop="20260610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Anna and Aaron are wedding photographers who have decided to go tiny in order to move their Denver business to warmer climates to maximize clientele year round.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260610230000 +0000" stop="20260611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Amber and Tommy are looking to build their first home, and they've decided going tiny is exactly the way they want to do it, keeping the beach theme of the surrounding Santa Barbara area in mind.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611000000 +0000" stop="20260611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Tim and Amber are looking to build a tiny house designed to allow their daughter Penny's imagination to run wild. They want a space that is both functional and safe for their bright toddler.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611010000 +0000" stop="20260611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Stacy and Jose want a tiny house that they can call home and watch their two young daughters grow up in.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611020000 +0000" stop="20260611030100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Michelle and Blake love having their friends over for drinks and some card playing; they've asked John and Zack to help build them a tiny house that not only has space to entertain their friends, but room to keep their two dogs entertained as well.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611030100 +0000" stop="20260611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>The Grahams are looking for a craftsman-style tiny house which needs to both hold up against the brutal winters they will soon face, and pack enough functionality for the whole family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611040000 +0000" stop="20260611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Tim and Amber are looking to build a tiny house designed to allow their daughter Penny's imagination to run wild. They want a space that is both functional and safe for their bright toddler.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611050000 +0000" stop="20260611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Stacy and Jose want a tiny house that they can call home and watch their two young daughters grow up in.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611060000 +0000" stop="20260611070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Michelle and Blake love having their friends over for drinks and some card playing; they've asked John and Zack to help build them a tiny house that not only has space to entertain their friends, but room to keep their two dogs entertained as well.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611070100 +0000" stop="20260611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>The Grahams are looking for a craftsman-style tiny house which needs to both hold up against the brutal winters they will soon face, and pack enough functionality for the whole family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611080000 +0000" stop="20260611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Vince and Sam work hard and play harder. They love to rock climb and go hiking with their dog; they want a tiny house that fits their fun-loving lifestyle. But Sam is a medical student so she needs her own quiet study space too.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611090000 +0000" stop="20260611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611100000 +0000" stop="20260611103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611103000 +0000" stop="20260611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611110000 +0000" stop="20260611113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joni Table Talk</title>
    <desc>Joni and guests tackle a wide range of relevant issues, controversial subjects and hard-hitting news topics with candor and wit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611113000 +0000" stop="20260611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611120000 +0000" stop="20260611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Jake's latest mountain lion chase leads him to an angry bear; Tom and Jack take on a commission to build an ancient atlatl; Jason builds a steel trap to keep the area's wild hogs in check; Kidd transforms a large wooden boat into a summer cabin.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Freak ATV crash plunges Kidd and Harry into free fall; Jake goes on ranch patrol to protect newborn calves; Nancy gives Tom the surprise of a lifetime; Josh attempts to wrangle a feral horse.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611140000 +0000" stop="20260611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Josh goes panning for gold in a quest to unearth the West's greatest treasure; Eustace fights to save his land, but must say goodbye to an old friend; Jason returns to the forge, putting his injured hand to the test.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611150000 +0000" stop="20260611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Josh hits the jackpot; Tom puts his handmade dugout canoe to the test; Jake makes his last stand against a massive predator; Eustace sees his dream of keeping his new land go up in flames; Kidd and Harry secure their future in the mountains.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611160000 +0000" stop="20260611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>As the spring melt sweeps the mountains, Jake sets his sights on bagging a black bear for the larder; Eustace and Raleigh race against time and weather to plant crops; Mike sets out to harvest a bounty from the Gulf of Alaska.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611170000 +0000" stop="20260611173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jennifer must package and transport a model ship that took 10 years to construct; Jarrett loads a crate of priceless dinosaur fossils.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611173000 +0000" stop="20260611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Marc's big rig is sidelined for repairs; Chris transports a boat by sea, but his attractive shipmates prove to be a distraction.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611180000 +0000" stop="20260611183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Chris and Robbie convert one of their rigs to run on vegetable oil; Roy hopes to lure his son into the transport business.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611183000 +0000" stop="20260611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>The presence of a bride-to-be messes up Chris and Robbie's carefully planned one-day run; Jarrett teams up with Roy to deliver a load.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611190000 +0000" stop="20260611193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Marc plans to pepper a friend's run with pranks; the strange owner of a cold, creepy load joins Jennifer on her delivery.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611193000 +0000" stop="20260611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Marc transports young partygoers to New Orleans for Mardi Gras; Jarrett learns that mixing business and pleasure can be costly.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611200000 +0000" stop="20260611203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Roy tries to repair a Linotype machine that he suspects he damaged during transit; Jarrett comes up with a brilliant plan after he breaks down while hauling a load.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611203000 +0000" stop="20260611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Roy transports giant animatronic hillbillies and a side load of cat caskets; Jennifer moves an antique Honda.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611210000 +0000" stop="20260611213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Marc moves 4 million bees, then gets stung when his cargo starts to flee; a dollhouse collection is transported.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611213000 +0000" stop="20260611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrett transports a mobile tavern and a side load of sod; Jenn's trailer has a difficult time with a large load of arcade games.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611220000 +0000" stop="20260611223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Robbie tries to prove a point by taking charge of a manly shipment; Jennifer picks up an interesting travel companion while hauling expensive mannequins through the heartland.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611223000 +0000" stop="20260611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Roy travels to Austin, Texas, to pick up a very large sculpture from an art collective; Jarrett's uncle helps him transport a flight simulator.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611230000 +0000" stop="20260611233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jennifer transports live bugs across the country; Marc and his daughter haul a number of Volkswagen buses.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260611233000 +0000" stop="20260612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Chris and Robbie encounter alien life-forms at a "Star Trek" convention; Jarrett tries to learn from experience when he hauls a load of large pumpkins.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260612000000 +0000" stop="20260613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Roy clashes with two customers when he hauls their goods to a Renaissance fair; the future of bicycling is entrusted to Jenn.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260610220000 +0000" stop="20260610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth confronts Nathan about his parenting style; Bill is offered a judgeship, but is unsure if he wants to take it; Rosemary hosts a girls-only night; Faith and Carson's romance blooms; Jesse finds surface oil, but can't afford to drill.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260610230000 +0000" stop="20260611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Gowen strikes oil, which splits Hope Valley into the haves and have-nots; Bill must settle a dispute among landowners; Nathan urges Bill to re-examine the judgeship offer; Rosemary must come clean to Lee about a deep, emotional anxiety she feels.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611000000 +0000" stop="20260611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Trying to stay on Elizabeth's good side, Lucas sets up a library for the town; Allie tricks Harper, Robert and Opal into believing the town has a haunted house; Bill conducts his first trial as a judge in Hope Valley when Jesse sues Gowen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611010000 +0000" stop="20260611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Lucas' past comes back to haunt him and others in Hope Valley; Lee and Gowen compete for workers; an old friend arrives with a new orphan.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611020000 +0000" stop="20260611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>The Ingalls of Wisconsin make a new life on the Kansas frontier.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611040000 +0000" stop="20260611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura and Mary are concerned that other students won't accept them on their first day of school; Nellie Oleson snubs them for their homespun dresses.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611050000 +0000" stop="20260611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Amy debates what to do when she receives money from an unexpected source; Lisa's racing plans are in jeopardy after an accident; Tim worries when Jessica is hiding something; Lou makes a big decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611060000 +0000" stop="20260611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>After another "Miracle Girl" moment, Amy reconsiders her role at the Youth Centre; Jack misses Lisa, especially after Tim and Jessica are forced to move into the house.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611070000 +0000" stop="20260611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>A dying woman tries to reconcile with her stern father for the sake of her illegitimate daughter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611080000 +0000" stop="20260611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>Jonathan's guidance helps the romance of a quadriplegic lawyer (James Troesh) and Mark's cousin (Margie Impert).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611090000 +0000" stop="20260611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>After a hailstorm devastates his crops, Charles learns of blasting work available in a faraway quarry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611100000 +0000" stop="20260611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>The Ingalls of Wisconsin make a new life on the Kansas frontier.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611120000 +0000" stop="20260611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura and Mary are concerned that other students won't accept them on their first day of school; Nellie Oleson snubs them for their homespun dresses.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>When Charles brings an old friend home to dinner, Caroline decides the man would be a perfect match for Widow Snider.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611140000 +0000" stop="20260611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Unleashed</title>
    <desc>While hosting a puppy party, a woman tries to convince an uptight executive to give in to his daughter's pleas to adopt a rescue dog.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611160000 +0000" stop="20260611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Advice to Love By</title>
    <desc>When a love advice author and a dating columnist cross paths, attraction blooms into more. Using strategies from their own playbooks, it's possible they've met their match: each other.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611180000 +0000" stop="20260611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Playing Cupid</title>
    <desc>A girl sets her single father up with her teacher after starting a matchmaking business for a school project.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611200000 +0000" stop="20260611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love by Chance</title>
    <desc>Claire, the owner of a new restaurant, is too busy to focus on relationships. Her mother decides to fix this by finding Claire the perfect man -- without telling Claire.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611220000 +0000" stop="20260611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>At the Founders' Day Festival, Elizabeth makes a move that might affect her future; an orphan struggles to accept his new life; Bill finds startling information about Gowen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260611230000 +0000" stop="20260612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Lucas gives Elizabeth writing advice that causes her to search for new inspiration; Rosemary and Lee plan a vacation; Faith returns home with a dilemma that may force her to part ways with Carson.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260612000000 +0000" stop="20260613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth helps Nathan navigate family tensions when his estranged father arrives in town after recently being released from jail.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260610223000 +0000" stop="20260611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Frozen</title>
    <desc>When their kingdom becomes trapped in perpetual winter, fearless Anna (Kristen Bell) joins forces with mountaineer Kristoff (Jonathan Groff) and his reindeer sidekick to find Anna's sister, Snow Queen Elsa (Idina Menzel), and break her icy spell. Although their epic journey leads them to encounters with mystical trolls, a comedic snowman (Josh Gad), harsh conditions, and magic at every turn, Anna </desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611005500 +0000" stop="20260611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Frozen II</title>
    <desc>Elsa the Snow Queen has an extraordinary gift -- the power to create ice and snow. But no matter how happy she is to be surrounded by the people of Arendelle, Elsa finds herself strangely unsettled. After hearing a mysterious voice call out to her, Elsa travels to the enchanted forests and dark seas beyond her kingdom -- an adventure that soon turns into a journey of self-discovery.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611030000 +0000" stop="20260611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Inspiring stories of miracles and answered prayers from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611040000 +0000" stop="20260611043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Cheryl claims to like men who aren't afraid to cry, but when Jim bursts into tears after a movie, she is surprised to find herself turned off by his sensitivity.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611043000 +0000" stop="20260611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>When Cheryl cooks for Dana and her boyfriend, she lets him believe that Dana actually did the cooking.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611050000 +0000" stop="20260611053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Cheryl offers to let Dana wear her wedding dress, unaware that the gown was destroyed in a fiery sports celebration years earlier.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611053000 +0000" stop="20260611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>An attractive woman's suggestion leads Jim to grow a mustache, much to the dismay of Cheryl, who retaliates by coloring her hair.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611060000 +0000" stop="20260611063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611063000 +0000" stop="20260611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Accident Compensation: Get Help Now!</title>
    <desc>Helping injured individuals get the compensation they are owed.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611070000 +0000" stop="20260611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Inspiring stories of miracles and answered prayers from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611080000 +0000" stop="20260611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611090000 +0000" stop="20260611093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NEW! Shark PowerDetect with DuoClean Detect Technology</title>
    <desc>Meet the new Shark PowerDetect Upright Vacuum with features like DuoClean Detect Technology, self-cleaning brush roll and odor neutralizing, and you will be cleaning faster, smarter and better!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611093000 +0000" stop="20260611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathroom Makeover</title>
    <desc>Transform your bath affordably in just one day!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611100000 +0000" stop="20260611103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611103000 +0000" stop="20260611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611110000 +0000" stop="20260611113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>The premature birth of the Matthews' baby brings everyone together, but increases tension between Cory and Topanga.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611113000 +0000" stop="20260611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>The rich father of a bride-to-be offers Cory $1 million to marry his daughter; Eric wants to adopt Tommy.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611120000 +0000" stop="20260611123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>Just as Mr. Feeny gets enough courage to ask out Dean Bolander, her ex-husband returns to win her back.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611123000 +0000" stop="20260611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>Cory and Topanga's agreement to tell everyone everything creates tension at Rachel and Jack's dinner party.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Amazing stories of people who have experienced God's blessings.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611140000 +0000" stop="20260611143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">700 Club Interactive</title>
    <desc>Highlighting current events and stories that will help bring encouragement to people.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611143000 +0000" stop="20260611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Taking an interest in health and safety, Cheryl sets new rules that cause Jim to feel stifled.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611150000 +0000" stop="20260611153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Cheryl and Jim's evening alone turns into an all-out food fight; Andy plots revenge on Jim for coaxing his children to play pranks on him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611153000 +0000" stop="20260611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim struggles to care for the kids and household while Cheryl is away, but several sympathetic neighborhood moms lend him a hand.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611160000 +0000" stop="20260611182500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jungle Book</title>
    <desc>Raised by a family of wolves since birth, Mowgli (Neel Sethi) must leave the only home he's ever known when the fearsome tiger Shere Khan (Idris Elba) unleashes his mighty roar. Guided by a no-nonsense panther (Ben Kingsley) and a free-spirited bear (Bill Murray), the young boy meets an array of jungle animals, including a slithery python and a smooth-talking ape. Along the way, Mowgli learns valu</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611182500 +0000" stop="20260611212500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aladdin</title>
    <desc>Aladdin is a lovable street urchin who meets Princess Jasmine, the beautiful daughter of the sultan of Agrabah. While visiting her exotic palace, Aladdin stumbles upon a magic oil lamp that unleashes a powerful, wisecracking, larger-than-life genie. As Aladdin and the genie start to become friends, they must soon embark on a dangerous mission to stop the evil sorcerer Jafar from overthrowing young</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260611212500 +0000" stop="20260612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Mansion</title>
    <desc>A woman and her son enlist a motley crew of so-called spiritual experts to help rid their home of supernatural squatters.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260612000000 +0000" stop="20260613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jungle Cruise</title>
    <desc>Dr. Lily Houghton enlists the aid of wisecracking skipper Frank Wolff to take her down the Amazon in his ramshackle boat. Together, they search for an ancient tree that holds the power to heal -- a discovery that will change the future of medicine.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260610220000 +0000" stop="20260610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Sgt. Olivia Benson is investigated by Internal Affairs after William Lewis' death; as pressure mounts, Olivia has to choose between her convictions and her badge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260610230000 +0000" stop="20260611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Murphy question a television producer when he is accused of molesting his daughter; Benson strives to discover the truth as accusations fly in the media.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611000000 +0000" stop="20260611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Taking an active approach to catching sex offenders, the team targets a photographer with a secret life whose fantasies may have crossed into reality.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611010000 +0000" stop="20260611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro must face the consequence of his reckless behavior; when an online ad for escorts leads to the rape and robbery of tourists, Benson discovers she has a connection to one of the suspects.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611020000 +0000" stop="20260611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson struggles to balance work and her new role of foster mother; when Amaro arrests a young prostitute with connections to Noah's mother, his undercover work sets off a dangerous chain of events.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611030000 +0000" stop="20260611040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a series of allegations are made against a superstar basketball player, Sgt. Benson and Detective Carisi (Peter Scanavino) do not agree on the authenticity of each woman's story; the investigation takes Rollins back to her former precinct.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611040000 +0000" stop="20260611050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Amaro's by-the-book handling of a starlet's arrest gets him back on the SVU squad in time to investigate the actress's latest offense, statutory rape.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611050000 +0000" stop="20260611060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The team tries to find a bike messenger -- who has kept a video diary of his troubles with women -- before he can commit another violent act; the new deputy chief calls Benson's leadership into question.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611060000 +0000" stop="20260611070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A college student becomes a target after her work as an online porn star is discovered by her classmates.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611070000 +0000" stop="20260611073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611073000 +0000" stop="20260611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Car accident? Free Legal Consultation</title>
    <desc>Legal professionals standing by to answer your questions.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611080000 +0000" stop="20260611083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSN Mint - America 250 Coin Roll Collection!</title>
    <desc>CSN Mint presents 1776-2026 U.S. Mint coin roll offers honoring America's 250th Anniversary, including the Emerging Liberty Dime, Enduring Liberty Half Dollar, and P&amp;D Quarter Roll Continuity.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611083000 +0000" stop="20260611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611090000 +0000" stop="20260611093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611093000 +0000" stop="20260611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Interested in Gold? Learn More!</title>
    <desc>Gold has been the best long-term asset class for thousands of years; find out how you can protect your financial future by diversifying your nest-egg with physical gold today.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611100000 +0000" stop="20260611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When the head swim coach of a community college is found dead at the bottom of the well, possible suspects think he may have been having an affair; a new intern (Laura Spencer) catches Sweets' attention.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611110000 +0000" stop="20260611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>A man who wanted to talk to Booth about a possible government cover-up is killed before their meeting takes place; as Booth and the team investigate the conspiracy surrounding the man's death, Booth's future with the FBI becomes uncertain.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611120000 +0000" stop="20260611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>As Brennan and the team try to absolve Booth and get him out of prison, the remains of a man who has been dead for 16 years prove to be significant; Booth encounters criminals he was responsible for incarcerating.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team works with Special Agent Aubrey to investigate a far-reaching conspiracy in the government; DNA found on a previous victim linked to the scandal helps the narrow down the suspect pool.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611140000 +0000" stop="20260611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>With intern Rodolfo's help, the team investigates the murder of a conservative radio host whose remains were found in a storm drain; Special Agent Aubrey endeavors to gain Booth's trust; Brennan worries about Booth's mental health.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611150000 +0000" stop="20260611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a Muslim college student and his younger brother are murdered, the team connects with the outraged imam of OA's former mosque, who insists the victims were wrongly targeted as terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611160000 +0000" stop="20260611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team investigates an extremist gun group after an anti-gun lobbyist building is bombed; SAC Bashar dangles a possible promotion for OA.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611170000 +0000" stop="20260611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team realize they have a cross-country serial killer on their hands; the case has ties to Isobel's father, Robert, and his hotel, leading to revelations about their fractured relationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611180000 +0000" stop="20260611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After an immigration agent is fatally shot at a hockey game, the team attempts to find the shooter, who they believe may also be targeting Congressman Curtis Grange, who was at the same game.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611190000 +0000" stop="20260611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a young couple is found murdered in a New York City park after returning from a vacation, the team searches for a suspect linked to the drug trade; Scola turns over a new leaf when it comes to his relationships.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611200000 +0000" stop="20260611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>OA is forced to confront one of his biggest fears when the team discovers that deadly sarin gas may have been sold to terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611210000 +0000" stop="20260611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a morning show host is murdered inside her home, the team tracks the killer; things become awkward for Scola when agent Nina Chase becomes part of the team during Maggie's recovery.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611220000 +0000" stop="20260611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>A killer is using drug mules to exploit airport security checkpoints; OA struggles to cope with the aftermath of the sarin gas exposure and the 10th anniversary of his army friend's death in Afghanistan.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260611230000 +0000" stop="20260612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a retired Drug Enforcement Administration agent is shot outside a bakery, the team works to determine if the victim's past cases or current bouncer job are connected to the murder; Nina and Tiffany clash over the use of an informant.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260612000000 +0000" stop="20260613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team pivots when their sting operation to secure a massive bomb from an illegal broker leads them to discover that the device is already in the wrong hands; Jubal's promise to be present at his son's birthday party is put to the test.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260610220000 +0000" stop="20260610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>Jane and Maura investigate the murder of a bride; Jane's new neighbor captures the attention of Angela, Frankie and Frost.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260610230000 +0000" stop="20260611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>Jane and Frankie work hard to solve the murder of someone who grew up with them; Jane and Maura must decide when to reveal the truth about Lydia's pregnancy to Angela.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611000000 +0000" stop="20260611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A statue breaks open to reveal a dead woman inside; the squad gets a new homicide detective; Dennis Rockmond returns to Boston and tries to woo Maura; Lydia goes into labor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611010000 +0000" stop="20260611020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>Jane and the team try to find the contamination source after a man dies from poisoning; Stanley's true feelings are revealed; Tommy and Lydia disagree about custody of their baby; Detective Korsak reunites with his ex-wife.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611020300 +0000" stop="20260611030300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A famous author's suicide might not be all that it seems; Frost reviews an old murder case; Jane discovers Angela's new romance.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611030300 +0000" stop="20260611040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>The virtual world and the real world collide when a microbrewer is killed; Angela starts seeing someone new; Jane and the team mentor underprivileged teenagers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611040100 +0000" stop="20260611050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A statue breaks open to reveal a dead woman inside; the squad gets a new homicide detective; Dennis Rockmond returns to Boston and tries to woo Maura; Lydia goes into labor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611050100 +0000" stop="20260611060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>Jane and the team try to find the contamination source after a man dies from poisoning; Stanley's true feelings are revealed; Tommy and Lydia disagree about custody of their baby; Detective Korsak reunites with his ex-wife.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611060400 +0000" stop="20260611070400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A famous author's suicide might not be all that it seems; Frost reviews an old murder case; Jane discovers Angela's new romance.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611070400 +0000" stop="20260611080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>The virtual world and the real world collide when a microbrewer is killed; Angela starts seeing someone new; Jane and the team mentor underprivileged teenagers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611080200 +0000" stop="20260611083200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Have Thinning Hair? Keranique Can Help Regrow Beautiful, Thicker Hair!</title>
    <desc>If you have thinning hair or hair loss, Keranique can help regrow thicker, longer and fuller hair. Keranique is the number 1 hair regrowth system for women. Regain your confidence with beautiful, thicker and fuller hair in just 3 easy steps!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611083200 +0000" stop="20260611090200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611090200 +0000" stop="20260611093200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611093200 +0000" stop="20260611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Jeremiah</title>
    <desc>In this weekly program, Dr. David Jeremiah delivers practical messages to the congregation at the Shadow Mountain Community Church in San Diego. Also featured is music from the Shadow Mountain Community Church Choir and Orchestra, as well as performances by musical guests that have included Steve Green and Charles Billingsley. Men and women who have been impacted by the Turning Point ministry also</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611100000 +0000" stop="20260611103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Creflo Dollar</title>
    <desc>Dr. Creflo Dollar ministers to people from all backgrounds with hopes for change; Creflo helps viewers find ways to renew their faith, mind, and spirit; based on the belief that the Bible is the written and inspired Word of God, the show is meant to invoke change in the lives of people across the globe; Creflo and his wife, Taffi, share their vision for everyone to hear the Word and gain understan</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611103000 +0000" stop="20260611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Today</title>
    <desc>James Robison was a former preacher who changed directions in his life and began hosting this television show alongside his wife, Betty, in order to reach out to help more people. This daily religious and self-help program welcomes guests who tell how they have successfully overcome difficulties in their lives by following God's word -- with the hope of encouraging others to do the same and look t</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611110000 +0000" stop="20260611113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joyce Meyer Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Noted for her humanitarian ministry efforts to aid suffering people around the world, Bible teacher Joyce Meyer reaches out to both Christians and non-Christians as she illustrates how to make each day better by applying biblical principles to every activity.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611113000 +0000" stop="20260611120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Balancing Act</title>
    <desc>Special edition of The Balancing Act.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611120000 +0000" stop="20260611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>The wedding day has arrived, but Brenda and Fritz are a bit preoccupied with work; someone may be leaving the squad.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>Brenda's squad investigates a quadruple murder that may be linked to an FBI case.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611140000 +0000" stop="20260611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>The squad investigates the kidnapping of a rich financier who is under investigation for ripping off investors.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611150000 +0000" stop="20260611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>The team goes on a city-wide hunt for an individual who is threatening to cause a mass casualty event; Tim's sister shows up unannounced with some surprising news; Lopez continues her inner struggle over Wesley's deal with Elijah.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611160000 +0000" stop="20260611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Desperate to break free from his connection to Elijah, Wesley tries to plant a listening device in his office to incriminate him; Officer Bradford and his sister, Genny, learn an unsettling truth about their father.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611170000 +0000" stop="20260611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Now that John Nolan knows about Bailey's past, he must decide if they still have a future; when a plane crashes in the middle of the city, the team races to find out why.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611180000 +0000" stop="20260611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>Alexis asks Castle for help proving a death row inmate's innocence 72 hours before his execution, but they uncover a secret that could seal the man's fate.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611190000 +0000" stop="20260611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>When a well-known relationship therapist is murdered, it seems that she was targeted due to the secrets she knew about her powerful and elite clients.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611200000 +0000" stop="20260611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>When a woman who looks very similar to Lanie is murdered, the team thinks the killer may be targeting members of the 12th precinct.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611210000 +0000" stop="20260611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team investigates when the body of an NCIS facilities manager is found four months after she went missing; as the team faces mandatory psych evaluations, Gibbs is concerned about Abby's recurring nightmares.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611220000 +0000" stop="20260611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Ducky orders the exhumation of a body from a 12-year-old case; the team investigates a Marine's death.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260611230000 +0000" stop="20260612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>When a helicopter crew's training mission ends in a disastrous crash, the NCIS team must figure out what happened and find the missing pilot; Ziva challenges McGee and Tony to a dare.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260612000000 +0000" stop="20260613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>When a petty officer is shot in a billionaire's car, the investigation leads the team to Gibbs' namesake.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260610223000 +0000" stop="20260610230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260610230000 +0000" stop="20260610233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Knicks Road to the Championship</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260610233000 +0000" stop="20260611000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>"Toy Story 5" red carpet premiere and cast interviews.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611000000 +0000" stop="20260611010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brilliant Minds</title>
    <desc>Wolf becomes fascinated with an unusual patient at Hudson Oaks who displays signs of being possessed; Carol and Thorne help newlyweds who are struggling with their sex life.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611010000 +0000" stop="20260611020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide investigates a suspicious high school fire; Novak gets an unexpected call; Violet brings a 51 firefighter onboard the ambulance for a shift.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611020000 +0000" stop="20260611030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Atwater reunites with an old friend from his academy days after a bombing rocks downtown Chicago.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611030000 +0000" stop="20260611033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611033400 +0000" stop="20260611043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actor Hugh Jackman; Niall Horan talks and performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611043700 +0000" stop="20260611053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actress Emily Blunt; authors Mike Schur and Joe Posnanski.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611053700 +0000" stop="20260611060700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611060700 +0000" stop="20260611063700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611063700 +0000" stop="20260611070700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>"Toy Story 5" red carpet premiere and cast interviews.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611070700 +0000" stop="20260611080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke encore: "A Lot More Free"; Anna Faris; "What's Creepin' Up On Me?"; Samara Weaving; Kelly Extra: Nicholas Christopher; author Jared Freid; Midland performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611080000 +0000" stop="20260611083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611083000 +0000" stop="20260611090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611090000 +0000" stop="20260611100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611100000 +0000" stop="20260611110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York @ 6AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611110000 +0000" stop="20260611130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Actress Emily Blunt; the 40th anniversary of "Ferris Bueller's Day Off"; shopping expert Adrianna Brach; TV personality Elena Besser.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611130000 +0000" stop="20260611140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>World Cup preview with Steve Kornacki; building muscle with Dr. Joseph Herrera; actor Scott Eastwood; choosing and using cooking oils; Johnny Orlando performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611140000 +0000" stop="20260611150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Documentary subjects Chris Evert and Martina Navratilova ("Chris &amp; Martina: The Final Set"); makeup tips with Trinny Woodall; Today Food with Melba Wilson; Father's Day gifts with Preston Konrad.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611150000 +0000" stop="20260611153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611153000 +0000" stop="20260611160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Live</title>
    <desc>Celebrity interviews and discussing recipes, beauty, fashion and current events pertinent to the tri-state region.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611160000 +0000" stop="20260611170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611170000 +0000" stop="20260611180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>The neighbors enjoy mixing business with pleasure then a murder makes them face the reality that a killer is in their midst.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611180000 +0000" stop="20260611190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611190000 +0000" stop="20260611200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "Til We Get It Right"; Lamorne Morris; "Kelly's Spellys"; Amy Grant; Jason Kirschner ("Blazing Humor"); Train performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611200000 +0000" stop="20260611203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611203000 +0000" stop="20260611210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611210000 +0000" stop="20260611213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611213000 +0000" stop="20260611220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611220000 +0000" stop="20260611223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 6</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611223000 +0000" stop="20260611230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611230000 +0000" stop="20260611233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 7</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260611233000 +0000" stop="20260612000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260612000000 +0000" stop="20260613000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Surviving Earth</title>
    <desc>Against all odds, an alpha male gorgonopsid fights to protect his family from predators and the deadly heat that surrounds them at every turn.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-12</date>
  </programme>
</tv>