<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260625161344 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="FX.us">
    <display-name>US | FX East</display-name>
    <icon src="https://tlgrm.re/images/fx-us.png" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465357">
    <display-name lang="US">FXX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470910">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470820">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FXX Canada</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465331">
    <display-name lang="US">Freeform HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465354">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="492942">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Mystery</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465105">
    <display-name lang="US">Fuse HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464897">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Family</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486672">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465241">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464774">
    <display-name lang="US">FYI Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470509">
    <display-name lang="Canada">CTV LIFE CHANNEL</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470299">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Global Toronto</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="481954">
    <display-name lang="US">Haunt TV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465167">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Mystery HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486726">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486720">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486853">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486821">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV Quiz</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465290">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465002">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime Real Women</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="469871">
    <display-name lang="US">KNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470474">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Much Music HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486751">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">More4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467015">
    <display-name lang="US">WNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464825">
    <display-name lang="US">MTVLIVE</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470737">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Makeful TV SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486755">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">MTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465080">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV - Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465207">
    <display-name lang="US">Revolt HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467402">
    <display-name lang="US">WPTZ-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465113">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV2: Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="468233">
    <display-name lang="US">WCAU-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470330">
    <display-name lang="Canada">ONETV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260625103000 -0400" stop="20260625133000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Mission: Impossible -- Fallout</title>
    <desc>Ethan Hunt and the IMF team join forces with CIA assassin August Walker to prevent a disaster of epic proportions. Arms dealer John Lark and a group of terrorists known as the Apostles plan to use three plutonium cores for a simultaneous nuclear attack on the Vatican, Jerusalem and Mecca, Saudi Arabia. When the weapons go missing, Ethan and his crew find themselves in a desperate race against time to prevent them from falling into the wrong hands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260625133000 -0400" stop="20260625170000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Avengers: Infinity War</title>
    <desc>Iron Man, Thor, the Hulk and the rest of the Avengers unite to battle their most powerful enemy yet -- the evil Thanos. On a mission to collect all six Infinity Stones, Thanos plans to use the artifacts to inflict his twisted will on reality. The fate of the planet and existence itself has never been more uncertain as everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260625170000 -0400" stop="20260625210000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Avengers: Endgame</title>
    <desc>Adrift in space with no food or water, Tony Stark sends a message to Pepper Potts as his oxygen supply starts to dwindle. Meanwhile, the remaining Avengers -- Thor, Black Widow, Captain America and Bruce Banner -- must figure out a way to bring back their vanquished allies for an epic showdown with Thanos, the evil demigod who decimated the planet and the universe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260625210000 -0400" stop="20260625213200 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Bear</title>
    <desc>A storm hits. Written by Christopher Storer; directed by Christopher Storer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260625213200 -0400" stop="20260625220700 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Bear</title>
    <desc>The staff prepares for the day. Written by Rene Gube &amp; Karen Joseph Adcock; directed by Christopher Storer.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260625220700 -0400" stop="20260626010000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Wolverine</title>
    <desc>Lured to a Japan he hasn't seen since World War II, century-old mutant Wolverine (Hugh Jackman) finds himself in a shadowy realm of yakuza and samurai. Wolverine is pushed to his physical and emotional brink when he is forced to go on the run with a powerful industrialist's daughter (Tao Okamoto) and is confronted -- for the first time -- with the prospect of death. As he struggles to rediscover the hero within himself, he must grapple with powerful foes and the ghosts of his own haunted past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626010000 -0400" stop="20260626030000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Antlers</title>
    <desc>A small-town Oregon teacher and her brother, the local sheriff, discover that a young student is harboring a dangerous secret with frightening consequences.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626030000 -0400" stop="20260626033000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Car accident? Free Legal Consultation</title>
    <desc>Legal professionals standing by to answer your questions.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626033000 -0400" stop="20260626040000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626040000 -0400" stop="20260626043000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Cindy Crawford talks about the latest breakthroughs in skincare</title>
    <desc>Join Cindy Crawford as she talks to real customers about the breakthrough skincare system that keeps them looking their best. Take a trip to the stunning French countryside to see the rare French melon that defies the aging process.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626043000 -0400" stop="20260626050000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626050000 -0400" stop="20260626053000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>America 250th Anniversary Coins: Enduring Liberty Half Dollars</title>
    <desc>Join Mike Mezack for a special presentation of the 1776-2026 Enduring Liberty Half Dollars-one-year-only U.S. Mint issues honoring America's 250th Anniversary, including rare rolls and certified MS67 collectibles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626053000 -0400" stop="20260626063000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626063000 -0400" stop="20260626070000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Overwhelmed with IRS Debt? Keys to Resolving Tax Debt</title>
    <desc>See how one company is changing people's lives by helping them put their tax problems to rest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626070000 -0400" stop="20260626100000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Empty Man</title>
    <desc>A series of mysterious disappearances in a small Midwestern town may be linked to a supernatural entity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626100000 -0400" stop="20260626120000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Fantastic Four</title>
    <desc>Transported to an alternate universe, four young outsiders gain superhuman powers as they alter their physical form in shocking ways. Reed Richards becomes Mr. Fantastic, able to stretch and twist his body at will, while pal Ben Grimm gains immense strength as the Thing. Johnny Storm becomes the Human Torch, able to control and project fire, while his sister Sue becomes the Invisible Woman. Together, the team must harness their new abilities to prevent Doctor Doom from destroying the Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626120000 -0400" stop="20260626150000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Black Widow</title>
    <desc>Natasha Romanoff, aka Black Widow, confronts the darker parts of her ledger when a dangerous conspiracy with ties to her past arises. Pursued by a force that will stop at nothing to bring her down, Natasha must deal with her history as a spy, and the broken relationships left in her wake long before she became an Avenger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625133000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fight Club</title>
    <desc>A depressed man suffering from insomnia meets a strange soap salesman named Tyler Durden and soon finds himself living in his squalid house after his perfect apartment is destroyed. The two bored men form an underground club with strict rules and fight other men who are fed up with their mundane lives. Their perfect partnership frays when Marla, a fellow support group crasher, attracts Tyler's att</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bullet Train</title>
    <desc>Ladybug is an unlucky assassin who's determined to do his job peacefully after one too many gigs has gone off the rails. Fate, however, may have other plans as his latest mission puts him on a collision course with lethal adversaries from around the globe -- all with connected yet conflicting objectives -- on the world's fastest train.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When Bob meets his personal hero -- a renegade radio DJ who refuses to compromise -- the Belchers get in over their heads while trying to help him stage a comeback.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When the kids have to run a mandatory mile for school on free-ice-cream day, they hatch an elaborate plot to sneak away; Bob and Linda frantically try to secure discount tickets to a show at the Wharf Arts Center.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Linda attempts to become more involved with the P.T.A.; Bob tries to cheer up a hardware store owner after unknowingly making a joke about his pet parrot that recently flew away.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>The Griffins force Brian to move out after he posts an offensive tweet that goes viral.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Vladimir Putin visits Quahog after Peter writes to him about discovering an alternate ending in the Russian version of one of his favorite films; Brian gets a job at a suicide hotline center and attempts a romance with a co-worker.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Meg takes up drinking, which both concerns and delights her father; Brian spies on his neighbors and suspects Principal Shepherd of a crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>A selfish Peter loses his Christmas spirit and is visited by ghosts of Christmas past, present, and future.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Brian is smitten with a female show dog and enters a show dog competition in which the winner gets to breed her; Peter and Lois go to extreme measures to try to convince Chris that Arthur Valentine doesn't exist.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Stewie and Brian get into a friendship-ending fight after Brian commits a terrible act to one of Stewie's beloved toys; Peter refuses to wash his hand after meeting his favorite breakfast cereal mascot, Boo Berry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When Stewie gets sent to see his school's child psychologist for a surprising session, he reveals major secrets about himself.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626003000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Stewie and Brian are detectives who embark on solving a string of mysterious murders set in Victorian-era London.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Wrexham</title>
    <desc>Wrexham AFC and two other clubs fight for the last playoff spot as the Reds' chances at being promoted to the Premier League come down to the final days and, in typical Wrexham fashion, seconds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626020100 +0000" stop="20260626030200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Wrexham</title>
    <desc>Wrexham AFC and two other clubs fight for the last playoff spot as the Reds' chances at being promoted to the Premier League come down to the final days and, in typical Wrexham fashion, seconds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626030200 +0000" stop="20260626033200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After Peter and the guys get caught pretending to be military veterans, a judge sentences them to join the U.S. Coast Guard.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626033200 +0000" stop="20260626040200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Brian convinces Stewie to teach him how to invest in the stock market; Peter, Quagmire, Cleveland and Joe look after the Drunken Clam while Jerome is away.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626040200 +0000" stop="20260626043200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>When professor Farnsworth builds a "what if" machine, Fry and the crew find out what would happen if their wishes were fulfilled.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626043200 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Fry and Bender join the military, unaware that Earth is about to go to war; Leela serves under Zapp Brannigan.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When Rex finds a body with signs of foul play during Charlie and Sarah's romantic weekend getaway, they discover the community they're staying in may be more hostile than it looks.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When Supt Donovan's journalism student daughter investigates the story behind a murder on her university campus, the team race to find the killer before someone else becomes the next victim.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When an important trial is jeopardized after Sarah's testimony is challenged by a former rival in court, it's up to Charlie, Rex and the rest of the Major Crimes team to uncover new evidence to save the case before time runs out.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a young man is found dead of an apparent overdose, Dixon fiercely pursues a homicide investigation as an old unsolved case comes back to haunt her; Price and Maroun risk putting a witness in harm's way to expose their suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An internet dating site becomes the source of terror for a young widow; Muncy struggles with Velasco's absence.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a young man is found dead of an apparent overdose, Dixon fiercely pursues a homicide investigation as an old unsolved case comes back to haunt her; Price and Maroun risk putting a witness in harm's way to expose their suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Bernard and Cosgrove are confronted with several suspects in the shooting of a headmaster at an elite private school; a teenager's life hangs in the balance as Price and Maroun debate who's more culpable -- the shooter or the enabler.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An internet dating site becomes the source of terror for a young widow; Muncy struggles with Velasco's absence.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The search for a suspect who drugs women's drinks in crowded bars leads the SVU to Muncy's brother; Churlish makes a risky move to impress Benson.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>A news segment announces that Wolf Cola is the official drink of Boko Haram; Dee and Dennis work on the PR nightmare; Charlie and Mac try to promote Fight Milk.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626013000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>When a cat-woman is found dead in an alley, Dennis becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang seeks the help of a professional arbitrator to decide which of them could be the rightful owner of a lottery ticket.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626023000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After finding out that she is a male stripper's "rock bottom," Dee sets out to prove that she is the best thing that ever happened to him; Dennis takes over for a stripper; Mac and Frank play a war game.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>A news segment announces that Wolf Cola is the official drink of Boko Haram; Dee and Dennis work on the PR nightmare; Charlie and Mac try to promote Fight Milk.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626033000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>When a cat-woman is found dead in an alley, Dennis becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang seeks the help of a professional arbitrator to decide which of them could be the rightful owner of a lottery ticket.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626043000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After finding out that she is a male stripper's "rock bottom," Dee sets out to prove that she is the best thing that ever happened to him; Dennis takes over for a stripper; Mac and Frank play a war game.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>A news segment announces that Wolf Cola is the official drink of Boko Haram; Dee and Dennis work on the PR nightmare; Charlie and Mac try to promote Fight Milk.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626053000 +0000" stop="20260626060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>When a cat-woman is found dead in an alley, Dennis becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626060000 +0000" stop="20260626063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang seeks the help of a professional arbitrator to decide which of them could be the rightful owner of a lottery ticket.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626063000 +0000" stop="20260626070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After finding out that she is a male stripper's "rock bottom," Dee sets out to prove that she is the best thing that ever happened to him; Dennis takes over for a stripper; Mac and Frank play a war game.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626070000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>The maid-of-honor winds up dead after a bachelorette party; it's up to Charlie and Rex to untangle the events of the night.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When Rex finds a body with signs of foul play during Charlie and Sarah's romantic weekend getaway, they discover the community they're staying in may be more hostile than it looks.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a popular physiotherapist is murdered, the team must investigate the victims of his alleged sexual assaults in order to track down the killer before they strike again.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626100000 +0000" stop="20260626110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie's Aunt Miranda and her friends are caught investigating an investment fraud scheme, so it's up to Charlie and Rex to get to the source of the fraud.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626110000 +0000" stop="20260626120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a starlet is killed onstage, Rex takes on a starring role while Charlie goes behind the scenes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>After an injury on the job, Jake is forced to take time off; Holt, Rosa and their significant others go on a double date.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>When Jake and Amy go undercover to catch an identity thief, the investigation brings them closer; the precinct says an unexpected goodbye.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parks and Recreation</title>
    <desc>Leslie helps Tom prepare for a big evening; April and Ben conduct interviews; Donna and Andy assist Ron with a life change.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parks and Recreation</title>
    <desc>For the final episode of Andy's TV show, Leslie hijacks part of the production, bringing Andy's pals in to honor his efforts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 Rock</title>
    <desc>Liz hires a new female comic to combat claims of misogyny at TGS; Jack tries to take out his competition -- who happens to be the executive's granddaughter -- for becoming successor to Kabletown.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 Rock</title>
    <desc>Liz tries to convince Angie to lure Tracy back home; Jack is embarrassed by the "Queen of Jordan" cameras; a former flame causes Frank to question his maturity.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay reluctantly takes Phil on a model-airplane excursion, and Gloria goes shopping with Alex. Meanwhile, Claire and Manny get to know each other as siblings.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay's ex-wife, Dede (Shelley Long), tries to make amends with everyone she offended at Jay and Gloria's wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Tensions rise during a day of barbecue and football at Jay and Gloria's in the wake of an incident between Manny and Luke at school.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay and Gloria have a disagreement about Manny's choice of outfit for his first day back at school; Cameron and Mitchell freak out when Lily gets a bump on the head.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>The family comes out to support Manny's newfound interest, fencing; Phil is determined to find Luke's hidden talent.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Claire wants to surprise Phil with a private performance by one of their favorite musicians (Edward Norton); Cameron and Mitchell invite their friend Sal (Elizabeth Banks) out for a night on the town.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>Ripley and Frost uncover shocking information that conflicts with their patient's DNR; Asher facilitates an unexpected reunion; the tension between Archer and Lenox comes to a head.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Pascal and Severide revisit the storage facility fire in hopes of uncovering new evidence; Cruz helps Mouch take his studying to the next level; Novak prepares a proposal for Chief Robinson for a whole blood program.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>As Richard Beck's timeline for a deadly attack moves up and Samantha panics, Ruzek and the team scramble to get ahead of unprecedented disaster.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Wrexham</title>
    <desc>Wrexham AFC and two other clubs fight for the last playoff spot as the Reds' chances at being promoted to the Premier League come down to the final days and, in typical Wrexham fashion, seconds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Wrexham</title>
    <desc>Wrexham AFC and two other clubs fight for the last playoff spot as the Reds' chances at being promoted to the Premier League come down to the final days and, in typical Wrexham fashion, seconds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Wrexham</title>
    <desc>With Wrexham fighting for a position in the playoffs and perhaps promotion to the Premier League, Phil Parkinson tries to keep his squad, and himself, grounded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Wrexham</title>
    <desc>Wrexham AFC and two other clubs fight for the last playoff spot as the Reds' chances at being promoted to the Premier League come down to the final days and, in typical Wrexham fashion, seconds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Wrexham</title>
    <desc>With Wrexham fighting for a position in the playoffs and perhaps promotion to the Premier League, Phil Parkinson tries to keep his squad, and himself, grounded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626060000 +0000" stop="20260626070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Wrexham</title>
    <desc>With Wrexham fighting for a position in the playoffs and perhaps promotion to the Premier League, Phil Parkinson tries to keep his squad, and himself, grounded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626070000 +0000" stop="20260626073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake Peralta, a talented but carefree detective, and his colleagues meet their new captain -- Ray Holt, a tightly wound man determined to improve the dysfunctional 99th precinct.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626073000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake thinks the graffiti case he's investigating is below him until he discovers the culprit is the deputy commissioner's son; Gina's psychic friend gets under Charles's skin.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake's co-workers help him find evidence to keep a suspect he arrested in custody; Gina and Rosa have a pie contest; Holt helps Terry look better to his in-laws.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626083000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake vows to get revenge when a detective from Special Crimes takes over his nearly solved murder case; Captain Holt and Gina help Terry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>Jana rebels from the monotonous life she and her parents are living.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night at the Museum</title>
    <desc>A night watchman (Ben Stiller) at a museum of natural history makes a startling discovery: Thanks to the unleashing of an ancient Egyptian curse, the museum's animals, birds, bugs and other exhibits spring to life after the building closes, and former President Teddy Roosevelt (Robin Williams) is among those the hapless guard encounters.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian</title>
    <desc>Once the night guard at the Museum of Natural History, Larry Daley (Ben Stiller) is now a successful purveyor of infomercial products. Soon after learning that his museum friends have been shipped to the Smithsonian Institution, Larry receives a distress call from Jedediah, who warns him that four of history's greatest villains have come to life and are planning to take over the Smithsonian first,</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lilo &amp; Stitch</title>
    <desc>A tale of a young girl's close encounter with the galaxy's most wanted extraterrestrial. Lilo is a lonely Hawaiian girl who adopts a small ugly "dog," whom she names Stitch. Stitch would be the perfect pet if he weren't in reality a genetic experiment who has escaped from an alien planet and crash-landed on Earth. Through her love, faith and unwavering belief in ohana, the Hawaiian concept of fami</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Toy Story</title>
    <desc>Woody (Tom Hanks), a good-hearted cowboy doll who belongs to a young boy named Andy (John Morris), sees his position as Andy's favorite toy jeopardized when his parents buy him a Buzz Lightyear (Tim Allen) action figure. Even worse, the arrogant Buzz thinks he's a real spaceman on a mission to return to his home planet. When Andy's family moves to a new house, Woody and Buzz must escape the clutch</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260626005500 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Toy Story 2</title>
    <desc>Woody (Tom Hanks) is stolen from his home by toy dealer Al McWhiggin (Wayne Knight), leaving Buzz Lightyear (Tim Allen) and the rest of the gang to try to rescue him. But when Woody discovers that he's actually a valuable collectible from a once-popular television show called "Woody's Roundup" and is reunited with his horse Bullseye, Jessie the yodeling cowgirl (Joan Cusack) and his faithful sidek</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Amazing stories of people who have experienced God's blessings.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>The Ghost of Andy gives Jim a glimpse of Kyle's future as a loser because of Jim's failed attempts to help his son during a softball game.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260626043000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Andy's new metal detector uncovers Jim's long-lost wedding ring, causing a problem for Jim, who's been hiding the fact that he lost it for years.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After the president of the NY Fed is gunned down trying to help a young woman in peril, the team races to find the killer and the missing woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a local club owner is found dead, the team works quickly to find the motive behind the murder of a seemingly innocent man; OA is smitten with a new love interest but is concerned that she's mixed up with the wrong crowd.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a federal judge is gunned down in broad daylight, the team is sent looking for a suspect with ties to a local Islamic center; Maggie reunites with a former colleague.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When the director of a Brooklyn migrant center is abducted and held hostage along with his wife, the team must work quickly to meet the demands of their kidnapper; Maggie picks Jessica's brain about motherhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After multiple people are targeted and killed with a poisonous gas in broad daylight, the team races to find the killer; Maggie continues to explore motherhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a bombing at a local restaurant leaves several injured or dead, including a congresswoman and someone close to Isobel, the team races to apprehend the suspect before another explosive goes off.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After an employee of the U.S. Army is shot in an industrial park, the team works to track down the killer who reveals a larger plot at play; Tiffany continues to struggle with the guilt surrounding Hobbs' death.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a retired FBI agent is tortured and killed while working a security job, Scola and Nina go undercover as a married couple deep in the diamond game as the team tries to find out who is responsible.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After an FDIC security guard is killed while tending to a pregnant woman in distress, the team works to locate the woman and the killer who took her hostage; OA and Isobel worry about Maggie as she navigates taking care of Ella.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team is thrown into a highly political case after four members of the Taliban are shot and one is kidnapped in New York with no record of their entrance into the country; OA struggles to open up to Gemma about his past in Afghanistan.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a truck driver is murdered and the drug he was transporting goes missing, the team hunts for those behind the remaining batch that is already wreaking havoc on the streets of New York.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The Somalian terrorist group behind the death of Agent Hobbs resurfaces, sending the team on a chase to take them down for good.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The assassination of a seemingly ordinary Brooklyn plumber launches the team into a globe-spanning investigation that ruffles feathers with the CIA; Tiffany struggles with fieldwork in the aftermath of the Hakim case.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Bull helps the parents of a former employee sue a drug company when their son commits suicide during a drug trial; the drug company brings its own scientist into the trial.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Bull finds himself working a case solo after he releases his team to enjoy Thanksgiving with their families; Chunk makes a major personal decision; Marissa's dinner with Kyle is abruptly canceled.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Brennan and Booth's investigation identifies a decomposed body found in a local alley as that of a friendless teen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Booth and Brennan investigate when police find the dug-up corpse of a young woman in the trunk of a Salvadoran gang member's car.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>At the scene of a plane crash involving Chinese diplomats, Brennan finds three small bone fragments that did not come from the plane and might have something to do with a local man who went missing five years earlier.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Brennan tries online dating but ends up the target of a shooting when she tries to meet her date at a local restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When the remains of a filmmaker are found in the ventilation shaft of an underground tunnel, Brennan and Booth discover a subterranean world of homeless people.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The investigation of the bones of a shooting victim leads to a counterfeiting ring.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Willie Nelson: The Outlaw Country King</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Rayne wants to find out where Abel is spending his time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Amy wants to know why Jonathan is behaving childishly.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Lexi wants to know what's behind her beau's behavior.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Pierre wants to investigate his girlfriend after finding a bite mark on her rear-end.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Lizet wants to know the truth about Nick.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Little girl breaks bowling ball, lazy dog plays keyboard, down the chair twice, man in tie plays world's smallest harmonica, amazing pool shot, photographer hit on sidelines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Anything goes with the comedic moments celebrating funny pets and people.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Cat chasing Hot Wheel car; bulldog hates cars; dog runs and runs around bush.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>A gorilla makes funny gestures and poses; a horse makes funny faces; a duck honks a horn.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Eagles: The Long Road</title>
    <desc>Paying tribute to the life and career of Glenn Frey, one of the main band members. Revisiting the achievements of one of the best-selling and most loved American rock bands of all time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Bowie: Out of This World</title>
    <desc>Few artists marked the 20th century like David Bowie marked it. He was an astonishing and eclectic performer whose work brought a new dimension to the music scene and queer culture. Driven, fierce and always wanting to escape conformity, he was an outsider and was considered as a man from another planet.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260626003000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stevie Nicks: Wild at Heart</title>
    <desc>For decades, Stevie Nicks has fronted one of the most successful bands in history, resurrecting them from the ashes; even with the trials and tribulations of being a member of Fleetwood Mac, Stevie has remained a role model.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Shalyce hopes to gain insight into why Rod seems to be avoiding her.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260626023000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Hailey wants to know why Mike doesn't answer his phone when she calls.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Jordan Crosby discovers his girlfriend has another boyfriend; following up.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260626033000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Danni Little finds her boyfriend lives with his other girlfriends; following up with Gemma Taylor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Excited to go on a date with her crush, Carlita is surprised to end up at his mother's house instead; "RuPaul's Drag Race" contestant Vanessa Vanjie Mateo goes on a date in Texas and when her date starts ignoring her, all hell starts breaking loose.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260626043000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Alex goes on a karaoke date with Kevin, but is sad to learn that Kevin invited some friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Yes, I Do</title>
    <desc>Busy chocolatier Charlotte has left helicopter mechanic James at the altar three times. Now, she somehow has to find a way to prove to him that she really does want to marry him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love by Chance</title>
    <desc>Claire, the owner of a new restaurant, is too busy to focus on relationships. Her mother decides to fix this by finding Claire the perfect man -- without telling Claire.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Once Upon a Prince</title>
    <desc>Susanna accepts help one day from Nate at her parents' store in Georgia. Sparks between them fly, but when a photo of them gets leaked to the press, Susanna is in for the shock of her life when Nate is called back home for his coronation as a king.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth and Rosemary don't agree about how best to share unsettling news in the town regarding the coal mines, but that's put behind them when Rosemary hears even more shocking news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>With the mine reopening imminent, Gowen decides to take drastic measures to make sure it stays closed; Elizabeth and Lucas struggle to communicate with each other; Lucas gets out of town to clear his head.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth worries about her relationship with Lucas; Bill helps Gowen through the fallout of the mine explosion; Rosemary and Lee receive some news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Hope Valley faces an economic downturn together; Elizabeth and Bill learn that the children of Hope Valley have made a discovery that could change the future of the town.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mary (Melissa Sue Anderson) is held hostage by the outlaw Jesse James (guest star Dennis Rucker). With Michael Landon, Karen Grassle and Melissa Gilbert.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Jonathan Garvey's barn burns down leaving the family with no means of support, but Jonathan is angry when his wife takes a job at the post office.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mary plans to meet a shy suitor at the Mankato Fair, until she encounters his charming balloonist boss.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh asks the questions as Tom from Liverpool, Jessica from Lincoln, Felix from Ilfracombe and Linda from Lowestoft join forces in the hope of winning thousands of pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Evening News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Changing Ends</title>
    <desc>Autobiographical comedy. ITV's Telethon has gripped the nation, but only some are willing to give while others are taking - meanwhile, Alan gets some unexpected attention.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Robert has a surprise visitor. Ross meets with Kylie.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Gary assures Todd that Kit's theory is unfounded, Susie exposes Will and Megan's game, Nina dreads a difficult conversation with Roy, and Jodie uses Ryan to make David jealous.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News at Ten</title>
    <desc>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625214500 +0000" stop="20260625224000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder - Smoke and Lies: True Crime Presents</title>
    <desc>Follow the investigation into the heartbreaking death of Nikitta Grender and the extensive police work that brought her killer to justice.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625224000 +0000" stop="20260625230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bradley and Barney Walsh: Breaking Dad</title>
    <desc>The boys have hit the Gold Coast, where Barney has sun, sea and some serious action planned - including setting his old man on fire in an epic stunt.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260625230500 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shop on TV</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Lingo</title>
    <desc>Adil Ray hosts the all-star game of words as Steps stars Faye Tozer and Lee Latchford-Evans try to avoid tragedy against comedian Russell Kane and Big Brother's Will Best.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626013000 +0000" stop="20260626043500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIFA WC2026: Turkey v USA</title>
    <desc>Tournament co-hosts USA and Turkey play their third and final group game at the 2026 FIFA World Cup in Los Angeles.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626043500 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Goals of the 1990s</title>
    <desc>A look at some of the greatest goals from the 1990s, including memorable World Cup strikes by Platt, Maradona and Owen, and Euros classics from Gascoigne, Suker and Poborsky.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Morning Britain</title>
    <desc>News, current affairs and lively debate.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626083000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lorraine</title>
    <desc>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">This Morning</title>
    <desc>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real-life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626113000 +0000" stop="20260626123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626123000 +0000" stop="20260626125500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Lunchtime News</title>
    <desc>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626125500 +0000" stop="20260626130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626130000 +0000" stop="20260626140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dickinson's Real Deal</title>
    <desc>Middlesbrough is home to David and his dealers. Tony Geering tries to catch himself some Mouseman; Corrie Jeffrey goes all out to buy a whisky decanter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626140000 +0000" stop="20260626150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern for the game show with only one question as Paisley sees if she can beat the infamous Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626150000 +0000" stop="20260626160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626160000 +0000" stop="20260626170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh asks the questions as Abi from Bradford, Greg from Southend-on-Sea, Gaynor from Coalville and Scott from London join forces in the hope of winning big money.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626170000 +0000" stop="20260626173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626173000 +0000" stop="20260626180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Evening News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>As Sherry goes into labor, Lorelai recalls being pregnant with Rory and the events leading up to the day she was born.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Lorelai and her new boyfriend (Billy Burke) spend a weekend in New York; Jess refuses to explain his black eye when he shows up for dinner with Rory and her grandmother.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love in Zion National: A National Park Romance</title>
    <desc>Sparks fly between an assistant curator and an American Indian park ranger as they explore Zion National Park.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Birthday Wish</title>
    <desc>When her boyfriend fails to propose, a woman makes a powerful birthday wish that leaves her surprised at the outcome.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Love Heist</title>
    <desc>Celebrity stylist Kayli must team up with hotel security chief Mills to track down an iconic piece of fashion history after it goes missing on her watch before the Chicago Costume Gala.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Falling Together</title>
    <desc>Natalie tries to bring feuding neighbors together in her new condo building. Her unexpected ally is the building's super who prefers to avoid getting involved.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>The roommates welcome Rose's recently blinded sister, whose independent manner is deceptive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260626023000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche panics when her father reveals his outlandish plans for the future.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy, Rose and Blanche reminisce about how they all came to live together.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260626033000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche fears she may be pregnant, but is actually going through menopause.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>The girls move into a Miami Beach hotel; they dress up to attend Burt Reynolds' movie premiere, only to be caught in a hotel raid, mistaken for prostitutes and dragged off to jail.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260626043000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy begs Blanche to go out with her ex-husband, Stan, but becomes jealous when the couple hits it off; Sophia and Rose begin selling sandwiches on the Boardwalk but inadvertently make an enemy of another vendor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Barrett-Jackson Auction</title>
    <desc>Collector car auctions return with the inaugural Columbus Auction, live and exclusive from the Ohio Expo Center &amp; State Fairgrounds, Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Barrett-Jackson Auction</title>
    <desc>Collector car auctions return with the inaugural Columbus Auction, live and exclusive from the Ohio Expo Center &amp; State Fairgrounds, Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Barrett-Jackson Auction</title>
    <desc>Collector car auctions return with the inaugural Columbus Auction, live and exclusive from the Ohio Expo Center &amp; State Fairgrounds, Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Barrett-Jackson Auction</title>
    <desc>Collector car auctions return with the inaugural Columbus Auction, live and exclusive from the Ohio Expo Center &amp; State Fairgrounds, Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Barrett-Jackson Auction</title>
    <desc>Collector car auctions return with the inaugural Columbus Auction, live and exclusive from the Ohio Expo Center &amp; State Fairgrounds, Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>Mary Berg explores lifestyle trends, do-it-yourself projects, home renovations, recipes and more; featuring celebrity guests, influencers and everyday heroes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie makes duck salad with giant croutons and cheat's rice pudding with stewed fruit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie Oliver shows how to cook oozy mushroom risotto, with spinach salad and quick lemon and raspberry cheesecake, all in just 30 minutes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>Tensions rise and fears are tested as teams race through Mississauga, Ontario and face a heart-pounding skyscraper traverse high above the city skyline.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Queen of the Castle</title>
    <desc>When beloved staff member Georgie gets engaged, Ann is deeply invested in making sure her wedding is held at Lympne Castle, making it as memorable as possible.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>The chefs are no longer competing on their teams, and it's each person for themselves as they fight for their place on the top level.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>A famous car from a classic film is stolen; an order from the acting district attorney puts Frank and Erin at odds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monk</title>
    <desc>An 800-pound man (Adam Arkin) who has not left his bed in 11 years is accused of murdering a local judge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Seeking a less hectic lifestyle in Yorkshire, a London couple have £425,000 to spend on a new home; Steve Brown is on hand to help them find it.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Pet Ate What?</title>
    <desc>Dr. G and Ben's investigation into a feline's mysterious meow takes a sharp turn, while at Trinity Hills 24 Hour Pet Hospital, Dr. Suttie's team takes on a big gulp by a suspected laundry-stealing pup; elsewhere, the Westwinds Mobile Veterinary Services Team investigates a horse with troublesome tastes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626003000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Pet Ate What?</title>
    <desc>Dr. Heather Suttie and team face a high-stakes emergency case with a prized show dog's hazardous chewing; Dr. G needs to be on the money when a tabby appears to have turned into a kitty bank.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef UK</title>
    <desc>Weekly amateur cooking contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Nicki Chapman helps a London couple find a property in Wiltshire, England.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>The remaining home cooks face an Italian-influenced Mystery Box Challenge; a season one winner Eric Chong-inspired elimination challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>A famous car from a classic film is stolen; an order from the acting district attorney puts Frank and Erin at odds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monk</title>
    <desc>An 800-pound man (Adam Arkin) who has not left his bed in 11 years is accused of murdering a local judge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626060000 +0000" stop="20260626070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>The chefs are no longer competing on their teams, and it's each person for themselves as they fight for their place on the top level.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626070000 +0000" stop="20260626073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie makes duck salad with giant croutons and cheat's rice pudding with stewed fruit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626073000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie Oliver shows how to cook oozy mushroom risotto, with spinach salad and quick lemon and raspberry cheesecake, all in just 30 minutes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>Fall gardening checklist; Canadian fall fashions; Mary's PEI adventures continue; TV host Suresh Doss ("Locals Welcome").</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary shares recipes that help people working from home or in an office have a tasty lunch without sacrificing convenience.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626093000 +0000" stop="20260626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Spencer prepares a 30-minute Italian feast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626100000 +0000" stop="20260626110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>The home cooks prepare meals for students; a fresh pasta Pressure Test.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626110000 +0000" stop="20260626120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>The Race continues in St. John's and Gander, Nfld., where the remaining teams compete for a coveted spot in the Season 11 finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626120000 +0000" stop="20260626123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary shows how to cater to food intolerances and allergies by amping up the flavor instead of using ingredient substitutions.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626123000 +0000" stop="20260626130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Spencer prepares pub food favorites.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Save My Reno</title>
    <desc>A couple looks to renovate their kitchen in the home they love.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>The remaining three chefs compete in a final battle on the barbecues.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Making It Home With Kortney &amp; Kenny</title>
    <desc>Miriam's been sketching floor plans of the perfect place to entertain; Kortney and Kenny are eager to help make her dreams a reality; they take the reins, but with such high homeowner expectations, they're afraid of disappointing.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>The Drew Crew team share their best pro tips, including the newest Drew Crewer Amirah Kassem, who discusses how to make the perfect party dish and provides easy ways to level up hosting.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>Mikel Welch tells Drew and Ross his best reno-free design hacks; Pilar Valdes shares her favorite pro tips when dining in Chinatown.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>Victor makes a surprising discovery about Nikki's diagnosis; Jack and Kyle take a big risk with Patty; Stephanie recruits Nate for a special project.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 5</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 6</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goldbergs</title>
    <desc>Upon their return home from college orientation, Adam and Brea each confess a secret that could affect the future of their relationship; Barry and Beverly openly admit their love of ice dancing and explore their shared passion together.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626003100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goldbergs</title>
    <desc>Barry joins the football team but is quickly benched due to his lack of playing ability; Adam helps Barry understand there are other ways he can contribute to the team; Beverly designs jackets and tries to get Murray and Erica to sell them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626003100 +0000" stop="20260626010100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghosts</title>
    <desc>A St. Patrick's Day staffing emergency gives Hetty the chance to step into an unlikely role at the restaurant as she regains her once-a-year ability to be seen and heard by the living; Kyle returns to watch over the ghosts and finds himself caught in an amusing supernatural dynamic.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626010100 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>As Olympia and the team take on a wrongful death case, Matty meets with a mysterious woman from Senior's past; Matty reflects on her relationship with her daughter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elsbeth</title>
    <desc>When "grief influencer" Raquel Drabowski's presumed-dead husband makes a miraculous return, their reunion takes a fatal plunge; Elsbeth's surprise reunion with an old friend could expose a dangerous undercover operation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 11</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626033500 +0000" stop="20260626040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626040500 +0000" stop="20260626050500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>The small Ontario town of Woodstock was the setting for one of Canada's most horrific child murders; through in-depth interviews with the families and investigators, we reveal the toll this small-town tragedy has taken on many lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626050500 +0000" stop="20260626053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626053500 +0000" stop="20260626063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>The remaining three chefs compete in a final battle on the barbecues.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626063500 +0000" stop="20260626073500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masters of Flip</title>
    <desc>Kortney and Dave try to create a light, bright and clean theme in their newest flip.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626073500 +0000" stop="20260626083500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Brother Canada</title>
    <desc>The houseguests face nominations with an HOH in place.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626083500 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SIGN OFF</title>
    <desc>Sign off.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Today</title>
    <desc>A natural health expert examines what the Bible says about food to determine the best way for us to enjoy healthy, beneficial meals.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626093000 +0000" stop="20260626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625155100 +0000" stop="20260625161600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Experts investigate why a Los Angeles hotel has become a magnet for death and if an ominous flight number associated with multiple aviation disasters is cursed.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625161600 +0000" stop="20260625171100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>Grotesque figures invade a woman's house in the middle of the night; the spirit of an old man follows a couple home after they visit the site of an airplane crash.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625171100 +0000" stop="20260625180500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>A woman is attacked by a demonic presence in her family's Texas home; a Toronto man receives a frantic message from an unsettling group of ghosts before confronting a dark and powerful entity lurking in his new apartment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625180500 +0000" stop="20260625185900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>A young mother is viciously attacked by an evil spirit after attempting to cleanse negative energy from her home; teenage siblings encounter a terrifying demonic figure while house sitting.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625185900 +0000" stop="20260625195300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>Wandering spirits seek to feed on the energy and emotions of unsuspecting patients and medical workers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625195300 +0000" stop="20260625204700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>The phenomenon of child ghosts and its consequences when medical facilities become their playgrounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625204700 +0000" stop="20260625214100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>Long term care facilities with elevated paranormal activity. Featuring: Oralia Cortez, Emily Bailey, Kaitlyn Elizabeth.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625214100 +0000" stop="20260625223600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>Cross paths with souls that linger after death; a nurse believes cold spots and odd noises are coming from a patient's stuck spirit, learn why trauma can bind the dead to the living; encounter a ghost that can't exit a hospital café.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625223600 +0000" stop="20260625230300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A bizarre trend happens in Ireland.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625230300 +0000" stop="20260625235200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>Uncovering the legacy of the famed DuPont family, who made a fortune in gunpowder manufacturing.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260625235200 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries: Family Spirits</title>
    <desc>Leitreanna, a lifelong practitioner of Seminole spiritualism, believes she is visited by her departed father as she endures an operation, seeing him comfort her when she is in pain.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>Mark investigates when the star player of a professional women's volleyball team, in which Norman has been asked to invest, is murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>When the judge presiding over Ben's latest case is found murdered, Ben is accused of the crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>When the judge presiding over Ben's latest case is found murdered, Ben is accused of the crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>A roofing contractor (George DiCenzo) is charged with murdering his wife's philandering personal-fitness trainer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>A narcotics officer (Titus Welliver) faces charges of murdering a fellow cop to cover up department corruption.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>A plastic surgeon is charged with the murder of his partner, but evidence later shows the doctor's twin brother may be the culprit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aurora Teagarden Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Aurora's high school reunion turns deadly when a body is found in the hotel pool; Aurora and her Real Murders Club help investigate which classmate was most likely to kill.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aurora Teagarden Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When Aida Teagarden's real estate client is found murdered, her sleuthing daughter, Aurora, sets out with her fiancé, Nick, and the Real Murders Club to solve the murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>In Ireland, the son of Jessica's friend (Fionnula Flanagan) is accused of killing another family member (Andrew Robinson).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica investigates her accountant and uncovers his gambling, an illegal casino and a police officer's murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A man (George Segal) who claims Jessica's novel closely resembles the story of his first wife's murder sues Jessica.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260625154000 +0000" stop="20260625161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>The first of tonight's episodes heralds the start of murder week, focusing on the events of just one day, during which Liam Connor meets his demise at the hands of Tony Gordon.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260625161500 +0000" stop="20260625165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Kevin fears for Sophie's safety and as the stags head for paintballing, the hens celebrate at the restaurant, where Carla confesses to Leanne that she is in love with Liam.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260625165000 +0000" stop="20260625175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic drama series set in a 1960s Yorkshire village. A dark family secret is found in an attic and brings Bellamy back in touch with a childhood sweetheart.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260625175500 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series set in a Yorkshire village in the 1960s. A feuding farmer's wartime past has explosive consequences.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Vera</title>
    <desc>Detective drama series. DCI Vera Stanhope investigates the brutal murder of a young physiotherapist gunned down at a luxury country retreat.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law and Order: UK</title>
    <desc>Ronnie Brooks and Matt Devlin investigate when a woman is brought into Accident and Emergency with flu-like symptoms and leaves in a body bag.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law and Order: UK</title>
    <desc>When a toddler goes missing, his mother reports him kidnapped and a massive police hunt is launched to find him, but the search throws up more questions than answers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260625225000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shetland</title>
    <desc>Perez reassesses the investigation in the aftermath of Jo's attack while needing to keep everyone on track, and the MIT arrives on Shetland.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626000500 +0000" stop="20260626011500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shetland</title>
    <desc>Troubled by what he's discovered about the scarf, Perez has to face the fact that Duncan may have been involved in Lizzie and Sally's murders.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626011500 +0000" stop="20260626013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626013000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George and Mildred</title>
    <desc>Domestic sitcom spin-off from the show Man About the House. George is ordered to watch his table manners when Mildred's sister comes round for dinner.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626053500 +0000" stop="20260626060500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George and Mildred</title>
    <desc>70s sitcom. Mildred's dreams of a cheap holiday clash with George's political allegiances.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626060500 +0000" stop="20260626070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Donald is furious to hear about Anna and Matthew's engagement and interrupts a celebration at the Kings' in a bid to sabotage the union. Brenda tries to apologise to Terry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626070500 +0000" stop="20260626074000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>The first of tonight's episodes heralds the start of murder week, focusing on the events of just one day, during which Liam Connor meets his demise at the hands of Tony Gordon.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626074000 +0000" stop="20260626081000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Kevin fears for Sophie's safety and as the stags head for paintballing, the hens celebrate at the restaurant, where Carla confesses to Leanne that she is in love with Liam.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626081000 +0000" stop="20260626102000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Touch of Frost</title>
    <desc>Detective drama series. Billy Conrad has Down's syndrome and something to hide, but is he capable of murder? Frost intends to keep an open mind.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626102000 +0000" stop="20260626112500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic drama series set in a 1960s Yorkshire village. A dark family secret is found in an attic and brings Bellamy back in touch with a childhood sweetheart.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626112500 +0000" stop="20260626123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series set in a Yorkshire village in the 1960s. A feuding farmer's wartime past has explosive consequences.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626123000 +0000" stop="20260626143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Barnaby tries to find out just who is targeting the Midsomer Vinae Winery - what does the attack have to do with the death of a child in a hit-and-run accident.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626143000 +0000" stop="20260626150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Anna presses ahead with plans for the wedding despite her recent news, while Matthew confesses his terrible secret to Carl. A mix-up means Andy does not get access to Sarah.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626150000 +0000" stop="20260626153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Rodney helps Anna arrange the funeral and the police confirm Donald died of natural causes. Andy tells Katie he is sick of being kept away from Sarah and will fight for custody.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626153000 +0000" stop="20260626160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Carla decides she can't marry Tony, but when it transpires Maria is pregnant, she realises there is no future for her with Liam. The police have worrying news for Kevin.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626160000 +0000" stop="20260626200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Series of Darts</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the World Series of Darts tournaments from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626200000 +0000" stop="20260626210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Agatha Christie's Poirot</title>
    <desc>The Case of the Missing Will: A wealthy man is murdered before he can change his will; when the will is then stolen, a doctor soon comes under suspicion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626210500 +0000" stop="20260626220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law and Order: UK</title>
    <desc>Prosecutor Alesha Phillips takes on the seemingly cut-and-dried case of the murder of a call girl but soon discovers that betrayal can lead people down the darkest paths.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Orange County</title>
    <desc>Reality show. Gina is caught between Katie and Heather after the paparazzi allegations, and Emily and Shane celebrate their 15th anniversary.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Aisling Bea, Chris Packham, and Kate Lawler join Stephen Mulhern hoping to 'say what they see' and guess well-known phrases for a chance to win 50,000 pounds for their charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Floor US</title>
    <desc>Rob Lowe hosts the American version of the game show. Contestants face questions about vending machines, action movies, Gen Z and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 1% Club</title>
    <desc>Lee Mack presents the ultimate leveller of a quiz show where it doesn't matter if you're not usually good at quizzes because the questions are all about logic and common sense.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Island</title>
    <desc>Glamorous singles live in a beautiful villa under the watchful gaze of an audience at home who have the power to decide who goes and who will win a huge cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625210500 +0000" stop="20260625213500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Island: The Debrief</title>
    <desc>Your daily drop of hot Love Island tea, and all the Villa gossip. With Shakira Khan, Toni Laites and Yasmin Pettet, nothing is off-topic or out of the question.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625213500 +0000" stop="20260625220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy series. After Joe loses a thief in a chase, Peter offers to train him for the decathlon at the Olympics for disabled athletes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625220500 +0000" stop="20260625223500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy about the trials and tribulations of family life. Lois encourages Peter to drink heavily after discovering his inebriated piano-playing skills.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625223500 +0000" stop="20260625230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated adventures of a patriotic CIA agent. After Stan and Roger fall out, Francine comes up with a plan to try and reunite the pair by faking Roger's kidnapping.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625230500 +0000" stop="20260625233500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>When a Stan Loves a Woman: Animated series. Stan and Francine's marriage is on shaky ground when Stan makes an alarming discovery.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260625233500 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>The Show (and Tell) Must Go On: Animated comedy. Louise takes a risk for her last show and tell by trying to recover a War of 1812-era cannonball from a beach cave at a high tide.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626000500 +0000" stop="20260626003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. Bob and Gene almost get swept out to sea when they attempt to move the rowing boat of a man trying to row from New Zealand to Nova Scotia.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626003000 +0000" stop="20260626012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Botched</title>
    <desc>US reality series. A woman whose nose has collapsed due to cocaine abuse seeks Dr Nassif's help, and a man hopes to get his 'soup bowl' chest fixed.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626012000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Home improvement programme. Brian McCourt and Sarah Keenleyside build a parents-only hideaway for two hardworking parents who have four children.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626053000 +0000" stop="20260626062500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern is at the helm as Myles goes head-to-head with the infamous Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626062500 +0000" stop="20260626072500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dress to Impress</title>
    <desc>Fitness coach Deji from Coventry is looking for love, and three single girls are hoping to win his heart via the medium of fashion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626072500 +0000" stop="20260626082500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Billie and Greg: The Family Diaries</title>
    <desc>The Shepherds enjoy a fading summer as Nelly goes to pony camp, Arthur dislikes his school uniform, and Billie stresses about a surprise makeover.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626082500 +0000" stop="20260626092500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Only Way is Essex</title>
    <desc>Having just celebrated their first anniversary, things are looking rosy when it comes to Harry and Frankie's romance. But scratch the surface, and all is not what it seems.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626092500 +0000" stop="20260626101500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Salt Lake City</title>
    <desc>US reality series. Angie celebrates her 25th wedding anniversary with a Mafia-themed party, and Whitney accuses Lisa of leaking rumours.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626101500 +0000" stop="20260626111000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Orange County</title>
    <desc>Reality show. Gina is caught between Katie and Heather after the paparazzi allegations, and Emily and Shane celebrate their 15th anniversary.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626111000 +0000" stop="20260626121000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>Graham Norton welcomes essential skills teacher Orla, development manager Kelly, and events duty officer Ben as they take on the fabled Wheel in the hope of winning 50,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626121000 +0000" stop="20260626131000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Aisling Bea, Chris Packham, and Kate Lawler join Stephen Mulhern hoping to 'say what they see' and guess well-known phrases for a chance to win 50,000 pounds for their charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626131000 +0000" stop="20260626141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Floor US</title>
    <desc>Rob Lowe hosts the American version of the game show. Contestants face questions about vending machines, action movies, Gen Z and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626141000 +0000" stop="20260626151000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Only Way is Essex</title>
    <desc>Halloween celebrations hit Essex with some hair-raising revelations and a bit of bad blood. Harry and Frankie address their relationship issues in an emotional chat.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260625154500 +0000" stop="20260625165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Champions</title>
    <desc>Fantasy espionage series. Nemesis sends its superagents to investigate why a country is breaking an international treaty by testing nukes under Antarctica.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260625165000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Minder</title>
    <desc>One Flew Over the Parents' Nest: Comedy-drama series. Arthur rents out Bert and Doreen's house while the unlucky pair are holidaying, but he hasn't bargained on one horrible fact.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Pickers</title>
    <desc>US documentary series. Mike Wolfe and Frank Fritz visit a theme park during a clear-out and later discover some shocking news about a collection of circus posters.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ice Road Truckers</title>
    <desc>Ray Veilleux spins out into oncoming big rigs, Jack Jessee battles a 200-ton monster haul to Prudhoe, and Alex Debogorski risks a bust by the DOT.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Clarkson returns to the host's chair as six contestants vie for a place in the famous hot seat and try to walk away with one million pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Motorbike Show</title>
    <desc>Henry Cole rides the rare Brough Superior, goes behind the scenes at a British Superbike race to check out Chris 'The Stalker' Walker and reunites with bike restorer Pete Thorne.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Berlin Station</title>
    <desc>The Eye Fears When It Is Done to See: April faces the loss of the tech when her assets are arrested and face deportation. Kirsch's spy swap goes horribly awry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hell's Kitchen</title>
    <desc>US cooking competition. 18 talented head chefs set out to impress Gordon Ramsay in the Signature Dish Challenge before embarking on their first dinner service.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Protectors</title>
    <desc>Adventure series about a European crime-fighting team. A young woman and her father call on the Protectors in Denmark to deliver a huge ransom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626003000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Protectors</title>
    <desc>Adventure series about a European crime-fighting team. An English boy is framed and arrested in Spain after a drug dealer plants marijuana in his backpack.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two and a Half Men</title>
    <desc>American sitcom about a rich bachelor. Alan avoids taking his 22-year-old girlfriend to Jake's birthday when he is worried about what Evelyn will make of her.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626013000 +0000" stop="20260626040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIFA WC2026: Paraguay v Australia</title>
    <desc>It's the final round of matches in the group stages and Paraguay take on Australia in Santa Clara.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626040500 +0000" stop="20260626043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Goals of the 1990s</title>
    <desc>A look at some of the greatest goals from the 1990s, including memorable World Cup strikes by Platt, Maradona and Owen, and Euros classics from Gascoigne, Suker and Poborsky.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626043000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Protectors</title>
    <desc>Adventure series about a European crime-fighting team. The Protectors go after industrial spies who threaten to bankrupt a chemical company by stealing their best products.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626053500 +0000" stop="20260626060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Protectors</title>
    <desc>Adventure series about a European crime-fighting team. The Protectors are hired by a Hungarian actress wanting to bury her late revolutionary father in their homeland.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626060000 +0000" stop="20260626070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. Thomas discovers that an elderly woman claiming to be Robin Masters' high school teacher actually works for the KGB as a killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626070500 +0000" stop="20260626080500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Saint</title>
    <desc>Drama series about a suave troubleshooter. Sinister agents kidnap the sister of an ex-RAF pilot with the aim of forcing him into stealing a top-secret jet.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626080500 +0000" stop="20260626091000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boon</title>
    <desc>Classic drama. Harry enlists Ken's help when an Austria-themed night at the Woodcote is used as a cover by a gang of criminals on the trail of hidden plans.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626091000 +0000" stop="20260626102000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Champions</title>
    <desc>Fantasy espionage series. Nemesis sends its superagents to investigate why a country is breaking an international treaty by testing nukes under Antarctica.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626102000 +0000" stop="20260626112500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BattleBots</title>
    <desc>Final: US robot combat series. Two teams square off in the seventh series final after four qualifying fights and four gruelling elimination battles.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626112500 +0000" stop="20260626123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. The president of a family-run business hires Thomas to investigate if his nephew is secretly siphoning off company funds to line his pockets.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626123000 +0000" stop="20260626133500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. Higgins begins researching the gruesome history of Second World War internment camps and becomes a target for murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626133500 +0000" stop="20260626144500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Saint</title>
    <desc>Simon Templar embarks on another adventure. The Saint is sent to jail to smash a large-scale prison escape organisation run by callous killers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626144500 +0000" stop="20260626155000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boon</title>
    <desc>Classic drama. Ken finds he's taken on more than he bargained for when he is hired to help a man leave town, and Harry might be sitting on an ecological time bomb.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626155000 +0000" stop="20260626165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Champions</title>
    <desc>Fantasy espionage series. The Champions investigate the murder of three students in the Austrian Alps.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>It's Rickie's turn to take on the Banker - join Stephen Mulhern to find out if he will take home a huge cash prize or become the latest member of the 1p Club.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Seeking success are brothers from Blackburn Hussain and Imran, mother and daughter duo Claire and Mia from Surrey and childhood sweethearts Esther and Adam from Birmingham.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Going for glory are Cheri and her daughter Rachel from Birmingham, Glasgow-based couple Mark and Dave, and colleagues-turned-couple Mark and Alissa from London. Hosted by Adil Ray.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Battling it out are Scouse sisters Brodie and Terrilea, couple Ian and Jacqui from Derbyshire, and mother and daughter Alex and Nicola from Leeds. Hosted by Adil Ray.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as one Chaser is all that stands between Karim Zeroual, Christopher Biggins, Ellie Leach, Des Clarke and thousands of pounds for their chosen charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260625235500 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>A family team of five from Southport take on a series of Top 10 list questions as they attempt to win 125,000 pounds. Quiz show, hosted by Warwick Davis.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626005000 +0000" stop="20260626014000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the rapid and ruthless quiz as contestants Matty and Laura, Sami and Alan, and Freya and Megan take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626014000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>It's Rickie's turn to take on the Banker - join Stephen Mulhern to find out if he will take home a huge cash prize or become the latest member of the 1p Club.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626100000 +0000" stop="20260626110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626110000 +0000" stop="20260626120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626120000 +0000" stop="20260626130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Going for glory are Cheri and her daughter Rachel from Birmingham, Glasgow-based couple Mark and Dave, and colleagues-turned-couple Mark and Alissa from London. Hosted by Adil Ray.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626130000 +0000" stop="20260626140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>A team of five Southampton uni friends take on the Tenable Tower as they attempt to win 125,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626140000 +0000" stop="20260626150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as one Chaser is all that stands between Karim Zeroual, Christopher Biggins, Ellie Leach, Des Clarke and thousands of pounds for their chosen charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626150000 +0000" stop="20260626160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the ruthless quiz as contestants Rachel and Nathan, Heather and Jordyn, and Sam and Angela take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626160000 +0000" stop="20260626170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern for the game show with only one question and find out if Paula can beat the Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626170000 +0000" stop="20260626180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Battling it out are Scouse sisters Brodie and Terrilea, couple Ian and Jacqui from Derbyshire, and mother and daughter Alex and Nicola from Leeds. Hosted by Adil Ray.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626180000 +0000" stop="20260626190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Fighting it out are Lingo-mad mother and daughter Adele and Molly from Manchester, Stoke-on-Trent couple Anita and Alex, and Leeds-based sisters Dominique and Tahiela.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626190000 +0000" stop="20260626200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Fighting it out are professional entertainers Nick and Tina, best friends Aaron and Gabriel from Leeds, and Salford-based couple Anna and Ollie. Hosted by Adil Ray.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626200000 +0000" stop="20260626210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as Adam Jones, Monica Dolan, Dom Wood and Dick McCourt take on a Chaser in a bid to win thousands of pounds for their chosen charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626210000 +0000" stop="20260626220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Detective Nyla Harper and James find themselves in the middle of a bank robbery which leads the entire team on a citywide manhunt; Tim and Lucy go on their first date.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>The search for a missing boy leads the team into the middle of a dangerous drug war between two rival gangs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Nolan and Celina must stand guard at a hospital after a dangerous prisoner needs surgery; Aaron, Lopez and Harper look into a string of robberies; Tim and Lucy consider how their secret relationship will affect their work; Lopez gets unexpected news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>When Castle and Beckett investigate the death of the creator of a long-running sketch show, they discover a secret that could explain his murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>An investigation into a death in the woods brings Castle back to a traumatic event from his childhood, leading to an obsessive search for answers; Beckett faces a crossroads.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>A call from a mysterious stranger ignites an explosive chain of events; the story is told from Castle's perspective as he searches for Beckett.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Gibbs and his team face a challenge when the wife and 9-year-old daughter of a Navy captain are kidnapped from their home, and the captain is held hostage in his own office.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Gibbs and his team investigate when the decomposed body of a woman in a wedding dress is found in a subterranean cell decorated to resemble a 1950s bedroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>When a Marine helicopter appears in the middle of a crop circle, Gibbs and the team investigate and encounter a town convinced that extraterrestrials played a role.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a Navy lieutenant's rape and murder; Ducky fears the killer is linked to an unsolved murder that has been haunting him for years.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260626020300 +0000" stop="20260626030300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The discovery of a civilian's body in a Marine bombing range leads the team to uncover a Mafia dumping ground, and Gibbs' partner, agent Fornell (Joe Spano), is accused of aiding the Mafia.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260626030300 +0000" stop="20260626040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team's assignment is to protect an Iraqi War veteran being targeted by terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260626040100 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>When a Marine helicopter appears in the middle of a crop circle, Gibbs and the team investigate and encounter a town convinced that extraterrestrials played a role.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A military family prepares for delivery; a woman with three boys at home hopes her baby is a girl; a newlywed couple is expecting their first child.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A woman forgets her birth plan at home; a mother of four boys hopes her next child is a girl; a surrogate mother gives birth.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>Two sportscasters make their first attempt at parenthood; a couple prepares for twins; a first-time mother experiences fear.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>In the first week of the competition, 12 children contend with topics including math and memory.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>Eleven children return for week two of the competition, battling it out in the rounds of spelling and geography.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>The remaining 10 academic warriors compete in this week's rounds of U.S. history and logic to advance toward the prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>The remaining nine competitors must conquer this week's challenging topics of current events and the human body.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>In week five of the competition, the eight remaining contestants prepare to do battle in the categories of literature &amp; fine arts and vocabulary.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>The seven remaining competitors face two brain-busting rounds of competition, advanced math and speed memory.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>The remaining six children must endure this week's rounds of advanced spelling and world landmarks in order to move on to the finals.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>The five remaining contestants must conquer this week's rounds of advanced logic and world history in order to advance in the competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius</title>
    <desc>The four finalists face off in an Academic Olympiad, a daunting compilation of all previous round topics; the winner receives a $100,000 college fund.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>The seven remaining competitors face two brain-busting rounds of competition, advanced math and speed memory.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>On the Money: Insurance Checkup with Ted Jenkin; Froyo makes a comeback; summer home maintenance with George Oliphant; Life Lessons: Secret to Strengthening Your Relationships with Samantha Boardman; cleaning everything with Melissa Garcia.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Date My...Dad; actress Lexi Minetree; Today Food with Matt Abdoo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11am</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">California Live</title>
    <desc>A daily lifestyle show that takes a ride through all of California, discovering many of the hidden treasures the state and its people have to offer including beauty, glamour, fitness, food, health, and tech.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "In My Life"; Rob Lowe; Ella Hunt; author Lauren Tarshis; chef Nadav Greenberg food demo; Kelly extra: Bryan Cranston and Jane Kaczmarek; married in the hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 3pm</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 4pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 5pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC 4 News at 6pm</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626013000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 7 PM</title>
    <desc>The latest in local breaking news, weather reports and feature stories covering the vast Southern California region.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626023000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Surviving Earth</title>
    <desc>Following our planet's most infamous mass extinction event, a mated pair of dinosaurs fight to survive an incredible 30-year period of darkness.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Americas</title>
    <desc>The Andes, Earth's longest mountain range; baby bears make treacherous descents, rare hummingbirds compete for mates, frogs freeze and revive and lizards battle for territory, all in a land of extremes -- plus new pop-up fun facts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a stranger threatens Rollins and Carisi's lives, they suspect it's connected to a case they worked together; Benson asks an old friend to come out of retirement for help with an investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626060000 +0000" stop="20260626063400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626063400 +0000" stop="20260626073700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Millie Bobby Brown; actor Sam Worthington; sombr talks and performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626073700 +0000" stop="20260626083700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Joel McHale; actress Alison Oliver.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626083700 +0000" stop="20260626090700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626090700 +0000" stop="20260626093700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626093700 +0000" stop="20260626103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "In My Life"; Rob Lowe; Ella Hunt; author Lauren Tarshis; chef Nadav Greenberg food demo; Kelly extra: Bryan Cranston and Jane Kaczmarek; married in the hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626103000 +0000" stop="20260626110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626110000 +0000" stop="20260626113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 4AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>There's no sound, but there sure are plenty of laughs. This crazy Quebec-based troupe uses the city as its stage, and its inhabitants, or victims, as characters! People are caught in a twisted yet funny web of comedic deception. This updated "Candid Camera" is a tad more risque and a little kookier with its practical jokes. The little snippets last only a few minutes, and some look more painful th</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>There's no sound, but there sure are plenty of laughs. This crazy Quebec-based troupe uses the city as its stage, and its inhabitants, or victims, as characters! People are caught in a twisted yet funny web of comedic deception. This updated "Candid Camera" is a tad more risque and a little kookier with its practical jokes. The little snippets last only a few minutes, and some look more painful th</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Sneezing cats; calamitous canines; dumpster-diving bears; rascally raccoons; counting down the top ten critter crack-ups of the week.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Video clips from the pet world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>They're fun, mischievous, sometimes dangerous, and at home, loving companions; they make life better just by being in it.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>The family we were born into can be our closest confidants, our partners in crime, and the people who know us best.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Harry Potter</title>
    <desc>The team races to the finish line on the first film, while kicking off the second; just as everything starts to come together, the team loses a family member.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer builds a robot suit and battles robots in competition; Lisa mourns the loss of Snowball II.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The Professor is upset when his parents return from virtual retirement aboard the Near-Death Star.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>There's no sound, but there sure are plenty of laughs. This crazy Quebec-based troupe uses the city as its stage, and its inhabitants, or victims, as characters! People are caught in a twisted yet funny web of comedic deception. This updated "Candid Camera" is a tad more risque and a little kookier with its practical jokes. The little snippets last only a few minutes, and some look more painful th</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>There's no sound, but there sure are plenty of laughs. This crazy Quebec-based troupe uses the city as its stage, and its inhabitants, or victims, as characters! People are caught in a twisted yet funny web of comedic deception. This updated "Candid Camera" is a tad more risque and a little kookier with its practical jokes. The little snippets last only a few minutes, and some look more painful th</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Harry Potter</title>
    <desc>The team races to the finish line on the first film, while kicking off the second; just as everything starts to come together, the team loses a family member.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Jerry, Elaine, George and Kramer search for something to take to a dinner party; Jerry and Elaine forget to take a number at the bakery; Kramer and George have trouble buying wine.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626003000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>George poses as a marine biologist while on a date with a former college classmate (Rosalind Allen); Elaine loses her electronic organizer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer builds a robot suit and battles robots in competition; Lisa mourns the loss of Snowball II.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626013000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The Professor is upset when his parents return from virtual retirement aboard the Near-Death Star.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BattleBots</title>
    <desc>Black Dragon has never been knocked out; Riptide has destroyed every opponent in seconds; these two formidable foes face each other in the ultimate match up.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer builds a robot suit and battles robots in competition; Lisa mourns the loss of Snowball II.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626043000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The Professor is upset when his parents return from virtual retirement aboard the Near-Death Star.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Harry Potter</title>
    <desc>The team races to the finish line on the first film, while kicking off the second; just as everything starts to come together, the team loses a family member.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626060000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BattleBots</title>
    <desc>Black Dragon has never been knocked out; Riptide has destroyed every opponent in seconds; these two formidable foes face each other in the ultimate match up.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Sneezing cats; calamitous canines; dumpster-diving bears; rascally raccoons; counting down the top ten critter crack-ups of the week.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626083000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Video clips from the pet world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <desc>Anthony Bourdain introduces W. Kamau Bell to the distinctive sights, tastes and sounds of Kenya.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625155000 +0000" stop="20260625162000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Shona and John Mitchell host at Larch Green Lodges in Langbank. Their guests are delighted by the sweeping views, but their hosting is blemished by a breakfast black pudding blunder.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625162000 +0000" stop="20260625165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The B&amp;Bers head for the Distant Hills Guest House in Spean Bridge, run by Dani and Cameron. The guests are blown away by the scenic views, but a dirty discovery leads to tears at feedback.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625165000 +0000" stop="20260625172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The final visit takes the B&amp;Bers to 18 Craigmillar Park in Edinburgh. The guests are impressed by host Craig's military precision, but their feedback leaves him in quite a huff.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625172000 +0000" stop="20260625175000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's payment day and the B&amp;Bers meet to discuss dirty remarks and filthy findings. After their differences are aired and discrepancies debated, the winner is announced.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625175000 +0000" stop="20260625185500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Location, Location, Location</title>
    <desc>Phil Spencer catches up with two young couples in Bristol and Hertfordshire - childhood sweethearts Rich and Bethan, and Laura and Ben, who moved from Bristol to Birmingham.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625185500 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PopMaster TV</title>
    <desc>.. grab your popcorn, throw on some popsocks and get ready to test your pop knowledge, as five more players take on the challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lorraine Kelly's Norwegian Odyssey</title>
    <desc>In the wild Vesteralen region, Lorraine spends time with the Sami people, enjoys a goat massage in the Arctic Circle, traverses the Lofoten Islands and encounters sea eagles.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Fifty-year-old Sara is rushed to A&amp;E after collapsing at work with a thunderclap headache. And Flynn was hit by a car while riding his bike and has hurt his leg.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625220500 +0000" stop="20260625231000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Lynn is rushed to A&amp;E after collapsing from a brain aneurysm. James is treated for a severely dislocated shoulder. And 30-year-old Lucas has a suspected urinary tract infection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260625231000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">999: On the Front Line</title>
    <desc>Paramedics treat a man who is fighting a life-threatening infection, and are called to a cardiac arrest in the street and a serious road traffic collision.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626001500 +0000" stop="20260626012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Fifty-year-old Sara is rushed to A&amp;E after collapsing at work with a thunderclap headache. And Flynn was hit by a car while riding his bike and has hurt his leg.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626012000 +0000" stop="20260626022500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Lynn is rushed to A&amp;E after collapsing from a brain aneurysm. James is treated for a severely dislocated shoulder. And 30-year-old Lucas has a suspected urinary tract infection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626022500 +0000" stop="20260626025500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Mandy and Peter dream of swapping their island life in Jersey for the warmer climate of the Canaries. Jasmine Harman shows them five fantastic properties in Fuerteventura for their £127k.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626025500 +0000" stop="20260626060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626060000 +0000" stop="20260626075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626075500 +0000" stop="20260626085500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heir Hunters</title>
    <desc>The race is on to find relatives of a Kent lady, but her father's family cause headaches. And on a case with a common surname in Wales, the team uncover the story of a naval hero.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626085500 +0000" stop="20260626095500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Find It, Fix It, Flog It</title>
    <desc>In Buckinghamshire, Simon O'Brien and Henry Cole restore a pair of manhole covers, a water pump and a beehive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626095500 +0000" stop="20260626102500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>John and Sue Blakemore host first, at the Golf House on the Isle of Wight. While breakfast is a big hit, a suspicious stain in the loo proves controversial.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626102500 +0000" stop="20260626105500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Nick and his best friend Layla welcome their rivals to The New Inn in St John's Wood, London. But guests John and Sue are left cold by their 'corporate and impersonal' room.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626105500 +0000" stop="20260626113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>At The Bunkroom in Chester, David is determined to prove that hostelling is for everyone - even if his wife isn't convinced. What will the guests make of the bunk beds and budget breakfast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626113000 +0000" stop="20260626120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The last visit of the week is to John Graham's The B&amp;B in Blackpool, where competition between the guests builds during a game of tenpin bowling. And there's tension at the dinner table.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626120000 +0000" stop="20260626123500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The B&amp;Bers meet one last time to find out how much they've been paid and confront their critics. Tension runs high, but who will be crowned best value B&amp;B of the week.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626123500 +0000" stop="20260626130500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Choir teacher Dionne serves up a menu that mixes European and Caribbean flavours, with a carnival flourish for good measure. Does it hit the right notes for her guests.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626130500 +0000" stop="20260626133500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Finance director Jane plans a fine dining menu of homemade ravioli, pork and panna cotta. But Denver is still upset about Jane calling her a goth.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626133500 +0000" stop="20260626141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Drama teacher and DJ Denver aims to bring a taste of Ibiza to Yorkshire, with a Spanish menu, Prosecco van and stilt walkers. But Darren finds it all a bit cringeworthy.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626141000 +0000" stop="20260626144000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Local legend Billy serves up tried-and-tested dinner party favourites. And the best is yet to come at the end of the night with a Frank Sinatra impersonator.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>In 1994, convicted murderer Randolph Dial escapes from a prison in Oklahoma and takes the deputy warden's wife, Bobbi Parker, with him, then, 10 years later, Parker is found living with Dial on a farm in Texas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "In My Life"; Rob Lowe; Ella Hunt; author Lauren Tarshis; chef Nadav Greenberg food demo; Kelly extra: Bryan Cranston and Jane Kaczmarek; married in the hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 6</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 7</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Surviving Earth</title>
    <desc>Following our planet's most infamous mass extinction event, a mated pair of dinosaurs fight to survive an incredible 30-year period of darkness.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Americas</title>
    <desc>The Andes, Earth's longest mountain range; baby bears make treacherous descents, rare hummingbirds compete for mates, frogs freeze and revive and lizards battle for territory, all in a land of extremes -- plus new pop-up fun facts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a stranger threatens Rollins and Carisi's lives, they suspect it's connected to a case they worked together; Benson asks an old friend to come out of retirement for help with an investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626033400 +0000" stop="20260626043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Millie Bobby Brown; actor Sam Worthington; sombr talks and performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626043700 +0000" stop="20260626053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Joel McHale; actress Alison Oliver.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626053700 +0000" stop="20260626060700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626060700 +0000" stop="20260626063600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626063600 +0000" stop="20260626070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626070500 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "In My Life"; Rob Lowe; Ella Hunt; author Lauren Tarshis; chef Nadav Greenberg food demo; Kelly extra: Bryan Cranston and Jane Kaczmarek; married in the hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626083000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Streets: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The band performs in Denmark; songs include "Fit But You Know It," "Dry Your Eyes," and "Could Be Well In.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kings of Leon: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The band performs in Denmark; songs include "On Call," "Fans," and "Knocked Up.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gnarls Barkley: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The group performs in Denmark; songs include "Crazy," "Smiley Faces," and "Going On.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Conor Maynard: MTV Brand New Live</title>
    <desc>Emerging British pop star Conor Maynard performs; songs include "Can't Say No" and "Vegas Girl"; live in London.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260626003000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>Silversun Pickups perform songs including "Lazy Eye," "Panic Switch," and "Well Thought Out Twinkles.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>All Time Low performs in New York City; songs include "Weightless," "Dear Maria, Count Me In," and "Damned If I Do Ya (Damned If I Don't).".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260626013000 +0000" stop="20260626023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Live</title>
    <desc>John Legend performs in Rome; songs include "Used to Love U," "Save Room" and "Green Light.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260626023000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes &amp; Holmes</title>
    <desc>Facing major structural and water issues at the river house, Mike and MJ decide to take the whole house down so they can rebuild it; at the country house, they notice water on the basement floor during a mechanical walk-through.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Christina Trevanion is in Peterborough, where experts Catherine Southon and Kate Bliss assist the teams before heading to Lichfield in Staffordshire for a very merry auction; Christina learns how "A Christmas Carol" helped to save the festive season.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes &amp; Holmes</title>
    <desc>Facing major structural and water issues at the river house, Mike and MJ decide to take the whole house down so they can rebuild it; at the country house, they notice water on the basement floor during a mechanical walk-through.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop: On the Road</title>
    <desc>The Repair Shop experts are off on a road trip across the UK fixing historical treasures and precious objects that cannot be brought to the barn.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>When Barbra Jean begins childbirth, Reba searches the wilderness for the camping father-to-be, Brock.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche falls for a handsome and successful businessman but is unsure whether she wants to take on the responsibility of his young children.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great British Sewing Bee</title>
    <desc>Britain's best home sewers are tested on their sewing and dressmaking skills.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Pottery Throw Down</title>
    <desc>Ten home potters from around the United Kingdom travel to Stoke-on-Trent, the home of British pottery, to take part in a competition to become top potter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Landscape Artist of the Year</title>
    <desc>Joan Bakewell and Frank Skinner find the nation's best landscape painter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great British Sewing Bee</title>
    <desc>Britain's best home sewers are tested on their sewing and dressmaking skills.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Pottery Throw Down</title>
    <desc>Ten home potters from around the United Kingdom travel to Stoke-on-Trent, the home of British pottery, to take part in a competition to become top potter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche falls for a handsome and successful businessman but is unsure whether she wants to take on the responsibility of his young children.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626053000 +0000" stop="20260626060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>When Barbra Jean begins childbirth, Reba searches the wilderness for the camping father-to-be, Brock.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626060000 +0000" stop="20260626070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626070000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Travelling Auctioneers</title>
    <desc>Will Kirk and Christina Trevanion take their mobile auction house on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626100000 +0000" stop="20260626110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes &amp; Holmes</title>
    <desc>Trusses go up at the river house until MJ learns that the permits have not been approved; Mike goes to a council meeting hoping to hear good news; at the country house, Mike and MJ welcome their designer Sarah Richardson who offers some good advice.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626110000 +0000" stop="20260626120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Below Zero Canada</title>
    <desc>Kim and Pierre's trapline expansion is well underway when a troublesome local resident threatens to derail their plans; Jon and his wife Lally brave extreme arctic conditions as they attempt to secure a supply of food.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626120000 +0000" stop="20260626123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blown Away</title>
    <desc>The hot shop meets the big top in a circus-themed challenge filled with whimsical creatures, from a bearded dragon lady to a dapper walrus.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626123000 +0000" stop="20260626130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blown Away</title>
    <desc>The glassblowers split up into pairs; one team collaborates on a troll-like tree baby, while the other forges flames and fiery chili peppers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626130000 +0000" stop="20260626140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Drink Masters</title>
    <desc>The competition heats up as the mixologists craft cocktails with a spicy kick; award-winning bartender Tiffanie Barriere guest judges.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Help! I'm In A Secret  Relationship! Delon was head over heels about Nikki for years, but over time </title>
    <desc>17 years later Nikki has reemerged, and Delon feels like the luckiest man alive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Geek Australia</title>
    <desc>A surprise bombshell shocks the group as the beauties and geeks hit the corporate world to avoid elimination.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Skin A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Dr Emma McMullen has her work cut out trying to help a patient with a challenging condition - and ends up needing a wipe down! And a patient's mole makes it hard to brush her hair.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Angelina opens up to the roommates. Mike is no longer the main character. The girls' planned trip to the Hamptons takes a detour thanks to Vinny.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Geordie Shore: From The Beginning</title>
    <desc>The boy-girl divide returns! Charlotte and Gaz aren't speaking, Becca and Jay are continually arguing, while Holly and James' nurse-patient relationship is back to strictly professional.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Angels</title>
    <desc>The Angels deal a tough hand in Vegas by challenging Local Artists. To guarantee an Ink Master spot, the Winner must beat an Angel by tattooing canvases affected by addiction.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master: Rivals</title>
    <desc>Eighteen Rival Artists enter for $100k and the Ink Master title. It's their worst nightmare as they're forced to ink with the enemy. The pressure is intense and one rival gets sent packing.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master: Rivals</title>
    <desc>Semi-nude models bring the heat and a game changing twist is revealed. Jacked pin ups make the critique a bloodbath and rivalries flare. True Blood's Joe Manganiello is Guest Judge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626014500 +0000" stop="20260626021000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Duffy Fortner is back for Redemption with some help from Season 6 Ink Master Kruseman. Season 5 Rivals Cris Element and Angel return.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626021000 +0000" stop="20260626023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Marq and Ty'Esha Reels return to the Ink Master shop to fix their unhappy Canvases' tattoos. Can their tattoos be reworked or have the ink stains set.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626023500 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just Tattoo Of Us USA</title>
    <desc>Best friends continue their lifelong prank war when ridiculous tattoos cross the line. A couple on the edge take out their frustrations in ink.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Cribs</title>
    <desc>Get the tour of Harleigh's fun and colourful Florida home. Then join us as we head to Jesse's Virginia pad, and from there it's just a short ride to Tucker's DC domicile.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626052000 +0000" stop="20260626061000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>Raised by a single mum, Jamie is a straight A student with big plans for the future. But after getting pregnant she struggles to mould her immature boyfriend into the father she never had.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626061000 +0000" stop="20260626070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>Catelynn removes her birth control and doesn't tell Tyler. Farrah goes on a vacation to Italy. Ryan and Mackenzie have a joint bachelor and bachelorette party. Amber learns she's pregnant.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626070000 +0000" stop="20260626073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626073000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626083000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626093000 +0000" stop="20260626103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Cowboys Stadium in Arlington, Texas is once again the venue for the Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders auditions. Five hundred candidates with dreams of making the DCC team arrive before sunrise.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626103000 +0000" stop="20260626120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Helping Jeanette find her catfish turns cray fast when Nev and Kamie find out Jeanette's cousin Kiara might be dating the same notorious catfish IRL.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo are joined by comedian Eric Andre to talk about his new movie, "Bad Trip"; "Freaky Fogies"; vomit-filled "Puke Radius.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo have fun on the farm in "Old MacDonald's," talk about people who are "Too Cool for Weights," and watch the athletic event: "Toilet Springs.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Nina Agdal get out their bats and hit some Whiffle Missiles and slam in their VR headsets in Crashing Into Reality.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Carly Aquilino look after tiny terrors, organize their crazed collections and make some new bathroom friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Lolo Wood welcome Devin Walker to check out some zero-star challengers, struggling to find answers with the trivia challenge, and chug beers with cool dude.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob and Steelo welcome Karrueche Tran to make sure that heads are safe in "Helmet Testers" and discover that donkeys need a rebranding in "Donkey'n Around.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo help fold up some "Human Origami," celebrate some "Casual Badasses" and go bananas with some monkeys that are "Big Chimpin'.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo shoot off some "Bottle Rockets," turn up the fear factor in "Real Scary," and hit the mid-'90s dance floor to "Grind it Out.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Puddle of Mudd frontman Wes Scantlin joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to get filthy with some "Mudd Buddies," get kicked out in "One Man Banned," and hire some "Scantlin Security.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob and Steelo welcome Lolo Wood to chug some water in "Stayin' Hydrated," experience small-town terror in "Living in Horrorville" and discover the importance of having good aim.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob Dyrdek, Steelo Brim and Lolo Wood see the pain of going viral in GRAM SLAMS, try to figure out what makes porches so dangerous in PORCH PUNISHED and meet some people with weird eating habits.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Lolo take off the training wheels in Two-wheel Rookies; seeing Saturday morning come to life in Living Cartoons; trying to live their lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Chris Pontius; "All Natural Weirdness"; "Party Boys.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo welcome the legendary Johnny Knoxville to face down to "Bull Bullies," get hit hard below the belt in "Final Blows" and take it to the sky in "Fly, Icarus, Fly.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Past members of the cast of Jersey Shore reunite to live together and go on vacation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>The Hamptons trip is in full swing; Mike is hunting for Sammi's blessing; Angelina is chasing a fresh start; Jenni is getting very messy.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>The Hamptons trip is in full swing; Mike is hunting for Sammi's blessing; Angelina is chasing a fresh start; Jenni is getting very messy.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hangover</title>
    <desc>Two days before his wedding, Doug (Justin Bartha) and three friends (Bradley Cooper, Ed Helms, Zach Galifianakis) drive to Las Vegas for a wild and memorable stag party. In fact, when the three groomsmen wake up the next morning, they can't remember a thing; nor can they find Doug. With little time to spare, the three hazy pals try to re-trace their steps and find Doug so they can get him back to </desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260626043000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jackass</title>
    <desc>Dressed in a bunny suit, Chris Pontius gets bitten by a dog; Steve-O snorts an earthworm. Host: Johnny Knoxville.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Internationally Known</title>
    <desc>Highlighting emerging artists and the top hits in Africa, Latin America, the U.K., and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Rappers Guapdad 4000, Stone Cold Jzzle, DW Flame and FourFive take their shots in the 3-point contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">DJ Drama's Gangsta Grillz Podcast</title>
    <desc>T.I. joins DJ Drama to discuss how they first connected, appearing on Never Scared, being released from his label and later signing to Atlantic, the impact of the Down with the King mixtape, the story behind Big Meech bringing Magic City to his work.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A mix of the best hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos, from the hottest new releases to favorite throwbacks.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>Lynae Vanee breaks down top headlines from her distinct perspective and lived experience.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>Lynae Vanee breaks down top headlines from her distinct perspective and lived experience.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Baller Alert Show</title>
    <desc>Marsha Ambrosius joins to discuss her ability to switch between her American and British accents, finding inspiration in Atlanta for writing her music, and shares her thoughts on the Amanda Seales' interview on Club Shay Shay.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Featuring the short films: "Sugar Daddy," "Dark Before Dawn," and "Paralysis.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">DJ Drama's Gangsta Grillz Podcast</title>
    <desc>T.I. joins DJ Drama to discuss how they first connected, appearing on Never Scared, being released from his label and later signing to Atlantic, the impact of the Down with the King mixtape, the story behind Big Meech bringing Magic City to his work.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A mix of the best hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos, from the hottest new releases to favorite throwbacks.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A mix of the best hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos, from the hottest new releases to favorite throwbacks.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Internationally Known</title>
    <desc>Highlighting emerging artists and the top hits in Africa, Latin America, the U.K., and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">REVOLT Sports Weekly</title>
    <desc>In the series premiere, host Mariah Rose covers Micah Parsons' big return to Dallas, the Giants benching Russell Wilson, Kawhi Leonard's wild contract requests, and more. Presented by Levi's®.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260626003000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Rappers Guapdad 4000, Stone Cold Jzzle, DW Flame and FourFive take their shots in the 3-point contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Out the Mud</title>
    <desc>NBA legends Zach Randolph and Tony Allen welcome a star-studded lineup of athletes and artists for can't-miss conversations about the journey to success.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Drink Champs: Happy Hour</title>
    <desc>Legendary Queens rapper N.O.R.E. and Miami hip-hop pioneer DJ EFN are joined by A-list guest stars for a boozy, raucous, and totally unfiltered show where nothing is off limits... after a few shots.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Laura Hayes; Bill Bellamy; Ted Carpenter; George Rogers (G.I. George).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260626033000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Reynaldo Rey; Eddie Griffin; Darcel Blagmon (Fat Doctor); Arceneaux &amp; Mitchell.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A mix of the best hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos, from the hottest new releases to favorite throwbacks.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the local news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>In 1994, convicted murderer Randolph Dial escapes from a prison in Oklahoma and takes the deputy warden's wife, Bobbi Parker, with him, then, 10 years later, Parker is found living with Dial on a farm in Texas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "In My Life"; Rob Lowe; Ella Hunt; author Lauren Tarshis; chef Nadav Greenberg food demo; Kelly extra: Bryan Cranston and Jane Kaczmarek; married in the hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 4</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5:30</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 6</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>In a classic game-show version of "Hangman," contestants solve word puzzles for cash and prizes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Surviving Earth</title>
    <desc>Following our planet's most infamous mass extinction event, a mated pair of dinosaurs fight to survive an incredible 30-year period of darkness.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Americas</title>
    <desc>The Andes, Earth's longest mountain range; baby bears make treacherous descents, rare hummingbirds compete for mates, frogs freeze and revive and lizards battle for territory, all in a land of extremes -- plus new pop-up fun facts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a stranger threatens Rollins and Carisi's lives, they suspect it's connected to a case they worked together; Benson asks an old friend to come out of retirement for help with an investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626033400 +0000" stop="20260626043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Millie Bobby Brown; actor Sam Worthington; sombr talks and performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626043700 +0000" stop="20260626053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Joel McHale; actress Alison Oliver.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626053700 +0000" stop="20260626061200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626061200 +0000" stop="20260626070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Top Story With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Reporting of breaking news and developing stories in real time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626070000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>Rachel Anderson is a vivacious single mother whose world revolves around her children; she fails to show up for work one day; her disappearance may have something to do with the terrifying telephone calls she's been receiving.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626083000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 430A</title>
    <desc>Early morning news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626100000 +0000" stop="20260626110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Jasmine has dealt with hardship and loss at every step of her life until she met Ryan, and while he seems to be perfect, his excuses of why he cannot meet have Nev and Kamie questioning him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>For six years, Pamela has spent thousands and has been kicked out of her home, all in pursuit of her sweet Fernando from Venezuela; but when "Catfish" comes calling, it seems that Fernando might be closer than anyone expected.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Vonni's fallen for online sweet-talker Andrew and has sent him hundreds of dollars to prove his love; now, Nev and Kamie help Vonni discover if Andrew is his one true love.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Reese was always successful with women until he met Jessica, a gorgeous girl who was doing more than playing hard to get; when a shady set of phone numbers sparks Reese's suspicions, he calls on Nev and Kamie to investigate.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Zark's been dating Roger for two years, but Roger will only show the bottom half of his face on video chat; Roger claims it's because he's sick, but an Instagram discovery leads Nev and Kamie to question Roger's intentions.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Nev and Laura Perlongo go on a wild ride to help Eli, who fell so hard for fellow gamer Boulevard, that he moved from Alaska to Chicago to be with her.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>Sketches include two old women battle with Satan; things go awry when a man goes mattress shopping; dance club patrons are forced to face the truth about themselves.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>A gangster participates in a drive-by; a mom writes a song for her son; two scam artists compete.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>Sketches include The Tea Party discovering a new hope; Bobby McFerrin duels with Michael Winslow; Jordan and Keegan debate who is blacker.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>Sketches include Keegan gets distracted while on the phone with his girlfriend; Keegan and Jordan having a mean boss; the birth of a new expression.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>Sketches include a neighborhood's reaction to a creature; exploring the black college experience; President Obama uses an anger translator.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626003000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>Sketches include Keegan and Jordan eavesdrop on white women who love black men; Wendell makes a music video; Kareem and Jahar go to the gym.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>Sketches include a guy chasing his girlfriend to the ends of the Earth; LMFAO literally cannot stop partying.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626013000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>Two friends get into an argument at a club; Meegan and André talk about their relationship; a rapper walks out of an interview; Conrad flies business select; Keegan has a new mustache.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>Sketches include an introduction to the newest set of East/West Bowl players; Devon the Landlord searches Jordan's apartment; Jordan is offended by an overly sexual co-worker.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626023000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Key &amp; Peele</title>
    <desc>Sketches include an emergency that changes a man's morning ritual; a henchman cramps the style of a supervillain; Jordan reminds Keegan that he's a grown-ass man.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) is taught a lesson about giving when he is forced to live the same day over and over.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626033000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) forgets Uncle Junior's (Garrett Morris) birthday, but hatches a plan to make it up to him. Guest stars: Ben Vereen and Savion Glover.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie poses as a British painter during an art auction and winds up searching for a collector's stolen painting.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626043000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Helen (Ellia English) ends up in therapy after an encounter with a mugger.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>In 1994, convicted murderer Randolph Dial escapes from a prison in Oklahoma and takes the deputy warden's wife, Bobbi Parker, with him, then, 10 years later, Parker is found living with Dial on a farm in Texas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "In My Life"; Rob Lowe; Ella Hunt; author Lauren Tarshis; chef Nadav Greenberg food demo; Kelly extra: Bryan Cranston and Jane Kaczmarek; married in the hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 4p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 5p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 6p</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 7p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Surviving Earth</title>
    <desc>Following our planet's most infamous mass extinction event, a mated pair of dinosaurs fight to survive an incredible 30-year period of darkness.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Americas</title>
    <desc>The Andes, Earth's longest mountain range; baby bears make treacherous descents, rare hummingbirds compete for mates, frogs freeze and revive and lizards battle for territory, all in a land of extremes -- plus new pop-up fun facts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a stranger threatens Rollins and Carisi's lives, they suspect it's connected to a case they worked together; Benson asks an old friend to come out of retirement for help with an investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626033400 +0000" stop="20260626043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Millie Bobby Brown; actor Sam Worthington; sombr talks and performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626043700 +0000" stop="20260626053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Joel McHale; actress Alison Oliver.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626053700 +0000" stop="20260626060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626060400 +0000" stop="20260626063300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626063300 +0000" stop="20260626073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626073000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626083000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626090000 +0000" stop="20260626093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 5:00a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626093000 +0000" stop="20260626100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 5:30a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626100000 +0000" stop="20260626110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 6a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: Modern Meditations</title>
    <desc>Featuring guided exercises of yoga and meditation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anjelica's Kettlebell Workout</title>
    <desc>Anjelica Scannura leads a workout.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Relieving symptoms of arthritis.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pilates Pupil</title>
    <desc>Strengthening, stretching and toning with Pilates.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Messages From Spirit with Colette Baron-Reid</title>
    <desc>Mediumship readings with spirits from the other side.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ayurvedic Way</title>
    <desc>Hosts Randall Mark and Amrita Sondhi approach cooking and exercise with wellness in mind through Ayurveda, an ancient Indian medicinal practice.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Visionary Gardeners</title>
    <desc>A poet remembers her late husband through the garden they built together; an artist creates sculptural works that honour the history of the land on which they reside.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Annika</title>
    <desc>Annika assembles her team to solve murders in the waters around Glasgow, and their first case looks a lot like a whale hunt gone wrong.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>The widow of one of Doc's patients believes her husband is trying to communicate from the grave; one of Louisa's students falls ill on a class trip.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>A prisoner dies in jail; Greengrass purchases a used police car.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">As Time Goes By</title>
    <desc>Lionel (Geoffrey Palmer) is nervous over his first book signing.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Gardens</title>
    <desc>The NTBG's staff of highly trained scientists, researchers, biologists, and botanists are dedicated to discovering, saving, and studying the world's rarest tropical plants, including those facing extinction.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260626010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>The widow of one of Doc's patients believes her husband is trying to communicate from the grave; one of Louisa's students falls ill on a class trip.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626010000 +0000" stop="20260626013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">As Time Goes By</title>
    <desc>Lionel (Geoffrey Palmer) is nervous over his first book signing.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626013000 +0000" stop="20260626020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ageless Gardens</title>
    <desc>A retiree adapts his home garden to age in place; dementia patients experience a tactile garden; a professional gardener demonstrates his knowledge of plants; a husband and wife decorate birdhouses for their backyard oasis.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626020000 +0000" stop="20260626030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Annika</title>
    <desc>Annika assembles her team to solve murders in the waters around Glasgow, and their first case looks a lot like a whale hunt gone wrong.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626030000 +0000" stop="20260626033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626033000 +0000" stop="20260626040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ayurvedic Way</title>
    <desc>Hosts Randall Mark and Amrita Sondhi approach cooking and exercise with wellness in mind through Ayurveda, an ancient Indian medicinal practice.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626040000 +0000" stop="20260626050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>A prisoner dies in jail; Greengrass purchases a used police car.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626050000 +0000" stop="20260626053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Messages From Spirit with Colette Baron-Reid</title>
    <desc>Mediumship readings with spirits from the other side.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626053000 +0000" stop="20260626060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Balance</title>
    <desc>Stunning videos of nature paired with soothing classical music create inspiration.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626060000 +0000" stop="20260626080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beautiful Little Classics</title>
    <desc>Performances by classical musicians.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626080000 +0000" stop="20260626083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Balance</title>
    <desc>Stunning videos of nature paired with soothing classical music create inspiration.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626083000 +0000" stop="20260626090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Chicken Soup</title>
    <desc>Thought-provoking messages.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
</tv>