<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260710201030 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="FX.us">
    <display-name>US | FX East</display-name>
    <icon src="https://tlgrm.re/images/fx-us.png" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465331">
    <display-name lang="US">Freeform HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470820">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FXX Canada</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470910">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465357">
    <display-name lang="US">FXX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470509">
    <display-name lang="Canada">CTV LIFE CHANNEL</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465241">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465105">
    <display-name lang="US">Fuse HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470299">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Global Toronto</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464897">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Family</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464774">
    <display-name lang="US">FYI Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465167">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Mystery HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="481954">
    <display-name lang="US">Haunt TV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465354">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="492942">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Mystery</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486672">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486853">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486720">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486726">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486821">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV Quiz</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465290">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465002">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime Real Women</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470474">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Much Music HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470737">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Makeful TV SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486755">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">MTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486751">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">More4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465080">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV - Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464825">
    <display-name lang="US">MTVLIVE</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465113">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV2: Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467402">
    <display-name lang="US">WPTZ-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465207">
    <display-name lang="US">Revolt HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467015">
    <display-name lang="US">WNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="468233">
    <display-name lang="US">WCAU-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="469871">
    <display-name lang="US">KNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470330">
    <display-name lang="Canada">ONETV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260710140000 -0400" stop="20260710163000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Incredibles 2</title>
    <desc>Telecommunications guru Winston Deavor enlists Elastigirl to fight crime and make the public fall in love with superheroes once again. That leaves Mr. Incredible with one of his greatest challenges ever -- staying home and taking care of three rambunctious children. As Violet, Dash and Jack-Jack offer him a new set of headaches, a cybercriminal named Screenslaver launches his dastardly plan -- hypnotizing the world through computer screens.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260710163000 -0400" stop="20260710190000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Cars</title>
    <desc>While traveling to California to race The King and Chick Hicks in the Piston Cup Championship, Lightning McQueen falls out of his trailer and winds up in a run-down town called Radiator Springs. He slowly befriends the town's odd residents, including Sally, Doc Hudson and Mater. When it comes time for him to leave, the championship is no longer his top priority.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260710190000 -0400" stop="20260710213000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Cars 2</title>
    <desc>Racecar Lightning McQueen (Owen Wilson) and his tow-truck buddy, Mater (Larry the Cable Guy), have had their share of adventures together but nothing like what they experience when they head overseas for the first-ever World Grand Prix. While Lightning has his eye on the road to the championship, Mater takes a detour to international espionage when he meets British master spy Finn McMissile (Michael Caine) and stunning spy-in-training Holley Shiftwell (Emily Mortimer).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260710213000 -0400" stop="20260711000000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Cars 3</title>
    <desc>Blindsided by a new generation of blazing-fast cars, the legendary Lightning McQueen finds himself pushed out of the sport that he loves. Hoping to get back in the game, he turns to Cruz Ramirez, an eager young technician who has her own plans for winning. With inspiration from the Fabulous Hudson Hornet and a few unexpected turns, No. 95 prepares to compete on Piston Cup Racing's biggest stage.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711000000 -0400" stop="20260711030000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Spider-Man: Across the Spider-Verse</title>
    <desc>After reuniting with Gwen Stacy, Brooklyn's full-time, friendly neighborhood Spider-Man is catapulted across the Multiverse, where he encounters a team of Spider-People charged with protecting its very existence. However, when the heroes clash on how to handle a new threat, Miles finds himself pitted against the other Spiders. He must soon redefine what it means to be a hero so he can save the people he loves most.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711030000 -0400" stop="20260711050000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Garfield Movie</title>
    <desc>Garfield, the Monday-hating, lasagna-loving indoor cat, finds himself on a wild outdoor adventure when his long-lost father draws him into a high-stakes heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711050000 -0400" stop="20260711053000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>CSN Mint: 2026 U.S. Silver Proof Set PF70</title>
    <desc>Celebrate America's 250th with the 2026 U.S. Mint Silver Proof Set, certified perfect NGC PF70 with the official America 250 logo. Includes 10 proof coins, one-year-only designs, fine silver issues and CSN exclusive numbering.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711053000 -0400" stop="20260711060000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Freedom to Leave the House! Inogen Portable Oxygen</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711060000 -0400" stop="20260711063000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711063000 -0400" stop="20260711070000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711070000 -0400" stop="20260711073000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>According to Jim</title>
    <desc>When Jim tries to solve Ruby's separation anxiety, he discovers that he doesn't have the willpower to leave his teary 6-year-old at school.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711073000 -0400" stop="20260711093000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Peter Rabbit 2: The Runaway</title>
    <desc>Bea, Thomas and the rabbits have created a makeshift family, but despite his best efforts, Peter can't seem to shake his mischievous reputation. Venturing out of the garden, Peter finds himself in a world where his mischief is appreciated. However, when his family risks everything to come looking for him, Peter must figure out what kind of bunny he wants to be.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711093000 -0400" stop="20260711113000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Garfield Movie</title>
    <desc>Garfield, the Monday-hating, lasagna-loving indoor cat, finds himself on a wild outdoor adventure when his long-lost father draws him into a high-stakes heist.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260711113000 -0400" stop="20260711143000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Spider-Man: Across the Spider-Verse</title>
    <desc>After reuniting with Gwen Stacy, Brooklyn's full-time, friendly neighborhood Spider-Man is catapulted across the Multiverse, where he encounters a team of Spider-People charged with protecting its very existence. However, when the heroes clash on how to handle a new threat, Miles finds himself pitted against the other Spiders. He must soon redefine what it means to be a hero so he can save the people he loves most.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260710182500 +0000" stop="20260710203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Princess and the Frog</title>
    <desc>Hardworking and ambitious, Tiana dreams of one day opening the finest restaurant in New Orleans. Her dream takes a slight detour when she meets Prince Naveen, who has been turned into an amphibian by evil Dr. Facilier. Mistaking her for a princess and hoping to break the spell, Naveen plants a kiss on poor Tiana, thereby turning her into a frog as well. The pair hop along on an adventure through t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260710203000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mulan</title>
    <desc>Fearful that her ailing father will be drafted into the Chinese military, Mulan takes his spot -- though, as a girl living under a patriarchal regime, she is technically unqualified to serve. She cleverly impersonates a man and goes off to train with fellow recruits. Accompanied by her dragon, Mushu, she uses her smarts to help ward off a Hun invasion, falling in love with a dashing captain along </desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brave</title>
    <desc>Merida (Kelly Macdonald), the impetuous but courageous daughter of Scottish King Fergus (Billy Connolly) and Queen Elinor (Emma Thompson), is a skilled archer who wants to carve out her own path in life. Her defiance of an age-old tradition angers the Highland lords and leads to chaos in the kingdom. Merida seeks help from an eccentric witch (Julie Walters), who grants her an ill-fated wish. Now, </desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711003500 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Moana</title>
    <desc>An adventurous teenager sails out on a daring mission to save her people. During her journey, Moana meets the once-mighty demigod Maui, who guides her in her quest to become a master way-finder. Together they sail across the open ocean on an action-packed voyage, encountering enormous monsters and impossible odds. Along the way, Moana fulfills the ancient quest of her ancestors and discovers the o</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Meet ordinary people who have experienced the extraordinary power of prayer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Million Dollar Nannies</title>
    <desc>A group of young celebrity nannies are off to Ibiza to create a top agency for the world's elite.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711053000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>When Jim gets financially rewarded for doing charity work, Cheryl tells him that he should return the money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2026 Silver Eagle is here &amp; it is a once-in-a-lifetime coin!</title>
    <desc>Join your hosts Kevin Cash &amp; Cory Cady as we discuss the 250th Anniversary of America with the official "America 250" logo on a Silver American Eagle label; we are locking in orders for this iconic release, but coins are limited! Don't miss out!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711063000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Have Thinning Hair? Keranique Can Help Regrow Beautiful, Thicker Hair!</title>
    <desc>If you have thinning hair or hair loss, Keranique can help regrow thicker, longer and fuller hair. Keranique is the number 1 hair regrowth system for women. Regain your confidence with beautiful, thicker and fuller hair in just 3 easy steps!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Meet ordinary people who have experienced the extraordinary power of prayer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">POOF! Bye Bye Under Eye Bags!</title>
    <desc>Plexaderm helps reduce Under Eye Bags, Dark Circles, and Wrinkles in just 10 minutes!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSN Mint - America 250 Silver Eagles</title>
    <desc>Join CSN Mint for two patriotic 1776-2026 Silver Eagle overstrikes featuring the American Flag Privy and Constitution Privy. Designed by Daniel Carr, struck using a retired Denver Mint press, and certified perfect MS70.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711103000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holes</title>
    <desc>A boy and his friends question the motives of a woman (Sigourney Weaver) who forces them to dig holes at a detention camp.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711133000 +0000" stop="20260711164500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl</title>
    <desc>Capt. Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp) arrives at Port Royal in the Caribbean without a ship or crew. His timing is inopportune, however, because later that evening the town is besieged by a pirate ship. The pirates kidnap the governor's daughter, Elizabeth (Keira Knightley), who's in possession of a valuable coin that is linked to a curse that has transformed the pirates into the undead. A gallant blac</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711164500 +0000" stop="20260711200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pirates of the Caribbean: Dead Man's Chest</title>
    <desc>When ghostly pirate Davy Jones comes to collect a blood debt, Capt. Jack Sparrow must find a way to avoid his fate lest his soul be damned for all time. Nevertheless, the wily ghost manages to interrupt the wedding plans of Jack's friends Will Turner and Elizabeth Swann.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711200000 +0000" stop="20260711234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pirates of the Caribbean: At World's End</title>
    <desc>Will Turner (Orlando Bloom) and Elizabeth Swann (Keira Knightley) join forces with Capt. Barbossa (Geoffrey Rush) to free Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp) from Davy Jones' locker. Meanwhile, the crew of the Flying Dutchman ghost ship wreaks havoc on the Seven Seas. The friends must navigate dangerous waters to confront Chinese pirate Sao Feng (Chow Yun-Fat) and, ultimately, they must choose sides in a b</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260711234500 +0000" stop="20260712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides</title>
    <desc>The checkered past of Capt. Jack Sparrow (Johnny Depp) catches up to him when he encounters Angelica (Penélope Cruz), a beautiful pirate that Jack once loved then left. Angelica forces him to accompany her to the Queen Anne's Revenge, the ship of the notorious Blackbeard (Ian McShane). Accompanied by a zombie crew, the trio sets sail to find the legendary Fountain of Youth. However, Jack's rival, </desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay and Gloria can't agree on what kind of anniversary gifts they want to exchange; the Dunphys go with Alex to Caltech for her college tour; Mitch, Cam and Lily take a new family portrait.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260710203000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Phil must make creative edits in Cam and Mitch's wedding video when footage reveals that Phil is responsible for a terrible cold that has plagued the family; Gloria and Jay try to help Manny cope with stress in different ways.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>The Dunphys stay in a cramped hotel room while the house is treated for mold; Gloria feels protective when Manny starts dating an older girl; Cameron wants to maintain his team's winning streak but fears Mitchell is a jinx.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Phil and Claire panic when an obnoxious couple looks at the house for sale next door; Jay learns Manny's girlfriend is the granddaughter of a business rival -- after forbidding Manny to see her; Cam and Mitch are scared of Lily's teacher (Tyne Daly).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>Goodwin is tasked with enforcing difficult cuts to hospital personnel; Charles' daughter is hospitalized after a car accident; a transplant patient makes a life-changing decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide puts his job on the line to help out one of their own; Kidd navigates Natalie's complicated relationship with her sister; Herrmann prepares to take the Chief test.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Still reeling from the death of informant Anna, Voight faces a new threat as he tries to keep the neighborhood clean; new wrinkles develop in the Upton, Halstead and Voight dynamic; the team gets a new chief.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Things go awry as the gang travels to Atlantic City for a charity benefit; Frank, Dee and Mac try to survive in the woods; Dennis and Charlie hitch a ride to the city and have the night of their lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang tries to figure out who the father of Dee's baby is by throwing a house party for all her former flings.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang attempts an image makeover to uncover the heart of gold that exists deep inside Frank's prostitute fiancée.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711023000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Dee and Dennis take the gang to their favorite childhood vacation spot; Mac, Frank and Charlie have the nights of their lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Things go awry as the gang travels to Atlantic City for a charity benefit; Frank, Dee and Mac try to survive in the woods; Dennis and Charlie hitch a ride to the city and have the night of their lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711033000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang tries to figure out who the father of Dee's baby is by throwing a house party for all her former flings.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang attempts an image makeover to uncover the heart of gold that exists deep inside Frank's prostitute fiancée.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711043000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Dee and Dennis take the gang to their favorite childhood vacation spot; Mac, Frank and Charlie have the nights of their lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Things go awry as the gang travels to Atlantic City for a charity benefit; Frank, Dee and Mac try to survive in the woods; Dennis and Charlie hitch a ride to the city and have the night of their lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711053000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang tries to figure out who the father of Dee's baby is by throwing a house party for all her former flings.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake launches a series of competitions to keep the precinct busy while they wait for the Serbian president's motorcade to arrive; Terry and Holt take on a new drug task force.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711063000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake challenges Capt. Holt that he can steal his watch; Gina is upset about getting kicked off her dance team; Terry confronts Gina about her attitude.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Holt and Jake need to root out a mole in the precinct before Deputy Chief Wuntch hears about it; Terry and Rosa go to a silent disco while searching for new leads for their drug task force.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711073000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 Rock</title>
    <desc>When Jack persuades Liz to go to Florida with him, they make a shocking discovery about his mother; Jenna and Tracy assume responsibility for the show in Liz's absence, resulting in disaster for Kenneth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake discovers the woman he hit it off with at the bar is the lawyer representing a perp he's trying to put in jail; Gina and Charles try to leave their relationship in the past.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake and Charles join forces with the lead investigator at the U.S. Postal Service to catch a drug dealer; the team helps Amy quit smoking.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A scientist (George Grizzard) creates a near-perfect mechanical man endowed with all the qualities he feels he is lacking.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>A professional pet sitter is killed by a tree while looking after a tiny dog; Hudson and Rex take the case and discover everything from blackmail to a foot fetish; Charlie needs Sarah's help.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie learns about a string of recent murders at his aunt's retirement home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A runaway bride calls the SVU for help on the day of her wedding; Rollins pitches in on her day off.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A suspect arrested for murder escapes police custody after months of waiting for his day in court; as a hostage situation erupts, Shaw must re-examine his conduct as the arresting officer; Price questions his faith in the justice system.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A runaway bride calls the SVU for help on the day of her wedding; Rollins pitches in on her day off.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a homeless migrant is murdered, evidence leads Cosgrove and Shaw to a mysterious cover-up at a construction site; Price and Maroun push a key witness to testify, knowing that speaking out could lead to legal consequences.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Agent Sykes struggles to cope on the anniversary of her sister's disappearance; Benson suspects a cold case from Manhattan could help her get closure.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires discover the mall.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nandor and Laszlo have a night out with Sean and his friends; Nadja discovers the source of her bad luck.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711020500 +0000" stop="20260711024000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires help Sean host a Pride parade; Nadja helps her doll achieve a long-held dream.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711024000 +0000" stop="20260711031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Colin runs for office; Nandor makes a new friend; Nadja reconnects with her roots.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711031500 +0000" stop="20260711034500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Coverage of a local water main break brings unwanted attention to the vampires.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711034500 +0000" stop="20260711042000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>When Guillermo is injured, Nadja takes him to urgent care; Colin has trouble feeding.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711042000 +0000" stop="20260711045000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nadja gives back to her community; Laszlo's experiments have some unexpected results.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711045000 +0000" stop="20260711052500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>A roast held in Laszlo's honor reveals dark secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711052500 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The housemates are invited for a weekend away at the home of a mysterious, illustrious vampire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires search for a missing Guillermo.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711063500 +0000" stop="20260711070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires discover the mall.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711070500 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>A stock market guru's fortune is stolen, setting Charlie and Rex on the trail of a very surprising thief...</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a truck transporting liquid explosive is hijacked by criminals, Charlie and Rex find themselves in a race against time to prevent the case from blowing sky-high.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Major Crimes investigates a dark web marketplace, Charlie and Rex protect a witness in their home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After an elite hockey prospect is found dead, Charlie and Jesse disagree over the prime suspect in the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>The Major Crimes team is forced to turn against Jesse when he becomes the prime suspect in a bank robbery.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a raw diamond is found at the crime scene of a murder, Major Crimes sets up a stakeout to take down the suspected gem smugglers; an undisclosed team connection threatens to derail the investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Major Crimes investigates a dark web marketplace, Charlie and Rex protect a witness in their home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After an elite hockey prospect is found dead, Charlie and Jesse disagree over the prime suspect in the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>The Major Crimes team is forced to turn against Jesse when he becomes the prime suspect in a bank robbery.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a raw diamond is found at the crime scene of a murder, Major Crimes sets up a stakeout to take down the suspected gem smugglers; an undisclosed team connection threatens to derail the investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>After a student accuses her of cheating on a test, Tina needs to get back to school to clear her name, but a snowstorm traps her and her family at home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260710203000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>A man trying to row from New Zealand to Nova Scotia visits the restaurant to have a burger, and it changes everything.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When Louise is accused of a theft at school, Linda uses her position as school office volunteer to try to solve the case from the inside.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When the coolest teens she's ever seen start coming into the restaurant, Tina decides she needs to be just like them; Gene and Louise get into a battle of wills over stinky socks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Louise brings Tina along on a mission to find the perfect item for her last-ever show-and-tell; Teddy goes overboard trying to impress a date at the restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Mr. Fischoeder challenges Bob to successfully prank him on April Fool's Day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>A gallery owner admires Chris' painting and invites the Griffins to New York; Peter envies an old classmate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260710233000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After Meg appears on a talk show, the network executives turn the Griffins' stupefying life into a reality series.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After Stewie is banished from his grandparents' house, Brian takes a trip to retrieve the terrible tyke.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711003000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter infiltrates the high school after it is gripped by a toad-licking craze. Guest voice: Gregg Allman.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Stewie develops a crush on a girl at his day-care center, while newly liberated Lois becomes a flight attendant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter becomes embroiled in the affairs of a mob family after he takes a mobster's nephew to the movies.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After undergoing liposuction, a newly lean and handsome Peter goes back for more plastic surgery. Voices of Seth MacFarlane, Alex Borstein, Seth Green and Mila Kunis.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711023000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>While fighting city hall, Peter declares his property an independent nation-state and makes himself president.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After Meg writes her first article for the school newspaper, Peter replaces her piece with one of his own.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711033000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter and his friends go on a drinking binge to find a winning ticket in a bottle; Lois works Ling too hard for a competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>After a devastating spaceship crash, the Professor attempts to resuscitate the crew with his birth machine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711043000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Leela and Zapp Brannigan find themselves stranded on an Eden-like planet.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Fry gets carried away with social media and posts an embarrassing video of Leela online.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711053000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Bender leads a campaign to legalize robosexual marriage between humans and robots.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Hank and Bobby declare a state of emergency to protect the house from disasters after Hank forgets to mail the insurance payment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711063000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>The football team forfeits a big game due to poor field maintenance, but Hank resolves to keep the booster club from replacing the field keeper.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Luanne takes a second job as a member of a roller-derby team to get out of credit-card debt.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711073000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>John Redcorn decides to build a casino to create a venue for his band to play, then finds out Texas does not allow gaming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathroom Makeover</title>
    <desc>Transform your bath affordably in just one day!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1916 Gold Rarity</title>
    <desc>Own the first-ever Gold issue of the legendary 1916 Mercury Dime today. This special 2026 Gold Mercury Dime comes with a bonus Silver Medal, both dated 1916 in tribute to the classic coin and graded Perfect 70 condition in exclusive holders!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>Each remaining contestant must create a brunch dish that incorporates both sweet and savory elements in just 45 minutes; one aspiring chef goes home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Frank intervenes when diplomatic immunity complicates a child abuse case; a robbery takes place while Eddie and Jamie are on a double date, and they are forced to take action.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monk</title>
    <desc>Monk gives new meaning to the phrase "don't drink the water" when he travels to Mexico to probe the mysterious death of a skydiver who drowned in midair.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Ginny Buckley helps a couple find a new countryside home in Northamptonshire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef</title>
    <desc>Each contestant must let their culture shine by creating a unique take on eggs Benedict; a second immunity pin is on the line; one team is saddled with a major disadvantage that could cost them everything.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef UK: The Professionals</title>
    <desc>The hunt for a young chef who wants to make it to the top of the culinary world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Steve Brown meets a pair of cycling fans on the hunt for a new home in the Peak District.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>Forty home cooks from across the country compete for a spot in the Top 14.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Frank intervenes when diplomatic immunity complicates a child abuse case; a robbery takes place while Eddie and Jamie are on a double date, and they are forced to take action.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monk</title>
    <desc>Monk gives new meaning to the phrase "don't drink the water" when he travels to Mexico to probe the mysterious death of a skydiver who drowned in midair.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>Each remaining contestant must create a brunch dish that incorporates both sweet and savory elements in just 45 minutes; one aspiring chef goes home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie shows how to make sticky pan-fried scallops with sweet chili rice, dressed greens and quick brownies.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711073000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Preparing cheat's pizza; three salads; and squashed cherries and vanilla mascarpone cream.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>Mary's zucchini lasagna; Nigerian cuisine; summer outfit recipes; reality dating show "Rezervations for Two"; Mary's sizzling summer reads.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Unlock the potential of the indispensable, but intimidating, cast iron pan with versatile recipes and tips to keep it pristine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Chef Spencer Watts cooks up a pizza feast that's quick and affordable.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All's Fair in Love &amp; Mahjong</title>
    <desc>A school nurse turns her love of the game Mahjong into a new path, inspired by a jovial contractor fixing up her home, who encourages her to take a chance on the future.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary believes that sandwich possibilities are endless; never get bored with her stacked recipe lineup, like the Tuna Niçoise sandwich; a French Riviera salad staple thrown onto crusty ciabatta; the classic charcuterie board on a bun.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The winner of the mystery box and the top three invention test contestants compete against each other for the chance at immunity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711133000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>In the MasterChef house, the contestants get a surprise message informing them of the upcoming group challenge and where they'll need to travel to.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The contestants' adventure continues as they arrive at their next destination; the ensuing challenge will see the previous two losing teams face elimination.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711163000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The contestants are in for a huge surprise when the judges reveal that it's survival week; the remaining competitors must cook for their lives every day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>In the midst of survival week, the contestants are surprised to discover that another elimination is imminent with the next challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711190000 +0000" stop="20260711200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>Survival week's remaining contestants learn about decision-making under pressure when they must decide which is more important to them, ingredients or time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711200000 +0000" stop="20260711210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The contestants go off site to Melbourne's Panama Dining Room where they must cook a main course and dessert for 25 people.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260711210000 +0000" stop="20260711230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>Amateur cooks from around Australia compete in a series of unique challenges judged by culinary experts and world-famous chefs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Blue Ridge Mountain Christmas</title>
    <desc>Hotel manager Willow returns to her stunning Virginia hometown to help her sister plan a Christmas wedding at the inn her family once owned.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Long Lost Christmas</title>
    <desc>Hayley is an interior designer who plans to surprise her recently widowed mother with the perfect holiday present -- the extended family she knows her mom yearns for.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">You, Me &amp; the Christmas Trees</title>
    <desc>An arborist falls in love with a farmer as she tries to save his trees before the town tree lighting.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Santa Class</title>
    <desc>Kate North, the owner of a struggling Santa School, and her instructor, Dan, must help an amnesia-stricken Santa Claus regain his memories to save Christmas and hopefully her school as well.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche encounters a former schoolmate who is the only man to ever turn her down.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711043000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose competes for St. Olaf's Woman of the Year honors, with a little help of Blanche and Dorothy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Sophia cries foul after being hit with a fly ball at the stadium; Stan tries to sue the ballpark.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711053000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche's tattered jacket, containing a winning lottery ticket, ends up in charity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche encounters a former schoolmate who is the only man to ever turn her down.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711063000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose competes for St. Olaf's Woman of the Year honors, with a little help of Blanche and Dorothy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Sophia cries foul after being hit with a fly ball at the stadium; Stan tries to sue the ballpark.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711073000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche's tattered jacket, containing a winning lottery ticket, ends up in charity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Barbra Jean shows off her new sleek figure and staunch dedication to the gym, which Brock fears is about spending time with her male trainer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Houston's premier real estate agent contacts Reba and Van for a meeting, exciting Reba but concerning Van that he will be her assistant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Van builds a new home office in the garage so he and Reba can be more productive, but Reba has a difficult time juggling family and the additional workload.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Kyra moves back in with Reba, who catches her drinking; Brock and Barbra Jean confess that they let Kyra have an occasional beer in their house.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Royal Christmas Crush</title>
    <desc>Ava accepts the opportunity of a lifetime to work at the Royal Ice Hotel, which leads to a surprise whirlwind romance with the most important guest of all, the prince himself.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Little Christmas Charm</title>
    <desc>A jewelry designer teams up with an investigative reporter to find the owner of a charm bracelet before Christmas Eve.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Christmas Detour</title>
    <desc>Two travelers become linked when a snowstorm grounds their flight in Buffalo. Paige desperately needs to find a way to New York City to meet her fiancé's parents, and it's up to Dylan, a fellow passenger and a guy she can't stand, to get her there.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas at the Plaza</title>
    <desc>When historian Jessica is hired to create the Plaza's Christmas display, she finds more than facts while teaming up with handsome decorator Nick to bring the display to life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Bramble House Christmas</title>
    <desc>While settling his father's estate, a man becomes suspicious as to why the man left his nurse a large sum of money after knowing her for less than two months before he died.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711200000 +0000" stop="20260711220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Christmas Carousel</title>
    <desc>Lila is hired by the royal family of Ancadia to repair a carousel and must work with the prince to complete it by Christmas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260711220000 +0000" stop="20260712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Miracle in Bethlehem, PA</title>
    <desc>A single woman with a newly adopted baby gets stuck in Bethlehem, Pa. With no room at the inn, she's forced to stay with a stranger who turns out to be the miracle she has needed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260712000000 +0000" stop="20260713000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">O Little Christmas Market</title>
    <desc>An artist fights to save her town's beloved Christmas market from a developer, but a budding romance with the architect tied to the deal may help bring about a Christmas miracle.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Chick eats seed out of man's mouth; Riley the dog gets ice from ice machine; chipmunk digging in coffee can for nut.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260710203000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>A man is hit by a ball at the batting cage; a football player knocks down a camera; a dog knocks over boy playing tee ball; hockey goalie cat.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Keirsten Lacie uncovers her girlfriend spending too much time with her stepsister.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Sayuri Zoldyck learns the truth about her boyfriend's visits to the strip club.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Brittany wants to find out why her boyfriend, Taylor, has become distant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Kesha wants to find out what's going on with Duke.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diddy: Monster's Fall</title>
    <desc>A look into the downfall of the disgraced hip-hop mogul, Sean "Diddy" Combs, who could no longer buy his way out of trouble, when a grand jury indicted Combs on a racketeering conspiracy. It included sex trafficking, forced labor and bribery.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tupac &amp; Biggie: Worlds Collide</title>
    <desc>Presenting the stories of rappers and rivals Tupac Shakur and Biggie Smalls.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stevie Nicks: Wild at Heart</title>
    <desc>For decades, Stevie Nicks has fronted one of the most successful bands in history, resurrecting them from the ashes; even with the trials and tribulations of being a member of Fleetwood Mac, Stevie has remained a role model.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>Charlamagne tha God joins WeezyWTF in interviewing a model who makes her entire living with her feet; Weezy dips her toes into the foot modeling world by shedding her shoes for Mr. Footagrapher.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711033000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>WeezyWTF heads back to school with her mom to learn the secrets of a successful phone sex business; a financial dominatrix teaches how she makes money from submissives.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Student Sex Workers</title>
    <desc>Jasmine is a paramedic science student worried that she is about to get kicked off her course because of her work as an exotic dancer, and webcammer; Carly Ray carried on with sex work after graduation and is now an award-winning porn star.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Student Sex Workers</title>
    <desc>Ella has been bullied out of her university after her peers discovered she was an award-winning porn star, and Akonne is a sports science student and a stripper who doesn't consider himself to be a sex worker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Vogue Williams: Is Monogamy Dead?</title>
    <desc>As she enters into her second marriage, television personality Vogue Williams explores the concept of monogamy in society and how it has changed over the years.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Our Transgender Love Story</title>
    <desc>"Next Top Model" host Joey Mead King is no stranger to the media, but her life was changed forever when her husband went public as transgender.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Allie falls for a handsome pilot who lives in her building. But when he disappears Allie is left heartbroken until he shows up again. Dorian goes on a date with a girl who has a Jekyll and Hyde-like personality.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>In 1995, Tanya was on a double date driving through the mountains; the boys hunt down an elk and leave the girls stranded in the Utah wilderness; 19-year-old Sam dates a much older army veteran with a dark past and an insatiable sexual appetite.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Meca Jackson worries that his girlfriend is slipping away right before his eyes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Alex Montoya discovers her girlfriend models with and without her clothes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elvis: Death of the King</title>
    <desc>Elvis Presley's charisma and musical talent made him the king of rock, but his rock star lifestyle led to a downfall that was as swift as his rise.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Snoop Dogg: Uncaged</title>
    <desc>The story and legacy of Snoop Dogg; from the 1990s hip-hop scene to his status as a pop culture icon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diana Ross: Supreme Sensation</title>
    <desc>From being the queen of Motown to taking on the world stage, Diana Ross has sold over 100 million records worldwide; her career spans decades, attracting generation after generation of loyal fans.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BKB 55: Carnage in Cardiff</title>
    <desc>Lee Selby vs. Antonio Rizzo; Dan Podmore vs. Jarome Hatch. From Vindico Arena in Cardiff Wales, U.K.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711170000 +0000" stop="20260711173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Rayne wants to find out where Abel is spending his time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711173000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Amy wants to know why Jonathan is behaving childishly.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Dog eating wedding cake; 80 years, 80 candles; Grandpa drops cake on lap.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>Drama revolves around three families in Genoa City.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 5</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 6</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goldbergs</title>
    <desc>With everyone living back at home, the house is full of Goldberg chaos; pregnant Erica enlists Beverly's help in clearing things out for the baby; Adam and Barry are forced to share a bedroom to make room for the baby nursery.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260710233000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Brother</title>
    <desc>Celebrity panelist Jerry O'Connell along with winners Taylor Hale and Derrick Levasseur offer never-before-seen broadcast footage from the house, exclusive interviews, surprise guest appearances and unprecedented behind-the-scenes access; former houseguests share firsthand insight and expertise as they analyze gameplay, assess the competition and give their insider's perspective.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Border Security: America's Front Line</title>
    <desc>A traveler headed to Vegas rolls the dice on getting into the US for a vacation; a family emigrating from Vietnam hope their enthusiasm translates; at JFK cargo facility, boxes of pancake mix fall flat.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Border Security: America's Front Line</title>
    <desc>A man from Mexico is questioned when it is indicated his vacation plans may include a work component; at JFK cargo facility a shipment of live moth pupas is put under the microscope; in San Francisco, an angry traveler points a finger at CBP.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>On July 30, 1985, a then eight-year-old Nicole Morin reportedly left her top-floor apartment on The West Mall in Etobicoke to meet a friend for a swim; she was never seen again; Nicole's disappearance marks a large and extensive search in Toronto; now, police are offering a new $50,000 reward for anyone with information about her disappearance.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 11</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711033500 +0000" stop="20260711040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711040500 +0000" stop="20260711050500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>In the fall of 2016, a football player went out with his teammates to celebrate an important win when tragedy struck; witnesses explain what they saw that fateful night and how Hicks was blindsided.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711050500 +0000" stop="20260711053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711053500 +0000" stop="20260711063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>Three chefs hit the grills running in the Wildfire Round as they fight to make it past the first elimination; the competition gets a bit cheeky in the Crossfire Round, and the judges are treated to an open-fire East Coast feast in the final round.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711063500 +0000" stop="20260711073500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masters of Flip</title>
    <desc>With the color pink as her inspiration, Kortney tries to balance masculine and feminine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711073500 +0000" stop="20260711083500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Brother Canada</title>
    <desc>Fifteen people share an isolated home and try to avoid being evicted by their housemates.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711083500 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SIGN OFF</title>
    <desc>Sign off.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rust Valley Restorers</title>
    <desc>Fantasies turn to nightmares when Connor enlists Rust Bros on a personal build; Avery goes over budget on his dream truck; James tackles a project from his past.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>The chefs are faced with the Wildfire Round, the Crossfire Round, and treat the judges to some southern hospitality in the Feast of Fire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fish'n Canada</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the best fishing spots in Canada.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Worst to First</title>
    <desc>Empty nesters Shelley and Mike are frustrated with the rising cost of homes in their desired neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711133000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fish TV</title>
    <desc>Hosts Leo Stakos, Ron James and Jeff Chisholm set their sights on great fishing destinations.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Employment Law Show</title>
    <desc>Host Lior Samfiru answers questions about employment rights and tackles the most important facets of employment law that are often overlooked by both employer and employee.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Christmas Ornament</title>
    <desc>Kathy plans to avoid any holiday traditions that bring back memories of her late husband until she receives an ornament from a handsome shop owner. To move on from her loss, Kathy works for a balance between her memories and finding a future.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Christmas Club</title>
    <desc>Two busy strangers meet when they help an elderly woman find her lost Christmas savings. Thanks to fate and Christmas magic, they also find something they were both missing: true love.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chateau Christmas</title>
    <desc>A world-renowned pianist rediscovers her passion for music after reuniting with her ex during the holidays.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>The women of Walnut Grove revolt when the men won't alter a law giving property to husbands only.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Nellie's imminent motherhood causes a rift between the in-laws over the religious upbringing of the child.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura and Almanzo make the mistake of agreeing to care for his nephews while their parents are on vacation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Amy and Ty spend the night in the supposedly haunted Hanley barn, trying to get to the bottom of a mystery.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Tim and Jack relive their glory days; Amy wonders if Ty is revisiting his past when he and Kit deal with her pregnant mare.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>Jonathan and Mark help a black family relocate to an exclusive neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>Jonathan, dressed as a werewolf, comes to the rescue when drunken teenagers harass a young trick-or-treater.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>The women of Walnut Grove revolt when the men won't alter a law giving property to husbands only.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Nellie's imminent motherhood causes a rift between the in-laws over the religious upbringing of the child.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura and Almanzo make the mistake of agreeing to care for his nephews while their parents are on vacation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Joe Kagan works up the courage to court Hester Sue, and learns she plans to marry an undertaker (Mel Stewart).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mrs. Oleson's constant interference prompts Laura to quit as Walnut Grove's teacher.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wedding Bells</title>
    <desc>When asked to be best man and maid of honor at a friend's wedding, two commitment-phobic professionals never expect that they're about to find romance of their own.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love, Again</title>
    <desc>A couple on the verge of a divorce must put aside their differences while planning their daughter's wedding, only to find that their own marriage may be worth saving after all.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sweeter Side of Life</title>
    <desc>When her husband dumps her for her acupuncturist, pampered housewife Desiree (Kathryn Morris) discovers there is more to life than money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711200000 +0000" stop="20260711220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Blossoms</title>
    <desc>A perfume maker wants to finish a formula left behind by her late father. She gets help from an inexperienced botanist with an uncanny sense of smell.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711220000 +0000" stop="20260711230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Witch</title>
    <desc>Cassie, Stephanie and Abigail help Martha throw Claire a baby shower, sparking memories of Cassie's own baby shower.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260711230000 +0000" stop="20260712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Witch</title>
    <desc>Sam is excited to perform surgery on a star basketball player; Joy makes a discovery and decides to revive the Middleton Exchange tradition.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260712000000 +0000" stop="20260713000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Witch</title>
    <desc>Joy's dream sends the three Merriwicks on a search for Phillip Harper, Joy's father.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers visit Perris, Calif.; Jarrod and Brandi bid on a unit filled with power tools and potential; Darrell brings along a fleet of trucks to haul away his anticipated high-volume purchases.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260710203000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The competition is stiff at a high-end storage facility; Dave and Jarrod find a unit containing a classic Jaguar; Brandi and Jarrod engage in a battle of the sexes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Six lockers owned by one tenant go up for auction, spurring wild rumors and excitement; Barry finds a vintage magazine; Jarrod asks Dave for an appraisal.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi and Jarrod argue over a horse head; a locker is littered with antique furniture; Dave makes another strange discovery.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Ivy drags Isaiah to Victorville as punishment for getting Cs on his report card; Kenny wants to furnish his new house, but there are eight reasons standing in his way; not to be cheesy, but Lisa learns a lot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrod and Brandi uncover the ultimate guy's unit among the lockers in Santa Ana, Calif.; Darrell and Dave battle over a valuable antique.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>A locker in Whittier, Calif., features a high payoff; Dave eyes a unit with a stockpile of antiques; Barry's locker may contain old weapons.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260710233000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi is fired up about expanding her brand in San Bernardino; Rene is positive that everyone is out to get him; Dusty tackles a locker dustier than him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders head to Rancho Cucamonga, Calif.; Ivy opens his wallet for the right locker; buyers Darrell and Brandon stay hungry.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711003000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders return to the Los Angeles neighborhood of Mission Hills; Dave begins his day $500 in the hole; Jarrod and Brandi find an ancient item.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers descend on Compton, Calif.; Darrell and Brandon can't get their rappers or their lockers straight; Jarrod and Brandi find a unique suit; Dave Hester finds himself in a tight squeeze; Barry uncovers an antique GPS system.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Barry and Kenny get fired up; Dave Hester makes a find worth cheering over; Brandi is exhausted; Darrell buys his biggest locker ever.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders peruse lockers in Mission Viejo, Calif.; Jarrod and Brandi uncover an unusual piece of art; Barry's accountant tries to keep him in check.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711023000 +0000" stop="20260711030100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>In Placentia, Calif., Jarrod and Brandi make a purchase that tips the scales in their favor; Rene and Casey buy a load of luggage; Darrell scores what he thinks is dental equipment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711030100 +0000" stop="20260711033100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi and Jarrod split up; Ivy hires a new employee to take care of the shop; Darrell finds success again; Rene learns how to strip.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711033100 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Dave Hester returns to the auctions; Darrell tries to prepare Brandon; an injury forces Ivy to change his game; Jarrod and Brandi's unit leads to a wild ride.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders head to Rancho Cucamonga, Calif.; Ivy opens his wallet for the right locker; buyers Darrell and Brandon stay hungry.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711043000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders return to the Los Angeles neighborhood of Mission Hills; Dave begins his day $500 in the hole; Jarrod and Brandi find an ancient item.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers descend on Compton, Calif.; Darrell and Brandon can't get their rappers or their lockers straight; Jarrod and Brandi find a unique suit; Dave Hester finds himself in a tight squeeze; Barry uncovers an antique GPS system.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711053000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Barry and Kenny get fired up; Dave Hester makes a find worth cheering over; Brandi is exhausted; Darrell buys his biggest locker ever.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders peruse lockers in Mission Viejo, Calif.; Jarrod and Brandi uncover an unusual piece of art; Barry's accountant tries to keep him in check.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711063000 +0000" stop="20260711070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>In Placentia, Calif., Jarrod and Brandi make a purchase that tips the scales in their favor; Rene and Casey buy a load of luggage; Darrell scores what he thinks is dental equipment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711070100 +0000" stop="20260711073100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi and Jarrod split up; Ivy hires a new employee to take care of the shop; Darrell finds success again; Rene learns how to strip.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711073100 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Dave Hester returns to the auctions; Darrell tries to prepare Brandon; an injury forces Ivy to change his game; Jarrod and Brandi's unit leads to a wild ride.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers visit Perris, Calif.; Jarrod and Brandi bid on a unit filled with power tools and potential; Darrell brings along a fleet of trucks to haul away his anticipated high-volume purchases.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The competition is stiff at a high-end storage facility; Dave and Jarrod find a unit containing a classic Jaguar; Brandi and Jarrod engage in a battle of the sexes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ruby Herring Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Ruby Herring and Detective Jake Killian investigate a suspicious fatal car accident; they solve the case, then Ruby finds new evidence that casts doubt on their conclusion.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ruby Herring Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When crime reporter Ruby Herring receives clues to a murder that happened five years earlier involving a local psychic, she joins forces with Detective Jake Killian to help crack the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught by Love</title>
    <desc>While on a journey of self-discovery, a resort guest gets swept into an undercover investigation for stolen jewels that turns into an unexpected and adventurous romance.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>An attorney (Patrick McGoohan) asks Jessica to testify for a colleague accused of murder on circumstantial evidence in Quebec.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica visits a convent to see a former sorority sister (Jane Powell) and winds up searching for a nun's killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Murder is on the agenda when top executives and their wives meet at a powerful tycoon's country estate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's cousin Emma MacGill, a colorful dance hall performer, must solve the murder of a wealthy friend.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica helps Sheriff Tupper (Tom Bosley) when his seemingly harmless deputy (Rick Lenz) is accused of murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A bomb kills a TV producer (Ken Swofford) who stole a plot from one of Jessica's books, making Jessica a suspect in his death.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>An attorney (Patrick McGoohan) asks Jessica to testify for a colleague accused of murder on circumstantial evidence in Quebec.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica visits a convent to see a former sorority sister (Jane Powell) and winds up searching for a nun's killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's friend is hit by a car shortly after being notified of her sister's death.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>The descendant of a tribe once inhabiting Cabot Cove has a land grant claiming the town as Indian territory.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Visiting her nephew Grady in New York, Jessica probes a murder involving the family of his college buddy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Amos Tupper must entertain his sister who has left her husband, but complications arise when his brother-in-law is murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jane Mysteries: Inheritance Lost</title>
    <desc>Singer Jane Da Silva inherits a nonprofit detective agency that helps people who aren't able to help themselves. With guidance from her aunt and a detective, Jane takes on the case of a mother's untimely death years earlier.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jane Mysteries: A Deadly Prescription</title>
    <desc>Jane seeks justice for a teenager who's wrongfully imprisoned for murder. She and Detective John work together to prove the teen's innocence and help reunite him with his mother.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jane Mysteries: Murder at Moseby</title>
    <desc>Jane goes undercover at her alma mater to help her college boyfriend solve a crime he may have witnessed years ago during the annual Edgar Allan Poe Festival.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711200000 +0000" stop="20260711220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jane Mysteries: Too Much to Lose</title>
    <desc>When a reporter interviewing Jane seeks help to find a missing colleague, Jane takes on the case. Irene has disappeared after winning a game show which leads Jane to uncover a web of deceit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260711220000 +0000" stop="20260712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Harmony Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Gethsemane and Eamon investigate the death of a sea captain; Tamera Mowry-Housley, Risteard Cooper and Marco Grazzini star.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260712000000 +0000" stop="20260713000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Harmony Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When a ghost hunter show comes to town, it's up to Gethsemane and Eamon to solve the unexpected murder of the host, allowing the brand-new spirit to crossover.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260710195900 +0000" stop="20260710202500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>When toys take on a life of their own, Alix wants nothing more to do with his haunted apartment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260710202500 +0000" stop="20260710205200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Lana encounters a murderous specter when she rents a cabin near a Thai temple of the dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260710205200 +0000" stop="20260710211800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>In his life, he was convinced he was bound for Hell, and in death his presence stalked his old home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260710211800 +0000" stop="20260710214400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Nightmares of rape and abduction.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260710214400 +0000" stop="20260710221100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>A hooded, noose-carrying wraith threatens the lives of Sherri and her sisters.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260710221100 +0000" stop="20260710223700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Ancestors.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260710223700 +0000" stop="20260710230400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Honey's son's life is saved by a ghost.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260710230400 +0000" stop="20260710235800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>An IT technician embarks on an intensive job trial at a large hospital and encounters multiple paranormal phenomena within its labyrinthine halls; a psychiatric nurse experiences frightening otherworldly encounters.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260710235800 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>A woman is confronted by a terrifying female apparition while spending the night in a Scottish castle; an 8-year-old boy has the play date from hell after being visited by the ghosts of a man and child.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711005300 +0000" stop="20260711014700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Help! My House Is Haunted</title>
    <desc>Explores why Diana's former butler, Paul Burrell, thinks that strange smoke and noises in his home can be a sign that the People's Princess is reaching out from beyond the grave; The team's investigation opens the door for two lost souls to reunite.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711014700 +0000" stop="20260711024200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>An IT technician embarks on an intensive job trial at a large hospital and encounters multiple paranormal phenomena within its labyrinthine halls; a psychiatric nurse experiences frightening otherworldly encounters.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711024200 +0000" stop="20260711033600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>A woman is confronted by a terrifying female apparition while spending the night in a Scottish castle; an 8-year-old boy has the play date from hell after being visited by the ghosts of a man and child.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711033600 +0000" stop="20260711043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Help! My House Is Haunted</title>
    <desc>Explores why Diana's former butler, Paul Burrell, thinks that strange smoke and noises in his home can be a sign that the People's Princess is reaching out from beyond the grave; The team's investigation opens the door for two lost souls to reunite.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711043000 +0000" stop="20260711052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>The team investigates paranormal activity linked to an overwhelming number of natural disasters, contacts spirits in a hotel built atop a hospital, explores an eerie B &amp; B, and finds troubled souls in America's most haunted city.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711052000 +0000" stop="20260711061100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Sailing to Bell Island, Newfoundland, where the investigators reach out to the ghosts left by a devastating Nazi U-boat attack during WW II; descending into darkness as the trio reveals a group of ghostly miners trapped underground for 80 years.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711061100 +0000" stop="20260711070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Shiver as paranormal investigators Corine, Leanne, and Kelly tap into the bloody history of one of Ireland's ghostliest spots; find out who, or what, is lurking in the shadows of this terrifying fortress, which could be a portal to the underworld.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711070100 +0000" stop="20260711075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathsheba: Search for Evil</title>
    <desc>Paranormal investigator Erin Goodpipe heads to Harrisville, R.I. to get the bottom of the rumors surrounding the witch, Bathsheba Sherman.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711075500 +0000" stop="20260711085000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathsheba: Search for Evil</title>
    <desc>Paranormal investigator Erin Goodpipe steps inside the Old Arnold Estate to find out who is haunting this Rhode Island property; abandoned by their community and plagued with increased spiritual activity, the Perron family adapts to their home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711085000 +0000" stop="20260711094400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>An IT technician embarks on an intensive job trial at a large hospital and encounters multiple paranormal phenomena within its labyrinthine halls; a psychiatric nurse experiences frightening otherworldly encounters.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711094400 +0000" stop="20260711103900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>A woman is confronted by a terrifying female apparition while spending the night in a Scottish castle; an 8-year-old boy has the play date from hell after being visited by the ghosts of a man and child.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711103900 +0000" stop="20260711113200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Help! My House Is Haunted</title>
    <desc>Explores why Diana's former butler, Paul Burrell, thinks that strange smoke and noises in his home can be a sign that the People's Princess is reaching out from beyond the grave; The team's investigation opens the door for two lost souls to reunite.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711113200 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>When toys take on a life of their own, Alix wants nothing more to do with his haunted apartment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711125100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Following paranormal investigators Leanne Sallenback, Kelly Ireland and Corine Carey as they begin their travels up British Columbia's famed gold rush trail to explore its history and its hauntings.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711125100 +0000" stop="20260711134400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Haunted Gold Rush follows paranormal investigators Leanne Sallenback, Kelly Ireland and Corine Carey as they travel British Columbia's famed gold rush trail and explore its history and its hauntings.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711134400 +0000" stop="20260711143600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Paranormal investigators Corine Carey, Leanne Sallenback and Kelly Ireland travel to San Antonio, Texas to answer the panicked calls of local residents who have experienced paranormal phenomena tied to the Battle of the Alamo in 1836.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260711143600 +0000" stop="20260711152900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>The team finds startling paranormal links to Montreal's boozy, corrupt past in the 1920s and '30s, such as a man whose corpse became an attraction, a woman haunted by ghost children, and a murder victim in a notorious cabaret.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>When a home invasion turns deadly, the team embarks on a race to track down priceless antique artifacts before any more lives are lost; Leroy enlists Hondo's help after an overdose hits close to home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>When control of a university chemistry lab is seized, the team races to thwart a devastating terror attack.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>During a trip to Bangkok to train alongside Thailand's premiere S.W.A.T. team, Hondo and his former military buddy stumble upon a wide-ranging heroin operation with ties to Los Angeles and find themselves on the run from a powerful drug kingpin.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA on ION Pregame Show</title>
    <desc>Studio coverage of the Women's National Basketball Association.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260710233000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Dallas Wings play the Toronto Tempo in a regular-season WNBA basketball game at Bell Center. The visiting Dallas look to guard Paige Bueckers who leads with points and assists while the Tempo look to Marina Mabrey. Dallas leads the season series 1-0.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA On ION Game Break Show</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Chicago plays Los Angeles in a regular-season WNBA basketball game at crpto.com Arena. The visiting Chicago Sky counter with Kamilla Cardoso with points and assists while the Los Angeles Sparks rely on Nneka Ogwumike to lead the home field.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <desc>When an overenthusiastic neighborhood watch group asks Magnum and Higgins to investigate a shady character living on their block, they are shocked to find that they may have inadvertently stumbled upon a serial killer on the loose.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <desc>When a young man in need of immediate emergency surgery goes missing with a bullet lodged in his chest, Ethan asks Magnum and Higgins to find him before it's too late; TC talks to a military recruit who may be enlisting for the wrong reasons.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <desc>When Higgins is abducted, Magnum discovers it's retaliation related to one of his first cases; Magnum, Rick and TC must break out an ex-client from prison in order to save her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711073000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What's Your Injury Case Worth?</title>
    <desc>Legal professionals are standing by 24/7. Call now for a free case evaluation and learn what your injury case may be worth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>NCIS teams with Homeland Security when the murder of a Navy master diver is discovered to be linked to the chatter concerning a foreign attack on the city.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team discovers a mole in the ranks while helping the Department of Homeland Security locate 900 pounds of missing explosives that are a threat to New Orleans.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The team joins forces with several federal agencies to stop a sniper who has been targeting crowded events in the city; FBI Special Agent Tammy Gregorio begins investigating Pride's team.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Pride faces more repercussions from the FBI after he helps a former Navy Intelligence Analyst who is the primary suspect in a multiple homicide case.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Carisi opens a police investigation when his niece reports a classmate for sexual assault; Stone learns there are no perfect witnesses when it comes to sex crimes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A girl's tragic death becomes a criminal case when a surgeon harvests her organs without parental consent.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a student disappears during a school trip to New York, the cops race to find a mysterious masked man; Fin and Stone both get visits from family.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711170000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU must break through military red tape when a soldier is suspected of sexual assault.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The search for an abducted woman and her young daughter leads Lt. Benson to cross paths with an old friend; Stone must make a tough decision on behalf of his sister.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260711190000 +0000" stop="20260711200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Rollins races to rescue a girl being held captive by her father.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When an 8-year-old is found dead on the Appalachian Trail, the team searches the forests for a man targeting children.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team pursues a killer who targets women; Hotchner turns to an FBI cadet for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>After helping a man get parole, Morgan regrets his decision when the man murders someone shortly after being released.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A series of bizarre, ritualistic murders brings the team to Miami; Reid experiences hallucinations and blinding headaches.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team pursues two young lovers on a killing spree; Prentiss receives frightening news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team investigates unusual murders in Los Angeles, and more information about Prentiss' past arises.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU heads to upstate New York to investigate mysterious disappearances; Prentiss receives troubling news about a former colleague.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Reid's ability to connect with an autistic child may prove helpful in finding the boy's missing parents; two former colleagues help Prentiss search for an old adversary.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>After a series of murders, Prentiss becomes suspicious of a former nemesis (Sebastian Roché) and fears for the safety of her team.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Prentiss prepares to confront her nemesis at last; the team asks J.J. to help find Prentiss and capture Doyle.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Mac and Riley head overseas together to prevent a governmental collapse and inadvertently inhale new, deadly microscopic technology.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Mac, Desi and Russ go undercover during a royal Indian wedding to protect a princess whose policies could put her life in danger; Bozer suspects Riley is up to her old hacking ways.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Mac and the team delve into the world of Italian car culture to track down a crime boss; Mac must lean on Desi when he discovers that he's losing the ability to control his hands; Mac and Desi move in together.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Mac and Desi travel with Bozer to his childhood home when his aunt dies in a tragic accident; they soon discover she may have been murdered for trying to expose the city's contaminated water supply.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Mac and Riley go missing and wake up 24 hours later in a cornfield with no memory of how they got there; they must unravel the mystery and find out how to get rid of the nanotrackers in their bodies, no matter the cost.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Special agents for the Department of External Services, Angus "Mac" MacGyver and Jack Dalton, work to recover a missing bioweapon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>MacGyver and the team attempt to rescue Jack's former CIA partner who went missing in Venezuela after finding evidence to take down an international arms dealer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>In Malaysia, MacGyver and the team extract a terrorist group's money man who has intel on an impending attack, but when the man is shot, MacGyver must keep him alive in order to learn the terrorists' plans.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Booth and Brennan go undercover at an Old West-style shooting competition; Angela and Hodgins talk about the future; Cam and Sebastian grow closer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a police officer's murder; the team decides what is important to their futures.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Hodgins navigates life in a wheelchair; when a public defender is murdered, several of her previous clients had motives to kill her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711170000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the death of a men's rights organization founder who may have been the victim of domestic abuse; Brennan loses her temper during an interrogation; Angela and the team struggle with Hodgins' bitterness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team hunts for a serial killer who appears to have sinister interactions with the victims' bodies before dumping them; Booth and Aubrey consult a behavioral analyst to help find clues to the killer's identity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711190000 +0000" stop="20260711200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>A suspect in the murder of a convicted felon who had been released to a halfway house has ties to Booth; Brennan testifies at an FBI hearing about her assault of an unarmed suspect from a previous case.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711200000 +0000" stop="20260711210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the death of a private investigator found frozen after being dumped in the Potomac; Aubrey finds shocking information connected to his father's whereabouts.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260711210000 +0000" stop="20260711220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the death of an a cappella singer whose body was found in a lab rat; Hodgins applies for an experimental nerve regeneration study; Booth tries to plan a summer trip with Parker; a new intern joins the lab.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Hope and Ruby inform Tyrone that they have traced his father, George follows Christina to a covert assignation with a mystery man, and Abi hires Adam in her fight against Idris.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News at Ten</title>
    <desc>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260710214500 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jack Reacher</title>
    <desc>Mystery action thriller film starring Tom Cruise and Rosamund Pike, 2012. When five people are gunned down by a sniper, only one man has the skills to take the true criminals out.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711000500 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shop on TV</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711034500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting action from the world of All Elite Wrestling - the roster features world-class talent including Jon Moxley, MJF, Ricochet and Adam Page.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711034500 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711071000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nations Champ Rugby: N.Z. v Italy</title>
    <desc>New Zealand entertain Italy in Wellington as the second round of matches in the inaugural Nations Championship get under way.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711071000 +0000" stop="20260711094000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nations Champ Rugby: Aus. v France</title>
    <desc>It's round two of the Nations Championship and Six Nations Champions France travel to Brisbane to take on Joe Schmidt's Australia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711094000 +0000" stop="20260711122000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nations Champ Rugby: Japan v Ire.</title>
    <desc>Ugo Monye is joined by Rory Best and Stuart Lancaster as Eddie Jones' Japan take on Ireland, with the match taking place in Newcastle, Australia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711122000 +0000" stop="20260711152000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nations Champ Rugby: Fiji v Eng.</title>
    <desc>Jill Douglas presents live coverage as England take on Fiji at Hill Dickinson Stadium in Liverpool in their second game of the inaugural Nations Championship.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711152000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nations Champ Rugby: S.A. v Scot.</title>
    <desc>It's a daunting task for Scotland as they face World Champions South Africa in Pretoria in their second match in the Nations Championship. Lauren Salter presents.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711181000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Evening News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711181000 +0000" stop="20260711181500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711181500 +0000" stop="20260711184000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It'll Be Alright on the Night</title>
    <desc>Tom Allen celebrates funny cock-ups from the world of entertainment featuring Idris Elba, Paul Rudd, Ant and Dec, Susanna Reid, Alan Carr and many more of our favourite stars.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711184000 +0000" stop="20260711193500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Wants to Be a Millionaire</title>
    <desc>Celebrity Special. A line-up of brave famous faces - including Celebrity Traitor Joe Marler and comedian Katherine Ryan - face the quiz hosted by Jeremy Clarkson.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711193500 +0000" stop="20260711194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Box Sneak Peek</title>
    <desc>Sneak peek of a brand new game show hosted by Gary Lineker in which celebrity contestants are plunged into the unknown as they visit mystery locations while enclosed in a box.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260711194500 +0000" stop="20260712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIFA WC2026: Norway v England</title>
    <desc>Live coverage as England face Norway in the 2026 FIFA World Cup Quarter-Final in Miami. Mark Pougatch is joined in the New York studio by Roy Keane, Gary Neville and Ian Wright.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ice Road Truckers: Deadliest Roads</title>
    <desc>Death is a Blind Corner Away: When the mountain begins to crumble underfoot, Lisa Kelly is in grave danger with an oversized nine-ton load in tow.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting action from the world of All Elite Wrestling - the roster features world-class talent including Jon Moxley, MJF, Ricochet and Adam Page.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260710230500 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the Ring</title>
    <desc>Documentary series set in the world of professional wrestling. A mythical love story between icons Randy Savage and Miss Elizabeth ends with tragic results.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Minder</title>
    <desc>And Sometimes Very Low: Drama series. The chips are down for Arthur's friend Maurice when the professional gambler is barred from casinos and mugged of all his winnings.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two and a Half Men</title>
    <desc>American sitcom. When Alan and Judith meet a teacher of Jake's to discuss his attitude, Alan loses interest in Kandi and turns toward his son's tutor instead.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two and a Half Men</title>
    <desc>American sitcom about a well-off bachelor. Charlie and Alan help Jake prepare when he is invited to a party that girls will also be attending.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711023000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorsport Mundial</title>
    <desc>This programme brings you up to date with the latest action from the world of motorsport and features race coverage, insights, and behind-the-scenes footage from the best series.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World of Sport</title>
    <desc>The Good, the Bad and the Ugly: Featuring George Best, Zaire at the World Cup, and a few funny own goals.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711052000 +0000" stop="20260711062000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>Luton Town and QPR meet in a Second Division top-of-the-table clash alongside action from Southampton against Nottingham Forest and Everton taking on Middlesbrough.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711062000 +0000" stop="20260711072000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>Featuring a Second Division London derby between Geoff Hurst's Chelsea and Charlton Athletic from November 1979, plus Norwich City v Southampton and Aston Villa v Stoke City.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711072000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Champions</title>
    <desc>Fantasy espionage series. The team is assigned the difficult task of establishing why three Interpol agents have apparently killed themselves.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Racing: The Opening Show</title>
    <desc>Megan Nicholls, Matt Chapman and the team are at Newmarket ahead of July Cup day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>Brian Moore introduces football highlights from April 1972 as Chelsea entertained Crystal Palace at Stamford Bridge and title-chasing Liverpool took on Coventry City.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711103000 +0000" stop="20260711105000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World of Sport</title>
    <desc>TV Firsts: Richard Henwood takes a look back at some television sporting firsts that include a 14-year-old Ronnie O'Sullivan.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711105000 +0000" stop="20260711111500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Made in Britain</title>
    <desc>See how frozen peas get from field to freezer in a few hours, then learn about the labour of love that goes into creating beautiful handmade marbles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711111500 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Return of Sherlock Holmes</title>
    <desc>Holmes is called to a manor house to investigate the murder of a country lord with a poker and reconcile the story of his bruised and battered wife with the facts.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Racing: Live from Newmarket</title>
    <desc>Live coverage of racing from Newmarket, York and Ascot. Today's feature race is the July Cup. Presented by Ed Chamberlin and Francesca Cumani.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711161500 +0000" stop="20260711183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sharpe</title>
    <desc>Napoleonic War-based action-adventure. France 1813 - the war enters its final stages as the French formulate a desperate plan to capture Wellington's spymaster.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711183000 +0000" stop="20260711213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nations Champ Rugby: Arg. v Wales</title>
    <desc>Lauren Salter presents as Wales face a tough trip to San Juan to take on Argentina in their second match of the Nations Championship.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260711213000 +0000" stop="20260712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting action from the world of All Elite Wrestling - the roster features world-class talent including Jon Moxley, MJF, Ricochet and Adam Page.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Island</title>
    <desc>Glamorous singles live in a beautiful villa under the watchful gaze of an audience at home who have the power to decide who goes and who will win a huge cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260710210500 +0000" stop="20260710213500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Island: The Debrief</title>
    <desc>Your daily drop of hot Love Island tea, and all the Villa gossip. With Shakira Khan, Toni Laites and Yasmin Pettet, nothing is off-topic or out of the question.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260710213500 +0000" stop="20260710220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy about family life. After reading an erotic novel, Peter gets the idea to write one himself. Carter is sued for publishing Peter's book on tape.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260710220500 +0000" stop="20260710223500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated US comedy about family life. After an accident puts Brian in hospital, he has a near-death experience that leads him to have a new lease of life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260710223500 +0000" stop="20260710230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated series. When the CIA's budget is cut, Roger suggests a telethon might help restore funds, but Stan claims the idea as his own.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260710230500 +0000" stop="20260710233500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated series about a family man who works for the CIA. Stan becomes the new adviser to his boss who soon takes advantage of his willingness to please.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260710233500 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. Gene tries to remember a perfect song that he wrote in his sleep, and Louise and Tina try to catch a cricket that is keeping Linda up at night.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711000500 +0000" stop="20260711003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Fight at the Not Okay Chore-Ral: Animated comedy. The Belchers end up in a bedtime story showdown when Bob and Linda suggest that the kids should take on more household chores.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711003000 +0000" stop="20260711005500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Botched: Most Outrageous Rejects</title>
    <desc>Compilation series counting down the top 10 rejects from Botched history.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711005500 +0000" stop="20260711012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Botched: Most Outrageous Before and After</title>
    <desc>A countdown of the top 10 most outrageous before and afters.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711012000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern for the game show with only one question and find out if Paula can beat the Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Home improvement programme. Brian McCourt and Sarah Keenleyside build a dream cottage retreat for a couple whose new home came with a mini-forest at the back.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711063000 +0000" stop="20260711065500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Home improvement programme. Brian McCourt and Sarah Keenleyside build an outdoor film theatre for a quintessential family-friendly neighbourhood to enjoy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711065500 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dress to Impress</title>
    <desc>Youtuber Zac is in Manchester hoping to find his dream Northern Gent. Will any of the three guys impress with their style choices.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dress to Impress</title>
    <desc>In London, dancer Kea hopes to be impressed by the choices of three single lads. Will any of them shine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern as Tracie gets her chance to take on the Banker in the game show with only one question.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711100500 +0000" stop="20260711110500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern as Richard steps up to play his game against the Banker and tries to take home a huge cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711110500 +0000" stop="20260711120500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Alex joins Stephen Mulhern and gets his chance to open the iconic red boxes - he may be swayed by one of the Banker's offers, or resist for a shot at 100,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711120500 +0000" stop="20260711131000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>Graham Norton invites executive assistant Yemi, funeral celebrant Richard and support worker Aimee to take on the Wheel and some tricky puzzles for the chance to win 50,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711131000 +0000" stop="20260711141500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rio</title>
    <desc>Colourful animated adventure comedy film featuring the voices of Jesse Eisenberg and Anne Hathaway, 2011. A domesticated macaw from America goes on an adventure in Rio de Janeiro.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711141500 +0000" stop="20260711142000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711142000 +0000" stop="20260711150500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rio</title>
    <desc>Colourful animated adventure comedy film featuring the voices of Jesse Eisenberg and Anne Hathaway, 2011. A domesticated macaw from America goes on an adventure in Rio de Janeiro.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711150500 +0000" stop="20260711161000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ice Age: Collision Course</title>
    <desc>Animated adventure comedy film sequel featuring the voices of Ray Romano and Denis Leary, 2012. When Scrat's acorn sends an asteroid to Earth, the Herd must find a way to stop it.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260711161000 +0000" stop="20260711161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Drama series about a curmudgeonly country doctor. After Martin and Louisa tell Dr Timoney about their failed date night, she questions whether they are compatible.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law and Order: UK</title>
    <desc>Crime drama. Ronnie and Joe are on the hunt for the killer of a seemingly innocent man when the investigation leads them to ex-DI Natalie Chandler, Ronnie's old boss.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law and Order: UK</title>
    <desc>Crime drama series. When the body of a woman is discovered, Ronnie wonders if she really killed herself or if there might be a terrorist connection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260710225000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trial and Retribution</title>
    <desc>When a 15-year-old girl goes missing and her bloodstained clothes are found, Detective Superintendent Walker heads the investigation into her murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George and Mildred</title>
    <desc>Domestic sitcom. George wonders how he can break the news that he has resigned from his job to Mildred without incurring her wrath.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George and Mildred</title>
    <desc>Domestic sitcom spin-off from the hit '70s show Man About the House. George has to babysit Tarquin when Jeffrey and Ann entrust him to the Ropers for the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711053500 +0000" stop="20260711064500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>A body with gunshot wounds to the head is washed ashore. Although the corpse is unidentifiable, two women each claim that it must be their missing husband.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711064500 +0000" stop="20260711075000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>Drama series about a Cornish police detective. Wycliffe is summoned to trace a farmer who has disappeared.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711075000 +0000" stop="20260711085500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>Drama series. When a schoolgirl is found dead in a science lab after a school disco, Wycliffe sets out to discover whether it's a case of murder or suicide.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711085500 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Endeavour</title>
    <desc>When DC Endeavour Morse investigates the disappearance of a missing Oxford schoolgirl, he soon risks all in a search for justice that will ultimately shape his destiny.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Darling Buds of May</title>
    <desc>Part One: Comedy-drama series. Ma starts making plans for a lavish wedding, but has Pop overreached himself with his offer of a stately home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711131000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Darling Buds of May</title>
    <desc>Part Two: Comedy-drama. Pop Larkin is about to join the large number of villagers who wish with all their hearts that they'd never met Corinne Perigo..</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711131000 +0000" stop="20260711151000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Murder mystery drama. When Barnaby and Scott investigate the murder of a pub barman, Barnaby wonders if it may be the result of a case of mistaken identity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711151000 +0000" stop="20260711171000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Things That Go Bump in the Night: The murder of an undertaker takes Barnaby and Scott to a village where residents are divided about the rights and wrongs of a spiritualist church.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711171000 +0000" stop="20260711191000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Barnaby and Scott dig into the luxury lifestyles of the rowing set when the annual Midsomer Regatta is brought to a standstill after a body is found in a river.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711191000 +0000" stop="20260711210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>When one of the world's rarest orchids is smuggled illegally into Midsomer Malham, it triggers a catalogue of passion, jealousy and death.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711210500 +0000" stop="20260711225500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Vera</title>
    <desc>Detective drama series. DCI Vera Stanhope investigates a mysterious death in a quiet coastal town with clues that keep revolving around one street.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260711225500 +0000" stop="20260712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inspector Morse</title>
    <desc>Morse investigates the death of a member of the Clarets XI old boys' cricket team and realises that the players have more than cricket on their minds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Wants to Be a Millionaire</title>
    <desc>Six more contestants compete for a place in the million-pound hot seat - find out if anyone has got what it takes to answer 15 questions to win one million pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260710235500 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>A team of five from Windsor play to take home a big cash prize by answering a series of Top 10 list questions in the quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711005000 +0000" stop="20260711013500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the ruthless quiz as contestants Eloise and Dave, Gabriele and Besrat, and Catherine and Helen take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711013500 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>It's Ronnie's turn to take on the Banker - join Stephen Mulhern to find out if she will take home a huge cash prize or become the latest member of the 1p Club.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Battling it out this time are friends Rebecca and Rachel from Liverpool, married couple Kaz and Rich from North Wales, and Deb with her mum Emily from Solihull and London.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Warwick Davis hosts as a team of five university friends take on a series of Top 10 list questions, but have they got what it takes to win a cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Wants to Be a Millionaire</title>
    <desc>Six more contestants compete for a place in the million-pound hot seat - find out if anyone has got what it takes to answer 15 questions to win one million pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the rapid and ruthless quiz as contestants Zeus and Sam, Gary and Kim, and Nicola and Brad take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern as Leon gets his chance to open the iconic red boxes and goes up against the Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711170000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Seeking supremacy this time are sisters Hinisha and Darshika from Leicester, Brian and his son Paul from Runcorn, and best mates Tasha and Leanne from Basildon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Facing the puzzlewords this time are couple Kate and Stu from Worcestershire and two teams from Wiltshire, couple Robbie and Aimee and Debs with her son Ben.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711190000 +0000" stop="20260711200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Graham Norton invites AJ Odudu, Gok Wan and Charlotte Church to try their luck at spinning the Wheel and solving puzzles to win big for charity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711200000 +0000" stop="20260711210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Are four celebrities clever enough to take on one of the country's finest quiz brains? Bradley Walsh hosts as Cheryl Baker, Laura Tobin, Jason Bell and Mark Steel face The Chase.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711210000 +0000" stop="20260711220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260711220000 +0000" stop="20260712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Gibbs suffers a temporary memory loss as he recovers from his injuries; the team tries to prevent a terrorist attack on the U.S. Navy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team must learn to work without Gibbs, who has retired; Ziva witnesses a political assassination and the FBI wants her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>NCIS temporarily reinstates Gibbs when an escaped convict threatens his friend's life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>While searching the abandoned and bloody car of a missing Navy lieutenant, the team learns she had been profiling men to find the perfect mate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team is called to the scene of the murder of a petty officer who was part of an undercover arms operation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the death of a missing lance corporal, whose body was buried in the backyard of a vacant house and then exhumed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711020300 +0000" stop="20260711030300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team investigates when a Marine is attacked in his home and his daughter is kidnapped on Halloween; Abby's Halloween costume leaves McGee and Tony speechless.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711030300 +0000" stop="20260711040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Gibbs' team works with the Army Criminal Investigative Unit to investigate a suspected terrorist attack that killed a Marine colonel at a military country club.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711040100 +0000" stop="20260711050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team is called to the scene of the murder of a petty officer who was part of an undercover arms operation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711050100 +0000" stop="20260711060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the death of a missing lance corporal, whose body was buried in the backyard of a vacant house and then exhumed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711060400 +0000" stop="20260711070400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team investigates when a Marine is attacked in his home and his daughter is kidnapped on Halloween; Abby's Halloween costume leaves McGee and Tony speechless.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711070400 +0000" stop="20260711080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Gibbs' team works with the Army Criminal Investigative Unit to investigate a suspected terrorist attack that killed a Marine colonel at a military country club.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711080200 +0000" stop="20260711083200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711083200 +0000" stop="20260711090200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711090200 +0000" stop="20260711093200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Natural Blood Pressure Management</title>
    <desc>Cardiologist Dr. Ernst von Schwarz, M.D. shows how to manage your blood pressure naturally and help protect your heart for life with My Best Heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711093200 +0000" stop="20260711100200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711100200 +0000" stop="20260711103200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711103200 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joint Relief Revolution</title>
    <desc>Join Connie Craig-Carroll and health visionary Ken Meares as they uncover OmegaXL, the groundbreaking natural supplement transforming lives by tackling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711113000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Have Thinning Hair? Keranique Can Help Regrow Beautiful, Thicker Hair!</title>
    <desc>If you have thinning hair or hair loss, Keranique can help regrow thicker, longer and fuller hair. Keranique is the number 1 hair regrowth system for women. Regain your confidence with beautiful, thicker and fuller hair in just 3 easy steps!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Never Scrub Your Floors Again</title>
    <desc>See why this cleaning tool replaces chemicals and hard labor!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711133000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260711143000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>JD splits the young rappers into two teams and challenges them to perform at a high school halftime show.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Kelly Rowland and her personal trainer visit the five young rappers; JD tests the children on both their mental and physical stamina in the "Catch the Beat" challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Bow Wow helps hone the young rappers' media skills to prepare them for a press conference, television interview and photo shoot; Nova throws another artist under the bus.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Before signing, JD tests the young rappers in a battle rap; John John Da Don, Arsonal, Charlie Clips, DNA and Calicoe prepare the group; a rapper makes an unforgettable decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Jermaine Dupri's five new artists are tested on their foundation; despite getting advice from Bow Wow, Ricci Bitti still makes a huge mistake.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Jermaine Dupri challenges the youngsters to rap with legendary beatboxer Doug E. Fresh; Lil Bri fights to keep her spot at the top.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Jermaine gives his young rappers the chance to create a song from scratch with producer Zaytoven and have their works broadcast on the radio; Ricci and her manager must shape up before Jermaine ships them out.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>The five young rappers perform for a hidden focus group, then use the group's feedback for an even bigger performance; Jordan and Rap-Unzel struggle to remember their lyrics despite Da Brat's help.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Jermaine Dupri's five new artists are tested on their foundation; despite getting advice from Bow Wow, Ricci Bitti still makes a huge mistake.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Bow Wow helps hone the young rappers' media skills to prepare them for a press conference, television interview and photo shoot; Nova throws another artist under the bus.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Before signing, JD tests the young rappers in a battle rap; John John Da Don, Arsonal, Charlie Clips, DNA and Calicoe prepare the group; a rapper makes an unforgettable decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>After thirteen weeks of challenges, the artists prepare for their final performance; JD makes a decision, and awards one rapper the chain and the contract.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Ghost Stories</title>
    <desc>After losing her boyfriend, Tracy strikes a deal with the devil; Fairuza is attacked by a ferocious entity; Della is saved by her guardian angel; a spirit forces Patrick into a battle for his life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Ghost Stories</title>
    <desc>Linda and her sister discover an old house with a murderous history; Carlos is rescued by a spirit; Victoria was raised in house built on a burial ground; Dot realizes a ghost is watching over her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>In week five of the competition, the eight remaining contestants prepare to do battle in the categories of literature &amp; fine arts and vocabulary.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711113000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711133000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bring It!</title>
    <desc>The Dancing Dolls challenge their rivals to a street battle; tension on the dance floor sparks a clash between dancers and spectators; Camryn gets the opportunity to lead the Dancing Dolls in a parade.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bring It!</title>
    <desc>The Dancing Dolls prepare to defend their title against local rivals; Mimi tries to convince Dianna to let the mothers back into the dance studio during rehearsal; Sunjai gets the chance to compete in Stand Battle for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Wedding day has come and gone, and now the three newlywed couples are off on their honeymoons; one couple hits an instant roadblock at the airport.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711170000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Honeymoons continue for two of the couples, as they start to familiarize themselves with their new spouses; explosive revelations come to light about Mia's past.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260711180000 +0000" stop="20260711190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Back to reality for Danielle and Bobby, and Amber and Dave, as they return from honeymoons; Tristian feels betrayed by Mia's dishonesty.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Marvel</title>
    <desc>In the decades preceding the current Marvel Cinematic Universe, Marvel struggled through box office flops like "Howard the Duck," corporate skulduggery, and a bankruptcy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Fed up with Bart's unending torture, Lisa files a restraining order against her brother, which forces him to live in the backyard.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Bender searches the universe for his missing shiny metal rear end.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include an exploding portable toilet and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>A group of pranksters does a prank called Bagels Thrown at Crippled Man's Face in public and record people's reactions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Marvel</title>
    <desc>In the decades preceding the current Marvel Cinematic Universe, Marvel struggled through box office flops like "Howard the Duck," corporate skulduggery, and a bankruptcy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Highlights of the funniest moments from the first 100 episodes, including the characters' botched relationships and catchphrases.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711003000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Elaine tries to convert a gay acquaintance (Robert Mailhouse) to heterosexuality; George and his date have secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Fed up with Bart's unending torture, Lisa files a restraining order against her brother, which forces him to live in the backyard.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Bender searches the universe for his missing shiny metal rear end.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Ninja Warrior</title>
    <desc>The eastern regional qualifying rounds continue in Las Vegas as ninjas compete for a spot in the all-new regional finals; hosts Matt Iseman and Akbar Gbajabiamila, along with co-host Zuri Hall, select their fastest pick of the night.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baby Mama</title>
    <desc>When single executive Kate Holbrook (Tina Fey) decides the time is right to finally have a baby, she hires a working-class woman (Amy Poehler) from South Philadelphia to act as her surrogate mother. However, Kate's careful planning goes out the window when the woman shows up on her doorstep needing a place to live. A comic battle of wills breaks out between the pair as they prepare for the blessed</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Ninja Warrior</title>
    <desc>The eastern regional qualifying rounds continue in Las Vegas as ninjas compete for a spot in the all-new regional finals; hosts Matt Iseman and Akbar Gbajabiamila, along with co-host Zuri Hall, select their fastest pick of the night.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baby Mama</title>
    <desc>When single executive Kate Holbrook (Tina Fey) decides the time is right to finally have a baby, she hires a working-class woman (Amy Poehler) from South Philadelphia to act as her surrogate mother. However, Kate's careful planning goes out the window when the woman shows up on her doorstep needing a place to live. A comic battle of wills breaks out between the pair as they prepare for the blessed</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>In this battle of the sexes game, the ladies may be sitting in the back, but they are front and center when it comes to answering questions right!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711103000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Two brothers try to impress their gorgeous friend with their cash cab wits; but it's possible it will be Marcia who will be the impressive one, all the way to their destination.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Four young guys get into the Cash Cab and announce their collective brain will win the game; after cruising through the Red Light Challenge with flying colors, things take a turn for the worse, and they must ask for help from a beautiful woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711113000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>When four guys hail a cab after dinner at a trendy Eglinton pub, the last thing they expect is to end up on a quiz show; once they're in the cash cab, the last thing this bunch expects is to be kicked out.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bridesmaids</title>
    <desc>Annie (Kristen Wiig) is a single woman whose own life is a mess, but when she learns that her lifelong best friend, Lillian (Maya Rudolph), is engaged, she has no choice but to serve as the maid of honor. Though lovelorn and almost penniless, Annie, nevertheless, winds her way through the strange and expensive rituals associated with her job as the bride's go-to gal. Determined to make things perf</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Boss</title>
    <desc>Wealthy CEO Michelle Darnell (Melissa McCarthy) always gets her way, until she's busted for insider trading and sent to federal prison. After leaving jail, Darnell finds herself broke, homeless and hated. Luckily, she tracks down former assistant Claire (Kristen Bell), the only person who's willing to help. While staying with Claire and her young daughter, the ex-con devises a new business model f</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711173000 +0000" stop="20260711193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big</title>
    <desc>At a carnival, young Josh Baskin wishes he were big, only to wake up the next morning and discover his wish came true. But the more Josh experiences life as an adult, the more he longs for the simple joys of childhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711193000 +0000" stop="20260711220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Boss</title>
    <desc>Wealthy CEO Michelle Darnell (Melissa McCarthy) always gets her way, until she's busted for insider trading and sent to federal prison. After leaving jail, Darnell finds herself broke, homeless and hated. Luckily, she tracks down former assistant Claire (Kristen Bell), the only person who's willing to help. While staying with Claire and her young daughter, the ex-con devises a new business model f</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260711220000 +0000" stop="20260712000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bridesmaids</title>
    <desc>Annie (Kristen Wiig) is a single woman whose own life is a mess, but when she learns that her lifelong best friend, Lillian (Maya Rudolph), is engaged, she has no choice but to serve as the maid of honor. Though lovelorn and almost penniless, Annie, nevertheless, winds her way through the strange and expensive rituals associated with her job as the bride's go-to gal. Determined to make things perf</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Pottery Throw Down</title>
    <desc>Ten home potters from around the United Kingdom travel to Stoke-on-Trent, the home of British pottery, to take part in a competition to become top potter.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Cheyenne convinces her mother to try speed-dating after Reba has a disastrous night on the town.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose befriends Dorothy's former college buddy (Lois Nettleton), not knowing that the woman is a lesbian.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Chris works his magic on a scrapbook full of memorabilia cherished by a J. R. R. Tolkien fan; Dom lavishes attention on a sentimental workbench; Suzie and Brenton nail an important fix on a Blitz-era manicure set.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon, Gino and Fred's Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Gordon Ramsay, Gino D'Acampo and Fred Sirieix join forces for a summer: they spend three weeks traveling through Italy, France and Scotland, with each inviting the other two to their home turf to help them put on an event with personal significance.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gogglebox</title>
    <desc>The Goggleboxers share their thoughts on "The Celebrity Traitors," "Love Is Blind," "Coronation Street," "The Girlfriend," "Nightmares of Nature," "The Reluctant Traveller" and "Yorkshire Air 999.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Pull back the cover on the book-making process at Ligare Book Printers in Sydney; follow a novel on its journey from pixels to pages; discover how paper is made in Tasmania; meet a biologist developing an innovative algae-based ink.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711023000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Dr Karl gets the scoop on how two of our most popular ice creams are made. Australians each devour around 18 litres of ice cream a year, making us the third-largest population of ice cream eaters on the planet.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon, Gino and Fred's Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Gordon Ramsay, Gino D'Acampo and Fred Sirieix join forces for a summer: they spend three weeks traveling through Italy, France and Scotland, with each inviting the other two to their home turf to help them put on an event with personal significance.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gogglebox</title>
    <desc>The Goggleboxers share their thoughts on "The Celebrity Traitors," "Love Is Blind," "Coronation Street," "The Girlfriend," "Nightmares of Nature," "The Reluctant Traveller" and "Yorkshire Air 999.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose befriends Dorothy's former college buddy (Lois Nettleton), not knowing that the woman is a lesbian.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711053000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Cheyenne convinces her mother to try speed-dating after Reba has a disastrous night on the town.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Chris works his magic on a scrapbook full of memorabilia cherished by a J. R. R. Tolkien fan; Dom lavishes attention on a sentimental workbench; Suzie and Brenton nail an important fix on a Blitz-era manicure set.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Travelling Auctioneers</title>
    <desc>Will Kirk and Christina Trevanion take their mobile auction house on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lakefront Luxury</title>
    <desc>Joseph and Natalie are searching for a lakefront home for their active family; they are looking for a house with easy water access for the kids and a gourmet kitchen for themselves.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711103000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lakefront Luxury</title>
    <desc>Aimee and Sabby love to travel and are on the hunt for a lakefront property that feels like a permanent vacation; they are considering three homes, a rustic 1960s build with a stone fireplace, a modern new build with a sleek kitchen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Scenic River Journeys</title>
    <desc>Meandering through the black waters of a primordial river immortalized in a folk song.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Canadian Baking Show</title>
    <desc>The top seven candidates prepare homegrown classics.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Extreme Weather Salvage</title>
    <desc>Phil Risko's team at Northstar works fast to refloat a trawler that's been blown onto the shore of a national park in New Jersey; the team improvises to get it back to sea before it suffers further damage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Below Zero Canada</title>
    <desc>Desperate to harvest a musk ox, Becky, Dene and Thi head out into the unforgiving barren lands of the Northwest Territories; Kim and Pierre try to outfox a wolf that threatens their new trap line; Bentley begins preparing a wolf hide for market.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">History by the Numbers</title>
    <desc>The Soviet Red Army and the Western Allies are in a race to the finish line.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Canadian Baking Show</title>
    <desc>The top seven candidates prepare homegrown classics.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260711170000 +0000" stop="20260711180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hoarders Canada</title>
    <desc>David and Elizabeth have been co-dependent hoarders for as long as their adult children can remember; the couple had to remortgage their home because of their addiction to buying items sold on television, such as Tiffany-style lamps.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sheryl Crow: MTV Unplugged</title>
    <desc>In this 'Unplugged', taped at the Brooklyn Academy Of Music in New York City, Crow performs material from her debut album, including her Grammy award-winning single 'All I Wanna Do'.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tattoo Fixers</title>
    <desc>Harry wants a tattoo dedicated to a very intimate part of himself after surviving testicular cancer. Matt doodles on his own legs with a tattoo machine his parents got him for Christmas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Geordie Shore: From The Beginning</title>
    <desc>The gang return from Amsterdam and it's time to tear Newcastle a new one. Vicky and Ricci celebrate breaking the Geordie Shore relationship curse and the gang try out speed dating.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Angels</title>
    <desc>Tattoo legend Ed Hardy helps the Angels in their search of San Francisco's supreme Artists. One local artist faces off against an Angel by tattooing members of the LGBTQ community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master: Master vs Apprentice</title>
    <desc>In the most insane challenge yet, Artists must tattoo 4 on 1 to transform Canvases into wild animals. An unexpected twist surprises the judges and results in a shocking elimination.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master: Master vs Apprentice</title>
    <desc>An insane new tattoo style pushes the Artists' limits, resulting in mind-blowing masterpieces and mind-boggling mistakes. Tension soars between two top dogs as allies and enemies are made.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711014500 +0000" stop="20260711021000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Tensions run high when two angry Canvases return to confront both of their Artists from a botched Team Challenge. Four Artists return, but only 2 will get a shot at Redemption.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711021000 +0000" stop="20260711023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Three Ink Master Redemption Veteran Artists, Christian Buckingham, Duffy Fortner and Jime Litwalk return, each with a new fuming Canvas and a bone to pick.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711023500 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just Tattoo Of Us USA</title>
    <desc>A woman pressures her boyfriend to get engaged, but he wants to curb her nosy tendencies first, and a bro code breach is punished with ink.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Cribs</title>
    <desc>Meet cousins Jacob and Chase as they show off their palatial New Jersey home. Then we jet to Michigan, as Emily shows off a house with more colour than a box of crayons.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711052000 +0000" stop="20260711061000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>Devon wants to raise her baby with her boyfriend Colin, an Iraq war veteran who is still in the reserves. If Colin is deployed, can Devon handle not living at home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711061000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>It's two weeks into training camp, and Kelli and Judy are fixing to make their first cuts. This week the girls are expected to master the world famous DCC kick line and jump split.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>It's week three and the rookie candidates are brought in for their DCC "Makeovers." They're given a new look with a hair and make-up revamp and are transformed in the DCC mold.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Tonight's rehearsal starts with a big bang when DCC Technical Director Kitty Carter makes a surprise visit to Valley Ranch.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Lauren met Derek online years ago. Derek is caring, supporting Lauren after she had a baby with a former boyfriend. Lauren thinks Derek could be the one, so why has he avoided meeting her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Divorcee Shawny calls Nev and Max to help uncover the shadowy identity of her attempt at new love. But things get interesting as they discover that Shawny may have secrets of her own.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Nev and Kamie receive an anonymous email from a whistleblower reporting a catfishing! But when our hosts arrive to help the named victim, they uncover a deeper conspiracy of deception.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711133000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711143000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260711153000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sommerdahl Murders</title>
    <desc>Crime drama from Walter Presents. A shooting at a funfair leaves Dan and Flemming facing a group who don't like dealing with the police. In Danish/subs. (S5 Eps1.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Nineteen-year-old fitness fanatic Josh is flown to King's after being injured in a canal barge accident. And two best friends are recovering from a Sunday night out clubbing.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260710230500 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>A powerful and cautionary episode following the work of King's College Hospital's A&amp;E department on the night when Whitney Houston died.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711001000 +0000" stop="20260711011500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">999: On the Front Line</title>
    <desc>Paramedics treat a man with a crippling cluster headache, a woman suffering from the effects of alcohol withdrawal, and a woman who's collapsed in a sauna.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711011500 +0000" stop="20260711022000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Nineteen-year-old fitness fanatic Josh is flown to King's after being injured in a canal barge accident. And two best friends are recovering from a Sunday night out clubbing.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711022000 +0000" stop="20260711025000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Perfect Pitch</title>
    <desc>The campers go wild at Mynydd Derwydd near Clocaenog Forest with a bushcraft skills workshop. But with next to no facilities, will 250 acres of stunning scenery win them over.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711025000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711075500 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The competition kicks off at Greenways of Malvern in Worcestershire, where owner Geri Atterbury likes to provide a home from home, but a lack of en suite puts some guests off.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711085500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Sean and Maxine hope to give their rivals the royal treatment at The Royal Forester in Bewdley. Some of their guests are blown away by the rooms, but there's a hairy encounter for others.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711085500 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Mum-and-son duo Sarah and Luke host at Ferry Lodge in Holyhead on Anglesey. But Sean and Maxine begrudge paying 50p for toiletries, and there's confusion over the 'Welsh' breakfast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Sanjeev and Elinor welcome their rivals to Court Colman Manor in Bridgend. Not everyone feels the spark during a lesson in making fire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711103500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;Bers meet for one last time to settle some scores and find out how much they've been paid. Tensions run high before the winner is announced.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711103500 +0000" stop="20260711113500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Sharon and Nev love the beautiful island of Malta and want to buy a holiday home there for all the family to enjoy. With a budget of £160,000, can Ben Hillman deliver their Maltese dream.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711113500 +0000" stop="20260711124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Midwife and beautician Lisa has been visiting Menorca since she was a child and now wants to buy a family holiday home, with space to create a beauty salon, in the resort of Cala en Porter.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711124000 +0000" stop="20260711134000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Hospital worker Sharon wants a spacious bolthole close to the beach in Torrevieja on Spain's beautiful Costa Blanca. Can Laura Hamilton find her dream property for £50,000.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711134000 +0000" stop="20260711144000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Sheila loves the Spanish lifestyle and wants to buy her own holiday home on the Costa Blanca. Laura Hamilton shows Sheila and her best friend Rose five impressive apartments for £55,000.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711144000 +0000" stop="20260711151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Drinks brand ambassador Dan serves up classic Greek grub, while some of his guests struggle to get a word in..</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711151500 +0000" stop="20260711155000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Computer fanatic Matt hosts the second night, with culinary cock-ups, revelations of scoffing sofas, and sumo shenanigans on the menu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711155000 +0000" stop="20260711162000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Dog walking entrepreneur Jordanna hosts a Mexican-themed evening featuring culinary compliments, offers of feet-kissing and some unwanted guests.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711162000 +0000" stop="20260711165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Jayne - the self-proclaimed number one florist in Hull - gives her guests a taste of Spain with her food, flamenco and fiesta. Tony comes dressed as a matador.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711165000 +0000" stop="20260711172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>The competition moves to Doncaster, where Tony serves up some countryside cuisine on a final night featuring hit-and-miss food, dirty cutlery and a wolf-whistling hoo-ha.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711172000 +0000" stop="20260711175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The competition kicks off at Watergate Yard in Sleaford, Lincolnshire, where hosts Ryan and Hollie have a unique style and 15,000 mannequins up their sleeves.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711175500 +0000" stop="20260711182500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Mum and daughter Holly and Meg host the week's second visit at Birdholme Glamping in Nottinghamshire, where they aim to make glamping even more glam.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260711182500 +0000" stop="20260711185500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>At Holly Hill Inn, Tom's already let all his competitors know that he runs the best place in Richmond, North Yorkshire. So why's he feeling so hard done by at feedback time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon's excitement about his Meemaw's visit fades when she butts heads with Amy; Raj questions his relationship with Emily after meeting someone new.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260710203000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Amy and Sheldon host a Valentine's Day edition of Fun With Flags; Penny and Leonard wrestle with getting older; Howard and Bernadette make a discovery in their hot tub; Raj is torn between Emily and another woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>The gang celebrates news of Bernadette's pregnancy by singing karaoke; Wolowitz's reaction to the pregnancy announcement worries Bernadette; Wolowitz believes he needs to make more money to support his growing family.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>For the first time in nine years, the gang celebrates Sheldon's birthday -- surprising him with a special guest.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Leonard, Sheldon and Wolowitz file for a patent on their new invention; Penny, Amy and Bernadette give dating advice to Koothrappali after his breakup with Emily.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon makes a surprise revelation when Amy buys him a new laptop; Leonard and Wolowitz get sold out by Koothrappali after lying to their wives to attend a movie screening.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Friday</title>
    <desc>It's Friday and Craig Jones has just gotten fired for stealing cardboard boxes. To make matters worse, rent is due, he hates his overbearing girlfriend, Joi, and his best friend, Smokey, owes the local drug dealer money -- and that's all before lunch. As the hours drag on, Jones and Smokey experience the gamut of urban life, complete with crackheads, shoot-outs and overly sexual pastors, concentra</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Friday</title>
    <desc>Craig bails his friend out of trouble, survives a climactic confrontation with Debo, the neighborhood bully, and ends up with the girl. In Next Friday the bully is back as Debo, who spent two years behind bars, is released from prison. Fearing for his son's safety, Craig's father sends his son to live with Uncle Elroy. However, Craig soon learns that trouble can find you no matter where you live.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Friday After Next</title>
    <desc>Finds Craig (Ice Cube) and Day-Day (Mike Epps) back in the old neighborhood where it all began. It's Christmastime and a ghetto Santa Claus breaks into their run-down apartment, stealing all their presents, along with anything else he can stuff into his sack, including the rent money hidden in their stereo speakers. Their only hope to not get evicted before Christmas is to take jobs as security gu</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>WWE Diva, Paige; "Born Badass"; "Everyday Divas"; "Proper Smack.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711053000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Nina Agdal have outgrown trampolines; shoot some rare balls on the basketball court; celebrating heroes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo slam on their faces because they're Pocket Blocked; they whip out the inside clubs in Indoor Fores and face some sea scares in Holy Shark!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711063000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood Can't Stop Won't Stop, toss their stuff in Lazy Drops and take a break for Adult Recess.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Singer Allen Stone joins Rob, Steelo and Chanel to put smiles to the test in "Testing Positive" and get frustrated with technology in "Tech Wrecked.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711073000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get some solid "Dadvice," expose a few "Body Scams," and find out it was "All For Nothing.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Karrueche Tran play exterminator in "Bug Patrol"; getting emotional in "Love Tears"; going skating in the wild in "Stay in the Park.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and special guest Carly Aquilino have a fun-filled meal with some "Food Players"; showing off with some "Bike Fallin' Flossers"; covering their eyes while seeing "Dongs in the Wild.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Comedian Jo Koy joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to talk about people coming in "Far Too Hot," video game "Rage Quitters" and they celebrate people we call "Queen Denises.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo are living that "Bib Life," wondering if "They Still Got Payphones," and getting "Deranged With Downtime.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo celebrate couples who are "Too Old to Divorce," pay a little extra for the "Moron Coverage," and pay tribute to savvy shoppers in "I Had a Coupon.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711103000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood smash into some gates while "Riding the Fence," realize that love hurts while having a "Love Accident" and get bent out of shape with some "Noodle People.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and special guest Lolo Wood get spooked by syringes while having "Poke Panic"; getting some verbal payback with "Comeback Attacks"; feeling all the tread from being "Rolled Over.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711113000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood take a bite of "Windy Meals"; see who has "Glider Pains"; hit the links for "Muddy Strokes.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Chanel talk getting a "B.U.I."; what it takes for "Earning Your Wings"; why everything tastes better with "Skin Seasoning.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Nina Agdal welcome Jersey Shore's Angelina to learn about porch parties.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>Silversun Pickups perform songs including "Lazy Eye," "Panic Switch," and "Well Thought Out Twinkles.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260710203000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>All Time Low performs in New York City; songs include "Weightless," "Dear Maria, Count Me In," and "Damned If I Do Ya (Damned If I Don't).".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Live</title>
    <desc>John Legend performs in Rome; songs include "Used to Love U," "Save Room" and "Green Light.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Damiano David</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711003000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Push Showcase: Jordan Adetunji</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Ayra Starr</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Shaboozey</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: The Warning</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711023000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Flyana Boss</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH: Chappell Roan Interview</title>
    <desc>Chappell Roan loves her whole debut album.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711033000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Push Presents: Teddy Swims</title>
    <desc>Teddy Swims chats with MTV about life, music and his rise to superstardom, and gives us exclusive performances of two of his tracks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260711150000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Rico wants to move to England to care for his ailing mother, but his online relationship with Ja'mari, an international male model, is giving him second thoughts about leaving.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">F9 The Fast Saga</title>
    <desc>Dom Toretto and his crew come together to stop a world-shattering plot by the most skilled assassin and high-performance driver they've ever encountered, who is Dom's forsaken brother.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711001500 +0000" stop="20260711033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">F9 The Fast Saga</title>
    <desc>Dom Toretto and his crew come together to stop a world-shattering plot by the most skilled assassin and high-performance driver they've ever encountered, who is Dom's forsaken brother.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711033000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) takes Fancy (Garcelle Beauvais) to her 10-year high-school reunion after her boyfriend Silas (guest star Alan F. Smith) is delayed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Braxton's (Christopher B. Duncan) secret relationship with Cameron (Susan Wood) causes trouble when an old flame (guest star Tembi Locke) comes to town.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711043000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) is shocked when his mother comes to visit with her new, young fiancé (guest star Gerald Levert).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon (Shawn and Marlon Wayans) find $100,000 stashed in a garbage bag and debate its destiny.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711053000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) tells Monique (Paula Jai Parker) his true feelings about her while she's pretending to be married to Shawn (Shawn Wayans).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>At the request of a frightened Shawn and Marlon, Monique holds a seance to put a restless spirit at peace.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711063000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>When Marlon learns President Clinton may be at Pop's diner, he becomes obsessed with shaking his hand.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn loses his newsstand to T.C. in a card game and issues a new challenge with Pop's diner as the prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711073000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Monique (Paula Jai Parker) coaxes Marlon (Marlon Wayans) back onto the basketball court after an argument with Shawn (Shawn Wayans).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon (Shawn and Marlon Wayans) play Pygmalion with their country-girl cousin (Kim Wayans) and get shocking results.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>The gang is held hostage by a store Santa who demands they get into the spirit of the holiday or else.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>After becoming desperately lonely men, Shawn and Marlon (Shawn and Marlon Wayans) head to a church bazaar in search of women. With John Witherspoon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon (Shawn and Marlon Wayans) are forced to take over operations at the diner when Pops (John Witherspoon) succumbs to the flu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon and Shawn grow tired of each other's bad habits, forcing them to seek out others to room with.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711103000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn is left dateless on Valentine's Day when Marlon steals his girlfriend; Dee mistakes Pops for her secret admirer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon dream of fame when they help Pops host a cooking segment on the "Ken and Kiki Show.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711113000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon steals Shawn's recognition after Shawn saves a boy from death.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon scheme to find a way to protect Dee from the con artist she is falling in love with.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn's (Shawn Wayans) landlady (Adrienne Barbeau) makes a pass at him and Shawn must decide how to deal with the unwanted attention.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) decides acting is in his future and wants to get out of the newsstand business. Los Angeles Clippers' Brent Barry guest stars.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711133000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>After breaking his leg in a fall at the newsstand, Marlon (Marlon Wayans) decides to sue Shawn (Shawn Wayans) for his injuries.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon let Grandma live with them, then find she's overbearing.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 4</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5:30</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 6</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260710233000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>In a classic game-show version of "Hangman," contestants solve word puzzles for cash and prizes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>The judges are tougher than ever as auditions continue; dueling magicians go head-to-head, a multigenerational tumbling team flips into the spotlight and a laser-fueled dance trio ignites the stage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711033400 +0000" stop="20260711043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Reese Witherspoon; actress Zoey Deutch; comic Robert Smigel; performance from "Cats: The Jellicle Ball.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711043700 +0000" stop="20260711053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Professional basketball player Karl-Anthony Towns; actress Olivia Wilde; actor Stephen Root; chef Ham El-Waylly.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711053700 +0000" stop="20260711061200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711061200 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Top Story With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Reporting of breaking news and developing stories in real time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A mother's death initially appears to be a suicide, but when investigators start to interview those closest to her, an evil plot emerges.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Guest host Sibley Scoles dives into Philadelphia's famed art, music, food and fashion scene through some of its most creative and talented locals.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Very Local Presents</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom Protecting the Wild</title>
    <desc>Embarking on a scaly adventure from Texas to Florida to help rescue two of North America's most radical reptiles, Peter visits a nursery where baby lizards are raised while Dr. Rae teams up with a trained dog that can sniff out horned lizards.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711113000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forever Young With Dr. Pablo Prichard</title>
    <desc>When it comes to cancer, time can be the greatest ally, or the toughest enemy; Danielle and Dr. Pablo meet two women whose experiences reveal both sides of that truth; Danielle Fishel caught cancer early, while Betsy survived late-stage cancer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Tour de France</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the 113th edition of the cycling event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Earth Odyssey With Dylan Dreyer</title>
    <desc>Dylan Dreyer cruises the ocean floor for a look at the unique and curious crustaceans roaming the seas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711163000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tails of Valor</title>
    <desc>A veteran finds his perfect match, an Atlantic bottlenose dolphin; a cocker spaniel serves as a protector for a diabetic.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711170000 +0000" stop="20260711183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 MLB Draft</title>
    <desc>The best prospects from colleges and high schools around the U.S. and beyond are on hand to see if their big league dreams are about to come true. From Pennsylvania Convention Center in Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260711183000 +0000" stop="20260711220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Golf</title>
    <desc>From Edgewood Tahoe Resort in Stateline, Nev.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Baller Alert Show</title>
    <desc>Lifting the veil on what A-list guests like athletes, entertainers and influencers are doing to reach and maintain stardom, all while inspiring others to grind for greatness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>REVOLT shines a spotlight on rising filmmakers pushing the culture forward through dope short films.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">REVOLT Sports Weekly</title>
    <desc>In the series premiere, host Mariah Rose covers Micah Parsons' big return to Dallas, the Giants benching Russell Wilson, Kawhi Leonard's wild contract requests, and more. Presented by Levi's®.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Jeff Wittek, Chow Lee, Bootleg Kev, J Cruz, Big Boy, DoKnow, and Cosey take their shots in the 3-point contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Flau'jae</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Flau'jae with her latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260710233000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Latto</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Latto with her latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>REVOLT shines a spotlight on rising filmmakers pushing the culture forward through dope short films.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wrist Check Pod</title>
    <desc>Close friends and watch-collecting enthusiasts Perri Dash and Rashawn Smith welcome celebrities, friends, and fellow collectors for a deep dive into the booming business and culture of the global watch community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untapped</title>
    <desc>Viewer-submitted music videos highlight untapped indie artists.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Rushion McDonald; Brandon Bowlin; Ted Carpenter; T.P. Hearn.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711033000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Robin Montague; Tommy Chunn; James Stephens III; Tony Woods.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A mix of the best hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos, from the hottest new releases to favorite throwbacks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untapped</title>
    <desc>Viewer-submitted music videos highlight untapped indie artists.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Rushion McDonald; Brandon Bowlin; Ted Carpenter; T.P. Hearn.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711063000 +0000" stop="20260711070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Robin Montague; Tommy Chunn; James Stephens III; Tony Woods.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711070000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Atlanta legends Big Bank and DJ Scream welcome the biggest names in hip-hop culture for unfiltered conversations.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">REVOLT Sports Weekly</title>
    <desc>In the series premiere, host Mariah Rose covers Micah Parsons' big return to Dallas, the Giants benching Russell Wilson, Kawhi Leonard's wild contract requests, and more. Presented by Levi's®.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Jeff Wittek, Chow Lee, Bootleg Kev, J Cruz, Big Boy, DoKnow, and Cosey take their shots in the 3-point contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711130000 +0000" stop="20260711140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711140000 +0000" stop="20260711143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Flau'jae</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Flau'jae with her latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260711143000 +0000" stop="20260711150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Latto</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Latto with her latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260710203000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260710213000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 6</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 7</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260710231500 +0000" stop="20260710233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Live</title>
    <desc>Celebrity interviews and discussing recipes, beauty, fashion and current events pertinent to the tri-state region.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260710233000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>The judges are tougher than ever as auditions continue; dueling magicians go head-to-head, a multigenerational tumbling team flips into the spotlight and a laser-fueled dance trio ignites the stage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711033400 +0000" stop="20260711043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Reese Witherspoon; actress Zoey Deutch; comic Robert Smigel; performance from "Cats: The Jellicle Ball.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711043700 +0000" stop="20260711053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Professional basketball player Karl-Anthony Towns; actress Olivia Wilde; actor Stephen Root; chef Ham El-Waylly.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711053700 +0000" stop="20260711060700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711060700 +0000" stop="20260711063600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711063600 +0000" stop="20260711070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>"The Hawk" premiere with Will Ferrell and the cast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711070500 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Melt With You"; Kyle MacLachlan; Aaron Moten; Veterans Community Project; bargains and deals with Lawrence Zarian and MorningSave; performance of "Beyond the Sea" from the musical "Just in Time"; Olympic figure skater Maxim Naumov.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Guest host Sibley Scoles dives into Philadelphia's famed art, music, food and fashion scene through some of its most creative and talented locals.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Lifestyle trends in food, nightlife, art, travel and entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open House NYC</title>
    <desc>Host Sara Gore presents a guide to upscale real estate in and around the Big Apple. In addition to a look at the hottest homes on the market, the show also provides interior design tips from specialists and a wealth of information on renovation and stylish living.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Saturday Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom Protecting the Wild</title>
    <desc>Embarking on a scaly adventure from Texas to Florida to help rescue two of North America's most radical reptiles, Peter visits a nursery where baby lizards are raised while Dr. Rae teams up with a trained dog that can sniff out horned lizards.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260711113000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Earth Odyssey With Dylan Dreyer</title>
    <desc>Dylan Dreyer voyages to Australia to meet kickboxing kangaroos, playful whales and the fearsome Tasmanian devil.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 4p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 5p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 6p</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 7p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260710233000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>The judges are tougher than ever as auditions continue; dueling magicians go head-to-head, a multigenerational tumbling team flips into the spotlight and a laser-fueled dance trio ignites the stage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711033400 +0000" stop="20260711043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Reese Witherspoon; actress Zoey Deutch; comic Robert Smigel; performance from "Cats: The Jellicle Ball.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711043700 +0000" stop="20260711053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Professional basketball player Karl-Anthony Towns; actress Olivia Wilde; actor Stephen Root; chef Ham El-Waylly.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711053700 +0000" stop="20260711060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711060400 +0000" stop="20260711063300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711063300 +0000" stop="20260711073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711073000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>"The Hawk" premiere with Will Ferrell and the cast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Guest host Sibley Scoles dives into Philadelphia's famed art, music, food and fashion scene through some of its most creative and talented locals.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">DraftKings Casino Report</title>
    <desc>DraftKings Casino, a top-rated casino app!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Birds Huddle</title>
    <desc>The latest news, commentary and opinion surrounding the Eagles and the NFL, along with sport-betting.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Game Time With Boomer Esiason</title>
    <desc>The former NFL quarterback interviews compelling figures in the sports and entertainment industries.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 6a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 7a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Tour de France</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the 113th edition of the cycling event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Child</title>
    <desc>Sheinelle Jones explores North America's iconic animals, including mountain lion cubs, a manatee mom and baby, and moose calves learning to cross forest streams.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711163000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forever Young With Dr. Pablo Prichard</title>
    <desc>When it comes to cancer, time can be the greatest ally, or the toughest enemy; Danielle and Dr. Pablo meet two women whose experiences reveal both sides of that truth; Danielle Fishel caught cancer early, while Betsy survived late-stage cancer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260711170000 +0000" stop="20260711183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 MLB Draft</title>
    <desc>The best prospects from colleges and high schools around the U.S. and beyond are on hand to see if their big league dreams are about to come true. From Pennsylvania Convention Center in Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Melt With You"; Kyle MacLachlan; Aaron Moten; Veterans Community Project; bargains and deals with Lawrence Zarian and MorningSave; performance of "Beyond the Sea" from the musical "Just in Time"; Olympic figure skater Maxim Naumov.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 3pm</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260710223000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 4pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 5pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC 4 News at 6pm</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 7 PM</title>
    <desc>The latest in local breaking news, weather reports and feature stories covering the vast Southern California region.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711023000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>The judges are tougher than ever as auditions continue; dueling magicians go head-to-head, a multigenerational tumbling team flips into the spotlight and a laser-fueled dance trio ignites the stage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711063400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711063400 +0000" stop="20260711073700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Reese Witherspoon; actress Zoey Deutch; comic Robert Smigel; performance from "Cats: The Jellicle Ball.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711073700 +0000" stop="20260711083700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Professional basketball player Karl-Anthony Towns; actress Olivia Wilde; actor Stephen Root; chef Ham El-Waylly.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711083700 +0000" stop="20260711090700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711090700 +0000" stop="20260711093700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711093700 +0000" stop="20260711103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Melt With You"; Kyle MacLachlan; Aaron Moten; Veterans Community Project; bargains and deals with Lawrence Zarian and MorningSave; performance of "Beyond the Sea" from the musical "Just in Time"; Olympic figure skater Maxim Naumov.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711103000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Protect Your Family From Identity Theft</title>
    <desc>Every 5 seconds there's a victim of identity theft; LifeLock helps alert you, restore your identity, and reimburse lost funds—leading the way in protecting families every day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>A journey through the historic port cities on the Sail4th 250 route, uncovering the maritime waterways that shaped the nation and continue to bring its living history to life today.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711113000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathroom Makeover</title>
    <desc>Transform your bath affordably in just one day!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Tour de France</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the 113th edition of the cycling event.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711160000 +0000" stop="20260711163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Each episode of this travel series sees the host becoming immersed with locals to experience unique culture, authentic cuisine and amazing conversations that turn every city into an unforgettable memory, and brings the world to the viewer through the exploration of inspiring and exciting destinations across the globe. Whether it's rediscovering a familiar road or taking the path less traveled, the</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711163000 +0000" stop="20260711170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Child</title>
    <desc>Sheinelle Jones explores North America's iconic animals, including mountain lion cubs, a manatee mom and baby, and moose calves learning to cross forest streams.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260711170000 +0000" stop="20260711183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 MLB Draft</title>
    <desc>The best prospects from colleges and high schools around the U.S. and beyond are on hand to see if their big league dreams are about to come true. From Pennsylvania Convention Center in Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260710200000 +0000" stop="20260710210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Annika</title>
    <desc>A brutal murder on Glasgow's canals hits close to home when the victim is identified as a former police officer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260710210000 +0000" stop="20260710220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Mrs. Tishell's crush on Martin takes a dramatic turn when, believing him to be her child, she leaves town with baby James.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260710220000 +0000" stop="20260710230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>The past haunts a bank manager; Greengrass fixes a golf tournament.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260710230000 +0000" stop="20260710233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Keeping Up Appearances</title>
    <desc>Hyacinth's father has an accident on his bicycle while chasing the milkwoman.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260710233000 +0000" stop="20260711000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ageless Gardens</title>
    <desc>A Yo-Yo Ma inspired public garden; monks wander contemplatively in nature's forest garden; a retired magazine editor advocates for grief gardening; innovative tower gardens aid remote northern communities in growing their own food year-round.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-10</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711000000 +0000" stop="20260711010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Mrs. Tishell's crush on Martin takes a dramatic turn when, believing him to be her child, she leaves town with baby James.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711010000 +0000" stop="20260711013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Keeping Up Appearances</title>
    <desc>Hyacinth's father has an accident on his bicycle while chasing the milkwoman.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711013000 +0000" stop="20260711020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ageless Gardens</title>
    <desc>A printmaker turns her lush garden into a living art gallery, where dancers, visual artists, and musicians all come together; a cosmopolitan artist combines floral imagery in playful and complex works, and finds inspiration growing in his back alley.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711020000 +0000" stop="20260711030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Annika</title>
    <desc>A brutal murder on Glasgow's canals hits close to home when the victim is identified as a former police officer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711030000 +0000" stop="20260711033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Healthcare expert Domenic Pilla.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711033000 +0000" stop="20260711040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ZoomerLife: Health, Wellness &amp; Longevity</title>
    <desc>The world's leading artists, doctors, filmmakers and scientists participate in a panel discussion.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711040000 +0000" stop="20260711050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>The past haunts a bank manager; Greengrass fixes a golf tournament.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711050000 +0000" stop="20260711053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Divine Intervention</title>
    <desc>Nohemie converted to Judaism to marry a Jewish man, who she is now separated from.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711053000 +0000" stop="20260711060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Balance</title>
    <desc>Stunning videos of nature paired with soothing classical music create inspiration.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711060000 +0000" stop="20260711080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beautiful Little Classics</title>
    <desc>Performances by classical musicians.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711080000 +0000" stop="20260711083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Scriptures</title>
    <desc>Nature videography and classical music with passages of scripture from the world's religions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711083000 +0000" stop="20260711090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Chicken Soup</title>
    <desc>Thought-provoking messages.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711090000 +0000" stop="20260711093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kabalah Yoga With Audi Gozlan</title>
    <desc>Audi Gozlan demonstrates a new system of yoga and meditation known as Kabbalah Yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711093000 +0000" stop="20260711100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711100000 +0000" stop="20260711103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: Blissful Living</title>
    <desc>A series of yoga designed to calm the nerves and strengthen the spirit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711103000 +0000" stop="20260711110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Deborah demonstrates gentle, healing yoga poses designed to strengthen and sculpt muscles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711110000 +0000" stop="20260711113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anjelica's 22 Minute Workout</title>
    <desc>A revival of the '80s aerobics series offers workouts for a wide range of ages and abilities.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711113000 +0000" stop="20260711120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kabalah Yoga With Audi Gozlan</title>
    <desc>Audi Gozlan demonstrates a new system of yoga and meditation known as Kabbalah Yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711120000 +0000" stop="20260711123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260711123000 +0000" stop="20260711130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Yoga to improve one's sex life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-11</date>
  </programme>
</tv>