<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260501185232 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="FX.us">
    <display-name>US | FX East</display-name>
    <icon src="https://tlgrm.re/images/fx-us.png" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465331">
    <display-name lang="US">Freeform HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470910">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470820">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FXX Canada</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465105">
    <display-name lang="US">Fuse HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464774">
    <display-name lang="US">FYI Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="492942">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Mystery</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465241">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464897">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Family</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486672">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486726">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486853">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486821">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV Quiz</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465290">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465002">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime Real Women</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486751">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">More4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486755">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">MTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465167">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Mystery HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464825">
    <display-name lang="US">MTVLIVE</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465357">
    <display-name lang="US">FXX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470509">
    <display-name lang="Canada">CTV LIFE CHANNEL</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465354">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="481954">
    <display-name lang="US">Haunt TV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470299">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Global Toronto</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465113">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV2: Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465207">
    <display-name lang="US">Revolt HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="468233">
    <display-name lang="US">WCAU-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486720">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470330">
    <display-name lang="Canada">ONETV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470737">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Makeful TV SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470474">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Much Music HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467402">
    <display-name lang="US">WPTZ-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467015">
    <display-name lang="US">WNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="469871">
    <display-name lang="US">KNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465080">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV - Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260501120000 -0400" stop="20260501150000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>X2</title>
    <desc>Stryker (Brian Cox), a villainous former Army commander, holds the key to Wolverine's (Hugh Jackman) past and the future of the X-Men. This threat re-ignites the call for a mutant registration act. Stryker starts a full-out assault on Professor Xavier's (Patrick Stewart) mansion and school. After escaping his plastic cell, Magneto (Ian McKellen) proposes a partnership with Xavier and the X-Men to combat this new formidable enemy they both have in common.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260501150000 -0400" stop="20260501173000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>X-Men: The Last Stand</title>
    <desc>The discovery of a cure for mutations leads to a turning point for Mutants (Hugh Jackman, Halle Berry, Famke Janssen, Anna Paquin, Rebecca Romijn, Kelsey Grammer). They may now choose to give up their powers and become fully human or retain their uniqueness and remain isolated. War looms between the followers of Charles Xavier (Patrick Stewart), who preaches tolerance, and those of Magneto (Ian McKellen), who advocates survival of the fittest.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260501173000 -0400" stop="20260501200000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Wolverine</title>
    <desc>Lured to a Japan he hasn't seen since World War II, century-old mutant Wolverine (Hugh Jackman) finds himself in a shadowy realm of yakuza and samurai. Wolverine is pushed to his physical and emotional brink when he is forced to go on the run with a powerful industrialist's daughter (Tao Okamoto) and is confronted -- for the first time -- with the prospect of death. As he struggles to rediscover the hero within himself, he must grapple with powerful foes and the ghosts of his own haunted past.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260501200000 -0400" stop="20260501230000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>X-Men: Days of Future Past</title>
    <desc>Convinced that mutants pose a threat to humanity, Dr. Bolivar Trask develops the Sentinels, enormous robotic weapons that can detect a mutant gene and zero in on that person. In the 21st century, the Sentinels have evolved into highly efficient killing machines. With mutants now facing extinction, Wolverine volunteers to go back in time and rally the X-Men of the past to help change a pivotal moment in history and thereby save their future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260501230000 -0400" stop="20260502020000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>X-Men: Apocalypse</title>
    <desc>Worshiped as a god since the dawn of civilization, the immortal Apocalypse (Oscar Isaac) becomes the first and most powerful mutant. Awakening after thousands of years, he recruits the disheartened Magneto (Michael Fassbender) and other mutants to create a new world order. As the fate of the Earth hangs in the balance, Professor X (James McAvoy) and Raven (Jennifer Lawrence) lead a team of young X-Men to stop their seemingly invincible nemesis from destroying mankind.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260502020000 -0400" stop="20260502050000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Real Steel</title>
    <desc>Charlie Kenton used to be a prizefighter but lost his chance to win a title when heavy, towering robots took over the boxing ring. Now working as a small-time promoter, Charlie pieces together scrap metal into low-end fighters, barely earning enough to make it from one underground venue to the next. After hitting rock bottom, Charlie reluctantly teams with his estranged son, Max, to build and train a championship robot for a last shot at redemption.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260502050000 -0400" stop="20260502053000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>America 250th Anniversary Coins: Enduring Liberty Half Dollars</title>
    <desc>Join Mike Mezack for a special presentation of the 1776-2026 Enduring Liberty Half Dollars-one-year-only U.S. Mint issues honoring America's 250th Anniversary, including rare rolls and certified MS67 collectibles.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260502053000 -0400" stop="20260502060000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Freedom to Leave the House! Inogen Portable Oxygen</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260502060000 -0400" stop="20260502063000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260502063000 -0400" stop="20260502070000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260502070000 -0400" stop="20260502093000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Daredevil</title>
    <desc>Attorney Matt Murdock (Ben Affleck) is blind, but his other four senses function with superhuman sharpness. By day, Murdock represents the downtrodden. At night, he is Daredevil, a masked vigilante, a relentless avenger of justice. When Wilson Fisk (Michael Clarke Duncan) hires Bullseye (Colin Farrell) to kill Daredevil, Murdock must rely on his own senses and search out the conspirators against justice -- which may include his own girlfriend, Elektra (Jennifer Garner).</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260502093000 -0400" stop="20260502113000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Elektra</title>
    <desc>Assassin-for-hire Elektra works for a mysterious international organization known as the Hand, for which she kills her targets without question, and in a conspicuous red bustier, no less. When the Hand asks her to kill Mark Miller and his daughter, Abby, while they're on holiday, Elektra's conscience kicks in, and she decides to protect her targets rather than eliminate them. Of course, the Hand isn't so willing to let them off the hook.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260502113000 -0400" stop="20260502143000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Black Widow</title>
    <desc>Natasha Romanoff, aka Black Widow, confronts the darker parts of her ledger when a dangerous conspiracy with ties to her past arises. Pursued by a force that will stop at nothing to bring her down, Natasha must deal with her history as a spy, and the broken relationships left in her wake long before she became an Avenger.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260501163000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night at the Museum</title>
    <desc>A night watchman (Ben Stiller) at a museum of natural history makes a startling discovery: Thanks to the unleashing of an ancient Egyptian curse, the museum's animals, birds, bugs and other exhibits spring to life after the building closes, and former President Teddy Roosevelt (Robin Williams) is among those the hapless guard encounters.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian</title>
    <desc>Once the night guard at the Museum of Natural History, Larry Daley (Ben Stiller) is now a successful purveyor of infomercial products. Soon after learning that his museum friends have been shipped to the Smithsonian Institution, Larry receives a distress call from Jedediah, who warns him that four of history's greatest villains have come to life and are planning to take over the Smithsonian first,</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">National Treasure</title>
    <desc>Historian and code-breaker Ben Gates (Nicolas Cage) has been searching his whole life for a rumored treasure dating back to the creation of the United States. Joining an expedition led by fellow treasure hunter Ian Howe (Sean Bean), Gates finds an ice-locked Colonial ship in the Arctic Circle that contains a clue linking the treasure to the Declaration of Independence. But when Howe betrays him, G</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502003000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">National Treasure: Book of Secrets</title>
    <desc>When a long-missing page from the diary of assassin John Wilkes Booth suddenly resurfaces, it implicates the great-great grandfather of treasure hunter Ben Gates (Nicolas Cage) as a conspirator in Lincoln's death. Ben's globetrotting quest to prove his ancestor's innocence leads him to a closely guarded book containing the nation's deepest secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Meet ordinary people who have experienced the extraordinary power of prayer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>A chance meeting in the supermarket lets Jim in on Cheryl's secret: though she says the doctor told her to stay in bed, her doctor actually wants her to be active.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502043000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>The devil (James Lipton) comes to collect on a deal Jim made with him back when Jim was courting Cheryl.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim guilts the older kids into doing household chores after Jonathan's special blanket goes missing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>When Dana, Cheryl's sister and best friend, moves away, Jim realizes he must find Cheryl a new friend as soon as possible.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2026 Silver Eagle is here &amp; it is a once-in-a-lifetime coin!</title>
    <desc>Join your hosts Kevin Cash &amp; Cory Cady as we discuss the 250th Anniversary of America with the official "America 250" logo on a Silver American Eagle label; we are locking in orders for this iconic release, but coins are limited! Don't miss out!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Meet ordinary people who have experienced the extraordinary power of prayer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rare Silver &amp; Gold Coins</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nuwave Forever, Air Purifier With Never Replace Filters</title>
    <desc>B. Johnson shares the Nuwave Forever Air Purifier with NeverReplace Filters; get the smart Wi-Fi-enabled air purifier that helps achieve zero airborne pollutants without any additional replacement filters.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1776 - 2026 250th Anniversary Quarter Celebration Program</title>
    <desc>2026 will be one of the most historic years ever in U.S. coinage; join your host Mike Mezack to learn about the incredible U.S. Quarter program and get a chance at an exclusive P&amp;D Roll!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cindy Crawford talks about the latest breakthroughs in skincare</title>
    <desc>Join Cindy Crawford as she talks to real customers about the breakthrough skincare system that keeps them looking their best. Take a trip to the stunning French countryside to see the rare French melon that defies the aging process.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502103000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NEW! Shark PowerDetect with DuoClean Detect Technology</title>
    <desc>Meet the new Shark PowerDetect Upright Vacuum with features like DuoClean Detect Technology, self-cleaning brush roll and odor neutralizing and you will be cleaning faster, smarter and better!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502123500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Mouse Detective</title>
    <desc>Rodent supersleuth Basil and his bumbling partner must thwart evil Ratigan's plot to depose the Mouse Queen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502123500 +0000" stop="20260502144000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beverly Hills Chihuahua</title>
    <desc>Chloe, a pampered Chihuahua from Beverly Hills, gets an unwelcome taste of the real world when she gets lost in a tough part of Mexico. With no Rodeo Drive boutiques in sight, she is out of her element, until scrappy street dogs Delgado and Papi lend her a paw, helping her find her way home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502144000 +0000" stop="20260502164000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beverly Hills Chihuahua 2</title>
    <desc>Papi and Chloe's lives turn upside down when they have a litter of puppies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502164000 +0000" stop="20260502184000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tarzan</title>
    <desc>In this Disney animated tale, the orphaned Tarzan (Tony Goldwyn) grows up in the remote African wilderness, raised by the gentle gorilla Kala (Glenn Close). When a British expedition enters the jungle, Tarzan encounters the beautiful Jane (Minnie Driver) and recognizes that, like her, he's human. Falling in love with Jane, Tarzan is torn between embracing civilization and staying with his gorilla </desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502184000 +0000" stop="20260502204500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Luca</title>
    <desc>A boy tries to help his best friend hide a fantastical secret -- he turns into a sea monster whenever he comes in contact with water.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502204500 +0000" stop="20260502225500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Bug's Life</title>
    <desc>Flik is an inventive ant who's always messing things up for his colony. His latest mishap was destroying the food stores that were supposed to be used to pay off grasshopper Hopper. Now the strong-arming insect is demanding that the ants gather double the food or face annihilation. To avert disaster, Flik goes on a journey to recruit fighters to defend the colony. When he meets a band of high-flyi</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260502225500 +0000" stop="20260503000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ratatouille</title>
    <desc>Remy (Patton Oswalt), a resident of Paris, appreciates good food and has quite a sophisticated palate. He would love to become a chef so he can create and enjoy culinary masterpieces to his heart's delight. The only problem is, Remy is a rat. When he winds up in the sewer beneath one of Paris' finest restaurants, the rodent gourmet finds himself ideally placed to realize his dream.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>A stock market guru's fortune is stolen, setting Charlie and Rex on the trail of a very surprising thief...</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a young man is found dead of an apparent overdose, Dixon fiercely pursues a homicide investigation as an old unsolved case comes back to haunt her; Price and Maroun risk putting a witness in harm's way to expose their suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>As Benson and Carisi put a vengeful crime boss on trial, Fin tries to help a woman who was drugged and left for dead; Velasco takes drastic action to get information from a witness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a young man is found dead of an apparent overdose, Dixon fiercely pursues a homicide investigation as an old unsolved case comes back to haunt her; Price and Maroun risk putting a witness in harm's way to expose their suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>As Benson and Carisi put a vengeful crime boss on trial, Fin tries to help a woman who was drugged and left for dead; Velasco takes drastic action to get information from a witness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Bernard and Cosgrove are confronted with several suspects in the shooting of a headmaster at an elite private school; a teenager's life hangs in the balance as Price and Maroun debate who's more culpable -- the shooter or the enabler.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A car accident leads the detectives on a search for an ambulance driver assaulting his charges; Fin gives Detective Bruno a tour of Manhattan SVU.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Lives hang in the balance as detectives and prosecutors pursue justice in New York City. In cases ripped from the headlines, police investigate serious and often deadly crimes, weighing the evidence and questioning the suspects until someone is taken into custody. The district attorney's office then builds a case to convict the perpetrator by proving them guilty beyond a reasonable doubt. Working </desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>This groundbreaking series from executive producer Dick Wolf's "Law &amp; Order" franchise chronicles the ripped-from-the-headlines investigations of the NYPD's Special Victims Unit; led by courageous and compassionate Capt. Olivia Benson, this elite team includes Sgt. Odafin Tutuola, Detective Amanda Rollins, Officer Katriona Tamin and Deputy Chief Christian Garland, who focus on finding justice for </desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Lives hang in the balance as detectives and prosecutors pursue justice in New York City. In cases ripped from the headlines, police investigate serious and often deadly crimes, weighing the evidence and questioning the suspects until someone is taken into custody. The district attorney's office then builds a case to convict the perpetrator by proving them guilty beyond a reasonable doubt. Working </desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>This groundbreaking series from executive producer Dick Wolf's "Law &amp; Order" franchise chronicles the ripped-from-the-headlines investigations of the NYPD's Special Victims Unit; led by courageous and compassionate Capt. Olivia Benson, this elite team includes Sgt. Odafin Tutuola, Detective Amanda Rollins, Officer Katriona Tamin and Deputy Chief Christian Garland, who focus on finding justice for </desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Charlie asks Mac to beat up the waitress's new boyfriend; Dennis tries to convince Charlie that they are best friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After Mac's father is released from prison, Mac and Charlie stage their own deaths to save their lives; Frank, Dee and Dennis find unique ways of dealing with the loss.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Charlie asks Mac to beat up the waitress's new boyfriend; Dennis tries to convince Charlie that they are best friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After Mac's father is released from prison, Mac and Charlie stage their own deaths to save their lives; Frank, Dee and Dennis find unique ways of dealing with the loss.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a truck transporting liquid explosive is hijacked by criminals, Charlie and Rex find themselves in a race against time to prevent the case from blowing sky-high.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Major Crimes investigates a dark web marketplace, Charlie and Rex protect a witness in their home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After an elite hockey prospect is found dead, Charlie and Jesse disagree over the prime suspect in the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>The Major Crimes team is forced to turn against Jesse when he becomes the prime suspect in a bank robbery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a raw diamond is found at the crime scene of a murder, Major Crimes sets up a stakeout to take down the suspected gem smugglers; an undisclosed team connection threatens to derail the investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex receive an award for heroism while Major Crimes investigates an extremist threat.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After an elite hockey prospect is found dead, Charlie and Jesse disagree over the prime suspect in the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>The Major Crimes team is forced to turn against Jesse when he becomes the prime suspect in a bank robbery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502150000 +0000" stop="20260502161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Secrets of Hillsong</title>
    <desc>In 2015, a young pastor named Carl Lentz lands in New York City to spread the Word of Hillsong, an Australian megachurch; after allegations explode, Lentz is fired from his role and disappears; now he breaks his silence after more than two years.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502161500 +0000" stop="20260502173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Secrets of Hillsong</title>
    <desc>In their first interviews since their expulsion, Carl and Laura Lentz shed light onto the inner sanctum of Hillsong, detailing the burden of building the church's congregation and the response from leadership when it deemed Carl a liability.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260502173000 +0000" stop="20260502184500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Secrets of Hillsong</title>
    <desc>A group of international reporters discover Hillsong's founding father, Frank Houston, laid the groundwork for the church's pattern of covering up misconduct with non-disclosure agreements and hush money.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260501183000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 Rock</title>
    <desc>Liz tries to convince everyone that the show's hiatus is temporary; Jack turns to his nemesis, Devin Banks (Will Arnett), for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay takes Luke to the garage for some male bonding; Gloria and Claire take Lily dress shopping; Mitch, Cam, Alex and Manny spend a day at the museum; Phil helps Andy make an anniversary gift for his girlfriend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay is determined to get the adults' hotel suite upgraded; Claire tries to win back some money; Phil auditions to be a magician.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Mitch struggles to hide his genuine feelings about an unflattering wedding topper Cam's father made; Phil tries to help Gloria sell the apartment she had before Jay but they get sidetracked at a salon; Jay wants to host a nice family evening.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260501203000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>The family joins Phil as he travels to Australia to fulfill his mother's wish that he see the land where he was conceived.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Phil cannot handle the stress when he tells Claire an elaborate lie; Gloria is tasked with organizing this year's family portrait; Jay covertly enters Stella in a dog show.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay, Gloria and Manny challenge one another to try something new; Mitch and Cam sell a couple of their prized possessions to fund the wedding; the kids play a joke on Phil and Claire.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>The team fights to save the life of one of their own; Frost and Abrams butt heads with their patient.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Cruz's past comes back to haunt him; Severide prepares to teach an arson class at the academy; Mouch searches for a victim's next of kin.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Ruzek gets mixed up in a case after a late-night poker game is raided; afraid of becoming like his father, Ruzek struggles to stand down and allow Intelligence to carry out the investigation while he remains on leave.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>In an effort to get in shape, Charlie and Mac join a fitness group; it turns out to be a new way of life and maybe a cult.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The foursome demonstrate Chardee MacDennis for an interested board game executive, but the game sends things into chaos despite the gang's truce.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After falling out of the window, Frank thinks that it's 2006; the other three see this as a chance to fix their past mistakes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502023000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Dennis and Frank face Dee and Mac for control of the mountain; Charlie learns the slopes have their own set of rules.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>In an effort to get in shape, Charlie and Mac join a fitness group; it turns out to be a new way of life and maybe a cult.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502033000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The foursome demonstrate Chardee MacDennis for an interested board game executive, but the game sends things into chaos despite the gang's truce.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After falling out of the window, Frank thinks that it's 2006; the other three see this as a chance to fix their past mistakes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502043000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Dennis and Frank face Dee and Mac for control of the mountain; Charlie learns the slopes have their own set of rules.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>In an effort to get in shape, Charlie and Mac join a fitness group; it turns out to be a new way of life and maybe a cult.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The foursome demonstrate Chardee MacDennis for an interested board game executive, but the game sends things into chaos despite the gang's truce.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake is thrilled to work with Detective Dave Majors, until he learns Majors intends to ask Amy out; Charles and Gina want Terry to turn down a job offer at a private firm.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>When Wuntch lets Peralta work his dream case, Holt worries she's setting him up to fail; Amy, Rosa and Gina help Terry host a field trip.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>After an injury on the job, Jake is forced to take time off; Holt, Rosa and their significant others go on a double date.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502073000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 Rock</title>
    <desc>Liz and Kenneth try to track Tracy down; Jack helps Jenna with her new project; Pete challenges the writers and crew to a contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>When Jake and Amy go under cover to catch an identity thief, the investigation brings them closer; the precinct says an unexpected goodbye.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>After Holt is transferred, the precinct's new captain arrives, creating chaos; Amy and Jake face the consequences of their kiss.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob Marley: Roots of the Man</title>
    <desc>The life of Jamaican Robert Nesta Marley, known around the globe as reggae musician Bob Marley.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prince: My Name Is</title>
    <desc>An inside look at Prince's life, his innovative music, his mysterious persona, and his influence on the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Snoop Dogg: Uncaged</title>
    <desc>The story and legacy of Snoop Dogg; from the 1990s hip-hop scene to his status as a pop culture icon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of Joy</title>
    <desc>Fed up with the family's bad habits, Joy institutes a health boot camp for everyone; Rodney makes some changes to Joy's beloved tennis court.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of Joy</title>
    <desc>Joy recruits the millionaire matchmaker Patti Stanger to find the perfect man for her sister; Rodney takes Spanish lessons from his father-in-law.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Joanne amps up marriage pressure on her boyfriend; Ivory meets with a therapist to discuss her past; Denise receives some unsettling news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Denise needs to put together her fashion designs for Carnie Wilson but lacks focus; Lornalitz plans a trip to Puerto Rico; Rosie confronts an abusive ex.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Tensions grow between Denise and Lornalitz; Ivory considers having a baby on her own; Joanne's singing career stalls.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260501233000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Lornalitz hashes out the past with her abusive sister; Denise decides to jump back into the dating scene.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Better Criminal</title>
    <desc>A detective in the LAPD is forced to work for two warring crime syndicates while under an internal investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bodied</title>
    <desc>A progressive graduate student finds success and sparks outrage when his interest in battle rap as a thesis subject turns into a competitive obsession.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502043000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>Weezy's mom gets rejuvenated with a visit to a doctor who specializes in sexual health; Weezy meets Chai, who has invested in their true sexual self and made it their own, giving them a priceless return.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>If two's company, then three's a blast when Weezy and Sauanas Jackson take their friendship beyond the next level and try out three-way dating, using modern tech and old-school advice.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>Weezy works up a sweat when she finds out exactly what's so good about NFT's and Crypto; Weezy finds out there is serious money to be made.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>Sofia Franklyn joins Weezy in finding out the world of stripping isn't run by the women that power the industry; Reagan informs Weezy of the stripper strike; Candace Cain teaches the girls how to interact with the pole.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>Charlamagne tha God calls in to explain the challenges that still face Black queer creators in this industry; Weezy and Mandii B break down their rise to fame and how they make money while showing how wild it gets at their live shows.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sex Clinic</title>
    <desc>Hugo, who rarely uses condoms, comes in for an STI test; Lonan, who's a virgin, wants advice ahead of his "first time"; Esther wants the perfect vagina; Chelsie needs a new contraceptive implant fitted inside her arm.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blondie: Glass Heart</title>
    <desc>The story of Blondie and their rise from small clubs in New York City to selling out shows around the globe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Gabe plans a picturesque date on a sailboat, but it quickly goes awry; while working her first job at a carnival, Amy gets asked out by a corny manager; fresh out of being un-engaged, Victoria's date goes from romantic to creepy very quickly.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Excited to go on a date with her crush, Carlita is surprised to end up at his mother's house instead; "RuPaul's Drag Race" contestant Vanessa Vanjie Mateo goes on a date in Texas and when her date starts ignoring her, all hell starts breaking loose.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unbreakable</title>
    <desc>Cody and Jess dream of becoming parents; Jaimee sets her sights on becoming a hairdresser; online clairvoyant Jacqui looks to the future.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unbreakable</title>
    <desc>Jacqui faces her demons; Jaimee faces a major challenge; meeting Barney, who just wants to boogie.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of Joy</title>
    <desc>Joy wants a hit record of her own, and Rodney struggles to comply but worries that his greatest love may turn out to be his toughest client.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502123000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of Joy</title>
    <desc>Joy asks Rodney to take her to the studio, but he's got his hands full with clients; Joy plays instructor and gives the children a day on the tennis court.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of Joy</title>
    <desc>Joy is in full planning mode for RJ's birthday; Rodney takes Heavenly to the studio to record a song for RJ.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260502133000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House of Joy</title>
    <desc>Joy decides to go into the fashion business when she strikes upon an idea of making t-shirts with her favorite Bible verses; Rodney considers making a drastic change.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Mike's scouting trip for bears turns into an alpine goat hunt; Jake brings in the big dogs to settle an old score with a problem lion; Tom and Sean check beaver sets to see if their new trapping grounds will pay off.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Jake tracks a dangerous mother lion and her young; Kidd and Harry go on the offensive against a pack of coyotes that is targeting their cattle; Eustace and Raleigh track a rogue black bear that's been raiding a neighbor's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers peruse lockers in Orange, Calif.; Ivy uses an unusual landscaping tool to get a hole in one; Darrell's eye for upscale furniture leads him to a high-end hoard; Rene scores a video game cache.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501203000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Dave expands his inventory with a surprise medical device; a furniture locker proves enlightening to Rene; Ivy discovers unexpected green.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The Dotsons make their return in Adelanto, Calif.; Dave attempts to get his motors running; Darrell stumbles across a curious collection; Rene goes nuts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Rene encounters some unexpected "high" tech in Costa Mesa, Calif.; Darrell goes on a cross-cultural haberdashery journey; Kenny kick-starts his career with some "hot" pockets.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Mary finally locates a vintage goodie in El Monte, Calif.; Ivy uncovers decades-old family fun; Darrell revisits a childhood pastime.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Kenny finds relief in a locker; Brandi joins forces with Mary; Dave makes a historic discovery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Ivy can't get enough during a visit to Montebello, Calif.; Dave gets a taste of carnival fun; Brandi and Jarrod engage in some vintage-style shredding.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260501233000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders hope for big scores in trendy North Hollywood, Calif.; Jarrod and Brandi refuse to be seduced by the allure of Tinseltown treasures; solo buyer Rene makes trouble for everyone else.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Rene brings his father, Gunter, to the auction festivities in Montebello, Calif.; instigators Darrell and Brandon get sneaky; Ivy forges on despite an injury; Dave eyes a big score.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502003000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrod locates the party locker he has always wanted; Rene finds a new mobile business opportunity; Ivy's footwear makes a big impact.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Ivy finagles some vintage outdoor accessories; Dave is subjected to an unexpected audit; Emily's departure spoils a buyer's day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Darrell gets a chance to school his friend in Moreno Valley, Calif.; Dave's fortunes go up in flames; Jarrod and Brandi dive back in and hit bottom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Dave does not intend to lose another great locker when the buyers return to Palm Springs, Calif.; Rene attempts some inside information; Ivy must buy big in order to make the trip worth his time; Mary enlists an unlikely ally.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502023000 +0000" stop="20260502030100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Mary's unit brings out her inner voice; Kenny attempts to clothe America; Brandi and Jarrod get a leg up on the competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502030100 +0000" stop="20260502033100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers hope to land late-night treasures in Huntington Beach, Calif.; Darrell and Brandon look for great lockers on their home turf; Dave seeks a score or a sucker.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502033100 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>A marathon auction in Van Nuys, Calif., catches Jarrod and Brandi unprepared; Darrell faces the competition alone; Mary tries to prove herself as a serious buyer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Rene brings his father, Gunter, to the auction festivities in Montebello, Calif.; instigators Darrell and Brandon get sneaky; Ivy forges on despite an injury; Dave eyes a big score.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502043000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrod locates the party locker he has always wanted; Rene finds a new mobile business opportunity; Ivy's footwear makes a big impact.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Ivy finagles some vintage outdoor accessories; Dave is subjected to an unexpected audit; Emily's departure spoils a buyer's day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Darrell gets a chance to school his friend in Moreno Valley, Calif.; Dave's fortunes go up in flames; Jarrod and Brandi dive back in and hit bottom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Dave does not intend to lose another great locker when the buyers return to Palm Springs, Calif.; Rene attempts some inside information; Ivy must buy big in order to make the trip worth his time; Mary enlists an unlikely ally.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Mary's unit brings out her inner voice; Kenny attempts to clothe America; Brandi and Jarrod get a leg up on the competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502070100 +0000" stop="20260502073100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers hope to land late-night treasures in Huntington Beach, Calif.; Darrell and Brandon look for great lockers on their home turf; Dave seeks a score or a sucker.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260502073100 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>A marathon auction in Van Nuys, Calif., catches Jarrod and Brandi unprepared; Darrell faces the competition alone; Mary tries to prove herself as a serious buyer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>After a series of murders, Prentiss becomes suspicious of a former nemesis (Sebastian Roché) and fears for the safety of her team.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Prentiss prepares to confront her nemesis at last; the team asks J.J. to help find Prentiss and capture Doyle.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team must stop a gang of suspected murderers that is targeting a new victim nightly.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team must investigate targeted killings in Florida while each member is dealing with feelings about losing Prentiss.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A stalker in San Diego targets college students; Strauss scrutinizes the team after the loss of Prentiss.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team travels to a North Carolina town where one woman was found badly injured and another is missing, and discovers those may not be the only victims.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team investigates when bodies are found buried beneath the ocean floor off Florida; Morgan is rattled when his aunt thinks her missing daughter is one of the victims.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a suspected human trafficking ring; Hotchner suggests changes are coming; J.J. returns to the team.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A Senate committee questions the members of the BAU team; a familiar face may help keep the team united.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team investigates a series of murders in Oklahoma; Reid gives JJ and Prentiss the cold shoulder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>After a mass murder at an Internet security company, evidence indicates that the person responsible is not a typical serial killer; Prentiss is required to complete recertification training.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A killer targets survivors of a high-school massacre, who have gathered for a reunion; Hotch fears that his son is being bullied.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>MacGyver and the team must steal diamonds before terrorists beat them to it and trade the jewels for a weapon of mass destruction.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>When Murdoc drugs and kidnaps MacGyver, Mac must escape and join the team to save Murdoc's next victim.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>The team's Halloween plans are interrupted when the vice president's son's plane goes down with a mysterious prisoner on board.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Mac and the team attempt to extinguish a massive oil wellhead fire set by a rebel group in Nigeria.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>MacGyver uses a heater and hot sauce to help a key presidential candidate in Ecuador receive a heart transplant he desperately needs after a rebel group tries to sabotage delivery of the organ.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>MacGyver and Jack "steal" a priceless painting to draw out an infamous stolen art dealer; Riley's estranged father asks to be part of her life; Matty sends Bozer to a spy training camp.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Mac and the team follow mercenaries who are transporting stolen lethal nerve gas; Jack confronts Elwood about Riley; Bozer is pushed to his limit in spy school.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Mac must help college students stranded on a research ship in the Arctic Ocean; Jack kidnaps Elwood to find out what he's up to; Bozer's feelings toward Leanna grow stronger.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When the corpse of the host of a popular reality show is found partially decomposed in an outhouse, Brennan and Booth must separate the killer from many suspects; Booth discovers that Brennan juggles two relationships.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502150000 +0000" stop="20260502160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When Booth's son, Parker, finds a finger in a bird's nest, the team launches an investigation to find the rest of the body; Booth asks Sweets to psychoanalyze his son; Sweets confronts Hodgins about his attitude in the lab.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502160000 +0000" stop="20260502170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>A teen discovers a dismembered, headless body in a pool of purple water; the team struggles to find enough evidence to locate a killer until getting insight from Zack, who studies the case at his psychiatric facility.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502170000 +0000" stop="20260502180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Booth and Brennan investigate when the remains of a disliked office manager are found in a building elevator shaft; Angela and Hodgins try to figure out their altered relationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502180000 +0000" stop="20260502190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Skeletal remains with remnants of breast implants are found in the Chesapeake Bay; when the body's lower half is discovered, the team realizes that initial assumptions about the victim may be wrong.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260502190000 +0000" stop="20260502200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When the smashed remains of a famous artist are found in an impounded junkyard car, the team must race against the clock to find evidence of murder before the car is put on exhibit as the sculptor's ultimate display for the sake of his art.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hats Off to Love</title>
    <desc>Stella designs hats and fascinators for socialite Rosalind and meets her son Christian who's training a horse to compete in the Louisville Derby.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Taking a Shot at Love</title>
    <desc>Sparks fly between a ballet instructor and a professional hockey player as she tries to help him recover from the same injury that sidelined her dancing career.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Bride for Christmas</title>
    <desc>Aiden (Andrew Walker) bets his friends that he can convince a woman to marry him by Christmas, and he sets his sights on Jessie (Arielle Kebbel), a young woman who has sworn off serious relationships.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jingle Bell Run</title>
    <desc>Self-described bookworm Avery is paired with retired hockey star Wes to compete in a holiday race across America. The team struggles through themed challenges until romance runs its course.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche has trouble dealing with her father's plan to marry a much younger woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502023000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose's daughter and Dorothy's son visit their mothers at the same time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose, Blanche and Dorothy take a vacation at a resort that doesn't live up to its reputation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502033000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>While Dorothy is laid off from teaching, she finds work at the same museum where Blanche goes to work.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy and Blanche contrive an answer to Rose's personal ad.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502043000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Sophia takes action when a depressed, gun-toting Santa Claus threatens to ruin Christmas for her and her housemates.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche has trouble dealing with her father's plan to marry a much younger woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose's daughter and Dorothy's son visit their mothers at the same time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Waltons</title>
    <desc>John-Boy catches a friend stealing chickens, then learns that the man who was robbed has been shot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Waltons</title>
    <desc>The family prepares for the county fair; Olivia has a visit from her childhood sweetheart (Peter Donat), now wealthy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Waltons</title>
    <desc>A teenage orphan who once stayed with the Waltons returns with news of a tryout with a professional baseball scout.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Dr. Jack Morgan returns to Houston with the intention of resuming his romance with Reba, despite the fact that he is still married.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba advises Van to treat Cheyenne as an equal in the family budget, which prompts him to give her an allowance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>In an effort to save Brock and Barbra Jean from losing their home, Reba and Van buy their house and rent it out to them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502103000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>After the family makes fun of Reba's poor eyesight, she secretly gets laser eye surgery, which leaves her temporarily blind.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>A court-mandated anger-management session goes from bad to worse for Reba, Brock, Van and Cheyenne when Barbara Jean joins the fray.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502113000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>A physical reveals that Reba has high blood pressure; Van asks for Brock's advice on anniversary gifts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bridal Wave</title>
    <desc>A woman planning for her wedding at a resort meets a charming local right before the ceremony and has to choose between the man who can care for her financially or the man who truly understands her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Date With Love</title>
    <desc>A boy from a small town takes a big shot and asks his celebrity crush to prom on video. She says yes after the video goes viral, but things get a bit complicated when she realizes she might be falling for the boy's teacher.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502160000 +0000" stop="20260502180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Appetite for Love</title>
    <desc>Sparks fly when a woman (Taylor Cole) returns to her hometown in Tennessee to convince her stubborn ex-boyfriend (Andrew W. Walker) to sell his restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502180000 +0000" stop="20260502200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sweet Autumn</title>
    <desc>Aunt Dee splits her candy shop between her niece Maggie and maple farmer Dex. Following letters Dee left, the two uncover the reason for her decision during the Sweet Autumn festival.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260502200000 +0000" stop="20260502220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 27-Hour Day</title>
    <desc>Taking a break from her wellness empire, an entrepreneur develops a budding romance with a handsome man at a relaxing retreat.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wedding March 3: Here Comes the Bride</title>
    <desc>It's a full Valentine's Day weekend at the inn when Olivia and Mick host their families. Things get chaotic when Mick's sister decides to have her wedding at the inn that weekend and Mick's daughter announces plans to drop out of college.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wedding March 4: Something Old, Something New</title>
    <desc>Mick, Olivia and the rest of the Willow Lake Inn team help a couple set up the wedding of their dreams, but complications soon arise when the bride starts to have second thoughts about the plans.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Debbie Macomber's Dashing Through the Snow</title>
    <desc>A young woman becomes stranded in an airport at Christmastime and accepts a ride from a man who rented the last rental car in town. As they head north, a hint of romance develops when they encounter a few bumps on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Christmas Shepherd</title>
    <desc>Sally is heartbroken when her dog runs away during a thunderstorm. When she learns he was found by Mark, a widower, she travels to Boston to get him. Sally and Mark are given the best Christmas gifts of their lives when they fall in love.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Caroline reluctantly leaves the children with a baby sitter when Charles invites her on a 6-day trip to Mankato.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Substitute-teacher Caroline deals with a boy (Dirk Blocker) ridiculed for his limited literacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>After Laura's pet raccoon bites her and the dog, Charles and Caroline discover it is rabid.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Lou must contend with the new ranch hand and a threatening food truck when she returns from New York.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Lou is trapped at the ranch with the new ranch hand, Mitch.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>Two students receive some angelic motivation; as teachers, Jonathan and Mark motivate an overweight outcast and unscholarly athlete.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>A dog tries to lead Jonathan and Mark to his owners, a father and son trapped in a wrecked car.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Caroline reluctantly leaves the children with a baby sitter when Charles invites her on a 6-day trip to Mankato.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Substitute-teacher Caroline deals with a boy (Dirk Blocker) ridiculed for his limited literacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>After Laura's pet raccoon bites her and the dog, Charles and Caroline discover it is rabid.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>A mute coppersmith (Chuck McCann) plans to end a controversy over a proposed church bell.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Burning the midnight oil preparing for a school contest, Mary causes a fire, and Caroline orders her to withdraw.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Duke</title>
    <desc>Marine Sergeant Terry Pulaski returns from fighting in Afghanistan with scars that are both mental and physical. Feeling like a burden to his family, Terry takes off with his Border collie, Duke, to begin a life on the streets. But years later, when his faithful pet falls ill, he's forced to reach out for help and also bring himself to reconnect with the daughter he has long since left behind.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502160000 +0000" stop="20260502180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dater's Handbook</title>
    <desc>After reading a book about dating and changing her personality to find a lover, a woman realizes the man she wants is right in front of her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502180000 +0000" stop="20260502200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Unleashed</title>
    <desc>While hosting a puppy party, a woman tries to convince an uptight executive to give in to his daughter's pleas to adopt a rescue dog.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502200000 +0000" stop="20260502220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Favorite Wedding</title>
    <desc>Tess lasers through her best friend's wedding planning like the star doctor she hopes to become. After meeting the groom's best man, Tess maneuvers around him like a gurney in the emergency room, until she learns that he has a few moves of his own.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502220000 +0000" stop="20260502230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Witch</title>
    <desc>When two guests arrive at Grey House and are immediately at odds, Cassie uses her magic to bring them together; Sam tries to plan the perfect date for Cassie, but various nuisances keep getting in the way.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260502230000 +0000" stop="20260503000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Witch</title>
    <desc>The whole town is caught up in romance when Cassie helps Ben find an old film; Martha's promises to the town are in jeopardy when she overextends herself with the Middleton budget.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260503000000 +0000" stop="20260504000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Witch</title>
    <desc>When a visiting chef is unable to relax, Cassie arranges for her to spend a whole day at the stove stirring a special recipe to quiet her mind; Grace is presented with the Merriwick Wish Book for her birthday and encouraged to make an entry.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260501183000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bradley and Barney Walsh: Breaking Dad</title>
    <desc>The series begins in the iconic city of Sydney, where Brad's fear of heights is put to the test with a terrifying aerobatic flight and a trip on an extreme cable car.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Dawn's blindsided. Todd continues to manipulate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Theo plays cat-and-mouse with Todd, Megan's web of lies begins to unravel, Ronnie takes matters into his own hands, and Summer and Sarah get caught in the crossfire.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Neighbourhood</title>
    <desc>Graham makes a surprise visit to the triumphant alliance with a game-changing decision, and a friendly village BBQ explodes into a shouting match when tensions boil over.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News at Ten</title>
    <desc>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260501214500 +0000" stop="20260501234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The World's End</title>
    <desc>Sci-fi comedy film starring Simon Pegg and Nick Frost, 2013. Five friends recreate an epic pub crawl from 20 years earlier, but not everything about their hometown is as it seems.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260501234500 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shop on TV</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502025000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alan Titchmarsh's Gardening Club</title>
    <desc>Alan shares more tips and tricks as Martha Swales offers grow-your-own tips and Camilla Bassett-Smith explores a renowned Welsh horticultural gem.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502025000 +0000" stop="20260502040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502040500 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jason Atherton's Dubai Dishes</title>
    <desc>Jason invites us over for breakfast this time - he cooks a Spanish dish inspired by a full English.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic Park III</title>
    <desc>Action-adventure film sequel starring Sam Neill and William H Macy, 2001. A couple with a hidden agenda convince Dr Alan Grant to return to the region that housed Jurassic Park.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502082500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Your Weekend with Alan Titchmarsh</title>
    <desc>Joining Alan at Manor Farm this time are Tom Bradby, Les Dennis and Strictly's Janette and Aljaz. We also we meet Poppy the Pedigree Sussex cow who made headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502082500 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">James Martin's Saturday Morning</title>
    <desc>James is joined by presenter, DJ and I'm a Celebrity... Get Me Out of Here! star Kelly Brook, chefs Tommy Banks and Alex Dilling, and forager Alysia Vasey.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dermot's Taste of Ireland</title>
    <desc>Dermot begins his Irish food tour in the Glens of Antrim, getting hands-on at a traditional farm and dining like a king at Glenarm Castle with chef Paula McIntyre.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502113000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">James Martin's American Adventure</title>
    <desc>In this leg of his American adventure, James enters Los Angeles driving a vintage Porsche and drops in on his old friend and chef-to-the-stars Wolfgang Puck.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502121500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502121500 +0000" stop="20260502150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Racing: Live from Newmarket</title>
    <desc>Ed Chamberlin and Francesca Cumani present live racing from Newmarket - where the 2,000 Guineas takes centre stage - Thirsk and Goodwood.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502150000 +0000" stop="20260502153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point: Best Ever Finals</title>
    <desc>A look back at the game show's most thrilling end games as plucky players and famous faces alike take on the machine for its jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502153000 +0000" stop="20260502163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as Steve from Shropshire, Uzy from Birmingham, Aaron from Horsham and Diane from St Helens join forces in an attempt to take home thousands of pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502163000 +0000" stop="20260502164500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Evening News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502164500 +0000" stop="20260502170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502170000 +0000" stop="20260502180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Motsi Mabuse, Rob Delaney, and Amber Rose Gill join Stephen Mulhern to 'say what they see' and guess well-known phrases for their chance to win 50,000 pounds for charity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502180000 +0000" stop="20260502200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Britain's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>Britain's Got Talent goes live on Saturday nights for the Semi-Finals as the acts who impressed the judges during auditions must now compete for a place in the grand finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260502200000 +0000" stop="20260502210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It'll Be Alright on the Night</title>
    <desc>Tom Allen celebrates backstage bloopers and live blunders featuring our favourite TV shows and stars - expect nightmares for Ant and Dec, Bradley Walsh, Jill Scott and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260501175500 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Sitting Off the Dock of the Bay: Nostalgic police drama series. When a pirate radio station invades the airwaves, Blaketon dispatches Nick to investigate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Comedy-drama series. When Louisa's mum Eleanor arrives in Portwenn unexpectedly, neither she nor Martin are pleased by her solution to their baby's wailing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Comedy-drama series. PC Penhale has a surprise visit from his ex-wife, Louisa's mother Eleanor goes on a date, and Morwenna arrives at the surgery with an injured foot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">DCI Banks</title>
    <desc>Part One: Crime drama. When a journalist is found dead in a remote village, Banks notices a connection between the case and a mysterious death in the 1980s.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">DCI Banks</title>
    <desc>Part Two: Detective series. Banks races to locate a mysterious recording that appears to connect Jack Barber and the members of The Crystal Kiss together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260501225000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lewis</title>
    <desc>When Lewis and Hathaway investigate a young orphan's death, forensic evidence leads them to suspect a connection to the reformation of an old rock band.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502005500 +0000" stop="20260502012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">On the Buses</title>
    <desc>Enduring '70s British sitcom about a chirpy bus driver and his conductor pal. Blakey discovers that Stan and Jack are biting the hand that feeds them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502012000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lewis</title>
    <desc>When a babysitter is found dead, Lewis and Hathaway are drawn into diverse new worlds including squats, swinging suburbia, primate labs and fetish photography.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lewis</title>
    <desc>Lewis and Hathaway investigate when a controversial American academic is murdered after speaking at Oxford's Department of Criminology.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Endeavour</title>
    <desc>Crime drama. A baffling suicide, an anguished father searching for his missing daughter, and the robbery of medieval treasures strains the talents of DC Endeavour Morse.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Agatha Christie's Marple</title>
    <desc>Crime thriller. The town of Lymstock is thrown into turmoil when an outbreak of anonymous hate mail results in a woman's suicide and the letters become deadlier.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>The annual Wild West fair in the village of Ford Florey becomes terrifyingly real when locals clash over the ownership of a piece of wasteland.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502150000 +0000" stop="20260502170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Barnaby's wife is unsure if she might be responsible for a dead body found in a cemetery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502170000 +0000" stop="20260502190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>When Zoe sees a woman jump from a bridge and disappear underwater, Barnaby and Jones investigate the drowning.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502190000 +0000" stop="20260502210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Betrayal and blackmail fester as plans to re-enact an 1860 prize fight turn nasty and even Barnaby finds his judgement clouded. With John Nettles and Kevin McNally.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502210000 +0000" stop="20260502225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Grace</title>
    <desc>Crime drama. When a woman is discovered murdered in her flat, the evidence first points to a burglary gone wrong in a case that conceals a chilling secret.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260502225000 +0000" stop="20260503000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Touch of Frost</title>
    <desc>DI Frost investigates whether three male bodies found buried naked in the shape of a triangle are part of a satanic ritual.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Pickers</title>
    <desc>Mike Wolff has injured his back - but cannot afford to take time off to recuperate - and the guys make a big mistake with a Iowan farmer's collection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ice Road Truckers</title>
    <desc>Dalton rookie Ray Veilleux drives into a trucker's worst nightmare when he's distracted for a second.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ice Road Truckers</title>
    <desc>Ray Veilleux spins out into oncoming big rigs, Jack Jessee battles a 200-ton monster haul to Prudhoe, and Alex Debogorski risks a bust by the DOT.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting action from the world of All Elite Wrestling - the roster features world-class talent including Jon Moxley, MJF, Ricochet and Adam Page.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260501230500 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the Ring</title>
    <desc>Wrestling documentary series. A private Boeing 757 flight descends into a nightmare and erupts into one of wrestling's most infamous scandals.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502005500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sweeney</title>
    <desc>Classic '70s police drama series. Regan and Carter go after a man implicated in a robbery in which a policeman was shot, but is the past clouding Regan's judgement.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502005500 +0000" stop="20260502012500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two and a Half Men</title>
    <desc>American sitcom about a well-off bachelor. Charlie attempts to start a relationship with one of Jake's teachers, but it comes at a price for both of the boys.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502012500 +0000" stop="20260502015000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two and a Half Men</title>
    <desc>American sitcom about a well-off bachelor whose life is disrupted. Jake's adoration for his mother's new boyfriend makes his own father feel inadequate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502015000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502023000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorsport Mundial</title>
    <desc>This programme brings you up to date with the latest action from the world of motorsport and features race coverage, insights, and behind-the-scenes footage from the best series.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorsport Mundial</title>
    <desc>This programme brings you up to date with the latest action from the world of motorsport and features race coverage, insights, and behind-the-scenes footage from the best series.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>Brian Moore presents FA Cup Fifth Round action from the 1984/85 season - highlights include Third Division York City against Liverpool and Everton facing non-league Telford United.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502072500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>Brian Moore presents action from the 1984/85 football season including match highlights of Arsenal vs Manchester United, Nottingham Forest vs Southampton, and Celtic vs Aberdeen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502072500 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">E1 World Championship Highlights</title>
    <desc>Live coverage of the E1 Powerboats Series with action from the second round of the season, live from Lake Como in Italy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Racing: The Opening Show</title>
    <desc>Oli Bell and the team are at Newmarket ahead of the first classics of the season - the 1,000 and 2,000 Guineas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>Brian Moore introduces third round FA Cup highlights from January 1972 as Bobby Charlton's Manchester United travel to Southampton and West Ham entertain Luton Town.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502103000 +0000" stop="20260502104500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Football Rivalries: Arsenal v Spurs</title>
    <desc>Clips from famous matches between Arsenal and Tottenham Hotspur.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502104500 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hornblower</title>
    <desc>Conclusion of a two-part story about CS Forester's famous seafaring hero. Captain Sawyer is removed from command as the lieutenants must now evade a charge of mutiny.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Formula E Live</title>
    <desc>Formula E returns to Berlin for Round Seven. German driver Pascal Wehrlein can expect plenty of support from the locals - he currently tops the Driver's Championship.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502153000 +0000" stop="20260502154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Snooker v Darts</title>
    <desc>Neil Foulds and Chris Mason discuss whether it's harder to get a 147 break in snooker or complete a nine-dart finish in darts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502154500 +0000" stop="20260502164500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Pickers</title>
    <desc>Mike Wolff and Frank Fritz explore an 1879 opera house left untouched since the 1930s, and Danielle receives some information on a rare gas pump.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502164500 +0000" stop="20260502171500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">River Monsters</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Wade goes deep into the forbidding Alaskan wilderness to visit two big lakes where legend says that people have been vanishing for hundreds of years from.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502171500 +0000" stop="20260502181500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Living Daylights</title>
    <desc>Bond film starring Timothy Dalton and Jeroen Krabbe, 1987. 007 is called into action when the successful defection of a Soviet general to the West is followed by his kidnapping.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260502181500 +0000" stop="20260502182000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Chasing the jackpot this time are brothers Laurence and Ben from Hampshire, friends Karen and Helene from Scotland, and workmates Oliver and Franklyn from Huddersfield.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Battling it out this time are friends Rebecca and Rachel from Liverpool, married couple Kaz and Rich from North Wales, and Deb with her mum Emily from Solihull and London.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Floor</title>
    <desc>Rob Brydon hosts another edition of high-stakes trivia as only 41 contestants remain in the game of cutthroat strategy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260501235500 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>A family team of five from Southport take on a series of Top 10 list questions as they attempt to win 125,000 pounds. Quiz show, hosted by Warwick Davis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502005000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern as Felix takes to the hot seat hoping to turn the tables and take the Banker for all he's worth.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Chasing the jackpot this time are brothers Laurence and Ben from Hampshire, friends Karen and Helene from Scotland, and workmates Oliver and Franklyn from Huddersfield.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>A team of five Southampton uni friends take on the Tenable Tower as they attempt to win 125,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Floor</title>
    <desc>Rob Brydon hosts another edition of high-stakes trivia as only 41 contestants remain in the game of cutthroat strategy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502150000 +0000" stop="20260502160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the rapid and ruthless quiz as contestants Zeus and Sam, Gary and Kim, and Nicola and Brad take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502160000 +0000" stop="20260502170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Uche joins Stephen Mulhern as she opens the famous red boxes in the hope of becoming a jackpot winner and avoiding joining the 1p Club.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502170000 +0000" stop="20260502180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Battling it out this time are friends Rebecca and Rachel from Liverpool, married couple Kaz and Rich from North Wales, and Deb with her mum Emily from Solihull and London.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502180000 +0000" stop="20260502190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Seeking supremacy this time are sisters Hinisha and Darshika from Leicester, Brian and his son Paul from Runcorn, and best mates Tasha and Leanne from Basildon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502190000 +0000" stop="20260502200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Facing the puzzlewords this time are couple Kate and Stu from Worcestershire and two teams from Wiltshire, couple Robbie and Aimee and Debs with her son Ben.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502200000 +0000" stop="20260502210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Romesh Ranganathan's Parents' Evening</title>
    <desc>Things get tense as Alison Hammond and her son Aidan, Iain Stirling and his mum Alison, and Carol Vorderman and her son Cameron expose their faith in each other.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502210000 +0000" stop="20260502220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260502220000 +0000" stop="20260503000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>While investigating a naval commander's death, the team undergoes required psych evaluations.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>After a suicide bomber tries to assassinate the Belgravian Defense minister, the team must protect his daughter, who is studying in the U.S.; Gibbs looks into the death of a Marine who was killed in the bombing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A murdered Marine's fingertips and teeth are found in a stolen purse.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The brutal murder of a former investigative assistant connects to a crew planning to rob a woman's warehouse; a new special agent (Sarah Jane Morris) arrives at the office.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Gibbs is suspicious when Vance asks him to interrogate a teenage boy accused of killing his retired Marine father.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A message in blood left by a murdered officer leads NCIS to a manuscript that may contain classified information.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Special Agent Barrett investigates a death she believes is connected to a series of murders; Ziva introduces her boyfriend to the team.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A Navy lieutenant's murder is caught on tape by a Pentagon security camera; Gibbs reveals that Agent Barrett and her team will take over a case involving a serial killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502020300 +0000" stop="20260502030300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Tony revisits his days as a detective in Baltimore after learning that his former partner is likely the latest victim of the port-to-port killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502030300 +0000" stop="20260502040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>After receiving new evidence that the Port-to-Port killer has infiltrated the agency, the team races to track him down.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502040100 +0000" stop="20260502050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Special Agent Barrett investigates a death she believes is connected to a series of murders; Ziva introduces her boyfriend to the team.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502050100 +0000" stop="20260502060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A Navy lieutenant's murder is caught on tape by a Pentagon security camera; Gibbs reveals that Agent Barrett and her team will take over a case involving a serial killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502060400 +0000" stop="20260502070400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Tony revisits his days as a detective in Baltimore after learning that his former partner is likely the latest victim of the port-to-port killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502070400 +0000" stop="20260502080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>After receiving new evidence that the Port-to-Port killer has infiltrated the agency, the team races to track him down.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502080200 +0000" stop="20260502083200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pain Relief Revealed</title>
    <desc>Discover the hidden story of OmegaXL with John Walsh. He dives deep into the groundbreaking supplement that promises hope and relief for millions battling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502083200 +0000" stop="20260502090200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joint Relief Revolution</title>
    <desc>Join Connie Craig-Carroll and health visionary Ken Meares as they uncover OmegaXL, the groundbreaking natural supplement transforming lives by tackling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502090200 +0000" stop="20260502093200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502093200 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joint Relief Revolution</title>
    <desc>Join Connie Craig-Carroll and health visionary Ken Meares as they uncover OmegaXL, the groundbreaking natural supplement transforming lives by tackling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502103000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Natural Blood Pressure Management</title>
    <desc>Cardiologist Dr. Ernst von Schwarz, M.D. shows how to manage your blood pressure naturally and help protect your heart for life with My Best Heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502113000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502123000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Have Thinning Hair? Keranique Can Help Regrow Beautiful, Thicker Hair!</title>
    <desc>If you have thinning hair or hair loss, Keranique can help regrow thicker, longer and fuller hair. Keranique is the number 1 hair regrowth system for women. Regain your confidence with beautiful, thicker and fuller hair in just 3 easy steps!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joint Relief Revolution</title>
    <desc>Join Connie Craig-Carroll and health visionary Ken Meares as they uncover OmegaXL, the groundbreaking natural supplement transforming lives by tackling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260502133000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NEW! Shark PowerDetect with DuoClean Detect Technology</title>
    <desc>Meet the new Shark PowerDetect Upright Vacuum with features like DuoClean Detect Technology, self-cleaning brush roll and odor neutralizing, and you will be cleaning faster, smarter and better!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Celebrity stylist April Roomet and rapper Jeezy inspire the rappers to amp up their style; the rappers must earn money to shop for a photo shoot; one rapper copies another; an artist struggles to break free from a celebrity comparison.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Rappers iHeartMemphis and iAmDLOW give the contestants a lesson on generating buzz; the artists are challenged to create a signature dance that they must write, record and shoot a viral video for; one young artist struggles with dancing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>After the rappers get feedback from a focus group, one gets overconfident while another experiences a reality check; mentor Jadakiss tries to help the young rappers turn haters into fans.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>JD brings the group to his interview with the Durtty Boyz, where they throw the rappers an unexpected challenge; one rapper is shaken to the core.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>JD mixes up the management teams and then challenges the rappers to write, record and shoot a music video with past winners of "The Rap Game," Miss Mulatto and Mani.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>JD splits the young rappers into two teams and challenges them to perform at a high school halftime show.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Kelly Rowland and her personal trainer visit the five young rappers; JD tests the children on both their mental and physical stamina in the "Catch the Beat" challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Bow Wow helps hone the young rappers' media skills to prepare them for a press conference, television interview and photo shoot; Nova throws another artist under the bus.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Before signing, JD tests the young rappers in a battle rap; John John Da Don, Arsonal, Charlie Clips, DNA and Calicoe prepare the group; a rapper makes an unforgettable decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>After thirteen weeks of challenges, the artists prepare for their final performance; JD makes a decision, and awards one rapper the chain and the contract.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Kelly Rowland and her personal trainer visit the five young rappers; JD tests the children on both their mental and physical stamina in the "Catch the Beat" challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Bow Wow helps hone the young rappers' media skills to prepare them for a press conference, television interview and photo shoot; Nova throws another artist under the bus.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Before signing, JD tests the young rappers in a battle rap; John John Da Don, Arsonal, Charlie Clips, DNA and Calicoe prepare the group; a rapper makes an unforgettable decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>After thirteen weeks of challenges, the artists prepare for their final performance; JD makes a decision, and awards one rapper the chain and the contract.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Ghost Stories</title>
    <desc>After losing her boyfriend, Tracy strikes a deal with the devil; Fairuza is attacked by a ferocious entity; Della is saved by her guardian angel; a spirit forces Patrick into a battle for his life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Ghost Stories</title>
    <desc>Linda and her sister discover an old house with a murderous history; Carlos is rescued by a spirit; Victoria was raised in house built on a burial ground; Dot realizes a ghost is watching over her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>In week five of the competition, the eight remaining contestants prepare to do battle in the categories of literature &amp; fine arts and vocabulary.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pain Relief Revealed</title>
    <desc>Discover the hidden story of OmegaXL with John Walsh. He dives deep into the groundbreaking supplement that promises hope and relief for millions battling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502113000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502123000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502133000 +0000" stop="20260502160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502160000 +0000" stop="20260502170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Wedding day has come and gone, and now the three newlywed couples are off on their honeymoons; one couple hits an instant roadblock at the airport.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502170000 +0000" stop="20260502180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Honeymoons continue for two of the couples, as they start to familiarize themselves with their new spouses; explosive revelations come to light about Mia's past.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260502180000 +0000" stop="20260502190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Back to reality for Danielle and Bobby, and Amber and Dave, as they return from honeymoons; Tristian feels betrayed by Mia's dishonesty.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260501175000 +0000" stop="20260501185500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Location, Location, Location</title>
    <desc>We catch up with Steph and Mark, who have turned their Nottingham nest into every inch the family home. And did stylish pair Elliot and James achieve their Windsor wonderland.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260501185500 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It</title>
    <desc>Phil revisits Alex and Danny who were in turmoil over their semi in Preston. Was Kirstie's momentous conversion a hit, or did Phil's turnkey temptations come up trumps.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Panda</title>
    <desc>The Song of the Sirens: Comical French drama from Walter Presents. Will investigating a school of mermaids help Panda reel in a murderer? In French/subs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260501210500 +0000" stop="20260501221000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Cyclist and dad-of-three John has crashed face first into a car. Adrian, 89, arrives at A&amp;E with chest pains. He reminisces about his career as governor of Pentonville prison.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260501221000 +0000" stop="20260501231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Beth, 68, is rushed to A&amp;E after falling down her stairs and breaking her ankle. Leigh, 67, has head injuries after being knocked off his bicycle in a hit-and-run incident.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260501231500 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Emergency Helicopter Medics</title>
    <desc>The air ambulance teams work quickly to save Susan's life following a major gas explosion. A boating accident leaves holidaymaker Carol with a partially amputated foot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502002000 +0000" stop="20260502012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Cyclist and dad-of-three John has crashed face first into a car. Adrian, 89, arrives at A&amp;E with chest pains. He reminisces about his career as governor of Pentonville prison.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502012000 +0000" stop="20260502022500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Beth, 68, is rushed to A&amp;E after falling down her stairs and breaking her ankle. Leigh, 67, has head injuries after being knocked off his bicycle in a hit-and-run incident.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502022500 +0000" stop="20260502025500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Food Unwrapped</title>
    <desc>Jimmy Doherty visits Europe's biggest brewery. Kate Quilton challenges Matt Tebbutt to make crumpets. Plus: why is maple syrup so pricey.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502025500 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502075500 +0000" stop="20260502085500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Themis and Paolo love the beaches of Kapparis in Cyprus and want to buy their very own holiday home there. Jasmine Harman shows them five amazing properties for their £180,000 budget.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502085500 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Gaynor offers a warm welcome to her guests at the Nateby Inn B&amp;B in Cumbria. A cask-rolling competition turns out to be a barrel of laughs, but one guest hogs the limelight at dinner.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Graham and Julia host at Outfields Farm B&amp;B in Ravensden, Bedfordshire, where they treat their guests to an adrenaline-fuelled afternoon at an indoor skydiving centre.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502103500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Bob Osborne takes a laid-back approach to running the At Home B&amp;B in Chiswick, west London. His guests appreciate the art in his communal living space, but they're soon dishing the dirt.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502103500 +0000" stop="20260502110500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Andrew and Clare host at the Ammonite Lodge guest house in Chard, Somerset, where they hope to bowl their guests over with a traditional game of skittles.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502110500 +0000" stop="20260502113500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's the final day of the competition and everyone meets for one last time to settle some scores and find out how much they've been paid and who's been crowned the best B&amp;Bers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502113500 +0000" stop="20260502124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Grand Designs</title>
    <desc>Jonathan and Deborah are building a semi-subterranean, Hollywood Hills-style mansion with a swimming pool on a hemmed-in site in north London. But what will the neighbours think.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502124000 +0000" stop="20260502134000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Grand Designs</title>
    <desc>Kevin McCloud meets Kevin McCabe, an exponent of the ancient art of cob building, who wants to construct a castle entirely of mud. The huge scale of the task soon becomes clear.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502134000 +0000" stop="20260502144000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Carol longs to buy a holiday home on the beautiful island of Lanzarote for all her family to enjoy. Can Jasmine Harman find her perfect place on the buzzing east coast for £150,000.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502144000 +0000" stop="20260502151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>PR manager Emmy hopes to impress her guests with locally sourced Somerset produce. But she has a disaster with her hollandaise sauce.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502151500 +0000" stop="20260502155000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Radio DJ Steve serves up a cross between comfort food and fine dining. But he feels the pressure, and an unwanted ingredient ends up on one guest's plate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502155000 +0000" stop="20260502162000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Diminutive forklift driver Mel plans an exotic menu, including her version of duck vindaloo, and surprises her guests by breaking into song.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502162000 +0000" stop="20260502165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Business owner and muscleman Alan hopes to create a Zen evening. But with rotten beans, tofu cheesecake and soggy noodles on the menu, it could be a recipe for disaster..</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502165000 +0000" stop="20260502172500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Car dealer Andy is confident that his fine dining and swanky home will give his night the edge. But Mel isn't afraid to tell him exactly what she thinks of his fancy food.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260502172500 +0000" stop="20260502175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The competition begins in Newquay, where Oleg and Emma are banking on the amazing sea views and an afternoon of surfing setting them apart.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260501183000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Friendzone</title>
    <desc>Peter's in love with best friend Vic and must tell her before she moves away. Christie dreams of playing professional hockey... and taking things further with best friend Dylan.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just Tattoo Of Us</title>
    <desc>Mum and daughter besties Clare and Chloe put motherly love to the test. Girlfriends Shai and Abbie put their future on the line. And Geordie Shore's Beau dishes up some brotherly banter.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just Tattoo Of Us</title>
    <desc>Love fills the air as Geordie Shore's Thalia and mum Vanessa get inked. All's not well for Liam and Amber. Will jokers Hollie and Chelsea see the funny side of their tattoos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bar Rescue</title>
    <desc>In Tucson, Arizona, a struggling bar owner faces closure after five years. Jon Taffer tackles roaches, broken equipment and fading passion to save the business.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lenny Kravitz: MTV Unplugged</title>
    <desc>Brace yourself as we relive Lenny Kravitz's iconic MTV Unplugged! This episode of Unplugged was taped in New York City in April of 1994.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Help I Sexted My Boss</title>
    <desc>William Hanson and Jordan North help you navigate the challenges of modern life, answering your 21st century questions and finding solutions to everyday dilemmas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tattoo Fixers</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502001000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bar Rescue</title>
    <desc>Jon Taffer sends legendary mixologist, Phil Wills to rescue a filthy bar in Oxnard, California and help a newlywed couple realize their dreams.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Help I Sexted My Boss</title>
    <desc>William Hanson and Jordan North help you navigate the challenges of modern life, answering your 21st century questions and finding solutions to everyday dilemmas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502014500 +0000" stop="20260502023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master: Battle of the Sexes</title>
    <desc>The Artists must put needle to skin consistently to take out their Competitors. The Battle of the Sexes continues for $100K and the title of Ink Master.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502023500 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Lolo Wood get wild while partying in 'bar beserk', meet some unique huskies in 'weirdo wolves' and discover not everyone can handle two wheels in 'can't handle their hog'.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Jersey Shore star Vinny debuts his pristine Manhattan apartment. Soccer player Kai Novak shows off her fun Cali crib. Then, Bachelor star Nick Viall takes us around his L.A. home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502052000 +0000" stop="20260502061000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>Myranda finds that love isn't the answer to everything when she gets pregnant. As her mum battles substance abuse, Myranda and her boyfriend struggle with preparing for a baby on their own.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502061000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>Tyler posts a video of Carly which upsets Brandon and Teresa. Maci continues to struggle with Ryan about co-parenting. Amber is hurt by Gary because he won't let Leah spend the night.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Geek Australia</title>
    <desc>Sophie Monk introduces the new beauties and geeks as they set off on an exciting journey to learn from each other. Will any of these couples find love.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Geek Australia</title>
    <desc>Sophie Monk throws the geeks into the beauties' worlds, in a challenge set to test the geeks' confidence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502103000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Geek Australia</title>
    <desc>The beauties and geeks take over KIIS FM for a radio challenge and get permanently paired at an '80s prom night.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: Disasterclass</title>
    <desc>Reese was used to getting his way with women until he met Jesica. When a shady set of phone numbers sparks Reese's suspicions, he calls on Nev and Kamie to investigate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: Disasterclass</title>
    <desc>Emma is in over her head after an online relationship with EJ turns into a stalker who won't leave her alone! Will Nev and Kamie be able to find and stop EJ before he goes too far.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: Disasterclass</title>
    <desc>Tony met Tiana two years ago and became smitten with her, but big red flags send him to Catfish for help. Nev and Kamie embark on a wild goose chase, hoping to bring Tony answers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502150000 +0000" stop="20260502160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: Disasterclass</title>
    <desc>Caitlyn calls on Nev and Max to help separate the fact from fiction of her courtship with Kenton. Kenton insists she and her daughter move to Kentucky but is Kenton all he claims to be.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502160000 +0000" stop="20260502170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: Disasterclass</title>
    <desc>After five years of talking to Matt, Kim is ready to meet up. As Max and Nev try to bring the two together, they uncover buried secrets that threaten to drive a wedge between the couple.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502170000 +0000" stop="20260502180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: Disasterclass</title>
    <desc>Smart, single mum Miracle fell for Javonni, a dreamy-eyed Instagrammer. With Max on hiatus, Nev teams up with tv personality Charlamagne to take Miracle on a hunt for the man of her dreams.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502180000 +0000" stop="20260502190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: Disasterclass</title>
    <desc>Tyreme met the beautiful Tomorrow online over 9 months ago. Tyreme is ready to uproot his life to be with her. Will Nev and Max be able help Tyreme finally meet his Tomorrow.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260502190000 +0000" stop="20260502200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: Disasterclass</title>
    <desc>Ramon met Paola on Facebook and established an exclusive online relationship. But after many failed attempts to video chat, is she really who he thinks she is.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Beautiful Place to Die: A Martha's Vineyard Mystery</title>
    <desc>After being forced into early retirement, former detective Jeff Jackson returns to a quiet life on Martha's Vineyard. Quiet, at least, until a body washes up and he's drawn back into crime solving.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddled With Deceit: A Martha's Vineyard Mystery</title>
    <desc>Former Detective Jeff Jackson teams up with Dr. Zee Madeiras to track down their friend's missing emerald brooch, a thief and a murderer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ships in the Night: A Martha's Vineyard Mystery</title>
    <desc>Former Detective Jeff Jackson teams up with a local doctor to investigate the murder of an art gallery manager.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Martha's Vineyard Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When a local waitress is found dead on the beach and a mysterious deposit appears in Zee's bank account, Martha's Vineyard proves to be all but the simple, scenic life Jeff Jackson was after.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's friend is hit by a car shortly after being notified of her sister's death.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>The descendant of a tribe once inhabiting Cabot Cove has a land grant claiming the town as Indian territory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Visiting her nephew Grady in New York, Jessica probes a murder involving the family of his college buddy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Amos Tupper must entertain his sister who has left her husband, but complications arise when his brother-in-law is murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>An unhappy wife, a government official, a lovesick assistant and a self-centered astronomer are suspects in the murder of a young executive.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's friend is hit by a car shortly after being notified of her sister's death.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>The descendant of a tribe once inhabiting Cabot Cove has a land grant claiming the town as Indian territory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Visiting her nephew Grady in New York, Jessica probes a murder involving the family of his college buddy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>When Seth's estranged brother is murdered, Jessica must figure out if a cursed ruby from India is responsible.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>When Jessica visits a celebrated playwright friend, she encounters murder and an unexpected marriage proposal.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica hears the confession of a dying hit man who has just completed an assignment, only to find the victim isn't dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica suspects heirs and employees when a corpse appears in an elderly vintner's (Eli Wallach) cellar.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curious Caterer Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Goldy agrees to cater an elaborate wedding, but a dead groom and a missing bridezilla brings her together with Tom again.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502160000 +0000" stop="20260502180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curious Caterer Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Goldy Berry's medieval feast at Hyde Castle gets interrupted by a murder. She teams up with Detective Schultz to solve the mystery before the killer strikes again.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502180000 +0000" stop="20260502200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curious Caterer Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Goldy Berry caters a VIP concert and goes on a date with Tom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502200000 +0000" stop="20260502220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crossword Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When Tess prepares for a crossword challenge against a supercomputer, the engineer behind it gets murdered, spurring her and Logan to seek answers before they become the next victims.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260502220000 +0000" stop="20260503000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crossword Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Tess gets invited to be part of a popular game show, but when the host is unexpectedly murdered, she and Detective Logan O'Connor try to discover who was behind it all.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260503000000 +0000" stop="20260504000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipline Mysteries</title>
    <desc>A cryptic call about a planned jewelry heist draws a Detroit tip-line operator into a dangerous homicide case alongside a newly promoted detective.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-03</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Conor Maynard: MTV Brand New Live</title>
    <desc>Emerging British pop star Conor Maynard performs; songs include "Can't Say No" and "Vegas Girl"; live in London.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>Silversun Pickups perform songs including "Lazy Eye," "Panic Switch," and "Well Thought Out Twinkles.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260501203000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>All Time Low performs in New York City; songs include "Weightless," "Dear Maria, Count Me In," and "Damned If I Do Ya (Damned If I Don't).".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Live</title>
    <desc>John Legend performs in Rome; songs include "Used to Love U," "Save Room" and "Green Light.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Damiano David</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502003000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Push Showcase: Jordan Adetunji</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Ayra Starr</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Shaboozey</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: The Warning</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502023000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Flyana Boss</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH: Chappell Roan Interview</title>
    <desc>Chappell Roan loves her whole debut album.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502033000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Push Presents: Teddy Swims</title>
    <desc>Teddy Swims chats with MTV about life, music and his rise to superstardom, and gives us exclusive performances of two of his tracks.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501183000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Lisa agrees to enter a Krusty-sponsored "Li'l Starmaker" competition and fears when another contestant outperforms her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer begins to study the Rapture and believes he knows when the end times will come, so he begins warning others in an attempt to secure his place in heaven.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>The Flanders rent their rumpus room to a pair of college-age women who use it to run a soft-core webcam, making Ned so embarrassed that he moves his family to Humble, Pa.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>After forgetting Bob's birthday, Linda and the kids attempt to plan a last-minute surprise party; Linda asks Hugo if Bob can go with him while he's doing restaurant health inspections.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501203000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Tina decides to join the Junior Lifeguards but struggles with the training; business booms when Bob and Linda offer free Wi-Fi at the restaurant but it is soon threatened by a cyberattack.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When a malicious juice truck owner tries to set up shop in the Belchers' alley, Louise devises a plan to win back their turf; Linda learns that she can't always run to her sister's defense.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>The Belchers attend open houses for the free food; Linda meets a charming real estate agent and agrees to a private showing; the kids stumble upon an unexpected surprise; the family ends up getting involved with a real estate scheme.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Louise's extensive card collection gets confiscated at school and she devises a plan to get them back; Bob must give a eulogy for an old acquaintance despite an unfortunate incident that happened years ago.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>As Bob wonders about the worth of working in the restaurant business, a couple who fell in love at the restaurant asks the Belchers to cater their wedding; when things don't go as planned, Linda tries to save the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When teddy bear Rupert is recalled, Stewie is determined to get his best friend back; when Peter is sick and can't compete in a bowling tournament, Lois fills in for him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260501233000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter and the guys try to save The Drunken Clam from being closed after the bar's owner dies; Meg gets a job at a funeral home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>The Griffins move to a farm, where Peter starts a drug business.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502003000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Stewie's time machine malfunctions when he and Brian use it to travel to Las Vegas for a Bette Midler concert.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>The Griffins are invited to join a fancy country club, and must adjust to a new lifestyle.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Word that Peter believes a restaurant placemat is a treasure map pits the citizens of Quahog against each other as they search for the prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When everyone seems to love the vestigial twin that is growing out of Peter's neck better than him, Peter decides to have him amputated.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502023000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Quagmire is excited to meet a woman with a sex drive equal to his own, until she kidnaps him to make him her sex slave; a love triangle forms between Stewie, Brian and Stewie's teddy bear.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Meg spills her lunch on a new classmate; Peter harasses Brian in the nude.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502033000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter destroys the family's passports while they're in Italy, forcing them to deal with immigration laws.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Professor Farnsworth argues with scientific creationists; he decides to settle with his team on an uninhabited asteroid, where he soon discovers that evolutionary theory also works with robots.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502043000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>A revolutionary invention allows the crew members to exchange minds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Fry and company console alien leader Lrrr who, after a bungled invasion of Earth, is caught in the throes of a mid-life crisis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Sent underground for being a mutant, Leela leads an army of sewer-dwelling mutants in a rebellion against the surface people.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Luanne takes a second job as a member of a roller-derby team to get out of credit-card debt.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>John Redcorn decides to build a casino to create a venue for his band to play, then finds out Texas does not allow gaming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Dale protests against a smoking ban in Arlen by going from bar to bar disguised as the smoking bandit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>The teams tackle various challenges with the hope of winning two first-ever Chevrolet Silverado ZR2's, a once-in-a-lifetime trip for two around the world, a $250,000 cash prize, and the coveted title of "The Amazing Race Canada" champions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Pet Ate What?</title>
    <desc>A canine's strange appetite delivers a stomach full of surprises; a cat with hair-ific taste leads to a marathon recovery mission; Dr. G's son, Ben, joins him for an action-packed summer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Pet Ate What?</title>
    <desc>A Bernese Mountain Dog suspected of scarfing an unmentionable feast is a potential record-breaking challenge for Dr. G; a feline rushed to a clinic after a close encounter with a sewing kit sparks a race against the clock to save a family from loss.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>Eight social media stars battle it out on three kitchen levels for a chance at the grand prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Frank is blindsided when Mayor Chase bypasses him with a request for Jamie to head his security detail; Danny and Baez investigate the murder of a wealthy college student; Anthony fears money woes are leading his sibling down the wrong path.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>A local celebrity asks Frank to make an exception to the NYPD age limit; an encounter with an old rival leads Erin to look into an alleged wrongful conviction; Jamie is torn over whether to report a sergeant; Danny and Baez look for an abducted kid.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Helping prospective buyers find their dream home in the country.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>The seven remaining chefs must make a noodle dish that honors tradition while elevating this ingredient that is loved all over the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia: Back to Win</title>
    <desc>Curtis Stone returns for the second night in a row and sets up the ultimate challenge, to create a winter warmer ice-cream and pair it with a dessert.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Alistair Appleton helps a young couple move.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>The competitors face a Pressure Test with more than one surprise twist; a special guest.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Frank is blindsided when Mayor Chase bypasses him with a request for Jamie to head his security detail; Danny and Baez investigate the murder of a wealthy college student; Anthony fears money woes are leading his sibling down the wrong path.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>A local celebrity asks Frank to make an exception to the NYPD age limit; an encounter with an old rival leads Erin to look into an alleged wrongful conviction; Jamie is torn over whether to report a sergeant; Danny and Baez look for an abducted kid.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>Eight social media stars battle it out on three kitchen levels for a chance at the grand prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 15 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Moroccan bream; couscous salad; pomegranate and harissa; British burgers; shred salad; pickles and things.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502073000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 15 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie makes jerk pork, grilled corn and crunchy tortilla salad, minestrone, poached chicken and salsa verde.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>From fashion to beauty to décor to restaurant quality eats, Mary and her experts reveal their favourite dupes; the cast of "Degrassi: Whatever It Takes.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary shows how embracing your oven and baking for breakfast is the ultimate game-changer to switch up the daily grind.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Chef Spencer Watts prepares a homemade Thai feast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aurora Teagarden Mysteries: A Bone to Pick</title>
    <desc>Aurora Teagarden, librarian and proud member of the Real Murders Club, finds a human skull hidden in the window seat of her house.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary whips up a lemon raspberry loaf with a bright pink glaze, lemon Parmesan chicken; creamy lemon crab pasta with a nutty sesame topping, and a lemonade that is infused with seasonal berries and fresh mint.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502123000 +0000" stop="20260502141500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>International chef Curtis Stone sets the mystery box challenge; an hour to impress judges before the elimination round.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502141500 +0000" stop="20260502151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The bottom four from the invention round must do the Pressure Test; competitors must recreate a dessert dish by a top chocolatier to avoid elimination.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502151500 +0000" stop="20260502161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>Eliminated contestants have a second chance; one of the twelve can secure a place in the kitchen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502161500 +0000" stop="20260502171500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>Competitors team up and create a three-course menu for 100 people; Matt Sinclair guest stars to mentor the competitors.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260502171500 +0000" stop="20260502184500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The pop-up restaurant challenge leaves six members of the losing team with the threat of elimination; it's an elimination round with a twist.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>SWAT imposters commit home invasions; Hondo suspects the burglarized families are hiding something; Deacon and Luca are assigned to protect a visiting professional hockey player who is receiving death threats.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Hondo allows newbie Jim Street to go undercover to bust a ruthless trafficker; Hondo visits the teenager recently shot by a former member of the SWAT team.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Hondo's imprisoned childhood friend asks him to protect his son from gang violence; the team encounters a new local crime outfit; Luca's grandfather, an S.W.A.T. legend, passes away, and Luca struggles with his grief and a painful family secret.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The team must work during Christmas vacation when a drug cartel's cache of gold bars is stolen; Jessica approaches the president of the police commission with her ideas on how to improve the S.W.A.T. division.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>When a misconduct complaint filed against Hondo gets him taken off active duty, Deacon steps up to lead the team in finding a robbery crew that is hitting marijuana dispensaries.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The SWAT team tries to rescue civilian hostages during a prison riot; Hondo suspects an ulterior motive behind the uprising; Deacon's wife stops by the headquarters to celebrate Deacon's 10th anniversary with the SWAT division.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Hondo teams up with an old DEA friend to unmask the secret leader of a drug smuggling ring; Jessica begins implementing her new law enforcement community initiatives.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Hondo and the team join forces with the FBI on a manhunt to find a militia group planning a domestic terror attack; Jessica's new police initiatives move forward; she braces herself for the negative impact those initiatives could have.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Hondo and Jessica's secret relationship comes to a crossroads when the president of the police commission discovers their affair; Hondo and the team assist with the federal investigation to bring in an undocumented fugitive.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The team goes on the hunt for a serial killer who escaped justice two years prior by faking his death; Hondo worries that the team's former leader is spiraling into depression in the aftermath of being fired from the department.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Hondo's informant friend is killed while seeking information for a joint SWAT and FBI task force; when the FBI task force leader acts erratically, Jessica worries the woman's behavior will endanger the team in the field.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>A young heiress is kidnapped for ransom; the team goes on a citywide search to bring her home before she is harmed; the team worries that Mumford is moving too fast when he announces he's getting married for the fourth time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>As the team works to de-escalate a hostage situation, the mission takes a dangerous turn, which impacts the team; Street tires of his complicated romantic entanglements and agrees to let Chris make over his online dating profile.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pain Relief Revealed</title>
    <desc>Discover the hidden story of OmegaXL with John Walsh. He dives deep into the groundbreaking supplement that promises hope and relief for millions battling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502073000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Amidst Halloween festivities in New Orleans, a Naval Staff Judge Advocate dressed in a costume is found dead in a cemetery; the team debates Halloween costumes and activities.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The team investigate the murder of a Navy Officer assigned as a tech liaison with a private developer; Pride turns the carport into an auto shop.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A murdered petty officer -- with a proposal and an engagement ring -- is found in a Mardi Gras float storage facility; the members of the team are baffled when they cannot locate the victim's girlfriend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The team reopens a cold case when a stolen Navy-issue gun turns out to belong to a chief petty officer who died 40 years ago; the team makes their annual Thanksgiving dinner together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Callen pursues every alternative when his father is apprehended as part of a planned exchange for two American photographers held hostage in Iran.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502150000 +0000" stop="20260502160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>While investigating a missing person's case, the team uncovers a killer who puts on shows for high-paying voyeurs; Mosley assigns Callen as her partner on a joint ATF mission to apprehend someone from her past.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260502160000 +0000" stop="20260502170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>A notorious international weapons dealer returns to the states; Eric must go under cover at a bank.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260501184000 +0000" stop="20260501193200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Paranormal investigators Corine Carey, Leanne Sallenback and Kelly Ireland travel to San Antonio, Texas to answer the panicked calls of local residents who have experienced paranormal phenomena tied to the Battle of the Alamo in 1836.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260501193200 +0000" stop="20260501202500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>The team finds startling paranormal links to Montreal's boozy, corrupt past in the 1920s and '30s, such as a man whose corpse became an attraction, a woman haunted by ghost children, and a murder victim in a notorious cabaret.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260501202500 +0000" stop="20260501211800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Hunt for the truth in Massachusetts; Salem's ghosts -- including that of the first woman hanged for witchcraft -- reveal things about the city's infamous witch trials; a message from a man executed in the worst way imaginable.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260501211800 +0000" stop="20260501221000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Buccaneers who ran a South Carolina port in the golden age of piracy are summoned; the truth about a ghost ship and a creepy bedroom in the city's oldest tavern is uncovered; a spirit stalking one of the investigators is confronted.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260501221000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>The team investigates paranormal activity linked to an overwhelming number of natural disasters, contacts spirits in a hotel built atop a hospital, explores an eerie B &amp; B, and finds troubled souls in America's most haunted city.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501235900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>A nurse in Texas discovers her hospital is haunted by a mischievous boy whose pranks becomes increasingly malicious; a cook at a county hospital witnesses paranormal events in connection with the long-time janitor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260501235900 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>The spirit of a dead cat returns to protect its owners from an unfriendly canine presence; a woman and her young daughter are terrorized by a menacing shadow man.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502005900 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal Survivor</title>
    <desc>A woman is horrified to discover restless souls buried in the cemetery next to her house; when a man digs up an old tombstone in his yard, he unwittingly unearths a violent entity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502025500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>A nurse in Texas discovers her hospital is haunted by a mischievous boy whose pranks becomes increasingly malicious; a cook at a county hospital witnesses paranormal events in connection with the long-time janitor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502025500 +0000" stop="20260502035000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>The spirit of a dead cat returns to protect its owners from an unfriendly canine presence; a woman and her young daughter are terrorized by a menacing shadow man.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502035000 +0000" stop="20260502044800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal Survivor</title>
    <desc>A woman is horrified to discover restless souls buried in the cemetery next to her house; when a man digs up an old tombstone in his yard, he unwittingly unearths a violent entity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502044800 +0000" stop="20260502054100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Paranormal investigators Corine Carey, Leanne Sallenback and Kelly Ireland travel to San Antonio, Texas to answer the panicked calls of local residents who have experienced paranormal phenomena tied to the Battle of the Alamo in 1836.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502054100 +0000" stop="20260502063300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>The team finds startling paranormal links to Montreal's boozy, corrupt past in the 1920s and '30s, such as a man whose corpse became an attraction, a woman haunted by ghost children, and a murder victim in a notorious cabaret.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502063300 +0000" stop="20260502072600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Hunt for the truth in Massachusetts; Salem's ghosts -- including that of the first woman hanged for witchcraft -- reveal things about the city's infamous witch trials; a message from a man executed in the worst way imaginable.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502072600 +0000" stop="20260502081900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>Buccaneers who ran a South Carolina port in the golden age of piracy are summoned; the truth about a ghost ship and a creepy bedroom in the city's oldest tavern is uncovered; a spirit stalking one of the investigators is confronted.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502081900 +0000" stop="20260502091300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Destination Haunted</title>
    <desc>The team investigates paranormal activity linked to an overwhelming number of natural disasters, contacts spirits in a hotel built atop a hospital, explores an eerie B &amp; B, and finds troubled souls in America's most haunted city.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502091300 +0000" stop="20260502093900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>A woman finds her grandfather's ghost is attached to his home; a woman learns she's sharing her room with the old man that died there.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502093900 +0000" stop="20260502100600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Paalini and Kim's mothers protect them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502100600 +0000" stop="20260502103700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Dan and Susan become targets of ghosts when grave sites are disturbed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502103700 +0000" stop="20260502110400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>The ghosts of fallen soldiers return.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502110400 +0000" stop="20260502113100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>When a man moves down the street from where his father is buried, his dad reaches out; a woman's dead grandfather comes back to make sure she doesn't forget him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502113100 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Children see and play with ghosts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502125400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal 911</title>
    <desc>A Homeland Security officer is left shaken by an encounter with an otherworldly intruder inside an empty government building; a mysterious soldier saves a hospital corpsman's life during a hurricane; paramedics respond to a ghostly 911 call.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502125400 +0000" stop="20260502134900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal 911</title>
    <desc>The ghost of a young girl follows a police officer home from the scene of an accident; a spirit plays tricks on a deputy at an Alabama mansion; a paramedic is shocked to see the apparition of a bride and groom walking down the aisle of a church.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502134900 +0000" stop="20260502144300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal 911</title>
    <desc>An officer investigates a mysterious disturbance at a family gathering; a dark presence hitches a ride in a police car after a shooting; a paramedic overhears a ghostly argument.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260502144300 +0000" stop="20260502153800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal 911</title>
    <desc>A paramedic is spooked by a ghostly wind inside a closet; two kindly spirits help a firefighter locate a missing car crash victim on Christmas Eve; a bomb threat leads to a series of chilling events in a mall.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masters of Flip</title>
    <desc>A quick flip proves to be a profit risk.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>Game show host Deborah Norville ("The Perfect Line"); chef Nicole McLaughlin shares dirt-cheap dinner options.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>Matthew McConaughey talks about his book "Poems &amp; Prayers" and his movie "The Lost Bus.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>Drama revolves around three families in Genoa City.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 5</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 6</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goldbergs</title>
    <desc>Adam and Murray don't want to go on a camping trip, so father and son create a film faking it; Erica joins an all-girl a cappella group and learns an important lesson after taking over the group.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260501233000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>The cast of "The Devil Wears Prada 2"; Adam Scott ("Hokum"); Valerie Bertinelli ("Love Again"); Ziggy Marley (album "Brightside"); Soleil Moon Frye ("Punky Brewster").</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sheriff Country</title>
    <desc>Sheriff Mickey Fox investigates a fatal shooting that appears to be a tragic accident during a lavish Fraley family boar hunt, setting off a chain of events with far-reaching consequences for Edgewater.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Country</title>
    <desc>When a powerful storm sends a massive telephone pole crashing through a family home and traps a woman inside, station 42 races against time to try and pull off a dangerous rescue.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>Looking into some of Canada's most infamous criminal cases with extensive archives and intimate family interviews and exploring the lasting impacts on the community and justice system.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 11</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502033500 +0000" stop="20260502040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502040500 +0000" stop="20260502050700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Late Show With Stephen Colbert</title>
    <desc>Politician Pete Buttigieg; actor Andy Serkis; Late Show Home Shopping with Jon Stewart.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502050700 +0000" stop="20260502053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>The cast of "The Devil Wears Prada 2"; Adam Scott ("Hokum"); Valerie Bertinelli ("Love Again"); Ziggy Marley (album "Brightside"); Soleil Moon Frye ("Punky Brewster").</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502053700 +0000" stop="20260502063700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>Three chefs hit the grills running in the Wildfire Round, it's a BBQ brawl between fast and slow in the Crossfire Round; the judges take a trip to the bayou in the Feast of Fire.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502063700 +0000" stop="20260502073700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masters of Flip</title>
    <desc>A quick flip proves to be a profit risk.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502073700 +0000" stop="20260502083700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Brother Canada</title>
    <desc>The final four become the final three in a special eviction episode.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502083700 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SIGN OFF</title>
    <desc>Sign off.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rust Valley Restorers</title>
    <desc>Mike takes on the build of a 71 Camaro to honour a friend battling cancer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>In the Crossfire Round, the chefs face a battle of the epic sandwich; in the Feast of Fire, fruit meets flame for a fiery and flavorful marriage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fish'n Canada</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the best fishing spots in Canada.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260502123000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Disaster DIY</title>
    <desc>Kim's kitchen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Jasmine has dealt with hardship and loss at every step of her life until she met Ryan, and while he seems to be perfect, his excuses of why he cannot meet have Nev and Kamie questioning him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>William was once a catfish, but now returns as a hopeful looking for love; Nev and Kamie ditch Zoom and hit the streets to help William find out if he has got a shot at romance or if he's about to get a taste of his own medicine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>An online love story between Shay and Ceejay turned dark after Ceejay insisted Shay have a baby with her, tracking her every move; Nev and Tallulah Willis help Shay get answers so she can move on from the eight-year grip of Ceejay.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Chanel get horny with some "Honk Donkeys," play around with a couple "Game Lames," and get a bad case of "Tire-rrhea.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Dana White; "Banned-Kinis"; "Hot Heads.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Doing Anything for Applause; getting Clubbed; trying Big.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rapper O.T. Genasis joins Rob, Steelo, and Chanel to find out why "Everybody Mad," feel the "Cham-pain" and take a trip to "Wrong Beach.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo conjure up some "Psychic Energy," hold it in for as long as possible in the "Pee O.V. Lane," and call out desperation in "Reeks of the D.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260501233000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>"The Dog Whisperer" himself, Cesar Millan, joins Rob, Steelo and Chanel to recognize some "True Alphas," listen to some "Dog Whistles" and find their inner dog in "Perreros.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>The gift of "Danger Immunity"; the horror of "Ruined Reveals"; kids cursed with "The Dick Gene.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502003000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>"Wild 'N Out" star Justina Valentine joins Rob, Steelo and Chanel as they witness some "Secondhand Suck," check out some gym-goers who have a "Trial Membership" and try to avoid some "Water Damage.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo party with some jean queens, learn the consequences of being selfish in share or else, and watch the drama unfold in brunch opera.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>"Animals in Pants"; "Bong Brain"; "Am I High?".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo set off some "direworks, study the art of "drunkitechture" and give five stars to people's "ride oversharing.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502023000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>R&amp;B great Tank talks about his music turning people into savages, great things that are worth waiting for, and clueless people.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie and Fancy's (Jamie Foxx, Garcelle Beauvais) fledgling friendship founders because they can't stay out of the bedroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502033000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>While Jamie recoils from selling his soul to a big record label, he has a nightmare inspired by "The Matrix.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Aunt Helen won't let Jamie make his steamy music video at the hotel, and his star refuses to get naked.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502043000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>When Fancy (Garcelle Beauvais) meets someone new, Jamie (Jamie Foxx) tries to monopolize her time by pretending to be sick.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn sees a new side of himself as he discovers his street-self.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon lands a commercial role but finds it exploits African-Americans.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) must decide which lucky person will share his prize winnings -- a trip for two to Bermuda. With Shawn Wayans.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Dee's (Anna Maria Horsford) letter is selected as the winner in a magazine contest. With Marlon and Shawn Wayans.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Pops loans his brother Nate money to start a trucking business, but Nate goes into the catering business instead.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502073000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) takes a romantic interest in Dee's sister Natalie (Devika Parikh), only to be rejected.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>After Shawn and Marlon find Pops' old diary, they decide to reunite his favorite group, the Temptones.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>Lynae Vanee breaks down top headlines from her distinct perspective and lived experience.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Out the Mud</title>
    <desc>NBA legends Zach Randolph and Tony Allen welcome a star-studded lineup of athletes and artists for can't-miss conversations about the journey to success.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Baller Alert Show</title>
    <desc>Giveon joins hosts Ferrari Simmons and You Know BT to discuss the origins of his name, his new album Beloved, his interactions with fans, working at Chuck E. Cheese, being a songwriter, and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Rising filmmakers push the culture forward through their short works.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">REVOLT Sports Weekly</title>
    <desc>In the series premiere, host Mariah Rose covers Micah Parsons' big return to Dallas, the Giants benching Russell Wilson, Kawhi Leonard's wild contract requests, and more. Presented by Levi's®.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Jabari Banks, Flash Garments, and Swerve Strickland take their shots in the three-point contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>Lynae Vanee breaks down top headlines from her distinct perspective and lived experience.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Rising filmmakers push the culture forward through their short works.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wrist Check Pod</title>
    <desc>Close friends and watch-collecting enthusiasts Perri Dash and Rashawn Smith welcome celebrities, friends, and fellow collectors for a deep dive into the booming business and culture of the global watch community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untapped</title>
    <desc>Viewer-submitted music videos highlight untapped indie artists.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Marvin Thomas; Henry Welch; Ricky Harris; Blair Shannon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502033000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: William Wilson; Michael Colyar; Tony Brown; Ajai Sanders.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untapped</title>
    <desc>Viewer-submitted music videos highlight untapped indie artists.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Marvin Thomas; Henry Welch; Ricky Harris; Blair Shannon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: William Wilson; Michael Colyar; Tony Brown; Ajai Sanders.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Atlanta legends Big Bank and DJ Scream welcome the biggest names in hip-hop culture for unfiltered conversations.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">REVOLT Sports Weekly</title>
    <desc>In the series premiere, host Mariah Rose covers Micah Parsons' big return to Dallas, the Giants benching Russell Wilson, Kawhi Leonard's wild contract requests, and more. Presented by Levi's®.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502123000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Jabari Banks, Flash Garments, and Swerve Strickland take their shots in the three-point contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Ty Dolla $ign</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Ty Dolla $ign with his latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>Actors Valerie Bertinelli, Eric McCormack and Henry Czerny; author Touré Roberts; aesthetician Vanessa Lee shares beauty tips; MorningSave shoppable finds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Lied, I'm Sorry"; Padma Lakshmi; Max Burkholder; Thai Dang demo; Still Rise Farms; WIL: Hedgehog hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 4p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 5p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 6p</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 7p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260501233000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Met Gala fashion preview.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Horse Racing</title>
    <desc>Three-year-old fillies compete in this Grade 1 stakes race for the $846,300 winner's share of a $1.5 million purse. The race currently covers 1 and 1/8 miles and is held at Churchill Downs in Louisville, Ky.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502033400 +0000" stop="20260502043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Charlize Theron; actor Donnie Wahlberg; filmmaker Morgan Neville; Ashley McBryde performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502043700 +0000" stop="20260502053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Henry Winkler; actors Lea Michele, Aaron Tveit and Nicholas Christopher.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502053700 +0000" stop="20260502060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502060400 +0000" stop="20260502063900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502063900 +0000" stop="20260502073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Lied, I'm Sorry"; Padma Lakshmi; Max Burkholder; Thai Dang demo; Still Rise Farms; WIL: Hedgehog hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502073000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Met Gala fashion preview.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Each episode of this travel series sees the host becoming immersed with locals to experience unique culture, authentic cuisine and amazing conversations that turn every city into an unforgettable memory, and brings the world to the viewer through the exploration of inspiring and exciting destinations across the globe. Whether it's rediscovering a familiar road or taking the path less traveled, the</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">DraftKings Casino Report</title>
    <desc>DraftKings Casino, a top-rated casino app!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Birds Huddle</title>
    <desc>The latest news, commentary and opinion surrounding the Eagles and the NFL, along with sport-betting.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Game Time With Boomer Esiason</title>
    <desc>Nineteen-time NHL All-Star and Hall of Famer Ray Bourque.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 6a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>News headlines, interviews, and stories intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning for Americans and help viewers with their finances, health and well-being.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 8a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260502123000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 8:30a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>Graham Norton hosts as engineer John, safeguarding coordinator Roxy, and content writer Lewis all try to claim a possible 50,000 pounds by spinning the Wheel and solving puzzles.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 1% Club</title>
    <desc>Find out how clever you are as Lee Mack presents the quiz where it doesn't matter how good you are at quizzes and where 100 contestants could win up to 100,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pitch Perfect 2</title>
    <desc>Musical comedy film sequel starring Anna Kendrick and Rebel Wilson, 2014. The Bellas must get their act together for a shot at redemption after a very humiliating performance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260501210500 +0000" stop="20260501211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260501211000 +0000" stop="20260501222000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pitch Perfect 2</title>
    <desc>Musical comedy film sequel starring Anna Kendrick and Rebel Wilson, 2014. The Bellas must get their act together for a shot at redemption after a very humiliating performance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260501222000 +0000" stop="20260501225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Anarchic animated sitcom. When Meg finds that her tears make cookies delicious, she starts a business based on the discovery with Brian, Stewie and Chris as her backers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260501225000 +0000" stop="20260501232000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated sitcom. Peter gets a job at the grocery store while the brewery undergoes construction, and Joe uses his police stories to collaborate with Brian.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260501232000 +0000" stop="20260501234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Roger and Klaus begin a secret affair after accidentally going on an online date. Elsewhere, Steve tries to catch Hayley's pink eye to avoid a school fitness test.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260501234500 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>The Life and Times of Stan Smith: US animated comedy. Stan gets addicted to dying after Roger tricks him into thinking that he had a heart attack, and Klaus takes Steve to college.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502001500 +0000" stop="20260502004000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. Louise adopts a spider and discovers that keeping it around the Belcher home is a complicated matter, and Bob reconnects with old friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502004000 +0000" stop="20260502010500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. Courtney enlists Tina and Louise to convince Gene to appear in one of her music videos, and a locked briefcase causes curiosity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502010500 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Count Abdulla</title>
    <desc>The first episode of a comedy about a twenty-something British-Pakistani Muslim doctor. A chance encounter with a shadowy figure at a bus stop changes Abdulla Khan's life forever.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502055500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Project Bakeover</title>
    <desc>You Can't Survive on Bread Alone: Canadian reality series. Scott is the Bread Baron of Airdrie and crushing sourdough, but his staff are running amok and he owes 300,000 dollars.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502055500 +0000" stop="20260502062500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Mom Retreat: Home improvement programme. Brian and Sarah turn an underused backyard into a sports court, a new lounge space, and a luxurious 'mom's retreat'.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502062500 +0000" stop="20260502072500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dress to Impress</title>
    <desc>George, Justin and Lewis compete for the affections of Londoner Jen. Which of the three single shoppers' fashion choices will win them a date.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502072500 +0000" stop="20260502082000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon Ramsay's Food Stars USA</title>
    <desc>The first episode of the American version of the competitive cookery series. The competitors are split into teams and must create a food shack on the beach.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502082000 +0000" stop="20260502092000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon Ramsay's Food Stars USA</title>
    <desc>American competitive cookery series. The teams deliver food, drinks, and an impactful presentation to a charity gala for St Jude Children's Hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502092000 +0000" stop="20260502102000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts the iconic gameshow as one of his brave contestants faces the infamous Banker and could be in with a chance of winning a life-changing cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502102000 +0000" stop="20260502112500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts the exciting gameshow as one of his brave contestants dares to face the infamous Banker and could be in with a chance of winning a life-changing cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502112500 +0000" stop="20260502133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Britain's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>Britain's Got Talent goes live on Saturday nights for the Semi-Finals as the acts who impressed the judges during auditions must now compete for a place in the grand finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502133000 +0000" stop="20260502143500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts a celebrity special of the classic game show with Bill Bailey, Kathy Burke, and Gok Wan all trying to 'say what they see' in aid of charity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502143500 +0000" stop="20260502154000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nanny McPhee and the Big Bang</title>
    <desc>Fantasy family comedy film sequel starring Emma Thompson, 2010. Nanny McPhee is summoned again, this time to help a stressed mother whose children are running riot during WWII.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260502154000 +0000" stop="20260502154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260501183000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ageless Gardens</title>
    <desc>Adapting gardens to accommodate aging.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ayurvedic Way</title>
    <desc>Hosts Randall Mark and Amrita Sondhi approach cooking and exercise with wellness in mind through Ayurveda, an ancient Indian medicinal practice.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>A man reports his wife's disappearance to the police; Wycliffe is not entirely convinced he is being truthful.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Martin has his second GMC assessment; Buddy is missing; Ken's arrival doesn't bring good news for Al and Bert; Penhale isn't happy with the arrival of his predecessor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Billy Black hides from club owner Frank Armstrong; Sgt. Jill Criddle helps the police investigate Armstrong.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Keeping Up Appearances</title>
    <desc>Hyacinth intervenes when Daddy slips out and runs up a hefty bill in a store's toy department.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260501233000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Gardens</title>
    <desc>The Marimurtra Botanical Garden is a privileged place to enjoy rich botanical architectural landscaping in a paradise of the plant kingdom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Martin has his second GMC assessment; Buddy is missing; Ken's arrival doesn't bring good news for Al and Bert; Penhale isn't happy with the arrival of his predecessor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Keeping Up Appearances</title>
    <desc>Hyacinth intervenes when Daddy slips out and runs up a hefty bill in a store's toy department.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Visionary Gardeners</title>
    <desc>A poet remembers her late husband through the garden they built together; an artist creates sculptural works that honour the history of the land on which they reside.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>A man reports his wife's disappearance to the police; Wycliffe is not entirely convinced he is being truthful.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>A feature on comedian, author and activist, Mary Walsh.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502033000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Gardens</title>
    <desc>Exploring the healing nature of gardens and the transformative power derived from the act of gardening.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Billy Black hides from club owner Frank Armstrong; Sgt. Jill Criddle helps the police investigate Armstrong.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Divine Intervention</title>
    <desc>Rabbi Shmuley discovers her history of being raised in an orphanage and how this has impacted her constant need for love.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502053000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Scriptures</title>
    <desc>Nature videography and classical music with passages of scripture from the world's religions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beautiful Little Classics</title>
    <desc>Performances by classical musicians.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Scriptures</title>
    <desc>Nature videography and classical music with passages of scripture from the world's religions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Chicken Soup</title>
    <desc>Thought provoking messages.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kabalah Yoga With Audi Gozlan</title>
    <desc>Audi Gozlan demonstrates a new system of yoga and meditation known as Kabalah Yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: Blissful Living</title>
    <desc>A series of yoga designed to calm the nerves and strengthen the spirit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502103000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Relieving symptoms of chronic pain.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anjelica's 22 Minute Workout</title>
    <desc>A revival of the '80s aerobics series offers workouts for a wide range of ages and abilities.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes on Homes</title>
    <desc>Mike helps George "Boom Boom" Chuvalo with his kitchen disaster.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great British Sewing Bee</title>
    <desc>Britain's best home sewers are tested on their sewing and dressmaking skills.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Landscape Artist of the Year</title>
    <desc>Joan Bakewell and Frank Skinner find the nation's best landscape painter.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Dom and Pete revamp hand-painted drum; Kirsten patches up a beloved beer mug with a funny frog at the bottom; Lou and Mark give a late doc's tongue depressor creation a clean bill of health.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Journey back to Oswestry with experts Charles and Ben, who help two teams poke through a mountain of treasures that could be turned into cash; play along as Charlie challenges fairgoers to guess the purpose of a food-related item.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon, Gino and Fred's Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Gordon Ramsay, Gino D'Acampo and Fred Sirieix join forces for a summer: they spend three weeks traveling through Italy, France and Scotland, with each inviting the other two to their home turf to help them put on an event with personal significance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Peek inside the Bundaberg Master Brewery and find out how a soft drink is brewed; journey from the ginger farm to the packing line as Dr. Karl uncovers the fermentation formula for this spicy drink.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Dr. Karl visits the Kookaburra Sport cricket ball factory in Melbourne and learns how this global symbol of Australian sport is crafted from humble beginnings.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Restoration Australia</title>
    <desc>Host Anthony Burke joins a young couple, Steph and Paul, as they set out bravely and optimistically to write a happy, luxe new chapter for a storied 150-year-old Melbourne institution.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon, Gino and Fred's Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Gordon Ramsay, Gino D'Acampo and Fred Sirieix join forces for a summer: they spend three weeks traveling through Italy, France and Scotland, with each inviting the other two to their home turf to help them put on an event with personal significance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260502043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Peek inside the Bundaberg Master Brewery and find out how a soft drink is brewed; journey from the ginger farm to the packing line as Dr. Karl uncovers the fermentation formula for this spicy drink.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502043000 +0000" stop="20260502050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Dr. Karl visits the Kookaburra Sport cricket ball factory in Melbourne and learns how this global symbol of Australian sport is crafted from humble beginnings.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502050000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Game of Wool: Britain's Best Knitter</title>
    <desc>Examine catwalk dresses made from Aran sweaters and unique fabric-yarn bags.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Dom and Pete revamp hand-painted drum; Kirsten patches up a beloved beer mug with a funny frog at the bottom; Lou and Mark give a late doc's tongue depressor creation a clean bill of health.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Journey back to Oswestry with experts Charles and Ben, who help two teams poke through a mountain of treasures that could be turned into cash; play along as Charlie challenges fairgoers to guess the purpose of a food-related item.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dragons' Den</title>
    <desc>Budding entrepreneurs get three minutes to pitch their business ideas to five multimillionaires who are willing to invest their own cash to kick-start the businesses in the original "Shark Tank." After each pitch, the Dragons have the opportunity to ask questions about the venture. The entrepreneurs don't always have to answer, but of course what they choose not to address could very well affect t</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Travelling Auctioneers</title>
    <desc>Will Kirk and Christina Trevanion take their mobile auction house on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lakefront Luxury</title>
    <desc>Dennis and Melanie hunt for a lake house that can serve as both their home and workspace; Melanie is looking for a space that can accommodate her dance business, while Dennis wants the perfect man cave.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502103000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lakefront Luxury</title>
    <desc>Jordan and Aurelio search for a home that can accommodate their growing family in the future; they have a few big-ticket items on their wish list, including a gourmet kitchen, home office, dedicated children's room and a gym.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Drink Masters</title>
    <desc>Three bartenders face off in the finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Canadian Baking Show</title>
    <desc>The bakers have the opportunity to show off their abilities and creativity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hoarders Canada</title>
    <desc>Roz intends to unclutter her life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502140000 +0000" stop="20260502150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hoarders Canada</title>
    <desc>Roz intends to unclutter her life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260502150000 +0000" stop="20260502160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">History by the Numbers</title>
    <desc>Measure up the conqueror and ponder whether he was a villain or a hero to history; following his horde's path of atrocities, which paved the way for stability and tolerance, and examine the secrets of his lost tomb and legacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260501183000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Caught-on-camera videos that highlight the outrageous and wacky world of animals, hosted by comic Andy Woodhull.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>We'll see how not to impress a girl on a rollercoaster, what happens to a wig on a carnival ride and when trick birthday candles can really heat up a birthday party.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>See why skis do better when you keep them on, when sledding down a roof is not a good idea, when ice skating too fast leads to trouble, and where feeding a dog through a snow blower works just fine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Spider-Man</title>
    <desc>Making his journey from comics, to cartoons, to TV, all the way to the hands of Sam Raimi, bringing Spider-Man to life posed a major challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Marge grows to dislike her new car because it wouldn't be big enough if they were to decide to have another baby; Bart and his friend spy on Lisa.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Leela teams up with an environmentally aware feminist group to save an asteroid filled with primitive life forms.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>A wedding ring flies away; a priest exorcises a jig; corn goes flying!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Kilts meet fans, a kid fakes blindness and a handshake goes terribly wrong.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Spider-Man</title>
    <desc>Making his journey from comics, to cartoons, to TV, all the way to the hands of Sam Raimi, bringing Spider-Man to life posed a major challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Jerry (Jerry Seinfeld) begins dating his new maid (Angela Featherstone); George ponders a nickname; Elaine has to get the new area code.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502003000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Getting stuck in a Puerto Rican Day traffic jam brings about different responses from Jerry, Elaine, George and Kramer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Marge grows to dislike her new car because it wouldn't be big enough if they were to decide to have another baby; Bart and his friend spy on Lisa.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Leela teams up with an environmentally aware feminist group to save an asteroid filled with primitive life forms.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shaun of the Dead</title>
    <desc>Shaun is a 30-something loser with a dull, easy existence. When he's not working at the electronics store, he lives with his slovenly best friend, Ed, in a small flat on the outskirts of London. The only unpredictable element in his life is his girlfriend, Liz, who wishes desperately for Shaun to grow up and be a man. When the town is inexplicably overrun with zombies, Shaun must rise to the occas</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502043000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombieland</title>
    <desc>Nerdy college student Columbus (Jesse Eisenberg) has survived the plague that has turned mankind into flesh-devouring zombies because he's scared of just about everything. Gun-toting, Twinkie-loving Tallahassee (Woody Harrelson) has no fears. Together, they are about to stare down their most horrifying challenge yet: each other's company. Emma Stone and Abigail Breslin co-star in this double-hitti</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shaun of the Dead</title>
    <desc>Shaun is a 30-something loser with a dull, easy existence. When he's not working at the electronics store, he lives with his slovenly best friend, Ed, in a small flat on the outskirts of London. The only unpredictable element in his life is his girlfriend, Liz, who wishes desperately for Shaun to grow up and be a man. When the town is inexplicably overrun with zombies, Shaun must rise to the occas</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unassuming people enter a taxi cab as simple passengers taking a normal ride, only to be shocked when they discover that they're instant contestants. The host,Adam Grove, asks the passengers trivia questions as he escorts them to their destination.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502103000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502113000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Taxi passengers win money by answering trivia questions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Marge grows to dislike her new car because it wouldn't be big enough if they were to decide to have another baby; Bart and his friend spy on Lisa.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502123000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Leela teams up with an environmentally aware feminist group to save an asteroid filled with primitive life forms.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>Two young girls in Washington are snatched in broad daylight while riding their bikes; the case goes unsolved for decades, until a new detective with a local connection to the story tries to solve the mystery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Lied, I'm Sorry"; Padma Lakshmi; Max Burkholder; Thai Dang demo; Still Rise Farms; WIL: Hedgehog hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 4</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5:30</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 6</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260501233000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>In a classic game-show version of "Hangman," contestants solve word puzzles for cash and prizes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Horse Racing</title>
    <desc>Three-year-old fillies compete in this Grade 1 stakes race for the $846,300 winner's share of a $1.5 million purse. The race currently covers 1 and 1/8 miles and is held at Churchill Downs in Louisville, Ky.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502033400 +0000" stop="20260502043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Charlize Theron; actor Donnie Wahlberg; filmmaker Morgan Neville; Ashley McBryde performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502043700 +0000" stop="20260502053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Henry Winkler; actors Lea Michele, Aaron Tveit and Nicholas Christopher.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502053700 +0000" stop="20260502061200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502061200 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Top Story With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Reporting of breaking news and developing stories in real time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Lied, I'm Sorry"; Padma Lakshmi; Max Burkholder; Thai Dang demo; Still Rise Farms; WIL: Hedgehog hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Each episode of this travel series sees the host becoming immersed with locals to experience unique culture, authentic cuisine and amazing conversations that turn every city into an unforgettable memory, and brings the world to the viewer through the exploration of inspiring and exciting destinations across the globe. Whether it's rediscovering a familiar road or taking the path less traveled, the</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Very Local Presents</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>News headlines, interviews, and stories intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning for Americans and help viewers with their finances, health and well-being.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Earth Odyssey With Dylan Dreyer</title>
    <desc>Dylan Dreyer heads down to the waterfront to see the bevy of animal activity around the wild's busiest meeting place.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502123000 +0000" stop="20260502130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wildlife Nation With Jeff Corwin</title>
    <desc>Saving California condors and Massachusetts saltmarsh sparrows; condor sanctuary of the Ventana Wildlife Society; Jeff works with the Massachusetts Department of Fish and Wildlife.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502130000 +0000" stop="20260502133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Kids News</title>
    <desc>An organization working to protect the oceans; the sport of extreme ironing; learning about the circumstances VanGogh was dealing with when he painted Starry Night.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260502133000 +0000" stop="20260502140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tails of Valor</title>
    <desc>A therapy dolphin helps keep its handler afloat; a therapy animal brings hope to its handler.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501180000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>Actors Valerie Bertinelli, Eric McCormack and Henry Czerny; author Touré Roberts; aesthetician Vanessa Lee shares beauty tips; MorningSave shoppable finds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Lied, I'm Sorry"; Padma Lakshmi; Max Burkholder; Thai Dang demo; Still Rise Farms; WIL: Hedgehog hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501203000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 6</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260501231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 7</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501231500 +0000" stop="20260501233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Live</title>
    <desc>Celebrity interviews and discussing recipes, beauty, fashion and current events pertinent to the tri-state region.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260501233000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Met Gala fashion preview.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Horse Racing</title>
    <desc>Three-year-old fillies compete in this Grade 1 stakes race for the $846,300 winner's share of a $1.5 million purse. The race currently covers 1 and 1/8 miles and is held at Churchill Downs in Louisville, Ky.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502033400 +0000" stop="20260502043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Charlize Theron; actor Donnie Wahlberg; filmmaker Morgan Neville; Ashley McBryde performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502043700 +0000" stop="20260502053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Henry Winkler; actors Lea Michele, Aaron Tveit and Nicholas Christopher.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502053700 +0000" stop="20260502060700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502060700 +0000" stop="20260502063700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502063700 +0000" stop="20260502070700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Met Gala fashion preview.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502070700 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Lied, I'm Sorry"; Padma Lakshmi; Max Burkholder; Thai Dang demo; Still Rise Farms; WIL: Hedgehog hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Each episode of this travel series sees the host becoming immersed with locals to experience unique culture, authentic cuisine and amazing conversations that turn every city into an unforgettable memory, and brings the world to the viewer through the exploration of inspiring and exciting destinations across the globe. Whether it's rediscovering a familiar road or taking the path less traveled, the</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George to the Rescue</title>
    <desc>George Oliphant comes to the rescue of families in need of renovating their homes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open House NYC</title>
    <desc>Host Sara Gore presents a guide to upscale real estate in and around the Big Apple. In addition to a look at the hottest homes on the market, the show also provides interior design tips from specialists and a wealth of information on renovation and stylish living.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Saturday Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260501183000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">California Live</title>
    <desc>A daily lifestyle show that takes a ride through all of California, discovering many of the hidden treasures the state and its people have to offer including beauty, glamour, fitness, food, health, and tech.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>Actors Valerie Bertinelli, Eric McCormack and Henry Czerny; author Touré Roberts; aesthetician Vanessa Lee shares beauty tips; MorningSave shoppable finds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "I Lied, I'm Sorry"; Padma Lakshmi; Max Burkholder; Thai Dang demo; Still Rise Farms; WIL: Hedgehog hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 3pm</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 4pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260502000000 +0000" stop="20260502010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Horse Racing</title>
    <desc>From Churchill Downs in Louisville, Ky.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260502010000 +0000" stop="20260502013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">6PM: NBC4 News at 6PM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260502020000 +0000" stop="20260502023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 7 PM</title>
    <desc>The latest in local breaking news, weather reports and feature stories covering the vast Southern California region.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260502023000 +0000" stop="20260502030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260502030000 +0000" stop="20260502033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">California Live</title>
    <desc>Previously recorded; lifestyle show featuring the latest in travel, food and fashion.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260502033000 +0000" stop="20260502040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">California Live</title>
    <desc>Previously recorded; lifestyle show featuring the latest in travel, food and fashion.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260502040000 +0000" stop="20260503000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501183000 +0000" stop="20260501190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood go for a slam dunk in Mini Hoopin', fall into Work Holes and work up an appetite for Wild Glizzys.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501190000 +0000" stop="20260501193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Jenni JWOWW Farley hits the kitchen, meets people in need of help and shoots down advances.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501193000 +0000" stop="20260501200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>For the first time in nine years, the gang celebrates Sheldon's birthday -- surprising him with a special guest.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501200000 +0000" stop="20260501203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Leonard, Sheldon and Wolowitz file for a patent on their new invention; Penny, Amy and Bernadette give dating advice to Koothrappali after his breakup with Emily.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501203000 +0000" stop="20260501210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon makes a surprise revelation when Amy buys him a new laptop; Leonard and Wolowitz get sold out by Koothrappali after lying to their wives to attend a movie screening.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501210000 +0000" stop="20260501213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon shares a secret about Leonard when the two go on a weekend trip with Penny and Amy; Koothrappali goes all out with pregnancy gifts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501213000 +0000" stop="20260501220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>During a group get-together, a minor argument between Sheldon and Leonard turns into a heated debate, leaving the rest of the gang to choose sides.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501220000 +0000" stop="20260501223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>The gang runs into Penny's old boyfriend while out at a wine bar; Bernadette spends an evening with Sheldon; Koothrappali's introduction of his new girlfriend doesn't go as planned.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501223000 +0000" stop="20260501230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon wants to go to a movie screening, so he pays Stuart to spend the day with Amy; Penny has a difficult time connecting with Leonard's visiting mother.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260501230000 +0000" stop="20260502000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Get Hard</title>
    <desc>When a rich hedge-fund manager, James, is convicted of fraud and sentenced to a stretch in San Quentin, the judge gives him one month to get his affairs in order. Knowing that he won't survive more than a few minutes in prison on his own, James turns to Darnell, a Black businessman who's never even had a parking ticket, for help. As Darnell puts James through the wringer, both learn that they were</desc>
    <date>2026-05-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502013000 +0000" stop="20260502033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rush Hour 3</title>
    <desc>East meets West when the assassination of Ambassador Han leads to the reunion of Lee and Carter. In Paris, the pair must stay one step ahead of Chinese gangsters and Lee's childhood friend, as they track down an envelope containing the identity of a powerful crime lord.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502033000 +0000" stop="20260502060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Get Hard</title>
    <desc>When a rich hedge-fund manager, James, is convicted of fraud and sentenced to a stretch in San Quentin, the judge gives him one month to get his affairs in order. Knowing that he won't survive more than a few minutes in prison on his own, James turns to Darnell, a Black businessman who's never even had a parking ticket, for help. As Darnell puts James through the wringer, both learn that they were</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502060000 +0000" stop="20260502063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>"The Real Tarzan," Mike Holston, and some special guests join Rob, Steelo, and Chanel as they check out some "Risky Jobs," say "Arach No Thank You" to spiders and head down under with some "Auss.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502063000 +0000" stop="20260502070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo can't get off the ground in Vert Turds; they aren't afraid to put finger to feather in Barehanded Bird Bosses and need you to pull over in Car Barfy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502070000 +0000" stop="20260502073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Lolo Wood discover that misery loves company in "You're Coming Too"; struggling with weights in "Bad With Barbells"; meeting some really happy dads in "Stoked Dads.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502073000 +0000" stop="20260502080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get a grip with "Power Paws," things suddenly get serious in "Just Got Real" and "Mask Blindness" explores an affliction that strikes every October.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502080000 +0000" stop="20260502083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood try to get fit while doing some Risky Pull-ups, hit the gas by mistake with some Accidental Accelerators and take some wood below the belt from some Nut Crushing Trees.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502083000 +0000" stop="20260502090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Puddle of Mudd front man Wes Scantlin joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to get filthy with some "Mudd Buddies," get kicked out in "One Man Banned," and hire some "Scantlin Security.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502090000 +0000" stop="20260502093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Carly Aquilino enjoy some generational damage with "Grandslaughter," get absolutely no rest in "Homemade Hammocks" and fight the laughter with some tickle haters.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502093000 +0000" stop="20260502100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>On this episode of Ridiculousness, Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood are GETTIN' BOULDERED, witness MONITOR MAYHEM and slip around with ANIMALS ON ICE.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502100000 +0000" stop="20260502103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo see the glass half full of "Bright Siders," meet some strict "Wife Moms" and learn how to "Read the Room.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502103000 +0000" stop="20260502110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo watch "Commentary: On," admire people who do things the "Easy Way" and talk about the dangers of getting "Drunk Stuck.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502110000 +0000" stop="20260502113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob and Steelo welcome Nina Agdal to experience the joys of fall and discover that transporting balloons can be a pain.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502113000 +0000" stop="20260502120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Lexi Rivera get in the game with some "Late Night Athletes"; grabbing a sloppy drink from a few "Messy Mixologists"; celebrating annoying relationships with "Love to Hate Em.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260502120000 +0000" stop="20260502123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob and Sterling are joined by Brie Bella, who shares her fight response of choice; finding out what's over the line on the subway.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-02</date>
  </programme>
</tv>