<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260626230304 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="FX.us">
    <display-name>US | FX East</display-name>
    <icon src="https://tlgrm.re/images/fx-us.png" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470509">
    <display-name lang="Canada">CTV LIFE CHANNEL</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465331">
    <display-name lang="US">Freeform HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470910">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464774">
    <display-name lang="US">FYI Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465241">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465105">
    <display-name lang="US">Fuse HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486672">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465357">
    <display-name lang="US">FXX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470299">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Global Toronto</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464897">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Family</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470820">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FXX Canada</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465354">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="492942">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Mystery</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470474">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Much Music HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465167">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Mystery HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486720">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="481954">
    <display-name lang="US">Haunt TV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486726">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486853">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465290">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486821">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV Quiz</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465002">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime Real Women</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470737">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Makeful TV SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467015">
    <display-name lang="US">WNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486751">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">More4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486755">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">MTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464825">
    <display-name lang="US">MTVLIVE</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465080">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV - Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465113">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV2: Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467402">
    <display-name lang="US">WPTZ-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465207">
    <display-name lang="US">Revolt HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="469871">
    <display-name lang="US">KNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="468233">
    <display-name lang="US">WCAU-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470330">
    <display-name lang="Canada">ONETV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260626173000 -0400" stop="20260626200000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Doctor Strange</title>
    <desc>Dr. Stephen Strange's (Benedict Cumberbatch) life changes after a car accident robs him of the use of his hands. When traditional medicine fails him, he looks for healing, and hope, in a mysterious enclave. He quickly learns that the enclave is at the front line of a battle against unseen dark forces bent on destroying reality. Before long, Strange is forced to choose between his life of fortune and status or leave it all behind to defend the world as the most powerful sorcerer in existence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626200000 -0400" stop="20260626230000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Black Panther</title>
    <desc>After the death of his father, T'Challa returns home to the African nation of Wakanda to take his rightful place as king. When a powerful enemy suddenly reappears, T'Challa's mettle as king -- and as Black Panther -- gets tested when he's drawn into a conflict that puts the fate of Wakanda and the entire world at risk. Faced with treachery and danger, the young king must rally his allies and release the full power of Black Panther to defeat his foes and secure the safety of his people.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260626230000 -0400" stop="20260627020000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Enemy of the State</title>
    <desc>Corrupt National Security Agency official Thomas Reynolds (Jon Voight) has a congressman assassinated to assure the passage of expansive new surveillance legislation. When a videotape of the murder ends up in the hands of Robert Clayton Dean (Will Smith), a labor lawyer and dedicated family man, he is framed for murder. With the help of ex-intelligence agent Edward "Brill" Lyle (Gene Hackman), Dean attempts to throw Reynolds off his trail and prove his innocence.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627020000 -0400" stop="20260627050000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Kingdom of the Planet of the Apes</title>
    <desc>Many years after the reign of Caesar, a young ape goes on a journey that will lead him to question everything he's been taught about the past and make choices that will define a future for apes and humans alike.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627050000 -0400" stop="20260627053000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>2026 Silver Eagle is here &amp; it is a once-in-a-lifetime coin!</title>
    <desc>Join your hosts Kevin Cash &amp; Cory Cady as we discuss the 250th Anniversary of America with the official "America 250" logo on a Silver American Eagle label; we are locking in orders for this iconic release, but coins are limited! Don't miss out!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627053000 -0400" stop="20260627060000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Freedom to Leave the House! Inogen Portable Oxygen</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627060000 -0400" stop="20260627063000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627063000 -0400" stop="20260627070000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627070000 -0400" stop="20260627090000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Wild Hogs</title>
    <desc>Tired of their humdrum lives, some middle-aged friends decide to temporarily ditch their responsibilities and take a motorcycle trip. The freedom of the open road holds many surprises for the group, including an encounter with the Del Fuegos, a hardcore gang, who take a dim view of the novice bikers.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627090000 -0400" stop="20260627120000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>True Lies</title>
    <desc>Secretly a spy but thought by his family to be a dull salesman, Harry Tasker (Arnold Schwarzenegger) is tracking down nuclear missiles in the possession of Islamic jihadist Aziz (Art Malik). Harry's mission is complicated when he realizes his neglected wife, Helen (Jamie Lee Curtis), is contemplating an affair with Simon (Bill Paxton), a used-car salesman who claims he's a spy. When Aziz kidnaps Harry and Helen, the secret agent must save the world and patch up his marriage at the same time.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627120000 -0400" stop="20260627143000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Knight and Day</title>
    <desc>June Havens (Cameron Diaz) chats up her charming seatmate on a flight out of Kansas, but she doesn't realize that she will soon land in the middle of an international adventure. The fellow passenger, Roy Miller (Tom Cruise), is a covert operative who claims he has been set up to take a fall. Now his reluctant partner, June must dodge bullets in Boston, leap rooftops in Austria and evade bulls in Spain, while she and Roy learn that trust is the most important survival skill.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627143000 -0400" stop="20260627170000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Guardians of the Galaxy</title>
    <desc>Brash space adventurer Peter Quill finds himself the quarry of relentless bounty hunters after he steals an orb coveted by Ronan, a powerful villain. To evade Ronan, Quill is forced into an uneasy truce with four disparate misfits: gun-toting Rocket Raccoon, treelike-humanoid Groot, enigmatic Gamora, and vengeance-driven Drax the Destroyer. But when he discovers the orb's true power and the cosmic threat it poses, Quill must rally his ragtag group to save the universe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260627170000 -0400" stop="20260627200000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2</title>
    <desc>Peter Quill and his fellow Guardians are hired by a powerful alien race, the Sovereign, to protect their precious batteries from invaders. When it is discovered that Rocket has stolen the items they were sent to guard, the Sovereign dispatch their armada to search for vengeance. As the Guardians try to escape, the mystery of Peter's parentage is revealed.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>A buyer has £280,000 to relocate to south-west Wales.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef</title>
    <desc>It's the last round of auditions, and home cooks from the Americas vie for a chance to earn a white apron.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef UK</title>
    <desc>Weekly amateur cooking contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Find My Country House</title>
    <desc>Jasmin and Alex both grew up in Latrobe Valley and love the open spaces; now, they're looking for a home with plenty of room to grow.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>It's destination Argyll and Bute, Scotland, for Sonali Shah and a couple from Warwickshire, England.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>The home cooks prepare meals for students; a fresh pasta Pressure Test.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>DA investigator Anthony Abetemarco (Steve Schirripa) helps Erin when she is forced to take a case from a colleague, ADA Kelly Blake (Diane Neal); Eddie and Jamie pose as an elderly couple in order to catch a gang.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monk</title>
    <desc>A trip to an amusement park turns fatal as a detective and a mysterious informant get on a Ferris wheel; when the ride stops, the tipster is dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>The seven remaining chefs must make a noodle dish that honors tradition while elevating this ingredient that is loved all over the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie Oliver shows how to cook the perfect steak sarnie with crispy new potatoes, cheesy mushrooms and beetroot salad.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627073000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie Oliver makes chicken pie with French-style peas, sweet carrot smash, and berries, shortbread and Chantilly cream.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>Fall gardening checklist; Canadian fall fashions; Mary's PEI adventures continue; TV host Suresh Doss ("Locals Welcome").</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary shows how to cater to food intolerances and allergies by amping up the flavor instead of using ingredient substitutions.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Spencer prepares pub food favorites.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deadly Deed: A Fixer Upper Mystery</title>
    <desc>Shannon Hughes has taken on a charity project renovating a grand old Victorian mansion. When a local banker is found murdered inside, Shannon must dust off the clues and cement the truth before her renovation becomes a demolition.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary's bread recipes; any flavor drop biscuits or Mary's picks of lemon-blueberry-white chocolate and cheddar-chive, a crusty sandwich loaf.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary showcases her go-to recipes to lift the spirits; her Ginger Cinnamon Smoothie can help replenish some nutrients after a stomach upset; homemade Cheese Ravioli, with the option to make the dough or use a sneaky store hack.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The contestants spend time at the D'Arenberg Cube restaurant in the middle of McLaren Vale wine country; the bottom two teams from the night market challenge must face elimination.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The contestants take part in an immunity challenge at the spectacular Mt. Lofty House in the Adelaide Hills.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The contestants are divided into two teams where they must make an entrée, main, and dessert in two hours with each course featuring grapes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The contestants visit Maggie Beer's Eatery in the Barossa Valley for their elimination challenge, and participate in a masterclass at the Adelaide Markets.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>Following a massive week on the road in South Australia, the contestants return to the MasterChef kitchen in Melbourne to compete by making a dish that features bread.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>In the latest pressure test, the bottom three contestants have to recreate Alla Wolf-Tasker's Autumn-inspired duck dish.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627210000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The winner of the Mystery Box is sent straight through to the Immunity Challenge, where they have one last chance to cook for their lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627220000 +0000" stop="20260627230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>The contestants travel to the picturesque Dandenong Ranges where a fiery and stressful team challenge awaits them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260627230000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Beautiful Place to Die: A Martha's Vineyard Mystery</title>
    <desc>After being forced into early retirement, former detective Jeff Jackson returns to a quiet life on Martha's Vineyard. Quiet, at least, until a body washes up, and he's drawn back into crime solving.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260626223000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Toy Story 3</title>
    <desc>With their beloved Andy preparing to leave for college, Woody (Tom Hanks), Buzz Lightyear (Tim Allen), Jessie (Joan Cusack), and the rest of the toys find themselves headed for the attic but mistakenly wind up on the curb with the trash. Woody's quick thinking saves the gang, but all but Woody end up being donated to a day-care center. Unfortunately, the uncontrollable kids do not play nice, so Wo</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627005500 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Toy Story 4</title>
    <desc>Woody, Buzz Lightyear and the rest of the gang embark on a road trip with Bonnie and a new toy named Forky. The adventurous journey turns into an unexpected reunion as Woody's slight detour leads him to his long-lost friend Bo Peep. As Woody and Bo discuss the old days, they soon start to realize that they're worlds apart when it comes to what they want from life as a toy.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Meet ordinary people who have experienced the extraordinary power of prayer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Dana and Cheryl hesitantly entrust Ryan and Jim to watch the kids and baby Tanner while they have a girls night out.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627043000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Dana and baby Tanner stay with Jim and Cheryl for a night, but the baby's crying makes it impossible for Jim to sleep.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim does not tell Cheryl that their health insurance has been canceled after he has an argument with a claims representative.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627053000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Coach Jim turns his daughters' noncompetitive basketball team into tough, aggressive winners.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2026 Silver Eagle is here &amp; it is a once-in-a-lifetime coin!</title>
    <desc>Join your hosts Kevin Cash &amp; Cory Cady as we discuss the 250th Anniversary of America with the official "America 250" logo on a Silver American Eagle label; we are locking in orders for this iconic release, but coins are limited! Don't miss out!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627063000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Have Thinning Hair? Keranique Can Help Regrow Beautiful, Thicker Hair!</title>
    <desc>If you have thinning hair or hair loss, Keranique can help regrow thicker, longer and fuller hair. Keranique is the number 1 hair regrowth system for women. Regain your confidence with beautiful, thicker and fuller hair in just 3 easy steps!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Meet ordinary people who have experienced the extraordinary power of prayer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSN Mint - America 250 Coin Roll Collection!</title>
    <desc>CSN Mint presents 1776-2026 U.S. Mint coin roll offers honoring America's 250th Anniversary, including the Emerging Liberty Dime, Enduring Liberty Half Dollar, and P&amp;D Quarter Roll Continuity.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>In the last ever episode, Jim chokes on some food and finds himself on trial in heaven, where Andy represents the defense and Dana the Devil.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ice Age</title>
    <desc>Twenty-thousand years ago, Earth was a wondrous, prehistoric world filled with great danger, not the least of which is the beginning of the Ice Age. To avoid a terrible frostbite, the planet's majestic creatures - and a few small, slothful ones - begin migrating south. The story revolves around sub-zero heroes: a woolly mammoth, a saber-toothed tiger, a sloth and a prehistoric combination of a squ</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627153500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ice Age: The Meltdown</title>
    <desc>With global warming threatening their once-icy domain with widespread flooding, Manny (Ray Romano), Sid (John Leguizamo) and Diego (Denis Leary) set out to find a safe haven. Along the way, another mammoth (Queen Latifah), who thinks she is an opossum, joins the travelers on their perilous quest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627153500 +0000" stop="20260627181500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cars</title>
    <desc>While traveling to California to race The King and Chick Hicks in the Piston Cup Championship, Lightning McQueen falls out of his trailer and winds up in a run-down town called Radiator Springs. He slowly befriends the town's odd residents, including Sally, Doc Hudson and Mater. When it comes time for him to leave, the championship is no longer his top priority.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627181500 +0000" stop="20260627205000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cars 2</title>
    <desc>Racecar Lightning McQueen (Owen Wilson) and his tow-truck buddy, Mater (Larry the Cable Guy), have had their share of adventures together but nothing like what they experience when they head overseas for the first-ever World Grand Prix. While Lightning has his eye on the road to the championship, Mater takes a detour to international espionage when he meets British master spy Finn McMissile (Micha</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627205000 +0000" stop="20260627232000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cars 3</title>
    <desc>Blindsided by a new generation of blazing-fast cars, the legendary Lightning McQueen finds himself pushed out of the sport that he loves. Hoping to get back in the game, he turns to Cruz Ramirez, an eager young technician who has her own plans for winning. With inspiration from the Fabulous Hudson Hornet and a few unexpected turns, No. 95 prepares to compete on Piston Cup Racing's biggest stage.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260627232000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monsters, Inc.</title>
    <desc>Monsters Incorporated is the largest scare factory in the monster world, and James P. Sullivan (John Goodman) is one of its top scarers. Sullivan is a huge, intimidating monster with blue fur, large purple spots and horns. His scare assistant, best friend and roommate is Mike Wazowski (Billy Crystal), a green, opinionated, feisty little one-eyed monster. Visiting from the human world is Boo (Mary </desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When the CFO of a Fortune 500 company is found strangled in her home, Bernard and Cosgrove work to connect multiple dead ends to find her killer; McCoy and Price butt heads over a choice that could cost them the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A construction tycoon interferes with an SVU investigation into her family; Carisi struggles to get an indictment when the complainant backs down.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>As they prepare to attend an exclusive event on the vampire social calendar, the vampires try to survive without Guillermo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Guillermo's fate hangs in the balance as the vampires receive a promotion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>A forbidden artifact is used to help Nandor court a health club employee.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627023000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>An old flame returns, and an ancient vehicle is resurrected.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>As they prepare to attend an exclusive event on the vampire social calendar, the vampires try to survive without Guillermo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627033000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Guillermo's fate hangs in the balance as the vampires receive a promotion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>A forbidden artifact is used to help Nandor court a health club employee.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627043000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>An old flame returns, and an ancient vehicle is resurrected.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>As they prepare to attend an exclusive event on the vampire social calendar, the vampires try to survive without Guillermo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627053000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Guillermo's fate hangs in the balance as the vampires receive a promotion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>A forbidden artifact is used to help Nandor court a health club employee.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627063000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>An old flame returns, and an ancient vehicle is resurrected.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a starlet is killed onstage, Rex takes on a starring role while Charlie goes behind the scenes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When Jesse's sister contacts him for help, Jesse, Sarah and Rex head to Northern Ontario and find themselves in the middle of a deadly situation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Rex seeks help from Detective Sidney Scott to save his stranded and injured friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie gets a break in a long-unsolved kidnapping case that has haunted him, but runs into trouble when the abductee refuses his help.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>An imprisoned killer forces the station into lockdown by taking a hostage and attempting escape.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex sniff out the suspects when the Chief Superintendent of the St. John's Police Department dies at a popular restaurant and all signs point to poison.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Rex seeks help from Detective Sidney Scott to save his stranded and injured friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie gets a break in a long-unsolved kidnapping case that has haunted him, but runs into trouble when the abductee refuses his help.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>An imprisoned killer forces the station into lockdown by taking a hostage and attempting escape.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex sniff out the suspects when the Chief Superintendent of the St. John's Police Department dies at a popular restaurant and all signs point to poison.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Rex seeks help from Detective Sidney Scott to save his stranded and injured friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie gets a break in a long-unsolved kidnapping case that has haunted him, but runs into trouble when the abductee refuses his help.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260626220000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Barrett-Jackson Auction</title>
    <desc>Collector car auctions return with the inaugural Columbus Auction, live and exclusive from the Ohio Expo Center &amp; State Fairgrounds, Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Barrett-Jackson Auction</title>
    <desc>Collector car auctions return with the inaugural Columbus Auction, live and exclusive from the Ohio Expo Center &amp; State Fairgrounds, Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Barrett-Jackson Auction</title>
    <desc>Collector car auctions return with the inaugural Columbus Auction, live and exclusive from the Ohio Expo Center &amp; State Fairgrounds, Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Barrett-Jackson Auction</title>
    <desc>Collector car auctions return with the inaugural Columbus Auction, live and exclusive from the Ohio Expo Center &amp; State Fairgrounds, Columbus, Ohio.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Counting Cars</title>
    <desc>Musician DJ Ashba arrives in a 2004 Lamborghini Murciélago that he wants to be turned into the ultimate "man car," but Danny must make sure to include something special for DJ's wife; Ryan and Paulie hit the streets to score a classic Corvette.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Counting Cars</title>
    <desc>Danny gets started on flipping a 1971 Chevy C10 Pickup for a profit, then a snafu in the paint department threatens to blow the budget sky-high; Danny's bandmate, Stoney, gets in a fender bender.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1776 Silver Rarities</title>
    <desc>Collect every circulation dual date 1776-2026 denomination struck; each coin in this 10-Coin Silver Set is certified PF70UCAM in coveted First Day of Issue holders; included are some one-year only designs and strikes celebrating America's 250th.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1776 Silver Rarities</title>
    <desc>Collect every circulation dual date 1776-2026 denomination struck; each coin in this 10-Coin Silver Set is certified PF70UCAM in coveted First Day of Issue holders; included are some one-year only designs and strikes celebrating America's 250th.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Silver Eagle Rarity</title>
    <desc>RCTV is offering a groundbreaking 2025 American Silver Eagle featuring the first ever Eagle privy mark, graded perfect MS70. This unique issue ties for the lowest mintage Silver eagle and marks the first time an Eagle has been seen on the obverse!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Silver Eagle Rarity</title>
    <desc>RCTV is offering a groundbreaking 2025 American Silver Eagle featuring the first ever Eagle privy mark, graded perfect MS70. This unique issue ties for the lowest mintage Silver eagle and marks the first time an Eagle has been seen on the obverse!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Less is mostly more in Brea; Rene swings for the fences on a costly gamble; Brandi has to dig through trash but really puts her heart into it nonetheless; Ivy and Pops clear up confusion over a massive, mysterious mechanism.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Everything seems like business as usual in West Covina, Calif., until a crazy-looking vintage Mercury Zephyr pulls up, revealing an old friend; Darrell and his buddy stumble over the ultimate sketch artist; Ivy and his son can't seem to pick a lane.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>It's a regular father and son shootout in Victorville, Calif., as Ivy and Pops try to prove who among them is the most profitable; Brandi's secret weapon lands her more than she bargained for, but luckily Kenny is there to brighten her day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Kenny's fear of sharks inspires a controversial wardrobe choice; Rene brings his bargain army along to try and intimidate the competition while he gets his slice of the loot; Darrell won't take no for an answer, moving full-steam ahead.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Barry rolls up to Riverside, Calif., with his own masked bidder, and the two develop a winning strategy; Brandi and Danielle's mystery balls take them to South America... sort of; Rene needs a cleanse after going through his risqué room.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Lisa decides to be fact-based in Placentia, Calif., inadvertently complicating international relations; Ivy and his son conjure up a locker with some mysterious sports equipment; Rene won't be taken advantage of, allowing him to record a nice win.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi does everything she can to stay positive; Darrell finds a unit with some vintage totes, while Gunter plays on Rene's last nerve.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627143000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>San Bernardino, Calif., brings out the warrior in Ivy, who goes up against an upstart buyer; Kenny has his eye on a locker that leaves him needing a massage; Lisa angles for a smaller unit but ends up with the catch of the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi lets Danielle lead the way in Santa Ana, Calif., and their bargain purchase is a trip; Rene takes a gamble on interesting packaging; Ivy discovers that his acquisition may be a total game changer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627153000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi shows up in Riverside, Calif., dressed to distract and it kind of works; Rene bites off more than even he can chew but rings up quite a bit, nonetheless; Barry and Kenny flip when they go through their unit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>A small animal catches Lisa off guard, though she does snag a new type of prize; Ivy and Isaiah barrel their way through a unit, leaving them in need of a drink; Darrell keeps getting stuck behind an old lady.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627163000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Kenny tries to bribe the competition in Canyon Country and becomes more worldly as a result; Ivy and Isaiah make the most of their purchase; Brandi takes on the powers of darkness.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parking Wars</title>
    <desc>Woman faced with a boot won't stop crying; an enraged wife makes getting an impounded car back hard.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627173000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parking Wars</title>
    <desc>A man with a gun is upset about his booted car; an attractive ticket-writer dishes out tough love.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parking Wars</title>
    <desc>Rookie encounters an irate citizen; uncooperative partiers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260627183000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parking Wars</title>
    <desc>Citizens become irate after their cars are booted; Marylin issues tickets in a rowdy neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260626220000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Very Merry Mix-Up</title>
    <desc>A woman plans to meet her future in-laws at Christmas and, through a serendipitous series of events, spends the holiday with a warm and caring family whose son catches her eye.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Christmas Secret</title>
    <desc>A struggling single mother (Bethany Joy Lenz) searches for a lost family heirloom that she hopes will bring her love and good fortune in time for the holidays.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">We Met in December</title>
    <desc>After a magical night sharing hopes, dreams and a perfect kiss, strangers Annie and Dave lose each other with no way to connect. They embark on a quest to find each other by Christmas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Keller Christmas Vacation</title>
    <desc>A trio of reluctant adult siblings join their parents on a Christmas river cruise through Europe, each dealing with personal issues, only to find unexpected joy, romance and family bonds along the journey.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">An Alpine Holiday</title>
    <desc>Two vastly different sisters follow their late grandparent's steps and experience everything the Alps has to offer, including romance.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas at the Golden Dragon</title>
    <desc>When Romy and Rick's parents surprise them with news that they'll be closing their decades-old Chinese restaurant, the siblings soon find themselves reevaluating their futures.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas by Design</title>
    <desc>A fashion designer learns what's most important in life when she joins a Christmas challenge to create a new holiday-themed collection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas With Holly</title>
    <desc>The owner (Eloise Mumford) of a toy store falls in love with a man (Sean Faris) who cares for his orphaned niece.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">If I Only Had Christmas</title>
    <desc>A cheerful publicist teams up with a cynical business owner to help a charity in need at Christmastime.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Our Holiday Story</title>
    <desc>A loving couple shares the story of how they met and fell in love when their daughter's boyfriend comes to meet them for the first time at Christmas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sweetest Christmas</title>
    <desc>A struggling pastry chef is thrilled to learn that she has made it to the finals of the American Gingerbread Competition, but distractions in her love life threaten to derail her dreams of taking home the grand prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Royal Christmas</title>
    <desc>The queen of Cordinia schemes to break up her royal son's romance with a seamstress from Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260627220000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas by Starlight</title>
    <desc>A lawyer makes a deal with the heir to a development firm to spare her family's restaurant from demolition. However, she must spend the week posing as the legal counsel his father is demanding he hire in the wake of some costly mistakes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260628000000 +0000" stop="20260629000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Castle of Our Own</title>
    <desc>When an overworked architect takes an unexpected summer trip, a sandcastle contest and a contractor help her reconnect with her daughter, rediscover joy, and find love she never saw coming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Addiction: Michael Jackson</title>
    <desc>Family, friends and fellow musicians describe the life of the child prodigy turned king of pop Michael Jackson over his four-decade career, from his rise to fame to his later battle with tabloids.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627003000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Michael Jackson: Chase the Truth</title>
    <desc>Close friends, former staff and researchers paint an intimate portrait of pop star Michael Jackson's complicated world and put allegations of sexual abuse under the microscope.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bodied</title>
    <desc>A progressive graduate student finds success and sparks outrage when his interest in battle rap as a thesis subject turns into a competitive obsession.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627043000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Domino: Battle of the Bones</title>
    <desc>Hoping to reclaim his former glory, a fallen dominoes champion recruits his step-grandson to help him win an off-the-wall tournament.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Freedia Got a Gun</title>
    <desc>Devastated after learning her brother Adam was murdered, New Orleans bounce legend Big Freedia uses her platform to raise awareness about the complexities of gun violence, a nationwide epidemic that disproportionally harms Black communities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Laura offers to walk a man's dog and uses the opportunity to snoop through his house; Jordan goes out with a love interest, but he blacks out from heavy drinking, leaving him to put the pieces back together of what happened the night before.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Glenn strikes gold when a gorgeous man asks him on a gym date, but it deteriorates quickly as the man has serious rage issues; Hannah is charmed by a classmate's powerful performance; Jesse agrees to meet a guy from a dating app that is into kink.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Beautiful Latina models have big personalities and bigger dreams as they show the world that beauty comes in all sizes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Full-figure fashion's Latina models Ivory, Denise and LornaLitz face uncompromising shoots, risky agent juggling, overbearing exes and fierce competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Lorna reaps the rewards of having a sugar daddy; Denise tries her hand at video hosting; the drama explodes like fireworks at Ivory's birthday bash.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Denise dates Ivory's brother, but is shocked by a surprise announcement by her ex; Ivory tries online dating; Lorna receives some devastating news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Ivory, Lorna and Rosie compete for the same nude editorial shoot; the girls decide to give speed dating a try.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Lorna tries to ignore Ivory's curt criticism and lands a hot runway show; Denise fizzles at a video audition; a family emergency upsets plans.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curvy Girls</title>
    <desc>Denise struggles to balance her commitment to acting and her family; Lorna confronts her sugar daddy's demands; Ivory checks out her options for starting a family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Jordan Crosby discovers his girlfriend has another boyfriend; following up.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627143000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Danni Little finds her boyfriend lives with his other girlfriends; following up with Gemma Taylor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Birthday cake in a man's face; mop dog; daddy-daughter dance; kid runs and falls; woman tries to hold a goat while feeding it.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627153000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>A girl does a head stand in her dad's hand; baby falls in a box; don't feed these birds; dog throws metal pan; dog chases kids with hose; tumbling over in a toboggan.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>A water boarder hits a buoy; cat plays with a tent.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627163000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Funniest Pets and People is a solid half-hour of pure entertainment with a proven format featuring hysterical, fast-paced video clips submitted by viewers who share the funniest moments of their favorite Pets and People.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rolling Stones: Rock Royalty</title>
    <desc>Two old friends bumping into each other at a train station in England leads to formation of the Rolling Stones and the band's enduring success in music and business.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627183000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Beatles: In the Life</title>
    <desc>The Beatles took the world by storm in the 1960s and are still the best-selling band of all time with 183 million sales worldwide.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Eagles: The Long Road</title>
    <desc>Paying tribute to the life and career of Glenn Frey, one of the main band members. Revisiting the achievements of one of the best-selling and most loved American rock bands of all time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627213000 +0000" stop="20260627230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Killing John Lennon</title>
    <desc>A dramatic step-by-step breakdown behind the lead up to John Lennon's murder on Dec. 8, 1980.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260627230000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Luau</title>
    <desc>A man who owes a large sum of cash throws a party that soon spirals out of control just to raise some money.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626222000 +0000" stop="20260626231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Wants to Be a Millionaire</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Clarkson is on hand and hoping to make a millionaire of any one of the six new contestants in this edition.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260626231500 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIFA WC2026: Uruguay v Spain</title>
    <desc>Uruguay face Spain at the 2026 FIFA World Cup live from Guadalajara with Laura Woods, Gary Neville, Juan Mata and Ange Postecoglou.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627023500 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point: Best Ever Finals</title>
    <desc>Relive some of the most dramatic end games in Tipping Point history, including agonising trades and jackpot counters teetering on the edge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627041500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627041500 +0000" stop="20260627043500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627043500 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">James Martin's American Adventure</title>
    <desc>James ends his epic coast-to-coast exploration of the great US of A with a visit to New York City - one of his all-time favourite foodie hotspots - and a popular pizzeria.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627052500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">James Martin's French Adventure</title>
    <desc>James Martin's travels around France lead him to the beautiful lakeside town of Annecy, where he wanders around the market and cooks dishes using delicious local tomatoes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627052500 +0000" stop="20260627062000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">James Martin's Spanish Adventure</title>
    <desc>James visits a huge indoor food market in Bilbao, takes a funicular to a famous steak restaurant, heads to a winery on a seabed and learns how La Carolina is made.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627062000 +0000" stop="20260627072500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Your Garden</title>
    <desc>Alan Titchmarsh and his team reveal how adding water can transform any size of garden by creating two incredible water gardens, one outside in Kent and one inside.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627072500 +0000" stop="20260627082500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ainsley's Fantastic Flavours</title>
    <desc>Ainsley bigs up brunch with an Indian-inspired eggy bread and plant-based tacos, welcomes Emmett J. Scanlan and Jessica Sweetman, and explores the cheese of Malta.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627082500 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627110500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">James Martin's Saturday Morning</title>
    <desc>James welcomes actor Nigel Havers to his home in the Hampshire countryside and tastes delicious recipes from chefs Tom Aikens, Sabrina Gidda and Atul Kochhar.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627110500 +0000" stop="20260627113500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dermot's Taste of Ireland</title>
    <desc>Dermot spends a day oyster farming on the Atlantic , and wanders Sligo's family-run eateries to savour a gloriously Irish Surf 'N' Turf.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627113500 +0000" stop="20260627121000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">James Martin's Islands to Highlands</title>
    <desc>James returns to one of his favourite places in the UK - the beautiful county of Cornwall - with his pal and Michelin-starred chef Galton Blackiston.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627121000 +0000" stop="20260627122500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627122500 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Racing: Live from Newcastle</title>
    <desc>Francesca Cumani presents coverage of live racing from Newcastle and York.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as one Chaser is all that stands between Toby Anstis, Paula Radcliffe, Rav Wilding, Vanessa Feltz and thousands of pounds for their chosen charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627181000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Downton Abbey</title>
    <desc>Feature-length follow-up to the TV series starring Hugh Bonneville and Elizabeth McGovern, 2019. 1927: King George V and Queen Mary pay a visit to the Crawley family's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627181000 +0000" stop="20260627183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Evening News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627183000 +0000" stop="20260627184000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627184000 +0000" stop="20260627194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 1% Club</title>
    <desc>Find out how clever you are as comedy legend Lee Mack presents the quiz show where the questions have nothing to do with remembering facts and are all about logic and common sense.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627194500 +0000" stop="20260627234000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIFA WC2026: Panama v England</title>
    <desc>England take on Panama in their final World Cup group game. Mark Pougatch is alongside Roy Keane, Ian Wright and Gary Neville.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260627234000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Wants to Be a Millionaire? Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Clarkson is back and on hand hoping that Steph McGovern and Dion Dublin have got what it takes to walk away with one million pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260626233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>A reimagining of the show as a series that's been on the air for 60 years; a look back at the cultural events and issues tackled on the show through the decades.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260626233000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>To help get Brian's life in order, Stewie and Brian swap bodies using a machine that Stewie invents; chaos quickly ensues around Quahog when Stewie's machine goes haywire.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>To help promote the brewery to millennials, Peter adopts the millennial lifestyle; his methods soon attract the attention of a high-powered Silicon Valley executive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627003000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Quagmire loses his most treasured body part and must learn to live without it; Stewie and Brian search for Mort after learning there is a reward for turning him into the police for his involvement in a drug scam.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter falls into a coma and meets God face to face; he asks God some of life's tough questions.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Brian meets and falls in love with Jess, who reveals she has cancer; after she receives devastating news regarding her diagnosis, Brian proposes marriage to her.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Brian's marriage to Jess is not what he envisioned; at Peter's suggestion, Brian lets himself go, causing Jess to make a surprising decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627023000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Stewie quickly befriends a boy his age, but is devastated when he realizes he isn't invited to his birthday party; Peter and Lois attend a self-empowerment seminar.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After Brian teases Stewie for being small, Stewie invents a shrinking machine that results in both of them shrinking to a microscopic size.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627033000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Lois receives a surprising birthday present from her father, which leads to an unfortunate accident that leaves him dependent on Lois and the Griffins' care.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The guys are sentenced to death on Planet Amazonia by a race of giant women. Voices of Billy West, Katey Sagal, John DiMaggio, Phil LaMarr and Lauren Tom. Guest voice: Bea Arthur.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627043000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The crew is injected into Fry's body to fight off parasites he picked up from an egg-salad sandwich. Voices of Billy West, Katey Sagal, John DiMaggio, Phil LaMarr and Lauren Tom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Earthlings assault Bender as he delivers toys on behalf of the evil Santabot, who is frozen in a block of ice.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627053000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Fry searches the ruins of New York for a seven-leaf clover he remembers from his past. Voices of Billy West, Katey Sagal, John DiMaggio, Lauren Tom and David Herman.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Hank is appalled when he sees Bobby and his new friend (Eliza Dushku) imitating a boy band's suggestive dance moves.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627063000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Bill wolfs down a huge quantity of food at a record-breaking pace. Jeff Garlin, Kid Rock and Pamela Anderson guest star.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Connie's cousin (Lucy Liu) builds a crystal methamphetamine laboratory, and Peggy unknowingly enters it in the science fair.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627073000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Bobby challenges Peggy for supremacy in the kitchen on Thanksgiving Day, and Peggy responds by kidnapping his turkey.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Overwhelmed with IRS Debt? Keys to Resolving Tax Debt</title>
    <desc>See how one company is changing people's lives by helping them put their tax problems to rest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathroom Makeover</title>
    <desc>Transform your bath affordably in just one day!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Desperate for a teaching job, Peggy impersonates a nun to land a position at a parochial school, but having to teach a religion class might expose her.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Bill gets drunk and steals a military tank after learning he was used as a guinea pig in a secret army experiment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260626233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goldbergs</title>
    <desc>Adam and Brea attempt remaining just friends post-breakup; Beverly goes out of her way to protect Adam from further heartbreak; Barry tries to get closer with Erica.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260626233000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sheriff Country</title>
    <desc>A dramatic federal crackdown rocks Edgewater and forces Sheriff Mickey Fox to confront a sprawling investigation that pits loyalty to her community against the reach of the DEA.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Country</title>
    <desc>Bode participates in a high school drunk-driving drill that unexpectedly reconnects him with a former classmate; Three Rock reopens with a new crew and high hopes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>Jean-Bruno Fenelon reports finding his ex-partner, Marie Gabriel, dead; while he offers various theories about the killer, forensic evidence leads Ottawa police to the truth and the murderer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 11</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627033500 +0000" stop="20260627040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627040500 +0000" stop="20260627050500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>Documenting the battles Tori's family endured to ensure the perpetrators serve their sentences as outlined by the courts; this was a fight that has further challenged their healing process.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627050500 +0000" stop="20260627053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627053500 +0000" stop="20260627063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>The chefs are fired up to create unique signature dishes in the wildfire round; the crossfire round brings the heat; the judges are treated to breakfast for dinner in the final round.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627063500 +0000" stop="20260627073500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masters of Flip</title>
    <desc>Kortney's heart is set on a large kitchen island; Kortney tries to keep everyone on board with her plans.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627073500 +0000" stop="20260627083500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Brother Canada</title>
    <desc>The houseguests compete for the power of veto where the winner has the ability to veto a nominee up for eviction or leave the nominations the same.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627083500 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SIGN OFF</title>
    <desc>Sign off.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rust Valley Restorers</title>
    <desc>Mike and Avery embark on a cross-country road trip, which is interrupted by an unexpected call from home; JF borrows shop space from Mike to restore a 1955 GMC truck and his relationship with his brother.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>Three chefs compete in the Signature Round, the Crossfire Round, and prepare some flame-kissed New Orleans food in the Feast of Fire.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fish'n Canada</title>
    <desc>Showcasing the best fishing spots in Canada.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Disaster DIY</title>
    <desc>Aaron and Evadne try to impress each other by trying to reno the laundry room and fix a basement window.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fish TV</title>
    <desc>Hosts Leo Stakos, Ron James and Jeff Chisholm set their sights on great fishing destinations.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Employment Law Show</title>
    <desc>Host Lior Samfiru answers questions about employment rights and tackles the most important facets of employment law that are often overlooked by both employer and employee.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627143000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627153000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Food Bucket List</title>
    <desc>John visits a Surrey, BC, restaurant for a lesson in making authentically delicious Afghan favorites; he then goes to Toronto, ON, to twirl a fork in some wild green spaghetti; in Edmonton, AB, John gets into the French state of mind.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Disability Law Show</title>
    <desc>Explaining rights for individuals who are denied their long-term disability.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260626220000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All of My Heart</title>
    <desc>After inheriting half of a house, a young woman (Lacey Chabert) develops an unexpected friendship with her co-owner.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All of My Heart: Inn Love</title>
    <desc>Brian and Jenny are preparing for the grand opening of their bed and breakfast, Emily's Country Inn, when a big storm hits Buck County. Brian agrees to go back to Wall Street to boost their funds, while Jenny scrambles to keep the opening on track.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura wants to impress a newly discovered old buddy; Charles and Jonathan try to start a freight line, which leads them further away from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mary takes a teaching job in a backwoods community only to clash with a hostile woman bent on driving her away.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Caroline recalls her first meeting with Charles when he is late for their wedding anniversary celebration.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Jack asks Ty to join him on a cattle roundup; Ben avoids his aunts phone calls.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>A famous race horse is sent to Heartland for rehabilitation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>Jonathan and Mark encourage a mentally challenged boy to compete in the Special Olympics.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>Jonathan and Mark help a young couple adopt a mentally challenged boy.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura wants to impress a newly discovered old buddy; Charles and Jonathan try to start a freight line, which leads them further away from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mary takes a teaching job in a backwoods community only to clash with a hostile woman bent on driving her away.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Caroline recalls her first meeting with Charles when he is late for their wedding anniversary celebration.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>News of Charles' inheritance from a wealthy relative prompts townspeople to suggest uses for the money.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Charles helps Mr. Oleson's unloved nephew learn values by hiring him for odd jobs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sarah, Plain and Tall</title>
    <desc>In 1910 Kansas, widowed farmer Jacob Witting (Christopher Walken) is having a hard time raising his children and running his farm without the help of a wife. He puts an ad in the paper for a bride to help him, and gets a response from a woman named Sarah (Glenn Close), who only describes herself as "plain and tall." Sarah travels to the farm for a one-month trial period, but finds Jacob's stubborn</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Skylark</title>
    <desc>Sarah (Glenn Close) and farmer husband Jacob Witting (Christopher Walken) want to keep their family together, but a drought makes it difficult to farm their land and provide for their children. When a fire ruins several buildings on their property, Sarah takes stepdaughter Anna (Lexi Randall) and stepson Caleb (Christopher Bell) to her brother's home in Maine, leaving Jacob to tend what's left of </desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sarah, Plain and Tall: Winter's End</title>
    <desc>In this final chapter of the "Sarah, Plain and Tall" series, Sarah Witting and her husband, Jacob, are taken by surprise when Jacob's father, John, who abandoned his son and family many years earlier, returns to live with the Wittings as he faces the end of his life. As Jacob struggles to reconcile with John, the Wittings' children face troubles of their own, leaving Sarah alone to lead her family</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Yours</title>
    <desc>Cass, a busy, single mother, hires her friend Matt to help her take care of the kids. Eventually, she realizes that the person who could complete her family may have been there the whole time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627220000 +0000" stop="20260627230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Witch</title>
    <desc>Cassie pursues a temporary art history professorship while Sam diagnoses Adam; Abigail and Donovan realize that the missing diamond from the Middleton treasure may help break the curse.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260627230000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Witch</title>
    <desc>Sam successfully operates on Adam but not without complications; Joy, against Cassie's advice, dreams that Abigail and Donovan break up, and she tries to stop it from happening.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260628000000 +0000" stop="20260629000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Witch</title>
    <desc>Cassie displays Nathaniel Merriwick's paintings for Grey House's 225th birthday, inspiring Martha to direct a tableau vivant.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Herrmann and Mouch prepare to take their officer exams; Cruz receives a chilling omen; Carver takes care of a dog after its owner is injured on a call.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Tasked with shadowing a crisis prevention team, Upton finds her approach to policing at odds with the team's mental health clinician; Voight stands by Upton as she continues to struggle in her personal life.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After finding Dennis' erotic memoir, Mac and Frank try to profit from the masterpiece; Dee and Charlie spend a day in each other's shoes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After Dee has a heart attack, she and Dennis try to live healthier lifestyles; Charlie and Mac join the corporate workforce to get health insurance.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Hoping to make the bar a landmark, the gang tells the Philadelphia Historical Society that Paddy's Pub was responsible for cracking the Liberty Bell.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627023000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>To try to make their dreams come true, the gang decides to pay it forward and give an unlucky family an extreme home makeover.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After finding Dennis' erotic memoir, Mac and Frank try to profit from the masterpiece; Dee and Charlie spend a day in each other's shoes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627033000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After Dee has a heart attack, she and Dennis try to live healthier lifestyles; Charlie and Mac join the corporate workforce to get health insurance.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Hoping to make the bar a landmark, the gang tells the Philadelphia Historical Society that Paddy's Pub was responsible for cracking the Liberty Bell.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627043000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>To try to make their dreams come true, the gang decides to pay it forward and give an unlucky family an extreme home makeover.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After finding Dennis' erotic memoir, Mac and Frank try to profit from the masterpiece; Dee and Charlie spend a day in each other's shoes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627053000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After Dee has a heart attack, she and Dennis try to live healthier lifestyles; Charlie and Mac join the corporate workforce to get health insurance.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>When Jake starts accumulating unsolved cases, the other detectives worry his losing streak will rub off on them; Amy, Rosa and Gina run a program for at-risk youth; Boyle helps Sgt. Jeffords with a case.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627063000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake hits on an attractive medical examiner at a crime scene and holds up the autopsy report; Amy's purse-snatching case is stalled when the sketch artist is out sick.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Unhappy Amy must wear a costume to go on patrol with Charles; Jake bets Holt he can steal his Medal of Valor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627073000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 Rock</title>
    <desc>Hank wants to cancel "TGS," but Jack convinces him to let the cast and crew prove themselves with their 100th episode.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>When Sal's Pizza burns down, Jake goes out of his way to disprove the fire marshal's assumption that the owner set the fire; a computer virus exposes the precinct members' Internet browser histories.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake gets to spend the day with his hero, a former crime reporter; Terry and Charles work with Rosa on how she comes across on the witness stand.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A toy designer (Pat Hingle) visits his old neighborhood and finds it exactly as it was in his childhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Rex is on trial after his DNA is discovered at the scene of the murder of Donovan's former police informant.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Trapped in an isolated mansion during a storm, Charlie and Rex uncover a wannabe-killer after the hostess is drugged; Sarah fights to keep her alive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When two hikers are discovered murdered near a remote coastal trail, the team is on the hunt for a fugitive duo wanted in a series of grisly campsite murders.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Rex is on trial after his DNA is discovered at the scene of the murder of Donovan's former police informant.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Trapped in an isolated mansion during a storm, Charlie and Rex uncover a wannabe-killer after the hostess is drugged; Sarah fights to keep her alive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When two hikers are discovered murdered near a remote coastal trail, the team is on the hunt for a fugitive duo wanted in a series of grisly campsite murders.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Rex is on trial after his DNA is discovered at the scene of the murder of Donovan's former police informant.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260626233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA on ION Pregame Show</title>
    <desc>Studio coverage of the Women's National Basketball Association.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260626233000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Wintrust Arena in Chicago.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA On ION Game Break Show</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>From Chase Center in San Francisco.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <desc>New clients hire Magnum and Higgins to find their missing brother, which results in Higgins getting shot and TC abducted; Higgins and Magnum are surprised when her surgeon asks her out.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <desc>Higgins' job to repossess a plane goes south when a drug cartel opens fire at the plane, forcing her and Magnum to crash-land in the jungle; Higgins has her first date with Dr. Ethan Shah.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <desc>As Magnum, Higgins and TC try to pull one over on a Customs agent to get Higgins a green card, armed gunmen suddenly storm the federal building and start taking hostages.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathroom Makeover</title>
    <desc>Transform your bath affordably in just one day!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627073000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Injury Help with Vernon Davis</title>
    <desc>Injured? Vernon Davis hosts The Legal Help Center, where live agents are standing by 24/7 to answer your call. Find out if you have a case and how much it's potentially worth. Call Now!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Protect Your Family From Identity Theft</title>
    <desc>Every 5 seconds there's a victim of identity theft; LifeLock helps alert you, restore your identity, and reimburse lost funds—leading the way in protecting families every day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Natural Blood Pressure Management</title>
    <desc>Cardiologist Dr. Ernst von Schwarz, M.D. shows how to manage your blood pressure naturally and help protect your heart for life with My Best Heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Evidence suggests that the man responsible for saving a lieutenant's life is a soldier who was captured in Afghanistan.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Special Agent Pride and the team uncover a domestic drug ring -- led by Sonja's childhood friend, Marion Watkins (Samaire Armstrong), that is producing cocaine.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A Navy captain is murdered during an appearance on a local radio show; Pride's daughter comes home to talk about her plans for the future.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Agent Brody sees a connection between the case of a sailor struck by a party bus and the death of her sister; the team gets ready for the city's St. Patrick's Day celebrations.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>When a Russian bomber goes missing while flying over U.S. soil, Callen and Sam must track it down in the desert and secure its weapons and intel before the Russians on board destroy the plane; Hetty gives Nell a cryptic assignment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team is called to help find the missing star witness in the trial of a chief petty officer who Callen and Sam arrested for war crimes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Nell sends Sam to meet an informant who plans to blow the whistle on a military secret; Kensi and Deeks debate whether to buy their first house.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The body of a murdered Navy reservist is found by thieves in the midst of a robbery, and NCIS must work with the burglars to find the killer; Kensi and Deeks struggle to decide if they are ready to make the leap and buy a house.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>In order to get intel on a matter of national security, Kensi must come face-to-face with a sociopath who has been obsessed with her since she put him in jail years ago; Eric is desperate to keep Kensi safe, but he is forced to leave NCIS.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Before Christmas, Hetty assigns Callen the case of his former foster brother and his wife, who, upon reentry into the U.S., are framed for smuggling drugs across the border; Deeks is struggling with losing his job at NCIS.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team's murder investigation of a man who sold military information leads to the abduction of a doctor whose cutting-edge neurotechnology could be developed into advanced weaponry; Callen tries to have an important talk with Arkady.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627210000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>An organized crime leader tries to buy stolen defense technology; Deeks is kicked out of NCIS training only to find that Hetty has a life-changing surprise for him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260627220000 +0000" stop="20260627230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>When Sam's daughter is kidnapped after leading citywide protests, he will stop at nothing to find her; Deeks rejoins NCIS; Callen searches for answers about Anna.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU takes charge of a hostage situation at a law firm where Matt Simmons' wife works.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called upon when bioterrorism is suspected in a series of mysterious deaths; Garcia visits her stepbrother to take care of a difficult family issue.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called to Taos, N.M., when someone targets victims' temporal lobes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team questions the credibility of a former FBI agent's bizarre account.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When Reid and Garcia are abducted by a mass murderer, it's up to the rest of the team to find them; the BAU looks to their past to solve why the two heroes have been targeted.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team tracks a serial killer when remains of numerous victims are found in the walls of an elderly couple's home; the hunt becomes urgent after the BAU learns the killer's specific ritual of when to strike; Rossi reconnects with his ex-wife.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Packages with gruesome contents are delivered to six people in the Washington, D.C. area; Simmons and Kristy struggle to connect with their son, David, who is suspended from school for aggressive behavior.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>An international crime boss offers to surrender if he's allowed to return to the United States to watch his daughter walk down the aisle; MacGyver and the team crash the wedding to ensure the crime lord doesn't run.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>After a surprising introduction to Phoenix's newest recruit, Desi, MacGyver and team are assigned to protect a gun-sniffing dog who has a bounty on its head.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>The Phoenix must recover the body of a pilot whose plane crashed while testing an experimental laser mapping system that MacGyver designed; Riley tries to identify the hacker who tricked a SWAT team into arresting her and Elwood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>MacGyver and the team are asked to solve a locked-door mystery when a man working inside a remote, ultra-secure international seed vault disappears.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>When Nicholas Helman resurfaces to carry out a killing spree, the team is forced to get help from the one person who knows him best -- his protégé, Murdoc.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>MacGyver and Desi help a group of Syrian refugees who are being pursued by human traffickers; Bozer is trapped in Oversight's car, and it's rigged to explode.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Two American tourists go missing while doing a scavenger hunt through some of the world's most dangerous countries; the Phoenix team goes undercover as backpackers to find them and bring them home alive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>A cunning new adversary's carefully crafted plans force Mac to make an impossible choice: save the life of a friend or save the lives of hundreds of innocents; Mac receives new information that will drive a wedge between him and his father.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When the head swim coach of a community college is found dead at the bottom of the well, possible suspects think he may have been having an affair; a new intern (Laura Spencer) catches Sweets' attention.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>A man who wanted to talk to Booth about a possible government cover-up is killed before their meeting takes place; as Booth and the team investigate the conspiracy surrounding the man's death, Booth's future with the FBI becomes uncertain.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>As Brennan and the team try to absolve Booth and get him out of prison, the remains of a man who has been dead for 16 years prove to be significant; Booth encounters criminals he was responsible for incarcerating.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team works with Special Agent Aubrey to investigate a far-reaching conspiracy in the government; DNA found on a previous victim linked to the scandal helps the narrow down the suspect pool.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>With intern Rodolfo's help, the team investigates the murder of a conservative radio host whose remains were found in a storm drain; Special Agent Aubrey endeavors to gain Booth's trust; Brennan worries about Booth's mental health.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team and Special Agent Aubrey investigate the murder of a video game designer; intern Jessica talks about the educational cooperative with which she has been involved; Brennan and Booth talk about Christine's future.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team members investigate when remains are found in a stairwell at a convention they are attending; Brennan bumps into her publishing rival, Tess Brown; Wendell has news about his diagnosis.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627210000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The investigation into the death of a maid whose remains were found on the side of the road turns out to be a bigger case than originally thought; tensions rise between Cam and Brennan.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627220000 +0000" stop="20260627230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a billion dollar hedge fund company after severely damaged human remains are found under a merry-go-round.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260627230000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates when a crossword puzzle master is found in an urban fracking site; Daisy seeks comfort from her doula.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260628000000 +0000" stop="20260629000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates when a psychology professor known for his controversial social experiments is found dead; Brennan works with Aubrey.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Harry Potter</title>
    <desc>A new director tests the team as he tries to bring real magic to Hogwarts, as well as a new Dumbledore.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Jerry becomes obsessed when his date refuses to sample his pie; a clothing store mannequin resembles Elaine.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627003000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Kramer befriends a little person when he is hired as a stand-in for a soap opera; George wants to break up with a girlfriend.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Marge writes a novel, "The Harpooned Heart," using Homer and Ned as inspiration for her characters; Homer gets the book-on-tape version read by Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The Planet Express crew escape to Mars Vegas for the weekend, only to run afoul of Robot Mafia, who is looking to recover a debt.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Ninja Warrior</title>
    <desc>The new regional finals begin as ninjas from the western region compete for a spot in the national finals; the Tripleheader, a supersized three-lane racecourse, debuts as ninjas go head-to-head-to-head in side-by-side races.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Love You, Man</title>
    <desc>As his wedding day approaches, Peter Klaven (Paul Rudd) realizes he has no one to act as his best man. Through a series of "man-dates," he finds Sydney Fife (Jason Segel), and the pair become instant friends. But as Peter's "bro-mance" with Sydney grows stronger, it threatens his relationship with his fiancee (Rashida Jones), forcing Peter to make a choice.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Ninja Warrior</title>
    <desc>The new regional finals begin as ninjas from the western region compete for a spot in the national finals; the Tripleheader, a supersized three-lane racecourse, debuts as ninjas go head-to-head-to-head in side-by-side races.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forgetting Sarah Marshall</title>
    <desc>Struggling musician Peter Bretter is better-known as the boyfriend of TV star Sarah Marshall. After she unceremoniously dumps him, he feels lost and alone but makes a last-ditch bid to get over it by going to Hawaii. However, she and her new boyfriend are there in the same hotel.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Miss Congeniality</title>
    <desc>When a terrorist threatens to bomb the Miss United States pageant, the FBI rushes to find a female agent to go undercover as a contestant. Unfortunately, Gracie is the only female FBI agent who can "look the part" despite her complete lack of refinement and femininity. She prides herself in being "just one of the boys" and is horrified at the idea of becoming a girly girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Miss Congeniality 2: Armed and Fabulous</title>
    <desc>Gracie Hart (Sandra Bullock) was never thrilled to have to go undercover as a competitor in a beauty pageant. Now Gracie, who works for the FBI, is dealing with some very public attention thanks to her waltz down the runway. Her overnight celebrity does not impress her new partner, Sam Fuller (Regina King). But the pair has to put aside their differences when one of Gracie's former beauty queen pa</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627163000 +0000" stop="20260627183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two Weeks Notice</title>
    <desc>Dedicated environmental lawyer Lucy Kelson (Sandra Bullock) goes to work for billionaire George Wade (Hugh Grant) as part of a deal to preserve a community center. Indecisive and weak-willed George grows dependent on Lucy's guidance on everything from legal matters to clothing. Exasperated, Lucy gives notice and picks Harvard graduate June Carter (Alicia Witt) as her replacement. As Lucy's time at</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627183000 +0000" stop="20260627203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Lost City</title>
    <desc>Reclusive author Loretta Sage writes about exotic places in her popular adventure novels that feature a handsome cover model named Alan. While on tour promoting her new book with Alan, Loretta gets kidnapped by an eccentric billionaire who hopes she can lead him to an ancient city's lost treasure from her latest story. Determined to prove he can be a hero in real life and not just on the pages of </desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627203000 +0000" stop="20260627223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Miss Congeniality</title>
    <desc>When a terrorist threatens to bomb the Miss United States pageant, the FBI rushes to find a female agent to go undercover as a contestant. Unfortunately, Gracie is the only female FBI agent who can "look the part" despite her complete lack of refinement and femininity. She prides herself in being "just one of the boys" and is horrified at the idea of becoming a girly girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260627223000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Miss Congeniality 2: Armed and Fabulous</title>
    <desc>Gracie Hart (Sandra Bullock) was never thrilled to have to go undercover as a competitor in a beauty pageant. Now Gracie, who works for the FBI, is dealing with some very public attention thanks to her waltz down the runway. Her overnight celebrity does not impress her new partner, Sam Fuller (Regina King). But the pair has to put aside their differences when one of Gracie's former beauty queen pa</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260626220000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Garage Sale Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Jennifer Shannon puts the winning bid on a vintage Welte-Mignon player piano at the estate auction of a wealthy philanthropist, but soon realizes that the late owner may have led a less-than-charitable life before being murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Garage Sale Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Every year, Jennifer and her friend Miles Wexford participate in the organization of an auction of goods seized by the police; the night of the auction, Miles is found dead in his store.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica searches for a motive when a legendary maestro, who is about to lose control of his protégé, is found murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Burglaries and a murder occur when the carnival comes to Cabot Cove but doesn't seem to bring in a great deal of money.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Internal strife at an earthquake-shaken California zoo culminates in an employee's death from snake bite.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's probe of a friend's kidnapping in Amsterdam leads to two murders and a diamond-smuggling ring.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's discovery that Cabot Cove's Revolutionary War hero was actually a traitor results in a TV director's murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica searches for a motive when a legendary maestro, who is about to lose control of his protégé, is found murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Burglaries and a murder occur when the carnival comes to Cabot Cove but doesn't seem to bring in a great deal of money.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Internal strife at an earthquake-shaken California zoo culminates in an employee's death from snake bite.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's vacation to Honolulu becomes chaotic when the son of her host, power broker Matt Kincaid, vanishes during a hotly contested U.S. Senate election.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica investigates when, during a visit to San Francisco, an advice columnist (Eileen Brennan) falls victim to a crazed gunman.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Accidentally tapped into a closed-circuit video surveillance system, Jessica's neighbor witnesses scheming, a robbery and then a murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>While vacationing in Martinique, Jessica is called on to help an acquaintance (Wayne Rogers) accused of a woman's (Cassie Yates) murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crossword Mysteries</title>
    <desc>After several of the clues in her recent puzzles are linked to the murder of an art gallery owner, a crossword puzzle editor is drawn into the investigation; while searching for answers, she clashes with the no-nonsense detective overseeing the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crossword Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Tess dives into Logan's murder investigation of her friend who was about to propose with her help; as she grows closer to the truth, she fears it could ruin everyone's happily ever after.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crossword Mysteries</title>
    <desc>During Tess' birthday celebration, the headlining magician at the Magic Manor winds up dead, and Tess and Logan find themselves swept up in a world where things aren't always what they appear to be.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crossword Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When Tess prepares for a crossword challenge against a supercomputer, the engineer behind it gets murdered, spurring her and Logan to seek answers before they become the next victims.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260627220000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crossword Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Tess gets invited to be part of a popular game show, but when the host is unexpectedly murdered, she and Detective Logan O'Connor try to discover who was behind it all.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260628000000 +0000" stop="20260629000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nelly Knows Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When Dahlia's boyfriend is found dead, advice columnist Nelly joins Detective Hogan to help find the killer. However, as suspicions creep in, Dahlia becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626223500 +0000" stop="20260626230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated series about CIA agent Stan Smith. Stan is upset that he is not climbing the ladder fast enough at work, so starts a sideline in festive teddy bears.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626230500 +0000" stop="20260626233500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated series about a CIA man who is constantly on the alert for terrorism. When Stan surveils his neighbours, he ends up getting his ears burned.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260626233500 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. When Mr Fischoeder challenges Bob to prank him on April Fools' Day or face eviction, Bob grows suspicious of who is pranking whom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627000500 +0000" stop="20260627003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Stop! Or My Mom Will Sleuth!: Animated comedy. Linda attempts to figure out the truth when Louise is suspected of stealing a toy, and Bob helps Teddy design a new business card.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627003000 +0000" stop="20260627012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Botched</title>
    <desc>US reality series. A woman with a recurring keloid needs Dr Nassif to rid her ear of the huge growth, and a fan of a celebrity wants to emulate their figure.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627012000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts as Donna is given her opportunity to open the iconic red boxes and goes up against the Banker in a bid to take home a huge cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dress to Impress</title>
    <desc>20-year-old teaching assistant Kieren from Bury is hoping that one of three shoppers can win his heart via the medium of clothes. Will any of the dates impress.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627070500 +0000" stop="20260627081000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Dinner Date</title>
    <desc>Reality TV star Bobby Norris is given five menus put together by potential blind dates - whose menus will he most like the looks of, and will he want to have seconds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627081000 +0000" stop="20260627091000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Dinner Date</title>
    <desc>TV personality Jess Wright is given five menus put together by potential blind dates - whose menus will she most like the looks of, and will she want to have seconds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627091000 +0000" stop="20260627101500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal: Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts a special edition of the iconic game show as Strictly Come Dancing's Motsi Mabuse and Dancing on Ice's Oti Mabuse join forces to take on the Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627101500 +0000" stop="20260627111500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>It's Claire's turn to take on the Banker as Stephen Mulhern hosts the iconic game show with only one question.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627111500 +0000" stop="20260627122000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>It's Ronnie's turn to take on the Banker - join Stephen Mulhern to find out if she will take home a huge cash prize or become the latest member of the 1p Club.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627122000 +0000" stop="20260627132000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>Graham Norton hosts as accountant John, primary school teacher Jess, and care home assistant Paris all get spinning the wheel to try to take home a massive 50,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627132000 +0000" stop="20260627142000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts a celebrity special of the classic game show with Adjoa Andoh, Adrian Chiles, and Trevor Nelson all trying to 'say what they see' in aid of charity.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627142000 +0000" stop="20260627152000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Madagascar</title>
    <desc>Animated adventure comedy film featuring the voices of Chris Rock and Ben Stiller, 2005. A group of animals adjust to living wild after spending their lives in a New York zoo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627152000 +0000" stop="20260627152500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627152500 +0000" stop="20260627160500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Madagascar</title>
    <desc>Animated adventure comedy film featuring the voices of Chris Rock and Ben Stiller, 2005. A group of animals adjust to living wild after spending their lives in a New York zoo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627160500 +0000" stop="20260627171000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs</title>
    <desc>Animated adventure comedy film sequel featuring the voices of Ray Romano and John Leguizamo, 2009. An attempt by Sid to adopt three dinosaur eggs lands him in a strange world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627171000 +0000" stop="20260627171500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627171500 +0000" stop="20260627175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs</title>
    <desc>Animated adventure comedy film sequel featuring the voices of Ray Romano and John Leguizamo, 2009. An attempt by Sid to adopt three dinosaur eggs lands him in a strange world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627175500 +0000" stop="20260627185500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coyote Ugly</title>
    <desc>Comedy-drama film starring Piper Perabo and Adam Garcia, 2000. A young woman heads to New York City to pursue her dream of becoming a songwriter while working at a notorious bar.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627185500 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coyote Ugly</title>
    <desc>Comedy-drama film starring Piper Perabo and Adam Garcia, 2000. A young woman heads to New York City to pursue her dream of becoming a songwriter while working at a notorious bar.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 1% Club</title>
    <desc>Lee Mack hosts the quiz show where 100 contestants compete, but in order to win a up to 100,000 pounds they will need to answer a question only 1% of the country can get right.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260626225700 +0000" stop="20260626235200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>A youth worker's encounter at an overnight treatment center; hospital halls with a gang of ghosts; a counselor banished by a surly spirit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260626235200 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>A ghost girl becomes jealous of a teenage boy's new friend; a newlywed couple encounters horrific sights and smells before being attacked by a violent entity in their apartment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627004600 +0000" stop="20260627011200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>Ryan assembles his top investigators in preparation for facing the demon that has been following him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627011200 +0000" stop="20260627013800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>After antiques collectors bring a certain piano into their home, Lorraine Warren must lend her expertise to dismantle and destroy the instrument.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627013800 +0000" stop="20260627020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>A woman in Parkville, Md., calls on the services of agents when her roommate claims to have been attacked by a poltergeist.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627020300 +0000" stop="20260627025800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>A youth worker's encounter at an overnight treatment center; hospital halls with a gang of ghosts; a counselor banished by a surly spirit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627025800 +0000" stop="20260627035300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>A ghost girl becomes jealous of a teenage boy's new friend; a newlywed couple encounters horrific sights and smells before being attacked by a violent entity in their apartment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627035300 +0000" stop="20260627041900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>Ryan assembles his top investigators in preparation for facing the demon that has been following him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627041900 +0000" stop="20260627044500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>After antiques collectors bring a certain piano into their home, Lorraine Warren must lend her expertise to dismantle and destroy the instrument.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627044500 +0000" stop="20260627054000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A Russian soldier describes being lured into a swamp by an unnatural entity; an Ohio military base with a UFO connection; an interview with a US Air Force colonel whose alien-craft sightings are finally confirmed.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627054000 +0000" stop="20260627063400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission Unexplained</title>
    <desc>An Infantryman encounters an otherworldly presence on a training mission.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627063400 +0000" stop="20260627072900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission Unexplained</title>
    <desc>An intelligence analyst on a secret mission makes an unearthly discovery.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627072900 +0000" stop="20260627082300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathsheba: Search for Evil</title>
    <desc>Paranormal investigator Erin Goodpipe heads to Harrisville, R.I. to get the bottom of the rumors surrounding the witch, Bathsheba Sherman.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627082300 +0000" stop="20260627091700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathsheba: Search for Evil</title>
    <desc>Paranormal investigator Erin Goodpipe steps inside the Old Arnold Estate to find out who is haunting this Rhode Island property; abandoned by their community and plagued with increased spiritual activity, the Perron family adapts to their home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627091700 +0000" stop="20260627101200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>A youth worker's encounter at an overnight treatment center; hospital halls with a gang of ghosts; a counselor banished by a surly spirit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627101200 +0000" stop="20260627110700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scariest Night of My Life</title>
    <desc>A ghost girl becomes jealous of a teenage boy's new friend; a newlywed couple encounters horrific sights and smells before being attacked by a violent entity in their apartment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627110700 +0000" stop="20260627113200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>Ryan assembles his top investigators in preparation for facing the demon that has been following him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627113200 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>After antiques collectors bring a certain piano into their home, Lorraine Warren must lend her expertise to dismantle and destroy the instrument.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627125400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>Standing up to spirits that are hell-bent on punishing the living; pondering the nature of a nighttime intruder, facing off with a vengeful ghost who appears to a nurse's aide, and chasing an aggressive entity targeting a switchboard operator.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627125400 +0000" stop="20260627134900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>A medical assistant starting a job in a former TB hospital discovers she's not alone in the building; a rookie nurse takes her break in a room rumored to be haunted; a procedural nurse encounters a hostile entity within the walls of an old hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627134900 +0000" stop="20260627144300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>An orderly discovers his frightening gift for seeing spirits of the recently deceased and sensing those who are about to die; a hospice nurse realizes the end-of-life facility where she works is haunted by multiple spirits, including a black dog.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627144300 +0000" stop="20260627153800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>A nurse in Texas discovers her hospital is haunted by a mischievous boy whose pranks become increasingly malicious; a cook at a county hospital witnesses paranormal events in connection with the long-time janitor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627153800 +0000" stop="20260627163300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>A nurse aide discovers that her care facility contains a horrific creature that threatens her elderly patients; encounters in the hospital halls with a nefarious crone compels a teenager to hold vigil by her dying grandmother's bedside.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627163300 +0000" stop="20260627172700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Hospitals</title>
    <desc>A nurse assistant observes uncanny coincidences that emerge in connection with a long term care resident. A teenager at a psychiatric facility detects spirits in an abandoned building. While transporting a baby a nurse senses a disturbing presence.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627172700 +0000" stop="20260627175400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A look at why so many people see a vision of Jesus in seemingly normal things such as a tree stump or an antique cabinet.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260627175400 +0000" stop="20260627181800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Exploring the world of psychics.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260626225500 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shetland</title>
    <desc>Perez and the team begin a complex investigation when a severed hand washes up on a Shetland beach and further body parts are discovered in a dumped holdall.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627001500 +0000" stop="20260627012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shetland</title>
    <desc>A gruesome discovery at the Hayes house changes the course of the investigation as Perez establishes the probable cause for the murder and the disappearance.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627012000 +0000" stop="20260627013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George and Mildred</title>
    <desc>Domestic sitcom spin-off from the hit '70s show Man About the House. Mildred is flattered when George displays a rare stirring of jealousy.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627053500 +0000" stop="20260627064500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>Detective drama starring Jack Shepherd. Cornish police detective Charles Wycliffe has to dig deep when an archaeological student is found shot in her bed.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627064500 +0000" stop="20260627075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>Detective drama series starring Jack Shepherd. Wycliffe is uneasy about an apparent suicide on the secluded estate of Lord and Lady Bottrell.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627075500 +0000" stop="20260627095500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Endeavour</title>
    <desc>Crime drama. 1971 - Endeavour finds himself right back in the thick of it when an explosive murder at an Oxford college has potentially far-reaching political ramifications.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627095500 +0000" stop="20260627115500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>When the leader of a reading club is found battered to death, the club's activities are exposed and long-held secrets and desires return to haunt its members.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627115500 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Feature-length drama. The death of a hotel owner leads to murder and intrigue as DCI Barnaby uncovers a web of illicit affairs and shady business dealings.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Feature-length drama. The disappearance of a villager brings DCI Tom Barnaby face to face with an old adversary who has reinvented himself as a local squire.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World Series of Darts</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the World Series of Darts tournaments from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Agatha Christie's Poirot</title>
    <desc>David Suchet stars as Agatha Christie's fictional detective Hercule Poirot in this collection of murder mysteries where Christie's revered works are brought lovingly to life.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627210500 +0000" stop="20260627225500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Vera</title>
    <desc>Drama. Vera and the team investigate a murder at an Army barracks - sensing a connection to a death in Afghanistan, Vera uncovers the hidden trauma behind the crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260627225500 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inspector Morse</title>
    <desc>When valuable erotic paintings are stolen from a stately home, Morse delves into the minds and morals of the aristocracy as he tries to solve the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260626231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of the 90s</title>
    <desc>A look back at the wide variety of sports covered by ITV during the 1990s - from the 1990 World Cup to athletics and Euro '96 to snooker - that includes many memorable moments.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260626231500 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIFA WC2026: Cape Verde v Saudi Arabia</title>
    <desc>It's the final round of matches in the group stages and Cape Verde take on Saudi Arabia at the NRG Stadium in Houston.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627020500 +0000" stop="20260627021500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of the 80s</title>
    <desc>A look back at the wide variety of sports covered by ITV during the 1980s - from football to wrestling and double decker bus racing to boxing - that includes many iconic moments.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627021500 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of the 70s</title>
    <desc>A look back at the wide variety of sports covered by ITV during the 1970s - from horse racing to table football and Formula One to darts - that includes many memorable moments.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627052000 +0000" stop="20260627055000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Protectors</title>
    <desc>Adventure series about a European crime-fighting team. Harry masquerades as a drunk as he sets out to release a Canadian heiress from the clutches of a cult.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627055000 +0000" stop="20260627062000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Protectors</title>
    <desc>Part One: Adventure series about a European crime-fighting team. The Protectors have to rescue a group of tourists who are being held hostage on top of an Austrian mountain.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627062000 +0000" stop="20260627072000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>A look back at football highlights from May 1977 that features a big game at the top of the old First Division as Bob Paisley's Liverpool take on Ipswich Town at Anfield.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627072000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Saint</title>
    <desc>Simon Templar embarks on another adventure. The Saint is sent to jail to smash a large-scale prison escape organisation run by callous killers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Racing: The Opening Show</title>
    <desc>Leonna Mayor and the team are at Newcastle to preview all the action on Northumberland Plate day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>A nostalgic look back at the best of the iconic football show The Big Match.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">River Monsters</title>
    <desc>Extreme fishing series. Expert navigation is needed when Jeremy Wade heads to Colombia to investigate a creature blamed for killing a bride in the Amazon.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627115500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Pickers</title>
    <desc>US documentary series. Mike and Frank sort through three generations of clutter in Michigan before finding a stash of quirky collectables in Wisconsin.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627115500 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes</title>
    <desc>An act that seems to be a harmless prank played on a man with red hair is revealed to be an ingenious scheme planned by the sinister Professor Moriarty.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes</title>
    <desc>After foiling Moriarty's plans to sell the Mona Lisa, Holmes follows his arch-enemy to Switzerland for a fateful encounter at the Reichenbach Falls.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627141000 +0000" stop="20260627152000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Return of Sherlock Holmes</title>
    <desc>Holmes returns to Baker Street and explains how Moriarty alone died at the Reichenbach Falls.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627152000 +0000" stop="20260627173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hornblower</title>
    <desc>Drama series about CS Forester's famous seafaring hero. Promoted to acting lieutenant, Hornblower is forced to question his readiness for command.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627173000 +0000" stop="20260627194500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hornblower</title>
    <desc>Drama series about CS Forester's seafaring hero. Hornblower leads a daring raid on a French sloop and is rewarded by being allowed to set sail for England.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627194500 +0000" stop="20260627230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FIFA WC2026: Croatia v Ghana</title>
    <desc>It's the final round of matches in the group stages and Ghana take on Croatia in Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627230500 +0000" stop="20260627233500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Protectors</title>
    <desc>Part Two: Adventure series about a European crime-fighting team. The Protectors continue their efforts to rescue a group of tourists being held hostage on an Austrian mountain.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260627233500 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Protectors</title>
    <desc>Adventure series. Harry is called on to protect a Russian author that the Protectors smuggled into Britain and who is now publishing an anti-socialist book.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260628000000 +0000" stop="20260629000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Protectors</title>
    <desc>Adventure series. An old friend who has a new lead on an insurance fraud and invites Harry and the Contessa to Venice to pursue the case is murdered just before they arrive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A computer expert (Danica McKellar) claims to have witnessed a murder in the apartment across the way, but investigators find no physical evidence of a crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A Marine records his own death on video, as he falls off a cliff during a camping trip with his wife and his best friend, and Abby tries to reconstruct the camera, putting her technical skills to the test.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>When a female petty officer is found dead in the bed of a dance club bartender, the team suspects the officer's sister (Mya Harrison).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627020300 +0000" stop="20260627030300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>When a sailor in Washington receives a package containing a pair of blue eyeballs, Gibbs investigates a former Navy Intelligence agent who is now a private contractor in Paraguay.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627030300 +0000" stop="20260627040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A petty officer recently returned from duty is found dead backstage at a local bikini contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627040100 +0000" stop="20260627050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A Marine records his own death on video, as he falls off a cliff during a camping trip with his wife and his best friend, and Abby tries to reconstruct the camera, putting her technical skills to the test.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627050100 +0000" stop="20260627060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>When a female petty officer is found dead in the bed of a dance club bartender, the team suspects the officer's sister (Mya Harrison).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627060400 +0000" stop="20260627070400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>When a sailor in Washington receives a package containing a pair of blue eyeballs, Gibbs investigates a former Navy Intelligence agent who is now a private contractor in Paraguay.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627070400 +0000" stop="20260627080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A petty officer recently returned from duty is found dead backstage at a local bikini contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627080200 +0000" stop="20260627083200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627083200 +0000" stop="20260627090200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627090200 +0000" stop="20260627093200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Natural Blood Pressure Management</title>
    <desc>Cardiologist Dr. Ernst von Schwarz, M.D. shows how to manage your blood pressure naturally and help protect your heart for life with My Best Heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627093200 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">H2O X5 - Super Powerful 5-In-1 Multi-Use Steam Cleaner</title>
    <desc>Kills 99% of Bacteria, Viruses, and Germs with Steam! The 5-in-1 Lightweight, Fast, Powerful, And Completely Chemical Free Steam Cleaner! Lift and remove dirt and stains all around the home!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627143000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Single Black Female</title>
    <desc>Monica looks for a fresh start as she tries to land a gig as the host of an afternoon talk show. She soon becomes close friends with her new assistant, Simone, a deranged woman who plans to take over Monica's life for good.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627163000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Single Black Female 2: Simone's Revenge</title>
    <desc>After escaping the murderous clutches of her half sister, Simone, Monica gets a fresh start in Seattle as the host of a TV show. When amnesiac Simone sees her on TV, her memories come rushing back, leading to a fateful reunion between the sisters.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Single Black Female 3: The Final Chapter</title>
    <desc>Wrongfully convicted of murder, Monica gets released from prison, while her half sister, Simone, flees to Mexico. However, when Simone returns to Houston, bodies start to pile up, leaving the siblings pointing their fingers at each other.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260626235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260626235500 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>A team of five Southampton uni friends take on the Tenable Tower as they attempt to win 125,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627005000 +0000" stop="20260627014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the ruthless quiz as contestants Rachel and Nathan, Heather and Jordyn, and Sam and Angela take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627014500 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern for the game show with only one question and find out if Paula can beat the Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Fighting it out are Lingo-mad mother and daughter Adele and Molly from Manchester, Stoke-on-Trent couple Anita and Alex, and Leeds-based sisters Dominique and Tahiela.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Warwick Davis hosts the quiz show as five friends tackle a series of Top 10 list questions - can they beat the Tenable Tower and head home with the cash.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as Adam Jones, Monica Dolan, Dom Wood and Dick McCourt take on a Chaser in a bid to win thousands of pounds for their chosen charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the rapid and ruthless quiz as contestants Yuz and Scott, Karen and Mark, and Jess and Emma take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>It's Tyreece's turn to take on the Banker as Stephen Mulhern hosts the iconic game show with only one question.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Fighting it out are professional entertainers Nick and Tina, best friends Aaron and Gabriel from Leeds, and Salford-based couple Anna and Ollie. Hosted by Adil Ray.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Facing off are housemates Michael and James from Gateshead, competitive Kerris and partner Sandra from Stafford, and husband and wife Dave and Carol from the Wirral.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mangan, Kemi Rodgers and Tom Allen join Stephen Mulhern as they 'say what they see' and guess well-known phrases for a chance to win 50,000 pounds for their charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase: Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius determined to stop them winning the cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627210000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627220000 +0000" stop="20260627230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627230000 +0000" stop="20260627235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260627235500 +0000" stop="20260628000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Warwick Davis hosts the quiz show as five friends tackle a series of Top 10 list questions - can they beat the Tenable Tower and head home with the cash.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>JD splits the young rappers into two teams and challenges them to perform at a high school halftime show.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Kelly Rowland and her personal trainer visit the five young rappers; JD tests the children on both their mental and physical stamina in the "Catch the Beat" challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Bow Wow helps hone the young rappers' media skills to prepare them for a press conference, television interview and photo shoot; Nova throws another artist under the bus.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Before signing, JD tests the young rappers in a battle rap; John John Da Don, Arsonal, Charlie Clips, DNA and Calicoe prepare the group; a rapper makes an unforgettable decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>After thirteen weeks of challenges, the artists prepare for their final performance; JD makes a decision, and awards one rapper the chain and the contract.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Kelly Rowland and her personal trainer visit the five young rappers; JD tests the children on both their mental and physical stamina in the "Catch the Beat" challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Bow Wow helps hone the young rappers' media skills to prepare them for a press conference, television interview and photo shoot; Nova throws another artist under the bus.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Before signing, JD tests the young rappers in a battle rap; John John Da Don, Arsonal, Charlie Clips, DNA and Calicoe prepare the group; a rapper makes an unforgettable decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>After thirteen weeks of challenges, the artists prepare for their final performance; JD makes a decision, and awards one rapper the chain and the contract.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Ghost Stories</title>
    <desc>After losing her boyfriend, Tracy strikes a deal with the devil; Fairuza is attacked by a ferocious entity; Della is saved by her guardian angel; a spirit forces Patrick into a battle for his life.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Ghost Stories</title>
    <desc>Linda and her sister discover an old house with a murderous history; Carlos is rescued by a spirit; Victoria was raised in house built on a burial ground; Dot realizes a ghost is watching over her.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>In week five of the competition, the eight remaining contestants prepare to do battle in the categories of literature &amp; fine arts and vocabulary.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bring It!</title>
    <desc>The Dancing Dolls challenge their rivals to a street battle; tension on the dance floor sparks a clash between dancers and spectators; Camryn gets the opportunity to lead the Dancing Dolls in a parade.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bring It!</title>
    <desc>The Dancing Dolls prepare to defend their title against local rivals; Mimi tries to convince Dianna to let the mothers back into the dance studio during rehearsal; Sunjai gets the chance to compete in Stand Battle for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Wedding day has come and gone, and now the three newlywed couples are off on their honeymoons; one couple hits an instant roadblock at the airport.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Honeymoons continue for two of the couples, as they start to familiarize themselves with their new spouses; explosive revelations come to light about Mia's past.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Back to reality for Danielle and Bobby, and Amber and Dave, as they return from honeymoons; Tristian feels betrayed by Mia's dishonesty.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>The couples have moved in together, now they get the chance to make an impression on their spouses' friends and families; one bride is reluctant to meet her husband's friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Married at First Sight</title>
    <desc>Weddings and honeymoons are in the rearview mirror, and the challenges of day-to-day life set in; Dave and Amber bicker over household tasks; Tristian struggles to trust Mia.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260627210000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women: NY</title>
    <desc>The tension between Misty and the rest of the group escalates; Kristin's anxiety over her upcoming birthday mounts; the group throws Kristin a birthday bash.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon, Gino and Fred's Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Gordon, Gino and Fred search for the best BBQ in Texas; testing out cowboy gear with the guys; watch them try their hand at lumberjacking and go skinny-dipping in a watering hole before they serve a smoky buffet at a local rodeo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gogglebox</title>
    <desc>Caroline Aherne narrates as some of Britain's most opinionated viewers comment freely.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Dr. Karl slides behind the doors of a guitar factory to see how Australia's favorite instrument is made.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627023000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Dr Karl gets the scoop on how two of our most popular ice creams are made. Australians each devour around 18 litres of ice cream a year, making us the third-largest population of ice cream eaters on the planet.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon, Gino and Fred's Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Gordon, Gino and Fred search for the best BBQ in Texas; testing out cowboy gear with the guys; watch them try their hand at lumberjacking and go skinny-dipping in a watering hole before they serve a smoky buffet at a local rodeo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gogglebox</title>
    <desc>Caroline Aherne narrates as some of Britain's most opinionated viewers comment freely.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche's professor tells her that she can pass her course easily, in return for unsavory favors.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627053000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Pregnant Cheyenne believes she won the title of prom queen only because of Van's popularity, so she refuses to go; Reba and Brock react to a high-school student who asks Kyra to the prom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Lucia rescues a painting by an eminent Scottish artist; Hum along as Julyan makes a well-travelled Lebanese stringed instrument sing again, then restore a trailblazing pilot's historic headgear with Suzie.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Travelling Auctioneers</title>
    <desc>Will Kirk and Christina Trevanion take their mobile auction house on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Christina Trevanion is in Peterborough, where experts Catherine Southon and Kate Bliss assist the teams before heading to Lichfield in Staffordshire for a very merry auction; Christina learns how "A Christmas Carol" helped to save the festive season.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lakefront Luxury</title>
    <desc>Young professionals Jack and Laura have sold their home in the city and are searching for a lakeside escape; the first home on their search is a beautiful rustic home; the second home has an open-concept kitchen; the third home have a secret door.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lakefront Luxury</title>
    <desc>Retired couple Janet and Tom search for a lakefront property to enjoy fishing, one of their favorite pastimes. Their hunt leads them to three homes, all with unique amenities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Scenic River Journeys</title>
    <desc>Navigating the historic Potomac River from West Virginia to Chesapeake Bay, passing through Washington, D.C. and the national monuments and ending at George Washington's Mount Vernon estate.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Canadian Baking Show</title>
    <desc>The bakers take on three challenges for bread week.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Extreme Weather Salvage</title>
    <desc>Bundles of cedar wood tree trunks are smashed apart, releasing thousands of logs on the shoreline; Jeremy and his crew must work fast to recover the cargo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Below Zero Canada</title>
    <desc>Kim and Pierre's trapline expansion is well underway when a troublesome local resident threatens to derail their plans; Jon and his wife Lally brave extreme arctic conditions as they attempt to secure a supply of food.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">History by the Numbers</title>
    <desc>The inside track on five of the greatest heists in history; these are not petty robberies, but high-stakes operations meticulously planned and audaciously executed, with a cast of colorful characters from the mastermind to the snitch.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Pottery Throw Down</title>
    <desc>Ten home potters from around the United Kingdom travel to Stoke-on-Trent, the home of British pottery, to take part in a competition to become top potter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Pottery Throw Down</title>
    <desc>Ten home potters from around the United Kingdom travel to Stoke-on-Trent, the home of British pottery, to take part in a competition to become top potter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Pottery Throw Down</title>
    <desc>Dig into a real mystery when the 10 remaining potters attempt to throw a classic puzzle jug that will impress judges Keith and Rich; then feel the mood in the studio shift when the potters are hit with a surprise blindfolded second challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Pottery Throw Down</title>
    <desc>Ten home potters from around the United Kingdom travel to Stoke-on-Trent, the home of British pottery, to take part in a competition to become top potter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gogglebox</title>
    <desc>Caroline Aherne narrates as some of Britain's most opinionated viewers comment freely.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260627210000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Travelling Auctioneers</title>
    <desc>Will Kirk and Christina Trevanion take their mobile auction house on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260626231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 7</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626231500 +0000" stop="20260626233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Live</title>
    <desc>Celebrity interviews and discussing recipes, beauty, fashion and current events pertinent to the tri-state region.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260626233000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>The world's most talented amateur performers -- singers, dancers, magicians, comedians and more -- appear before celebrity judges and compete to win a life-changing prize, as well as millions of viewers' hearts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627033400 +0000" stop="20260627043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Hailing from Rockefeller Center in the heart of New York City, Jimmy has made it his mission to make sure viewers end the day with a smile; each weeknight, he hosts A-list guests, from movie stars to athletes, comedians, public figures and everyone in between; he also delivers a signature nightly monologue, performs in topical comedy sketches, plays fan-favorite games, and presents recurring segme</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627043700 +0000" stop="20260627053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>With his signature monologue and sharp newsy segments like "A Closer Look," Seth Meyers hilariously breaks down the day's biggest stories and takes the current political circus head-on. He then welcomes Hollywood's most beloved A-list guests, as well as people not seen anywhere else in late night, like political figures and other interesting newsmakers. With fan-favorite comedy segments that becom</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627053700 +0000" stop="20260627060700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627060700 +0000" stop="20260627063700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627063700 +0000" stop="20260627070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627070500 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "Weren't for the Wind"; Jamie Lee Curtis; "Scenes and Stories"; Caitriona Balfe; Shanti Bhavan; Growth Day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Jared Haibon heads down to Dallas, stirring up some southern charm with Opal Lee; Texas State Fair; chef Tiffany Derry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Victim of Nursing Home Abuse?</title>
    <desc>Have you or a family member been a victim of nursing home abuse?</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Lifestyle trends in food, nightlife, art, travel and entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Open House NYC</title>
    <desc>Host Sara Gore presents a guide to upscale real estate in and around the Big Apple. In addition to a look at the hottest homes on the market, the show also provides interior design tips from specialists and a wealth of information on renovation and stylish living.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Saturday Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>News headlines, interviews, and stories intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning for Americans and help viewers with their finances, health and well-being.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Saturday Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Saturday Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Saturday Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom Protecting the Wild</title>
    <desc>Dr. Rae explores the wonderful world of mustelids, such as sea otters in Seattle; Peter joins a biologist in British Columbia who's protecting orphaned fisher kits, and later witnesses a milestone when one of them takes its leap back into the wild.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom Protecting the Wild</title>
    <desc>In Queensland, Australia, Peter and Dr. Rae join volunteers providing critical animal protection for rescued koalas and witness the rehabilitation of rare tree kangaroos; at a zoo in Texas, Dr. Rae provides care to rescued baby spider monkeys.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627143000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Earth Odyssey With Dylan Dreyer</title>
    <desc>Dylan Dreyer explores the undersea world of the Portuguese coast, meets the only wild monkeys roaming free in Europe and discovers a remarkable Iberian hunter -- the chameleon.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Child</title>
    <desc>Sheinelle Jones heads down under to meet cute koalas, kickboxing kangaroos and adorable sea lions getting ready to take their first plunge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260627153000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forever Young With Dr. Pablo Prichard</title>
    <desc>Dr. Pablo sits down with Anthony Geisler to dive into the psychology of motivation, the evolution of fitness and the innovations reshaping health engagement; together, the pair will explore scalable systems designed to turn intention into habit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626220000 +0000" stop="20260626230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Mery, who's 17 weeks pregnant, is rushed to A&amp;E after falling down her stairs. Jessica has a netball injury. And a junior doctor carries out a chest procedure for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260626230500 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>A 79-year-old has chest injuries after a garden fall. A London Underground worker has had a suspected heart attack. And ex-sailor Peter has an infected splinter in his arm.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627001000 +0000" stop="20260627011500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">999: On the Front Line</title>
    <desc>Paramedics help a man who has collapsed by the side of a road, and a 15-year-old girl and a two-year-old boy who are both having seizures.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627011500 +0000" stop="20260627022000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Mery, who's 17 weeks pregnant, is rushed to A&amp;E after falling down her stairs. Jessica has a netball injury. And a junior doctor carries out a chest procedure for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627022000 +0000" stop="20260627025000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Dorothy wants a bolthole on Menorca. For seven years she's been caring for her husband, who is disabled after having a stroke. A holiday home will provide respite for them and his carers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627025000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627075500 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Julian and Anna Maria Shelley welcome their rivals to Shelley Guest House in Aberystwyth. They treat their guests to some old-school entertainment and a monumental continental breakfast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627085500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>John and Sharyn host at the five-star Ixworth House in Bury St Edmunds, Suffolk. John reveals his hidden talents, but his performance at breakfast proves hard to digest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627085500 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Part-time panto dame Graham Smith welcomes his rivals to the Georgian House and Mews in York. But some of his guests make hair-raising discoveries in their rooms.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Hazel Mcaleese hosts at the George Hotel in Orton, Cumbria. Will a spot of trout fishing have her guests hooked.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's the final day of the competition and time for the B&amp;Bers to face the music as they find out how much they've been paid and who's won.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627103500 +0000" stop="20260627113500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Lisa and her daughter are looking for a traditional Spanish holiday home with a modern twist near the inland villages of Andalucía. Jonnie Irwin lines up five options for their £75k budget.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627113500 +0000" stop="20260627124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Jonnie Irwin house-hunts around the hilltop town of Cómpeta, in southern Spain, with Michael and Seamus from Northern Ireland. They want a holiday home with space to entertain for £175k.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627124000 +0000" stop="20260627134000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Sarah and Adam from Sussex are looking for a Spanish holiday home in the coastal town of Mojácar, despite never having visited the area before. Jean Johansson shows them five properties.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627134000 +0000" stop="20260627144000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Elvis fan Sandra and husband Desmond search for their dream home near the beaches of Mar Menor in Spain. Can Danni Menzies get them all shook up? Or will it be heartbreak back at the hotel.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627144000 +0000" stop="20260627151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Construction director David is hoping to wow his guests with an evening dedicated to his favourite kind of food - a Chinese takeaway! But can he deliver five-star fodder.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627151500 +0000" stop="20260627155000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Comedian Sarah opts for an evening of hearty soul food and some blindfolded biscuit sniffing. But will a disastrous dessert and a furniture mishap ruin Sarah's gig.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627155000 +0000" stop="20260627162000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Hairdresser Steph attempts to win over her guests with an evening of Spanish food. Will she be a cut above the rest, or will she be saying 'adios' to the £1000 prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627162000 +0000" stop="20260627165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Coffee shop worker Lisa treats her guests to a taste of Mexico, even though she's never been there! After some cheesecake confusion there's a smashing end to the evening.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627165000 +0000" stop="20260627172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Carpet and flooring specialist Chris hopes that his music-inspired nosh will have his guests dancing on the ceiling. But with mixed reviews, can Chris reach the top spot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627172000 +0000" stop="20260627175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Lee and Emma host the week's first visit at the Laurel Bank Hotel in Fife, where the B&amp;Bers get into the swing of things on a golf course.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627175500 +0000" stop="20260627182500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Winnie and Ashley hope their guests will lap up the luxury of the Hidden Horizon glampsite in Clydebank, with hot tubs, bubbly and a Loch Lomond boat trip up their sleeves.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627182500 +0000" stop="20260627185500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Two B&amp;Bers don't feel so sweet about their suite at father and daughter Jav and Sara's Lemonfield Hotel in Seaburn, Sunderland. But will a spot of glass blowing completely shatter the mood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260627185500 +0000" stop="20260627193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Everything is going far too well on the week's final visit, to Gary and Chris's place - The Grays Hotel in Blackpool. So naturally, the B&amp;Bers root out some issues at breakfast.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Angels</title>
    <desc>The Lone Star state brings heavy hitters, as Dallas' best battle it out. An Angel Face Off takes an emotional turn when artists must create tattoos for canvases affected by colon cancer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master: Rivals</title>
    <desc>Josh ignites rivalries and sparks fly. Two Artists receive an advantage that no one in the competition has ever had, and their cutthroat strategy has tension soaring.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master: Rivals</title>
    <desc>Vendettas have the Artists at each other's throats. One Artist loses his cool while the others move one step closer to 100k and the title of Ink Master.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627014500 +0000" stop="20260627021000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Things get rough when Gentle Jay comes back to the Ink Master shop to face not one but three unhappy Canvases.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627021000 +0000" stop="20260627023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Honour is on the line as Lydia Bruno and Lalo return to redeem their mistakes on unhappy military veteran Canvases.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627023500 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just Tattoo Of Us USA</title>
    <desc>Things get hot when The Challenge's own lovebirds, Cara Maria and Paulie, risk their new relationship. Best frenemies make throwing shade an art form when they use ink on each other.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Cribs</title>
    <desc>In this episode of Teen Cribs our first stop is Samantha's Pennsylvania princess palace, then we get to check out Dylan's Colorado mountain mansion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627052000 +0000" stop="20260627061000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>After following her mum's footsteps by becoming a teen mum, Danielle strives to prove she can do things differently. But she soon learns she needs help managing school, a job and a baby.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627061000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom UK: Next Generation</title>
    <desc>Chloe is struggling to fully trust Jack. Isha feels like her and Jamie are drifting apart. Whitney goes on her first date in 2 years! Angel and Matt try to work through their issues.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom UK: Next Generation</title>
    <desc>Isha turns to the gym to improve her mental health. Whitney's reaches breaking point. Jack has got a big surprise planned for Chloe. It's showtime for Angel, who goes into labour.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom UK: Next Generation</title>
    <desc>Matt and Angel welcome a new member to the family! Jack makes a big promise to Chloe and E-H. Whitney and Elizabeth seal their bond. Isha and Jamie's relationship hits new highs and lows.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Superfan Keyonnah can hardly believe her luck, she's almost certain that she's been having an online relationship with her childhood crush, the rapper Bow Wow. Is this too good to be true.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Rudy met Tyrell in a teen chat room over 17 years ago but Tyrell has never been able to meet her! Rudy now wants Nev and Kamie to help her find her elusive longtime lover.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Brendan loves McKenna, but failed attempts to connect have left him wondering if McKenna is for real. Nev teams with social media sensation Karrueche Tran to help Brendan uncover the truth.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627143000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627153000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260627163000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Damiano David</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627003000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Push Showcase: Jordan Adetunji</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Ayra Starr</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Shaboozey</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: The Warning</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627023000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Flyana Boss</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH: Chappell Roan Interview</title>
    <desc>Chappell Roan loves her whole debut album.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627033000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Push Presents: Teddy Swims</title>
    <desc>Teddy Swims chats with MTV about life, music and his rise to superstardom, and gives us exclusive performances of two of his tracks.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Old School</title>
    <desc>After discovering his girlfriend has been participating in group sex, attorney Mitch feels his world come undone. He moves into a new place, which happens to be near a college campus, and tries to get his life back together. Two of his best friends, Frank and Beanie, start hanging out at Mitch's house, eventually turning the place into a wild party pad, much to the ire of the college's dean, Gordo</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Longest Yard</title>
    <desc>Disgraced pro football quarterback Paul Crewe (Adam Sandler) lands in jail, where manipulative Warden Hazen (James Cromwell) recruits him to advise the institution's team. This turns into a lead role quarterbacking a crew of inmates in a game against a team of prison guards. Aided by incarcerated ex-NFL coach Nate Scarborough (Burt Reynolds), Crewe and his team must overcome not only the bloodthir</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627033000 +0000" stop="20260627053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Old School</title>
    <desc>After discovering his girlfriend has been participating in group sex, attorney Mitch feels his world come undone. He moves into a new place, which happens to be near a college campus, and tries to get his life back together. Two of his best friends, Frank and Beanie, start hanging out at Mitch's house, eventually turning the place into a wild party pad, much to the ire of the college's dean, Gordo</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627053000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo welcome Steve-O to play an extreme version of "The Quiet Game," change the feng shui in the room by lighting a few "Ass Candles," and lose a tooth or three.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo discuss why grandmas clean the best in "Old Lady Clean," dumb new technology in "Terrible Tech," and the dangers of parades in "The Pain Parade.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627063000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and guest host Lolo Wood get clueless on the ocean and end up getting Sea Stupid, toss too many bags with Outta Control Cornhole, and have to work on their patience because they Hate.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and guest co-host Nikki Blaze preview some alternative transportation and learn what not to do in the house.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627073000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Chanel hang out with hip-hop superstar Wale, meet a few women with "No Chill," see who's "Numb to the Madness," and meet some "Fans of the District.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo get "Bottle Service," ask some out of control people to "Settle Down" and take a course in "Offensive Driving.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo say their prayers in "Messing With the Blessing"; meeting some hard-headed "Battering Pams"; sucking up some fun with "The Vac Pack.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo have a bloody good time in "Vampin' Out," smash the glass in "Shatter Days are for the Boys," and fall victim to the universe in "Cosmic Justice.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Chanel give out "Ridicky Awards" for categories including "The Biggest D...," "The Freedom Falcon," and "The Grand Slam.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo see viral hacks gone wrong in "It Worked on the Internet," "Liar Liars," and experience true devotion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo discover the dangers of hesitating in "Uncommitted," try jumping some rope in "Rope Dopes," and discuss the importance of oral hygiene in "Dentists Approved.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Arielle Vandenberg get elevated to boogie, try and steer clear of some bad bambis and score runs with style.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Dana White; "Banned-Kinis"; "Hot Heads.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Carly Aquilino discover the joys of being mean in "Ultimate A-Holes"; revealing some bizarre situations in "Can't Explain"; realizing that fueling up can be hard in "GA.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob Dyrdek, Steelo Brim and Carly Aquilino hide their cups from some clever Drink Thieves; celebrating found fashion with Wearable Weirdness; getting second-hand road rash from all the people in.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Gymnastics champion Laurie Hernandez joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to talk about her finely tuned "Slamdar," and the difference between her and "Street Gymnasts.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob and Stella welcome Carly Aquilino to see how easy it is to rattle the brain; the dark side of boat ownership.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Lolo Wood feel the pain of jumping off swings in "Sad Swing Exits"; experiencing the terror of "Accidental Explosions"; discovering that monkeys and cars don't mix in "Monkey Menaces.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627143000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood show off Weird Gym fits, keep on Working Through It and take a ride in Dirt Bike Dirted.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Chris Pontius; "All Natural Weirdness"; "Party Boys.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627153000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get ready to slow dance in "Prom Problems," pull over some "D-Student Drivers," and disrespect their elders in "Suck it, Grandpa!".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob and Steelo welcome Camille Kostek to discover the dangers of biking in "Mountain Misery," witness the worst case scenario in "Couldn't Have Gone Worse," and vow to never slide down a railing again in "Derailed.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260626214500 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nobody</title>
    <desc>Hutch Mansell fails to defend himself or his family when two thieves break into his suburban home one night. The aftermath of the incident soon strikes a match to his long-simmering rage. In a barrage of fists, gunfire and squealing tires, Hutch must now save his wife and son from a dangerous adversary -- and ensure that he will never be underestimated again.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Old</title>
    <desc>A vacationing family discovers that the secluded beach where they're relaxing for a few hours is somehow causing them to age rapidly, reducing their entire lives into a single day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627023000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) jumps to the service of a beautiful hotel guest (guest star Angelle Brooks); Junior and Helen (Garrett Morris, Ellia English) buy a karaoke player.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Braxton and Fancy (Christopher B. Duncan, Garcelle Beauvais) get raises, leaving Jamie (Jamie Foxx) feeling slighted.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627033000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Junior and Helen offer a free getaway, but a weekend together doesn't appeal to Jamie, Fancy and Braxton.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) hopes to find the perfect mate when the game show "Change of Heart" holds auditions. With Garrett Morris.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627043000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie and Uncle Junior rewire the hotel; Jamie dates Fancy's gold-digging pal.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) witnesses a bank robbery and his cooperation with the police puts him in danger. With Shawn Wayans and John Witherspoon.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627053000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>A former co-worker (guest star Jack Plotnick), now an Internal Revenue Service agent, threatens Shawn (Shawn Wayans).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon's letter-writing campaign gets the Williams family on a TV game show, but Shawn thinks Marlon should stay home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627063000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) accidentally challenges a boxing champion (guest star Hector "Macho" Camacho) to a fight.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) begins dating a single mother (guest star Kent Masters-King) and finds he has a lot in common with her 7-year-old son (guest star Jeremy Suarez).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627073000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon (Shawn and Marlon Wayans) take Dee's (Anna Maria Horsford) new boyfriend (guest star Richard Whiten) out for a night on the town.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon is tricked into signing a lease for a tenement apartment, then asks Shawn to help him get out of it.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon's (Marlon Wayans) research for an audition leads to a homeless man (guest star Lawrence Hilton-Jacobs) moving in with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn (Shawn Wayans) worries that Pops (John Witherspoon) will embarrass him when he meets his rich girlfriend's father (guest star Tucker Smallwood).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Rapper Busta Rhymes (as himself) saves the day after Marlon and Shawn (Marlon Wayans, Shawn Wayans) lose money for Dee's (Anna Maria Horsford) church benefit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon (Shawn Wayans, Marlon Wayans) go on "The Jerry Springer Show" and end up battling over Marlon's girlfriend (guest star Adriane Kelly). Jerry Springer also guest stars.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon (Shawn Wayans, Marlon Wayans) plot to keep Pops (John Witherspoon) from selling the family home by making it less marketable.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Pops (John Witherspoon) shows off his chili at a food festival, but he doesn't know its secret ingredient: dog food.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>After Shawn (Shawn Wayans) is swindled by a business agent, Marlon (Marlon Wayans) takes an acting job to help his brother.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon's (Marlon Wayans) new role as the breadwinner goes to his head, making life miserable for Shawn (Shawn Wayans).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn steps in to manage a better deal for Marlon on his sitcom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Pops (John Witherspoon) challenges a politician (guest star Ronnie Schell) running for councilman and insists on avoiding a mudslinging campaign.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Pops (John Witherspoon) feuds with his restaurant rival, Rick (guest star Earl Billings), while Shawn (Shawn Wayans) romances Rick's daughter, J'Leeta (guest star Tracey Cherelle Jones).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260626233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260626233000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>In a classic game-show version of "Hangman," contestants solve word puzzles for cash and prizes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>The world's most talented amateur performers -- singers, dancers, magicians, comedians and more -- appear before celebrity judges and compete to win a life-changing prize, as well as millions of viewers' hearts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627033400 +0000" stop="20260627043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Hailing from Rockefeller Center in the heart of New York City, Jimmy has made it his mission to make sure viewers end the day with a smile; each weeknight, he hosts A-list guests, from movie stars to athletes, comedians, public figures and everyone in between; he also delivers a signature nightly monologue, performs in topical comedy sketches, plays fan-favorite games, and presents recurring segme</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627043700 +0000" stop="20260627053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>With his signature monologue and sharp newsy segments like "A Closer Look," Seth Meyers hilariously breaks down the day's biggest stories and takes the current political circus head-on. He then welcomes Hollywood's most beloved A-list guests, as well as people not seen anywhere else in late night, like political figures and other interesting newsmakers. With fan-favorite comedy segments that becom</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627053700 +0000" stop="20260627061200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627061200 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Top Story With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Reporting of breaking news and developing stories in real time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>Karen and Mark Duenas manage to keep the romance alive even after raising five sons, then an ordinary night ends in a tragic murder that will test the bonds of family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Jared Haibon heads down to Dallas, stirring up some southern charm with Opal Lee; Texas State Fair; chef Tiffany Derry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Very Local Presents</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>News headlines, interviews, and stories intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning for Americans and help viewers with their finances, health and well-being.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Earth Odyssey With Dylan Dreyer</title>
    <desc>Dylan Dreyer embarks on a trek through the forests and woodlands to find the animals that love living green.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wildlife Nation With Jeff Corwin</title>
    <desc>Jeff embarks on a mission to promote the conservation of America's wildlife and wild places; Peregrine falcons; black bear cubs; saving a unique species of turtle.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Kids News</title>
    <desc>Teens and exercise; one of the chemicals in cigarettes that makes smoking particularly harmful to teens; examining the battle of Fort Sumter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tails of Valor</title>
    <desc>A surfing dog helps a young boy find his confidence in the water; a poodle helps a young woman who has a heart defect.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom Protecting the Wild</title>
    <desc>In Queensland, Australia, Peter and Dr. Rae join volunteers providing critical animal protection for rescued koalas and witness the rehabilitation of rare tree kangaroos; at a zoo in Texas, Dr. Rae provides care to rescued baby spider monkeys.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627143000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Earth Odyssey With Dylan Dreyer</title>
    <desc>Dylan Dreyer explores the undersea world of the Portuguese coast, meets the only wild monkeys roaming free in Europe and discovers a remarkable Iberian hunter -- the chameleon.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Child</title>
    <desc>Sheinelle Jones heads down under to meet cute koalas, kickboxing kangaroos and adorable sea lions getting ready to take their first plunge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627153000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forever Young With Dr. Pablo Prichard</title>
    <desc>Dr. Pablo sits down with Anthony Geisler to dive into the psychology of motivation, the evolution of fitness and the innovations reshaping health engagement; together, the pair will explore scalable systems designed to turn intention into habit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 KPMG Women's PGA Championship</title>
    <desc>From Hazeltine National Golf Club in Chaska, Minn.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: PGA Tour Golf</title>
    <desc>From TPC River Highlands in Cromwell, Conn.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260627220000 +0000" stop="20260627223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 6</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>Lynae Vanee breaks down top headlines from her distinct perspective and lived experience.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Shining a spotlight on rising filmmakers pushing the culture forward through dope short films; featuring the short films: "P*ssybaby," "For the Family" and "Patrol.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Michael Jackson</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Michael Jackson with his latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untapped</title>
    <desc>Viewer-submitted music videos highlight untapped indie artists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Pierre Edwards; D.L. Hughley; A.J. Jamal; Marva Moncrieffe (Simply Marvalous).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627033000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Cedric the Entertainer; Andre Covington; Angela Means.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A mix of the best hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos, from the hottest new releases to favorite throwbacks.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untapped</title>
    <desc>Viewer-submitted music videos highlight untapped indie artists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Pierre Edwards; D.L. Hughley; A.J. Jamal; Marva Moncrieffe (Simply Marvalous).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627063000 +0000" stop="20260627070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Cedric the Entertainer; Andre Covington; Angela Means.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627070000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Two-time NBA champion Josh Powell joins Big Bank, DJ Scream and Baby Jade to chat about learning how to zen out, the truth about athlete salaries, his life outside of basketball and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">REVOLT Sports Weekly</title>
    <desc>In the series premiere, host Mariah Rose covers Micah Parsons' big return to Dallas, the Giants benching Russell Wilson, Kawhi Leonard's wild contract requests, and more. Presented by Levi's®.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Rappers Guapdad 4000, Stone Cold Jzzle, DW Flame and FourFive take their shots in the 3-point contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Michael Jackson</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Michael Jackson with his latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Out the Mud</title>
    <desc>NBA legends Zach Randolph and Tony Allen welcome a star-studded lineup of athletes and artists for can't-miss conversations about the journey to success.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Features the short films "As Above, So Below: The Woman With the Trapped Soul," "Raising Nia," and "Off Fairfax.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627170000 +0000" stop="20260627180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Featuring the short films like "For Richard or Poorer" and "5-Star Rating.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627180000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Featuring the short films, "Bros Propose", "Patrol", "You've Matched.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Featuring the short films: "Sugar Daddy," "Dark Before Dawn," and "Paralysis.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260627200000 +0000" stop="20260627210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Shining a spotlight on rising filmmakers pushing the culture forward through dope short films; featuring the short films: "P*ssybaby," "For the Family" and "Patrol.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 4pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 5pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC 4 News at 6pm</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 7 PM</title>
    <desc>The latest in local breaking news, weather reports and feature stories covering the vast Southern California region.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627023000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>The world's most talented amateur performers -- singers, dancers, magicians, comedians and more -- appear before celebrity judges and compete to win a life-changing prize, as well as millions of viewers' hearts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627063400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627063400 +0000" stop="20260627073700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Hailing from Rockefeller Center in the heart of New York City, Jimmy has made it his mission to make sure viewers end the day with a smile; each weeknight, he hosts A-list guests, from movie stars to athletes, comedians, public figures and everyone in between; he also delivers a signature nightly monologue, performs in topical comedy sketches, plays fan-favorite games, and presents recurring segme</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627073700 +0000" stop="20260627083700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>With his signature monologue and sharp newsy segments like "A Closer Look," Seth Meyers hilariously breaks down the day's biggest stories and takes the current political circus head-on. He then welcomes Hollywood's most beloved A-list guests, as well as people not seen anywhere else in late night, like political figures and other interesting newsmakers. With fan-favorite comedy segments that becom</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627083700 +0000" stop="20260627090700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627090700 +0000" stop="20260627093700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627093700 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "Weren't for the Wind"; Jamie Lee Curtis; "Scenes and Stories"; Caitriona Balfe; Shanti Bhavan; Growth Day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Protect Your Family From Identity Theft</title>
    <desc>Every 5 seconds there's a victim of identity theft; LifeLock helps alert you, restore your identity, and reimburse lost funds—leading the way in protecting families every day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>A journey through the historic port cities on the Sail4th 250 route, uncovering the maritime waterways that shaped the nation and continue to bring its living history to life today.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathroom Makeover</title>
    <desc>Transform your bath affordably in just one day!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>News headlines, interviews, and stories intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning for Americans and help viewers with their finances, health and well-being.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Child</title>
    <desc>Sheinelle Jones heads down under to meet cute koalas, kickboxing kangaroos and adorable sea lions getting ready to take their first plunge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forever Young With Dr. Pablo Prichard</title>
    <desc>Dr. Pablo sits down with Anthony Geisler to dive into the psychology of motivation, the evolution of fitness and the innovations reshaping health engagement; together, the pair will explore scalable systems designed to turn intention into habit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA Weekend</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom Protecting the Wild</title>
    <desc>In Queensland, Australia, Peter and Dr. Rae join volunteers providing critical animal protection for rescued koalas and witness the rehabilitation of rare tree kangaroos; at a zoo in Texas, Dr. Rae provides care to rescued baby spider monkeys.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627153000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Earth Odyssey With Dylan Dreyer</title>
    <desc>Dylan Dreyer explores the undersea world of the Portuguese coast, meets the only wild monkeys roaming free in Europe and discovers a remarkable Iberian hunter -- the chameleon.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627160000 +0000" stop="20260627190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 KPMG Women's PGA Championship</title>
    <desc>From Hazeltine National Golf Club in Chaska, Minn.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260627190000 +0000" stop="20260627220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: PGA Tour Golf</title>
    <desc>From TPC River Highlands in Cromwell, Conn.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260626233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 7p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260626233000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Got Talent</title>
    <desc>The world's most talented amateur performers -- singers, dancers, magicians, comedians and more -- appear before celebrity judges and compete to win a life-changing prize, as well as millions of viewers' hearts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627033400 +0000" stop="20260627043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Hailing from Rockefeller Center in the heart of New York City, Jimmy has made it his mission to make sure viewers end the day with a smile; each weeknight, he hosts A-list guests, from movie stars to athletes, comedians, public figures and everyone in between; he also delivers a signature nightly monologue, performs in topical comedy sketches, plays fan-favorite games, and presents recurring segme</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627043700 +0000" stop="20260627053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>With his signature monologue and sharp newsy segments like "A Closer Look," Seth Meyers hilariously breaks down the day's biggest stories and takes the current political circus head-on. He then welcomes Hollywood's most beloved A-list guests, as well as people not seen anywhere else in late night, like political figures and other interesting newsmakers. With fan-favorite comedy segments that becom</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627053700 +0000" stop="20260627060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627060400 +0000" stop="20260627063300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627063300 +0000" stop="20260627073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627073000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Hosts Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover, Scott Evans and Zuri Hall take viewers behind the velvet ropes and onto the red carpet to deliver celebrity interviews and entertainment news stories in Hollywood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1st Look</title>
    <desc>Jared Haibon heads down to Dallas, stirring up some southern charm with Opal Lee; Texas State Fair; chef Tiffany Derry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">DraftKings Casino Report</title>
    <desc>DraftKings Casino, a top-rated casino app!</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Birds Huddle</title>
    <desc>The latest news, commentary and opinion surrounding the Eagles and the NFL, along with sport-betting.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Game Time With Boomer Esiason</title>
    <desc>The former NFL quarterback interviews compelling figures in the sports and entertainment industries.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 6a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>News headlines, interviews, and stories intended to inform, entertain, inspire and set the agenda each morning for Americans and help viewers with their finances, health and well-being.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 8a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 8:30a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 9a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 9:30a</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mutual of Omaha's Wild Kingdom Protecting the Wild</title>
    <desc>In Queensland, Australia, Peter and Dr. Rae join volunteers providing critical animal protection for rescued koalas and witness the rehabilitation of rare tree kangaroos; at a zoo in Texas, Dr. Rae provides care to rescued baby spider monkeys.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627143000 +0000" stop="20260627150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Earth Odyssey With Dylan Dreyer</title>
    <desc>Dylan Dreyer explores the undersea world of the Portuguese coast, meets the only wild monkeys roaming free in Europe and discovers a remarkable Iberian hunter -- the chameleon.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627150000 +0000" stop="20260627153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Child</title>
    <desc>Sheinelle Jones heads down under to meet cute koalas, kickboxing kangaroos and adorable sea lions getting ready to take their first plunge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260627153000 +0000" stop="20260627160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Forever Young With Dr. Pablo Prichard</title>
    <desc>Dr. Pablo sits down with Anthony Geisler to dive into the psychology of motivation, the evolution of fitness and the innovations reshaping health engagement; together, the pair will explore scalable systems designed to turn intention into habit.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626230000 +0000" stop="20260626233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">As Time Goes By</title>
    <desc>When Lionel and Jean were young they dreamt of a romantic holiday together in Paris. Now that dream has become reality, they find they are not alone in this lovers' paradise and that true love never runs smoothly.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260626233000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Gardens</title>
    <desc>The Marimurtra Botanical Garden is a privileged place to enjoy rich botanical architectural landscaping in a paradise of the plant kingdom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627000000 +0000" stop="20260627010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Doc clashes with the new district midwife over natural methods; Bert becomes enamored with a new restaurant employee.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627010000 +0000" stop="20260627013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">As Time Goes By</title>
    <desc>When Lionel and Jean were young they dreamt of a romantic holiday together in Paris. Now that dream has become reality, they find they are not alone in this lovers' paradise and that true love never runs smoothly.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627013000 +0000" stop="20260627020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ageless Gardens</title>
    <desc>A Yo-Yo Ma inspired public garden; monks wander contemplatively in nature's forest garden; a retired magazine editor advocates for grief gardening; innovative tower gardens aid remote northern communities in growing their own food year-round.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627020000 +0000" stop="20260627030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Annika</title>
    <desc>Annika's teenage daughter, Morgan, gets mixed up with suspects in a revenge slaying, and Norse mythology comes to life as Annika's team closes in.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627030000 +0000" stop="20260627033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627033000 +0000" stop="20260627040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ayurvedic Way</title>
    <desc>Hosts Randall Mark and Amrita Sondhi approach cooking and exercise with wellness in mind through Ayurveda, an ancient Indian medicinal practice.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627040000 +0000" stop="20260627050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Mike's old flame Penny arrives and claims that he is the father of her baby; Nick is warned that two gangsters have been released; Greengrass falls in love with a poacher; Nick and Jo consider moving to Australia.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627050000 +0000" stop="20260627053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Divine Intervention</title>
    <desc>Sarah is worried about how people portray themselves; Marlene wants to fix her relationship with her son and his family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627053000 +0000" stop="20260627060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Balance</title>
    <desc>Stunning videos of nature paired with soothing classical music create inspiration.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627060000 +0000" stop="20260627080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beautiful Little Classics</title>
    <desc>Performances by classical musicians.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627080000 +0000" stop="20260627083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Balance</title>
    <desc>Stunning videos of nature paired with soothing classical music create inspiration.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627083000 +0000" stop="20260627090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Chicken Soup</title>
    <desc>Thought-provoking messages.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627090000 +0000" stop="20260627093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kabalah Yoga With Audi Gozlan</title>
    <desc>Audi Gozlan demonstrates a new system of yoga and meditation known as Kabbalah Yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627093000 +0000" stop="20260627100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627100000 +0000" stop="20260627103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: Modern Meditations</title>
    <desc>Featuring guided exercises of yoga and meditation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627103000 +0000" stop="20260627110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Livening the skin.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627110000 +0000" stop="20260627113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anjelica's 22 Minute Workout</title>
    <desc>A revival of the '80s aerobics series offers workouts for a wide range of ages and abilities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627113000 +0000" stop="20260627120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kabalah Yoga With Audi Gozlan</title>
    <desc>Audi Gozlan demonstrates a new system of yoga and meditation known as Kabbalah Yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627120000 +0000" stop="20260627123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627123000 +0000" stop="20260627130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Yoga for grandparents.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627130000 +0000" stop="20260627133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shaolin Tai Chi</title>
    <desc>Learn how to control breathing to enhance energy levels, boost circulatory systems, and increase breathing capacity for stronger lungs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627133000 +0000" stop="20260627140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: The Elemental Series</title>
    <desc>A series of classical hatha yoga, plus mediations and breath work.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260627140000 +0000" stop="20260627143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anjelica's Kettlebell Workout</title>
    <desc>Anjelica Scannura leads a workout.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-27</date>
  </programme>
</tv>