<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260528013155 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="FX.us">
    <display-name>US | FX East</display-name>
    <icon src="https://tlgrm.re/images/fx-us.png" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465331">
    <display-name lang="US">Freeform HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464897">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Family</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464774">
    <display-name lang="US">FYI Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470820">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FXX Canada</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470910">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470299">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Global Toronto</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465105">
    <display-name lang="US">Fuse HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465241">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465357">
    <display-name lang="US">FXX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470509">
    <display-name lang="Canada">CTV LIFE CHANNEL</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="481954">
    <display-name lang="US">Haunt TV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465290">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465167">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Mystery HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465354">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="492942">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Mystery</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486726">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486720">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486672">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486821">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV Quiz</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486853">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465002">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime Real Women</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470737">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Makeful TV SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470474">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Much Music HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465080">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV - Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486755">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">MTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486751">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">More4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467015">
    <display-name lang="US">WNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465113">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV2: Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465207">
    <display-name lang="US">Revolt HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="469871">
    <display-name lang="US">KNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464825">
    <display-name lang="US">MTVLIVE</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470330">
    <display-name lang="Canada">ONETV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="468233">
    <display-name lang="US">WCAU-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467402">
    <display-name lang="US">WPTZ-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260527200000 -0400" stop="20260527223000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Bad Boys: Ride or Die</title>
    <desc>When their late police captain gets linked to drug cartels, wisecracking Miami cops Mike Lowrey and Marcus Burnett embark on a dangerous mission to clear his name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260527223000 -0400" stop="20260528010000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Bad Boys: Ride or Die</title>
    <desc>When their late police captain gets linked to drug cartels, wisecracking Miami cops Mike Lowrey and Marcus Burnett embark on a dangerous mission to clear his name.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528010000 -0400" stop="20260528030000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Hitman</title>
    <desc>A professional assassin known only as Agent 47 (Timothy Olyphant) gets caught up in a dangerous political takeover. He flees across Eastern Europe, hoping to find out who set him up and why. However, his growing attachment to a beautiful but traumatized young woman poses as great a threat to his survival as that of the Interpol and Russian agents who are hunting him down.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528030000 -0400" stop="20260528050000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Hitman: Agent 47</title>
    <desc>Genetically engineered from conception to be the perfect killing machine, he's the culmination of decades of research, endowed with unprecedented strength, speed, stamina and intelligence. Known only as Agent 47 (Rupert Friend), his latest target is a corporation that plans to unlock the secret of his past to create an army of killers even more powerful than him. With help from a young woman, the elite assassin confronts revelations about his own origins in an epic battle with his deadliest foe.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528050000 -0400" stop="20260528053000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528053000 -0400" stop="20260528060000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>NECTAR TRI-PILLOW -Cooler, Comfy, Better Sleep! Buy One Get One FREE!</title>
    <desc>Discover the Nectar Tri-Comfort Cooling Pillow for the ultimate sleep experience! Adjustable to three firmness levels to provide customized support and cooling all night long. Order NOW to get a second pillow FREE, plus a 30-night home trial!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528060000 -0400" stop="20260528063000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>1776 - 2026 250th Anniversary Quarter Celebration Program</title>
    <desc>2026 will be one of the most historic years ever in U.S. coinage; join your host Mike Mezack to learn about the incredible U.S. Quarter program and get a chance at an exclusive P&amp;D Roll!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528063000 -0400" stop="20260528070000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>1776 Rare Silver</title>
    <desc>Celebrate the 250th Anniversary of the USA with the limited edition dual date 1776-2026 Liberty Bell Privy Silver Eagle graded perfect PF70UCAM with the First Day of Issue designation. Limited to just 500,000 examples, this is a one of a kind rarity!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528070000 -0400" stop="20260528073000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>According to Jim</title>
    <desc>In an effort to outdo Cheryl's story about meeting Oprah, Jim makes up a story about his construction office catching fire.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528073000 -0400" stop="20260528080000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim helps Andy pick up a beautiful woman at the bar, but she turns out to be crazy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528080000 -0400" stop="20260528110000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Fast &amp; Furious Presents: Hobbs &amp; Shaw</title>
    <desc>Brixton Lore is a cybernetically enhanced soldier who possesses superhuman strength, a brilliant mind and a lethal pathogen that could wipe out half of the world's population. It's now up to hulking lawman Luke Hobbs and lawless operative Deckard Shaw to put aside their past differences and work together to prevent the seemingly indestructible Lore from destroying humanity.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528110000 -0400" stop="20260528133000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Bad Boys for Life</title>
    <desc>The wife and son of a Mexican drug lord embark on a vengeful quest to kill all those involved in his trial and imprisonment -- including Miami Detective Mike Lowrey. When Mike gets wounded, he teams up with partner Marcus Burnett and AMMO -- a special tactical squad -- to bring the culprits to justice. But the old-school cops must soon learn to get along with their new elite counterparts if they are to take down the vicious cartel that threatens their lives.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528133000 -0400" stop="20260528163000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Mission: Impossible -- Fallout</title>
    <desc>Ethan Hunt and the IMF team join forces with CIA assassin August Walker to prevent a disaster of epic proportions. Arms dealer John Lark and a group of terrorists known as the Apostles plan to use three plutonium cores for a simultaneous nuclear attack on the Vatican, Jerusalem and Mecca, Saudi Arabia. When the weapons go missing, Ethan and his crew find themselves in a desperate race against time to prevent them from falling into the wrong hands.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260528163000 -0400" stop="20260528190000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Equalizer 3 - The Final Chapter</title>
    <desc>Since giving up his life as a government assassin, Robert McCall finds solace in serving justice on behalf of the oppressed. Now living in Southern Italy, he soon discovers his new friends are under the control of local crime bosses. As events turn deadly, McCall becomes their protector by taking on the mafia.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528003000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night at the Museum: Battle of the Smithsonian</title>
    <desc>Once the night guard at the Museum of Natural History, Larry Daley (Ben Stiller) is now a successful purveyor of infomercial products. Soon after learning that his museum friends have been shipped to the Smithsonian Institution, Larry receives a distress call from Jedediah, who warns him that four of history's greatest villains have come to life and are planning to take over the Smithsonian first,</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Inspiring stories of miracles and answered prayers from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim feels guilty after cheating at a church's fund-raising bingo game.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528043000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>When Cheryl's friend gets expensive jewelry from her husband as gifts for no reason, Cheryl expects Jim to do the same; Jim finds these to be unreasonable requests and doubts the husband's intentions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim encourages Gracie and Ruby to open a lemonade stand but does not anticipate fierce competition from a neighbor kid's stand.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528053000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim tells Ruby's teacher that his wife is illiterate in order to lighten his daughter's homework load.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Accident? Start here.</title>
    <desc>After an accident, discover your options, avoid costly mistakes, and learn how to connect with an attorney to review your case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528063000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Accident Compensation: Get Help Now!</title>
    <desc>Helping injured individuals get the compensation they are owed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Inspiring stories of miracles and answered prayers from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NEW! Shark PowerDetect with DuoClean Detect Technology</title>
    <desc>Meet the new Shark PowerDetect Upright Vacuum with features like DuoClean Detect Technology, self-cleaning brush roll and odor neutralizing and you will be cleaning faster, smarter and better!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">POOF! Bye Bye Under Eye Bags!</title>
    <desc>Plexaderm helps reduce Under Eye Bags, Dark Circles, and Wrinkles in just 10 minutes!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>Cory is disappointed when Eric moves back home from college; Shawn's half brother unexpectedly shows up.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>Cory's effort to make a video of Eric, Jack and Shawn's apartment life turns sour when Jack and Shawn can't get along.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>Best buddies Shawn and Cory stop speaking to each other and seek new friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528123000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>Eric decides to start his own fraternity; Shawn begins to slack off on school work because he doesn't expect to get into college.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Amazing stories of people who have experienced God's blessings.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">700 Club Interactive</title>
    <desc>Highlighting current events and stories that will help bring encouragement to people.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528143000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Andy resents a wealthy client (Nana Visitor), then ends up dating her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim is unable to transport the girls' papier-mâché grizzly bear to school because he lost his truck in an arm-wrestling match and refuses to ask for it back.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528153000 +0000" stop="20260528181000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goonies</title>
    <desc>When two brothers find out they might lose their house they are desperate to find a way to keep their home. They find a treasure map and bring some friends along to find it. They are all out looking for the "X" and trying to get away from a group of bad guys who also want the treasure.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528181000 +0000" stop="20260528201500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beetlejuice</title>
    <desc>After Barbara and Adam Maitland die in a car accident, they find themselves stuck haunting their country residence, unable to leave the house. When the unbearable Deetzes and teen daughter Lydia buy the home, the Maitlands attempt to scare them away without success. Their efforts attract Beetlejuice, a rambunctious spirit whose help quickly becomes dangerous for the Maitlands and innocent Lydia.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528201500 +0000" stop="20260528225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cinderella</title>
    <desc>After her father unexpectedly dies, young Ella (Lily James) finds herself at the mercy of her cruel stepmother (Cate Blanchett) and stepsisters, who reduce her to scullery maid. Despite her circumstances, she refuses to despair. An invitation to a palace ball gives Ella hope that she might reunite with the dashing stranger (Richard Madden) she met in the woods, but her stepmother prevents her from</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260528225000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cruella</title>
    <desc>Estella is a young and clever grifter who's determined to make a name for herself in the fashion world. She soon meets a pair of thieves who appreciate her appetite for mischief, and together they build a life for themselves on the streets of London. However, when Estella befriends fashion legend Baroness von Hellman, she embraces her wicked side to become the raucous and revenge-bent Cruella.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Jack and Faith's friendship begins to complicate his relationship with Elizabeth; Abigail pitches in to help a struggling community; a wave of kindness in Hope Valley has everyone opening their heart for a grand occasion.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>The new coach of the town's football team endangers the boys' spirits and health in his attempt to regain past glories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>The School for the Blind's caretaker sets out to become a respectable farmer so that he may adopt two orphaned brothers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>A mother tries to reunite with the daughter she abandoned, now a blind artist, but meets with hostility.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Amy is hired and tasked with calming one of the wild horses, but its temperament may prove impossible to work with.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Jack is faced with painful memories from his past, and the family is at a loss for how to help him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>A former Vietnam nurse suffers from post-traumatic stress disorder; a teenage boy learns he's adopted.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>An adopted boy meets his biological mother who is a Vietnam veteran suffering from traumatic flashbacks of the war.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>The new coach of the town's football team endangers the boys' spirits and health in his attempt to regain past glories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>The School for the Blind's caretaker sets out to become a respectable farmer so that he may adopt two orphaned brothers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>A mother tries to reunite with the daughter she abandoned, now a blind artist, but meets with hostility.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura gets into a brawl with a woman she considers to be her rival and then leaves Almanzo.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Albert claims that he is tall and athletic in a letter to his pen pal; she has fabrications of her own to conceal her paralysis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just the Way You Are</title>
    <desc>Hoping to recharge her marriage, a professional matchmaker asks her husband out on a blind date.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Once Upon a Prince</title>
    <desc>Susanna accepts help one day from Nate at her parents' store in Georgia. Sparks between them fly, but when a photo of them gets leaked to the press, Susanna is in for the shock of her life when Nate is called back home for his coronation as a king.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hello, It's Me</title>
    <desc>A widow receives messages from her late husband, urging her to move on and heal with a new man in her life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Yes, I Do</title>
    <desc>Busy chocolatier Charlotte has left helicopter mechanic James at the altar three times. Now, she somehow has to find a way to prove to him that she really does want to marry him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Jack prepares to take a big step toward building a life with Elizabeth; Abigail welcomes Becky back into her home before making an emotional decision about their future as a family.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260528230000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Abigail has to come to terms with the sudden arrival of the children's aunt; Elizabeth, Jack and the rest of Hope Valley come to witness a powerful act of love that proves everyone is right where they belong.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260529000000 +0000" stop="20260530000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Jack's mother arrives in Hope Valley and quickly proves to be a challenge for Elizabeth; Rosemary plans her perfect wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Kyle and Whitney have realized they really don't need a lot of stuff to enjoy life and want to build a home to reflect just that.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Luke and Tina are avid mountaineer's and want a wood cabin tiny house of their dreams.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528030100 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Jared and Vanessa share a love of food and the outdoors; while Vanessa cooks with her prized gadgets, Jared has accumulated a ton of survival gear; they ask John and Zack to help them pare down to the essentials and build them a tiny house on wheels.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Dusty and Ashley have been traveling the world the past couple of years and are looking to finally lay down some roots and go tiny.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Kyle and Whitney have realized they really don't need a lot of stuff to enjoy life and want to build a home to reflect just that.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Luke and Tina are avid mountaineer's and want a wood cabin tiny house of their dreams.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528070100 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Jared and Vanessa share a love of food and the outdoors; while Vanessa cooks with her prized gadgets, Jared has accumulated a ton of survival gear; they ask John and Zack to help them pare down to the essentials and build them a tiny house on wheels.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tiny House Nation</title>
    <desc>Jeremy and Lindsay have traveled the world, and they are finally ready to settle down in a tiny house. Lindsay is a fantastic baker who needs functional kitchen space; Jeremy is 6'5 and isn't sure he will even fit in a tiny house.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pain Relief Revealed</title>
    <desc>Discover the hidden story of OmegaXL with John Walsh. He dives deep into the groundbreaking supplement that promises hope and relief for millions battling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joni Table Talk</title>
    <desc>Joni and guests tackle a wide range of relevant issues, controversial subjects and hard-hitting news topics with candor and wit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Kidd and Harry Youren hunt a black bear that tore up their camp; Martha and Elli Tansy finally have a bull moose in their sights; Tom Oar educates 9-year-old Hank McAfee on the traditional skills of trapping and skinning.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Tom Oar struggles with heart problems but refuses to give up his way of life; Jake Herak and Anika Ward have added five new puppies to their pack; Martha and Elli Tansy pack hundreds of pounds of meat; Mike Horstman hunts fox for their fur.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Tom receives a diagnosis for his heart condition; Jake hunts coyotes at night; Eustace rebuilds the road to Turtle Island; Mike hunts goats; Josh and Bonnie each harvest a deer; Kidd and Harry build a heavy-duty scow boat from scratch.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Mike climbs Kodiak Island's highest peaks to take down a mountain goat, then rappels down sheer cliffs to bring home his harvest. Martha and Elli use their tracked vehicle to scout new hunting grounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Kidd and Harry Youren use explosives to battle a deep freeze to protect their cattle's drinking supply; Jake Herak's young pups learn a big lesson in lion hunting; Josh Kirk takes aim at a pack of coyotes messing with his bison.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrett takes over an odd shipment for Jenn after she receives sad family news; Dusty gets involved in the transport of two antique fire engines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528173000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Tamera and Todd learn their giant Robin Hood statue load is damaged; Samko discovers she will be hauling more trees than expected.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrett is all thumbs when it comes to handling a one-of-a-kind art piece; Marc raises and transports a massive sculpture garden.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528183000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jenn tangles with a transit bus while hauling a load of Looney Tunes memorabilia; Dusty sets a record as he transports more than four tons of vinyl albums.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jenn hauls a massive bass drum belonging to the University of Texas Longhorn Band; Todd and Tamera must move a large train replica to a dental office.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528193000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrett attempts to protect antique Christmas dolls from cold conditions; Chris Kikelhan moves a WWII-era amphibious vehicle.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Animal lover Jenn moves six large Bengal tigers; the delivery of mythological figures to a residential neighborhood forces Marc to gets creative.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528013000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang uses the Internet to cyber stalk their prey; Frank tries to drum up business for Paddy's with a viral video.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang designs a scheme to extract an artifact; their plans are jeopardized when the owners are still at home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528023000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Mac confesses to a confused priest that his weight gain is the fault of the other members of the gang.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>It's an epic battle when the gang plays one of the most twisted board games ever; Dee and Dennis face Mac, Charlie and Frank.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528033000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang uses the Internet to cyber stalk their prey; Frank tries to drum up business for Paddy's with a viral video.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang designs a scheme to extract an artifact; their plans are jeopardized when the owners are still at home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528043000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Mac confesses to a confused priest that his weight gain is the fault of the other members of the gang.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>It's an epic battle when the gang plays one of the most twisted board games ever; Dee and Dennis face Mac, Charlie and Frank.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528053000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang uses the Internet to cyber stalk their prey; Frank tries to drum up business for Paddy's with a viral video.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang designs a scheme to extract an artifact; their plans are jeopardized when the owners are still at home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528063000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Mac confesses to a confused priest that his weight gain is the fault of the other members of the gang.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>Bookmaker Max Phillips learns that his son is dying in Vietnam and tries to save him. With Jack Klugman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528073000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>Two small-time promoters find that their fighter can't meet his opponent in the ring. With Lee Marvin.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A man recovering from a nervous breakdown sees a horrifying creature on the wing of his plane. With William Shatner.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>Thomas Patrick McNulty is given a watch that possesses a strange power.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A jockey's wish to become a giant in his profession has repercussions he may regret. With Mickey Rooney.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A vindictive doll takes revenge on a man who wants it destroyed. With Telly Savalas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a murder appears to mimic an infamous crime spree from the past, Charlie and Rex rush to stop the culprit from continuing a serial killer's legacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie lets Rex take the lead as they investigate a murder at a prestigious dog show.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a murder appears to mimic an infamous crime spree from the past, Charlie and Rex rush to stop the culprit from continuing a serial killer's legacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie lets Rex take the lead as they investigate a murder at a prestigious dog show.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a murder appears to mimic an infamous crime spree from the past, Charlie and Rex rush to stop the culprit from continuing a serial killer's legacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When Superintendent Donovan transports an inmate, who happens to be his former partner, he finds himself confronting the past and caught up in a daring and dangerous escape.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Terry believes the Pontiac Bandit is stealing cars again, but Jake is convinced his friend wouldn't do that; the rest of the squad fight to keep Shaw's a police bar after some firemen stake their claim to it.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528163000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake and Rosa must deal with a mother in mourning as they work and rework a crime scene to solve a difficult murder case with confusing evidence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parks and Recreation</title>
    <desc>Leslie and Ben disagree about her campaign ad; Chris makes Ron uncomfortable; Andy and April go to the doctor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528013500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>A roast held in Laszlo's honor reveals dark secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528013500 +0000" stop="20260528021000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The housemates are invited for a weekend away at the home of a mysterious, illustrious vampire.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528021000 +0000" stop="20260528024500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires search for a missing Guillermo.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528024500 +0000" stop="20260528031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nadja and Laszlo's new familiar poses problems for an increasingly anxious Guillermo, and the vampires enlist the services of a local necromancer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528031500 +0000" stop="20260528035000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>A roast held in Laszlo's honor reveals dark secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528035000 +0000" stop="20260528042500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The housemates are invited for a weekend away at the home of a mysterious, illustrious vampire.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528042500 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires search for a missing Guillermo.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nadja and Laszlo's new familiar poses problems for an increasingly anxious Guillermo, and the vampires enlist the services of a local necromancer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528053000 +0000" stop="20260528060500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>A roast held in Laszlo's honor reveals dark secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528060500 +0000" stop="20260528064000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires search for a missing Guillermo.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528064000 +0000" stop="20260528071000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nadja and Laszlo's new familiar poses problems for an increasingly anxious Guillermo, and the vampires enlist the services of a local necromancer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528071000 +0000" stop="20260528073500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Dennis and Dee quit their jobs and concoct a plan to go on welfare; Mac and Charlie suffer the consequences when Dennis and Dee quit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528073500 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>After a rousing debate on people's rights and freedoms, Mac and Dennis run Paddy's without rules or restrictions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex are thrust into action when a popular social media star meets an untimely demise while livestreaming her wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Charlie and Rex head into the woods to track a missing photographer, a mysterious organization throws the investigation off its trail.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate a fantasy role-playing game turned deadly when a player is found slain by a sword.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex are in deep water after a university rower is shot by a sniper during team practice.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Cultures clash when the death of a Parisian journalist has Charlie and Rex partnering with a French detective in an investigation that whisks the team to Saint Pierre and Miquelon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Charlie and Rex head into the woods to track a missing photographer, a mysterious organization throws the investigation off its trail.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate a fantasy role-playing game turned deadly when a player is found slain by a sword.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex are in deep water after a university rower is shot by a sniper during team practice.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Cultures clash when the death of a Parisian journalist has Charlie and Rex partnering with a French detective in an investigation that whisks the team to Saint Pierre and Miquelon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Charlie and Rex head into the woods to track a missing photographer, a mysterious organization throws the investigation off its trail.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate a fantasy role-playing game turned deadly when a player is found slain by a sword.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a public defender is murdered, Cosgrove and Shaw are surprised to find Price at the crime scene; his involvement in the trial compromises the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Agent Clay consults with Benson when a woman is found gravely injured at a remote campground and the suspect could be anywhere along the Eastern Seaboard; Bruno and Silva take a chance on an odd hunch to see if it becomes a lead.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elsbeth</title>
    <desc>A fallen '90s supermodel returns to New York for a reunion and revenge, leading Elsbeth to sort through old grudges and lies to catch a killer; Officer Hackett takes her turn in the spotlight.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Law</title>
    <desc>A woman hires rental children to play her family after a falling out with her biological children; Abby is devastated after reading Sofia's essay; Harry is lost after his breakup with Joanne.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 11</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528033500 +0000" stop="20260528040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528040500 +0000" stop="20260528050500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>Coaxed from her home for a photoshoot, a promising young athlete never returns: Caryn Lieberman brings us through the DNA breakthrough that cracks the case to a mother's national safety campaign.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528050500 +0000" stop="20260528053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528053500 +0000" stop="20260528063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>Three chefs enter the arena ready to grill in the Wildfire Round; it's a fierce battle of the kebab in the Crossfire Round; in the Feast of Fire, pub grub is on the menu.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528063500 +0000" stop="20260528073500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masters of Flip</title>
    <desc>Kortney and Dave flip a rundown property into a stunning home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528073500 +0000" stop="20260528083500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Brother Canada</title>
    <desc>The houseguests compete for the coveted Power of Veto where the winner has the ability to veto a nominee up for eviction or leave the nominations the same.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528083500 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SIGN OFF</title>
    <desc>Sign off.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Today With James Robison</title>
    <desc>The mother-daughter authors of "God Won't Leave You There" relate their lives and the lives of those in scripture to show how God's purpose is a promise that never fails.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News Morning</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast to start your day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Morning Show</title>
    <desc>Viewers from across the country are welcomed in for an hour of smart conversation, lifestyle segments, big-name guests and live performances.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tamron Hall</title>
    <desc>Viral social media personality Reesa Teesa is back with her memoir, "What the -- Do I Do Now?: Reclaiming Myself, One Piece at a Time"; "The Bachelorette" alumna and two-time New York Times bestselling author Hannah Brown gives a peek at her new book, "Reasons to Be Loved by You"; former monk and Peloton instructor Sam Yo joins us to discuss his new book, "The Monk's Mindset: Finding Stillness in </desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Property Brothers: Forever Home</title>
    <desc>An active family loves having room for sports in their backyard, but the low ceilings and an awkward layout inside keep the home from being perfect; Drew and Jonathan plan a modern renovation to turn this dated property into an ideal home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528163000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Save My Reno</title>
    <desc>David and Wemi hate their home's galley-style kitchen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>Three chefs are ready to burn the competition in the Wildfire Round; in the Crossfire Round, it's a battle with tuna loin; the chefs serve up a beef lovers' banquet in the Feast of Fire.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masters of Flip</title>
    <desc>Kortney and Dave take on a flip with a big addition and multiple living spaces.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>Sunny Anderson interviews "Beyond the Gates" stars Trisha Mann-Grant and Ambyr Michelle; and makes her PB&amp;J wings for Drew.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528193000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>Drew chats with Hilary Duff all about growing up in the spotlight, motherhood and her return to pop music with her latest album and tour.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>Victor and Nikki force Nick to face his issues; Phyllis gives Patty a history lesson; Kyle gives Jack surprising news about Diane.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 5</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 6</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260528223000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528003000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elvis Presley: The Final Hours</title>
    <desc>An examination of the last day of Elvis Presley's life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Wendy Spring learns out why her husband is suddenly interested in yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528023000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Jasmine Washington is concerned about her boyfriend's backsliding behavior.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Lindsey Johnson fears her unemployed boyfriend is not using his time wisely.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528033000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Mondo Brown discovers why his girlfriend has been so out of pocket lately.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sex Clinic</title>
    <desc>Zach hopes to get answers about his problematic penis; Michelle wants to know more about the skin growths on her thighs; Taleela seeks some advice.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sex Clinic</title>
    <desc>A male stripper comes in to get a rash looked at, and Emily requests an STI test.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sex Clinic</title>
    <desc>Marco finds a lump on his penis; Harriette gets her dry vagina examined; Iffy seeks help for ongoing issues with premature ejaculation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sex Clinic</title>
    <desc>Taps has ejaculation issues; Tracy's concerned she might be a sex addict; Tom needs an STI test; Jordan has a lump on his bum.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Amy Winehouse: The Tragic Downfall</title>
    <desc>Diving into the life and struggles of singer and songwriter Amy Winehouse.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Lily agrees to go on a date with a handsome older man, but things turn sour when he gets high; Che is vacationing in Mexico and picks up a Norwegian hottie, but he gets caught by her husband and seized by the Mexican police.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>When Phelisha agrees to date a white co-worker, she's shocked to see him dressed up as 50 Cent; Cory scores with a MILF, but leaves a treasured family heirloom at her house and must retrieve it the only way he knows how -- in disguise.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Nicholas is worried about his relationship with Ava.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Jill wants to know why Rose constantly wants alone time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Freedia: Queen of Bounce</title>
    <desc>Freedia reunites with her father; the team rocks Buku Fest.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Freedia: Queen of Bounce</title>
    <desc>Team Freedia shoots a video for Dangerous and prepares for a European tour; Queen Diva suffers a career-threatening injury.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Freedia: Queen of Bounce</title>
    <desc>Team Freedia kicks off the European tour in Berlin; Freedia must make an important decision regarding Team Freedia's future.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Beatles: In the Life</title>
    <desc>The Beatles took the world by storm in the 1960s and are still the best-selling band of all time with 183 million sales worldwide.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528143000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Killing John Lennon</title>
    <desc>A dramatic step-by-step breakdown behind the lead up to John Lennon's murder on Dec. 8, 1980.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Willie Nelson: The Outlaw Country King</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Wendy Spring learns out why her husband is suddenly interested in yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528173000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Jasmine Washington is concerned about her boyfriend's backsliding behavior.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Lindsey Johnson fears her unemployed boyfriend is not using his time wisely.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528183000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Mondo Brown discovers why his girlfriend has been so out of pocket lately.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas in Carolina</title>
    <desc>Career-driven investment banker Elle has given up on love until she meets Wesley, who invites her to his hometown in South Carolina, where she rediscovers the spirit of Christmas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">How to Ruin the Holidays</title>
    <desc>As a family prepares for a final Christmas together in their family home, Michelle works to redefine her relationships with her father and siblings.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528000000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two Tickets to Paradise</title>
    <desc>When two weddings are ruined by both the bride and groom getting left at the altar, they still decide to take their honeymoons, not knowing they are heading to the same resort in Hawaii.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose explains to her daughter why she has so little money to leave in her will.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528023000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Even man-hungry Blanche finds it difficult to tolerate her niece's promiscuous nature.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy needs surgery after injuring herself during tap dancing lessons.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528033000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche falls for a handsome and successful businessman but is unsure whether she wants to take on the responsibility of his young children.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche's professor tells her that she can pass her course easily, in return for unsavory favors.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528043000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche, Dorothy and Rose vie for a charity award while fighting the flu.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose must look for work after she loses her grief-counseling job.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528053000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose explains to her daughter why she has so little money to leave in her will.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Even man-hungry Blanche finds it difficult to tolerate her niece's promiscuous nature.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528063000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy needs surgery after injuring herself during tap dancing lessons.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Waltons</title>
    <desc>An unscrupulous student at Boatwright University steals John-Boy's notes; the blame falls on a good friend of John-Boy's, causing a great deal of hurt and distrust.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Waltons</title>
    <desc>Grandpa gets angry and moves out with Grandma after John suggests he take life a little easier.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>As he tries to woo a powerful sports agent who also happens to be gay, Van accidentally "outs" his mother-in-law.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba and Cheyenne throw a surprise party in honor of Van's new arena football contract, but the real surprise comes when Van announces he has been traded to a team in Denver.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba confronts Brock and Barbra Jean's therapist when she learns he holds her responsible for most of their marital problems; Cheyenne prepares to console Van on his first visit home but is crushed to find that he loves his life in Denver.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>When Reba encourages Brock to follow his dream of playing professional golf, Barbra Jean gets upset, fearing it may lead to the end of her marriage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Cheyenne's emotions about Van living part-time in Denver boil over when she learns that he lied about having to return to Denver early.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba and Barbra Jean battle over who should host Thanksgiving dinner and feelings get hurt; BJ cooks.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba allows Kyra to spend time unsupervised with her boyfriend, but she questions that decision when she learns they broke the rules.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528123000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Cheyenne and the rest of the family try to cheer Van up after a knee injury ends his arena-football career; Van receives a payout from the team but begins to blow the money on gifts for the family.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche fears she may be pregnant, but is actually going through menopause.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528133000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>The girls move into a Miami Beach hotel; they dress up to attend Burt Reynolds' movie premiere, only to be caught in a hotel raid, mistaken for prostitutes and dragged off to jail.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy begs Blanche to go out with her ex-husband, Stan, but becomes jealous when the couple hits it off; Sophia and Rose begin selling sandwiches on the Boardwalk but inadvertently make an enemy of another vendor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528143000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>A neighbor dies shortly after having a heated argument with Rose.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Lorelai, Rory and Emily take a road trip to North Carolina to attend a wedding; Lane goes into labor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528013000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Lois becomes a black belt while working out the aggression she feels toward the tourists who flock to Quahog during autumn.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Meg agrees to kiss her nerdy news partner only to discover that the kiss has been broadcast around the world; Stewie teaches the neighborhood bully a lesson.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528023000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter joins a traveling Renaissance fair and is forced to defend his family's honor in a duel with the infamous Black Knight.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When Peter puts everything he owns on the line to buy a fishing boat, he must hunt down a famous man-eating fish to recoup his losses.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528033000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Stewie vows to keep his parents from procreating when they decide to have another baby, and he finally shrinks himself down to microscopic size in order to destroy all of Peter's sperm.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>A Wall Street power player from the 1980s replaces Professor Farnsworth as CEO of Planet Express and starts making changes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528043000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Wanting to become a chef, Bender seeks mentoring from Helmut Spragel, formerly the world's greatest culinary artist.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Amy's romance with Kif results in a surprise pregnancy, and Kif must return to his home world to give birth in a swamp.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528053000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Leela is honored for her achievement as a starship captain at the orphanage where she was raised; with Fry's help, Leela learns what happened to her parents.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Hank finds ancient artifacts buried in his front lawn and ends up enduring an all-out archaeological dig.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528063000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Hank's revenge against another parent (voice of Sally Field) almost ruins Halloween when it is seen as a cult activity. Voices of Mike Judge and Kathy Najimy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Hank unknowingly buys crack as fishing bait and is arrested for buying drugs. Guest voice: campaign adviser James Carville.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528073000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Bobby finds success as a model for husky children's clothes, much to the dismay of Hank. Voices of Mike Judge, Kathy Najimy, Pamela Segall and Brittany Murphy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NEW! Shark PowerDetect with DuoClean Detect Technology</title>
    <desc>Meet the new Shark PowerDetect Upright Vacuum with features like DuoClean Detect Technology, self-cleaning brush roll and odor neutralizing and you will be cleaning faster, smarter and better!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1776 Rare Silver</title>
    <desc>Celebrate the 250th Anniversary of the USA with the limited edition dual date 1776-2026 Liberty Bell Privy Silver Eagle graded perfect PF70UCAM with the First Day of Issue designation. Limited to just 500,000 examples, this is a one of a kind rarity!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Have Thinning Hair? Keranique Can Help Regrow Beautiful, Thicker Hair!</title>
    <desc>If you have thinning hair or hair loss, Keranique can help regrow thicker, longer and fuller hair. Keranique is the number 1 hair regrowth system for women. Regain your confidence with beautiful, thicker and fuller hair in just 3 easy steps!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women</title>
    <desc>In the years after the Civil War, Jo March lives in New York and makes her living as a writer, while her sister Amy studies painting in Paris. Amy has a chance encounter with Theodore, a childhood crush who proposed to Jo but was ultimately rejected. Their oldest sibling, Meg, is married to a schoolteacher, while shy sister Beth develops a devastating illness that brings the family back together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Whitney Houston: I Wanna Dance With Somebody</title>
    <desc>Discovered by record executive Clive Davis, Whitney Houston rises to fame in the 1980s to become one of the greatest singers of her generation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big George Foreman</title>
    <desc>From Olympic Gold medalist to World Heavyweight champion, boxer George Foreman leads a remarkable life. He finds his faith, retires and becomes a preacher. When financial hardship hits his family and church, George steps back in the ring and regains the championship at age 45, becoming the oldest heavyweight champion in boxing history.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>A gang of bikers mourning the loss of their leader hang out at Bob's Burgers; Louise's bunny ears are stolen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528203000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>The Belcher kids ditch their usual trick-or-treating route and head to a neighborhood known for distributing full-size candy bars; Linda and Bob go to Teddy's "Black and Orange" party.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Bob fires the kids so they won't have to work during their summer break, but they get so bored they find other work; Bob hires Mickey the bank robber.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260528213000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When Bob brings his family along for a cooking job on a docked cruise ship, the ship departs with them aboard, leaving no one to tend the restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia: Back to Win</title>
    <desc>The top five battle it out for the last immunity of the season.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Jonnie Irwin meets a house-hunter who has spent 30 years living and working in Hong Kong.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>The semi-finalists vie to go viral and are faced with an egg-ceptionally technical pressure test.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>As Frank races to stop a biological weapon attack on the city, he tries to hide the threat of danger from his family; Jamie and Danny's conflict comes to a head.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>A criminal from Danny's past kidnaps Jackie; Jamie meets his new partner; an officer accidentally shoots an innocent man.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>The 15 chefs who qualified for the draft are matched with their mentors and are given their first team challenge; each chef must create an incredible Italian dish.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie Oliver prepares "Pregnant Jools's Pasta" with crunchy chicory and watercress salad and little frangipane tarts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528073000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>On the menu is Rogan Josh curry with fluffy rice, carrot salad, poppadoms, and flatbread.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>Chef Chuck Hughes spotlights new restaurants in Canada; time-saving tech; viral kitchen hacks tested; actress Lauren Ash ("Superstore").</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary Berg is making low-effort recipes that cook slowly, starting with porchetta and then porchetta sandwiches with zesty caper and herb mayo; Mary prepares slow roasted squash and a classic pot roast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Spencer prepares a family-style roast beef dinner.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>Canadian chefs compete in culinary challenges until only one remains.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>The teams make their way to Toronto, where after the opening bell, racers are faced with a tough climb.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary Berg shares picnic recipes that are simple to make and easy to take, like Chicken Pot Hand Pies, Salmon Rillette and customizable Fridge Door Salad.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528123000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Tips for making fish and chips.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Danny and Jackie discover that a woman who recanted an abuse claim is in a relationship with a powerful councilman; Linda returns to work, causing upheaval for Danny.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>When two murder victims turn out to be members of the same group, Danny suspects a serial killer; Erin faces off with her ex-husband in court.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>Canadian chefs compete in culinary challenges until only one remains.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>Mary Berg explores lifestyle trends, do-it-yourself projects, home renovations, recipes and more; featuring celebrity guests, influencers and everyday heroes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie makes duck salad with giant croutons and cheat's rice pudding with stewed fruit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528173000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie Oliver shows how to cook oozy mushroom risotto, with spinach salad and quick lemon and raspberry cheesecake, all in just 30 minutes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528185700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>The teams make their way to Toronto, where after the opening bell, racers are faced with a tough climb.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528185700 +0000" stop="20260528192800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Selena + Chef</title>
    <desc>Selena bows down to two iconic chefs who have been behind many dinners in her life: restaurateurs, authors and BFFs Jon and Vinny; together, they attempt to make roasted chicken with cilantro sauce and a tomato bruschetta appetizer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528192800 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Selena + Chef</title>
    <desc>The great Nancy Silverton helps Selena craft an ambitious vegetable buffet, but before Selena and her friends can dig into the stunning multi-color bounty, a series of hilarious technical difficulties brings Selena's kitchen to its knees.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>The chefs battle it out to make the best barbecue feast; in the elimination round, two chefs go head-to-head and make an elevated dish using cauliflower.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Danny and Jackie discover that a woman who recanted an abuse claim is in a relationship with a powerful councilman; Linda returns to work, causing upheaval for Danny.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528004200 +0000" stop="20260528013500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unexplained: Caught on Camera</title>
    <desc>The dark energies have turned a woman's home upside down and targeted her children in the dead of night; meeting a couple who swear they can summon UFOs; tamping down the fear when a graveyard ghoul pops into view.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528013500 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>Black mists that may have demonic influence haunt a girl; Chip Coffey joins the team on the case and makes a psychic connection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528025500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Encounter: UFO</title>
    <desc>Aircraft pilots and passengers have a scary experience when they come into proximity to objects that don't appear on radar, accelerate at dizzying speeds and then stop on a dime.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528025500 +0000" stop="20260528032100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A bizarre trend happens in Ireland.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528032100 +0000" stop="20260528034600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Experts investigate the otherworldly origins of crop circles and a never-ending stream of ghost sightings in a picturesque English town.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528034600 +0000" stop="20260528043900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unexplained: Caught on Camera</title>
    <desc>The dark energies have turned a woman's home upside down and targeted her children in the dead of night; meeting a couple who swear they can summon UFOs; tamping down the fear when a graveyard ghoul pops into view.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528043900 +0000" stop="20260528053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>Probe the eerie Civil War apparitions inside a Confederate general's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528053000 +0000" stop="20260528062100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>The APRA collaborates with the mayor of West Point, Ky., who's invested in the preservation of the town; the team assesses paranormal activity in two purportedly haunted locations -- the Lynch House and Hardy Hotel.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528062100 +0000" stop="20260528071100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>APRA ambitiously conducts its most ambitious investigation to date; a full-scale paranormal experiment during a once-in-a-lifetime eclipse.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528071100 +0000" stop="20260528080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>Examine a poetic town where paranormal activity has become a daily occurrence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528080200 +0000" stop="20260528085300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries: Family Spirits</title>
    <desc>Every family has a ghost story; a child who recognizes a long-deceased grandparent in a photo album, a distraught daughter seeing her mother moments after she passes; do these supernatural occurrences persist for a deeper, ancestral reason?</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528085300 +0000" stop="20260528092000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>The ghosts of fallen soldiers return.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528092000 +0000" stop="20260528094700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>When a man moves down the street from where his father is buried, his dad reaches out; a woman's dead grandfather comes back to make sure she doesn't forget him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528094700 +0000" stop="20260528101300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Children see and play with ghosts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528101300 +0000" stop="20260528104000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Sharon and Greg unleash ghostly forces while experimenting with the paranormal.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528104000 +0000" stop="20260528110600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Ghosts of people who died in a hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528110600 +0000" stop="20260528113300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Paalini and Kim's mothers protect them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528113300 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Dan and Susan become targets of ghosts when grave sites are disturbed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528122500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Experts investigate why a Los Angeles hotel has become a magnet for death and if an ominous flight number associated with multiple aviation disasters is cursed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528122500 +0000" stop="20260528125000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Elvis' music will live on forever.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528125000 +0000" stop="20260528131500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Exploring beliefs about where people go when they die, reincarnation and unlocking past life memories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528131500 +0000" stop="20260528134100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Experts investigate the 1961 alien abduction of Betty and Barney Hill; they explore past life regression and the possibilities of reincarnation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528134100 +0000" stop="20260528140600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Broadhaven, a sleepy little seaside village in Wales, is known as the UFO capital of Europe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528140600 +0000" stop="20260528143100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>The Prince of Pop's incredible talent is matched only by his alleged salacious personal life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528143100 +0000" stop="20260528145600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Pots of gold and wishes granted is what's promised if you catch a Leprechaun.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260528145600 +0000" stop="20260528152200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Experts investigate if a mysterious caller had inside knowledge about the assassination of President John F. Kennedy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A bank manager is shot during a robbery; Jane's brother may face more trouble as his relationship with Maura begins to grow.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528020300 +0000" stop="20260528030300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A former classmate is found dead at Jane's high school reunion; Korsak gets a visit from his ex-wife; Jane's old flame returns.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528030300 +0000" stop="20260528040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>The mother of a performer is stabbed to death at a dance competition; Korsak's stepson is accused of shooting a police officer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528040100 +0000" stop="20260528050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A witness agrees to testify against a gang member after a community activist is gunned down; TV host Bill O'Reilly criticizes the police department.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528050100 +0000" stop="20260528060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A bank manager is shot during a robbery; Jane's brother may face more trouble as his relationship with Maura begins to grow.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528060400 +0000" stop="20260528070400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A former classmate is found dead at Jane's high school reunion; Korsak gets a visit from his ex-wife; Jane's old flame returns.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528070400 +0000" stop="20260528080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>The mother of a performer is stabbed to death at a dance competition; Korsak's stepson is accused of shooting a police officer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528080200 +0000" stop="20260528083200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Have Thinning Hair? Keranique Can Help Regrow Beautiful, Thicker Hair!</title>
    <desc>If you have thinning hair or hair loss, Keranique can help regrow thicker, longer and fuller hair. Keranique is the number 1 hair regrowth system for women. Regain your confidence with beautiful, thicker and fuller hair in just 3 easy steps!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528083200 +0000" stop="20260528090200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528090200 +0000" stop="20260528093200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528093200 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Jeremiah</title>
    <desc>In this weekly program, Dr. David Jeremiah delivers practical messages to the congregation at the Shadow Mountain Community Church in San Diego. Also featured is music from the Shadow Mountain Community Church Choir and Orchestra, as well as performances by musical guests that have included Steve Green and Charles Billingsley. Men and women who have been impacted by the Turning Point ministry also</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Creflo Dollar</title>
    <desc>Dr. Creflo Dollar ministers to people from all backgrounds with hopes for change; Creflo helps viewers find ways to renew their faith, mind, and spirit; based on the belief that the Bible is the written and inspired Word of God, the show is meant to invoke change in the lives of people across the globe; Creflo and his wife, Taffi, share their vision for everyone to hear the Word and gain understan</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Today With James Robison</title>
    <desc>James Robison is a former preacher who changed directions in his life several years ago and began hosting this television show alongside his wife, Betty, in order to reach out to help more people. This daily religious and self-help program welcomes guests who tell how they have successfully overcome difficulties in their lives by following God's word -- with the hope of encouraging others to do th</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joyce Meyer Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Noted for her humanitarian ministry efforts to aid suffering people around the world, Bible teacher Joyce Meyer reaches out to both Christians and non-Christians as she illustrates how to make each day better by applying biblical principles to every activity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Balancing Act</title>
    <desc>AFib and stroke awareness; concierge wellness care; redefining prostate cancer treatment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>A possessive husband is a suspect in the death of a fitness trainer; the team must work in hazmat suits as part of anti-terrorism training.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>Two Hispanic teens die in a racially motivated gang-shooting; a cousin of one of the victims plans to exact revenge on a rival black gang.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>Brenda's team hunts for a serial killer suspected of murdering a deputy DA's wife.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Officers Nolan and Harper escort four juvenile offenders to a Scared Straight program at a correctional facility, but it quickly becomes a riotous situation; Nolan is uncertain about Grace after she fails to introduce him to her ex-husband.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Officers Nolan, Chen and West are squeezed harder than ever before as their training officers evaluate whether they are truly ready for the job; one of the rookie classmates is involved in a shooting.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Nolan's discovery goes much deeper than he expected and could put his life and career in jeopardy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>Castle and Beckett must investigate a mysterious case from 1947 in order to solve the present-day murder of a treasure hunter.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>Castle and Beckett discover that the killer they are pursuing is part of an international conspiracy, and they must work with a CIA agent with whom Castle has a history.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>Beckett and Castle must stop a series of events that could result in a war.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Following a deadly attack, one member of the team reminisces.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A Naval petty officer and sole witness in an upcoming murder trial disappears.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528000000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curious Caterer Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Goldy agrees to cater an elaborate wedding, but a dead groom and a missing bridezilla brings her together with Tom again.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica investigates when a wealthy yachtsman is murdered two days before a big race, and his rival's daughter is charged with the crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Seth's niece returns to Cabot Cove for her wedding only to have her groom die accidentally before the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>While Jessica is in Atlanta to address mystery writers, a lethal virus is stolen from the Biological Research Institute.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>After a San Francisco radio station changes its music format from classical to rock, the promoter who engineered the switch dies and Jessica searches for the killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A financier (Howard Duff), reportedly swept overboard during a hurricane, turns up in Jessica's yard disguised as a handyman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica investigates when a wealthy yachtsman is murdered two days before a big race, and his rival's daughter is charged with the crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Seth's niece returns to Cabot Cove for her wedding only to have her groom die accidentally before the event.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>While Jessica is in Atlanta to address mystery writers, a lethal virus is stolen from the Biological Research Institute.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Remington Steele</title>
    <desc>Dogged by Roselli, Remington and Laura fly to London in pursuit of a stolen painting.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Remington Steele</title>
    <desc>Dogged by Roselli, Remington and Laura fly to London in pursuit of a stolen painting.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Remington Steele</title>
    <desc>A suave mystery man enters private-detective Laura Holt's life when he goes after $2 million in gems she is assigned to protect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>Mark investigates the death of a friend whom he soon discovers had not only two wives, but numerous girlfriends.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>Mark investigates the murder of a woman who died due to a malfunction in the computer system in her home; Steve decides to find a place of his own.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>A murder and attack at his beach house prompt Mark to investigate a hospital staff member who was having an affair with the deceased's young wife.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>Steve wins a dream date on a game show, but the dream ends abruptly when Steve gets shot and his date is killed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>Matlock defends a young executive (Tim Busfield) framed in the murder of a starlet (Shawn Weatherly).</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>Matlock is hired to defend a live-in nurse (Lise Cutter) charged with the killing of her multimillionaire patient (Ed Quinlan).</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>Matlock gets a second chance at justice when a former client, convicted of murder, kills an inmate in self-defense.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>Ben defends a rebellious young soldier framed in the murder of his sadistic lieutenant.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>While defending Private Hughes (Tony Becker), Matlock uncovers a scandal that could ruin four officers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Curious Caterer Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Goldy Berry's medieval feast at Hyde Castle gets interrupted by a murder. She teams up with Detective Schultz to solve the mystery before the killer strikes again.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260529000000 +0000" stop="20260529020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Justice</title>
    <desc>A law school student and her friends set out to prove her brother is innocent of murder, but the only way to clear his name is to find the real killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260529020000 +0000" stop="20260529030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Newly successful mystery writer J.B. Fletcher gets involved in a murder at a New York publisher's costume bash.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260529030000 +0000" stop="20260529040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>With her first hit mystery, Maine widow Jessica Fletcher makes a promotional trip to New York, and becomes involved in a murder at a publisher's costume bash.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260529040000 +0000" stop="20260529050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica travels to San Francisco for a family wedding and discovers that the groom (Jeff Conaway) faces a murder charge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528000000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scripps National Spelling Bee Semi-Finals</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the 101st Scripps National Spelling Bee.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Danny and Gormley race to find Gus Vanderlip, a committed detective who is dangerously determined to uncover how a rapist he arrested is back on the streets; on the eve of their anniversary, Jamie and Eddie are sent on an undercover assignment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>The Reagans' professional lives converge when an allegation of jury tampering against Erin intertwines with Danny and Baez's homicide case; Frank clashes with his friend and confidant, Archbishop Kearns over the death penalty.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Danny works with British investigator Christopher Granger to pursue an international fugitive; Erin faces pressure from her boss to secure an indictment against an officer; Jamie investigates a sports gambling website accused of scamming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Frank intervenes when tensions rise between Mayor Chase and the fire commissioner of New York City; Erin is blindsided when Henry agrees to testify for the defense in a case she is prosecuting; human remains are discovered in a storage unit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Danny and Baez scrutinize an art gallery suspected of selling counterfeit pieces after a detective investigating the establishment is murdered; Eddie is conflicted when she discovers her former partner crossed the line to get a client help.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Natural Blood Pressure Management</title>
    <desc>Cardiologist Dr. Ernst von Schwarz, M.D. shows how to manage your blood pressure naturally and help protect your heart for life with My Best Heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528073000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Car accident? Free Legal Consultation</title>
    <desc>Legal professionals standing by to answer your questions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2026 Silver Eagle is here &amp; it is a once-in-a-lifetime coin!</title>
    <desc>Join your hosts Kevin Cash &amp; Cory Cady as we discuss the 250th Anniversary of America with the official "America 250" logo on a Silver American Eagle label; we are locking in orders for this iconic release, but coins are limited! Don't miss out!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates when a gang member's remains are found in a burnt-out car; when Sweets learns that one of the boys from the center where he volunteers is a gang member's son, he decides to help.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team devises a plan to use a donated cadaver to draw out Pelant; Sweets returns to work and believes Agent Flynn isn't who he seems.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the murder of a high school principal who was dying of cancer; Brennan and Booth plan their wedding; a virtual profiling system threatens Sweets' job.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team tries to keep the details of an investigation away from Brennan so she will focus on her wedding; Max shows up with a suspicious bag of cash.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Unable to relax on their honeymoon, Booth and Brennan decide to help a local detective solve the murder of a Nazi war criminal; Hodgins and Angela look after Christine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a drug deal gone bad after the body of a college student is found; Detective Hailey Upton temporarily joins the team and finds her investigative methods clash with the Bureau's more buttoned-up environment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team welcomes a new member, Special Agent Tiffany Wallace, as they search for killers who orchestrated a mass shooting at a media company; OA's personal connection with the case threatens to cloud his judgment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team races to stop an active serial killer after three women are found weighted down at the bottom of a lake; Jubal looks into an old closed case after there are multiple similarities to the recent victims.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When the leader of a drug cartel and one of the world's most wanted men is apprehended by the team, the entire FBI headquarters is put at risk when his henchmen unveil a plot to free him; Isobel must make a difficult decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>A shooting at a quinceañera leaves two dead, but the team believes they may not have been the intended targets; Maggie is conflicted as the team decides the best plan of action for using a witness to take down their suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a young girl who was kidnapped from a cabin during a family vacation; Maggie questions her relationship with Nestor when she learns he hasn't been completely honest with her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team must infiltrate a drug trafficking gang after the robbery of a chemical plant leaves two customs agents dead; Nestor offers his help on the case, giving Maggie new insight into his character.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team hunts a killer who is fatally shooting seemingly unrelated targets; new agent Tiffany Wallace experiences tension between her work as an FBI agent and the responsibility she feels to her community as a Black woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260528230000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After a bomb leaves three people dead, the team presses a reluctant informant to gather information from his close friends who are under suspicion; OA and his girlfriend clash over where the informant's rights lie.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>While conducting a profiling course on his birthday, Rossi gets a call from serial killer Tommy Yates, who gives him the location of his latest victim.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team investigates when home invasions involving casualties strike upscale neighborhoods in San Diego.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates when a bizarre hieroglyph is found under a deceased homeless man's armpit; Reid decides to take his mother out of a clinical study early to bring her home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team is called in to investigate when male bodies are discovered that seem to be impossible to identify.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When a BAU member gets in trouble in Mexico, the team enlists the services of the International Response Team for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>When a condemned ax-murderer on death row appeals for his life, the team must investigate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>Horatio finally learns the truth about what happened to his brother, and the repercussions will change his life forever.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>Horatio finds himself with a price on his head when he makes plans to shut down the illegal smuggling operation of one of Miami's fiercest gangs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>A rich couple's daughter dies when the family is trapped on a burning yacht in shark-infested waters.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>When a teenage tourist goes missing, the team investigates the dark side of Miami's nightclub scene.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>Evidence suggests that a confessed killer is actually innocent; Horatio works to collar the actual culprit before the man falls victim to the system.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>Three suburban housewives on a weekend in Miami are the prime suspects when their hotel's handsome pool boy is found murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>When a woman Horatio has been dating is murdered, and he is the last one to see her alive, the team tries to learn who would have the motive and the method to frame him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>A convicted murderer escapes and begins to kill again, and the assailant's original arresting officer, Mac Taylor (Gary Sinise), comes to help Horatio Caine recapture the felon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>Ryan's life is in jeopardy when the team is caught in the midst of a deadly divorce case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a group of video gamers that has started to play the game in real life, killing police officers, stealing evidence, raping women, and robbing a bank.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CSI: Miami</title>
    <desc>Horatio and his team investigate the murder of a suspected drug lord as one member of the group is arrested for buying marijuana.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When Angela and Hodgins wake to find a corpse in their bedroom, they believe Pelant is behind it; against Booth's wishes, Angela and Hodgins start their own investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates when two bodies are found at the same burial plot; Brennan and Booth discuss after-death arrangements; Daisy returns for the first time since the breakup.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When a female roller derby skater is killed and dismembered, Angie goes undercover to help solve the case; Cam tries to learn more about Booth's secretive hospital appointments.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>While in the hospital after being shot at the lab, Brennan struggles with visions of her mother that defy her usual logic; evidence may link Brennan's attacker to the Jeffersonian.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>As the team investigates the death of a seemingly innocent 15-year-old boy, they learn that he was involved in illegal activity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260528230000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When a well-educated but eccentric intern starts working at the Jeffersonian, Brennan tries to be more open-minded about scientific questions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260529000000 +0000" stop="20260529010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the death of a young man whose remains were found at a hazardous waste disposal facility; Cam and Arastoo struggle to keep their relationship secret; Brennan and Booth try to decide where to take their vacation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260529010000 +0000" stop="20260529020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The investigation into the death of a former Marine leads the team to a group obsessed with preparing for the apocalypse; Sweets finds an apartment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260529020000 +0000" stop="20260529030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team investigates when an undercover cop turns up dead with a bag of diamonds inside his body; Brennan struggles to be likable as the subject of a documentary film.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528013000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">On the Buses</title>
    <desc>'70s sitcom about a bus company. Olive is furious when Arthur flirts with a brassy-looking conductress at a busmen's darts match and then fails to come home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528053500 +0000" stop="20260528060500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">On the Buses</title>
    <desc>Enduring '70s British sitcom. The busmen decide to get fit after reading an article which states that drivers have a shorter life expectancy than conductors.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528060500 +0000" stop="20260528063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Shane discovers Danielle's stash of drugs when he searches Zak and Eli's van. Ross struggles with his feelings for Donna, and Lily tells Pearl about Peter's financial troubles.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528063500 +0000" stop="20260528070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Eli gets word that Danielle has been taken to London following her arrest and decides to track her down. Donna is jealous after finding out Ross spent the night with Chas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528070500 +0000" stop="20260528074000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Steve lets himself into the pub to find Michelle enjoying breakfast with her friend JD. Tina exacts revenge on David at the salon and Teresa's poisoning begins to take effect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528074000 +0000" stop="20260528081000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Tina continues to make a scene in front of the shop's clients, much to the horror of David's bosses. Becky offers Michelle advice about Steve, and Molly loses her engagement ring.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528081000 +0000" stop="20260528102500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inspector Morse</title>
    <desc>Morse finds romance in an unlikely setting when he investigates the suspicious death of a woman deacon as Oxford's first-ever female chaplain is about to be appointed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528102500 +0000" stop="20260528112500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series. A death in custody puts Mike's career on the line, and Greengrass and Bernie discover a novel way to supplement their income with taxis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528112500 +0000" stop="20260528123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series set in a Yorkshire village. An old flame of Mike's turns up in Aidensfield as Greengrass loses his heart to an aristocratic lady poacher.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528123000 +0000" stop="20260528143500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Barnaby accompanies Joyce on a spa weekend to Swavely Manor, but when a woman is found dead in the floatation chamber, he quickly finds himself investigating.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528143500 +0000" stop="20260528154000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Marlon hopes to brighten Donna's day by buying her a new dress and accompanying her to the fundraising ball. Katie is annoyed to learn that Nicola is working at Home Farm.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528154000 +0000" stop="20260528161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Tony ruthlessly steps up his business campaign and Kevin falls foul of a hoax call-out. A worried Steve begins to suspect Michelle had an ulterior motive for their reconciliation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528161500 +0000" stop="20260528165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Kevin reports his suspicions to the police, and Tony's menacing behaviour leaves an elderly resident in danger. Meanwhile, Molly despairs of ever finding her engagement ring.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528165000 +0000" stop="20260528175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama. A spate of burglaries results in a young woman being hospitalised, Greengrass and Bertie try modern art, and Nick and Jo come to a big decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528175500 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series. The return of a notorious felon has Blaketon longing for his old job, and Nick, Jo and Katie finally decide to leave Aidensfield.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Vera</title>
    <desc>Detective drama series. DCI Vera Stanhope tries to catch a murderer after two young people are killed in the same way - drowned and surrounded by flowers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lewis</title>
    <desc>When an old friend of Hathaway's takes their own life, Lewis investigates a link between his death and a religious group whose members are being murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528225000 +0000" stop="20260528235000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scott and Bailey</title>
    <desc>Rachel struggles to adjust to living with Sean. Janet discovers a severed head at a crime scene.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260528235000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scott and Bailey</title>
    <desc>A businessman shoves a homeless man, not realising he has killed him. So why is he running away? The story flashes back to the events of last year.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260529005500 +0000" stop="20260529012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">On the Buses</title>
    <desc>Enduring '70s sitcom about a chirpy bus driver and his conductor. Stan has to pull off the road when freezing fog blankets the Home Counties and makes visibility nil.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260529012000 +0000" stop="20260529013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260529013000 +0000" stop="20260529050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260529050000 +0000" stop="20260529053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">On the Buses</title>
    <desc>Classic sitcom about a chirpy bus driver and his conductor pal. The inspector bans all the garage staff from smoking on duty - with dangerous consequences.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260529053500 +0000" stop="20260529060500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">On the Buses</title>
    <desc>Classic sitcom about a chirpy bus driver and his conductor pal. Stan loses his wages at the dog track and is unable to pay housekeeping money to his mum.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260529060500 +0000" stop="20260529070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Marlon hopes to brighten Donna's day by buying her a new dress and accompanying her to the fundraising ball. Katie is annoyed to learn that Nicola is working at Home Farm.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528012000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528055000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Patti Stanger: The Matchmaker</title>
    <desc>US reality series set in the world of dating. Patti Stanger helps a single mother and empty-nester get her groove back.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528055000 +0000" stop="20260528062000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Stained Glass Studio: Home improvement programme. Brian and Sarah build a spacious studio and an inspiring deck area who have filled their bungalow's living space.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528062000 +0000" stop="20260528072000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dress to Impress</title>
    <desc>Connor, otherwise known to many as Mr Wigan, is hoping to be impressed by the style choices of three potential suitors in Manchester.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528072000 +0000" stop="20260528082000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Billie and Greg: The Family Diaries</title>
    <desc>The Shepherds head to Abu Dhabi for their first work trip abroad as a family of five, and it's extra-special as it's Margot's first-ever holiday.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528082000 +0000" stop="20260528092000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Only Way is Essex</title>
    <desc>Shelby may have made amends with Liv, but relations with Clelia are still frosty after she voiced some brutal opinions about Shelby's approach to friendship.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528092000 +0000" stop="20260528101000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Salt Lake City</title>
    <desc>US reality series. Whitney takes over on the final day of the Palm Springs trip as Monica and Lisa's tension reveals itself in head-to-toe drag.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528101000 +0000" stop="20260528110500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Orange County</title>
    <desc>Reality show. Gina and Emily bond with Jenn and learn about the reality of her complicated relationship before a flamingo-inspired boat party.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528110500 +0000" stop="20260528120500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>It's a couples' edition as Graham Norton welcomes three pairs - Corinne and Aaron, Quamelle and Adam, and Len and Nancy - all hoping to keep the spark alive and win 50,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528120500 +0000" stop="20260528130500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts a special celebrity edition of the much-loved game show with Denise Van Outen, Coronation Street star Charlie Condou, and Jo Brand lining up this time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528130500 +0000" stop="20260528141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Floor</title>
    <desc>With 65 contestants left, Rob Brydon hosts another gripping edition of quiz duels as we find out who will outsmart the rest and stay standing on The Floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528141000 +0000" stop="20260528151000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Only Way is Essex</title>
    <desc>Things have been far from friendly between Liv and inseparable duo Courtney and Chloe M for a while now. But on her first night in Marbs, Liv kicked off big time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528151000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Salt Lake City</title>
    <desc>US reality series. Lisa is still hurt by the accusations from Palm Springs as the rumours about Angie's marriage reach a boiling point.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Orange County</title>
    <desc>Reality show. Jenn urges Tamra to apologise and invite Shannon to the CUT closing party, and Heather contemplates the next chapter of her life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts a celebrity special of the game show with Ashley Roberts, Tim Vine, and Mel Giedroyc competing to identify well-known phrases and win thousands for charity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Floor</title>
    <desc>Only 57 contestants remain on The Floor - Rob Brydon hosts as the duels get sharper and the competition starts heating up.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 1% Club Kids Special</title>
    <desc>Lee Mack hosts the quiz show where 100 contestants compete, but in order to win up to 100,000 pounds, they need to answer a question only one per cent of the country can get right.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy series about family life. When Quagmire gains local fame, Peter becomes jealous and attempts a new world record by eating as many nickels as he can.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528203000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter, Quagmire, Joe and Cleveland start a mishmash covers band, only to discover they cannot play. Meg saves the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy series about family life. Cleveland has trouble with his marriage after his wife is caught in bed with Quagmire.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528213000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy about US family life. Bonnie convinces Lois to join her Tae-Jitsu class. Quahog is invaded by New York 'leafers' looking at the pretty autumn leaves.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. Meg, who fancies newscaster Tom Tucker, applies for an internship at the local TV station. Stewie loses his tricycle to a bully.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528223000 +0000" stop="20260528230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated series about a CIA man who is constantly on the alert for terrorism. Roger and Steve set their sights on fame and fortune in New York City.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528230500 +0000" stop="20260528233500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated series about a CIA man. Stan accepts an endorsement from the local chapter of Gay Republicans after missing out on the Republican National Convention.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260528233500 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When Louise, Rudy and Millie keep missing out on clay coins given as prizes at their ancient Greek history class, they plot a scheme of revenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528022500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rising Bills: How Can You Save Money? Tonight</title>
    <desc>With the war in Iran fuelling the cost of living crisis, Paul Brand finds out which household bills could rise and assesses what we can do to keep costs down.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528022500 +0000" stop="20260528032000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Neighbourhood</title>
    <desc>It's the final day in the Neighbourhood as the last two households go head-to-head in the grand finale for a life-changing £250,000.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528032000 +0000" stop="20260528043500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528043500 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Lingo</title>
    <desc>Adil Ray hosts the game of words as Coronation Street stars Lucy Fallon, Julia Goulding, Jack P Shepherd and Colson Smith go head-to-head in a battle to win big money for charity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Morning Britain</title>
    <desc>News, current affairs and lively debate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lorraine</title>
    <desc>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">This Morning</title>
    <desc>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real-life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528123000 +0000" stop="20260528125500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Lunchtime News</title>
    <desc>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528125500 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dickinson's Real Deal</title>
    <desc>The Den descends on Weston Super Mare, where Mark Stevens goes gaga for a gold Guinea and Aiden Pass votes with his wallet for some US election ephemera.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Going for glory this time are South London brothers Kevin and Ian, Bailey and his auntie Jo from Kettering, and siblings Kevin and Karen from Cumbria and Barnsley.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point for Soccer Aid</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts a Soccer Aid for UNICEF special in which three famous faces take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of claiming its £10,000 jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as all that stands between Ben from County Antrim, Reid from Leeds, Susan from Kent, Jonny from Leicester and thousands of pounds is one of the Chasers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528173000 +0000" stop="20260528183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Evening News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528183000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Over the Counter: Our Hidden Drug Addiction? Tonight</title>
    <desc>Sam Holder examines how over-the-counter drugs present significant dangers of becoming habit-forming and even addictive if not used correctly.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Kammy is carted off in a police car. Laurel fights her confusing attraction.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528193000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Ryan's memory is jolted when Danielle publicly accuses Todd, Idris makes a move on Leanne, Daniel owns up to Ken, and Eva approves of Hope's positive effect on Will.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Taste for Murder</title>
    <desc>Joe discovers a hand found in a dead shark that has links to the Mafia as he struggles to come to terms to Angelica's decision about her future. Lara uncovers a shocking clue.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News at Ten</title>
    <desc>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528213000 +0000" stop="20260528214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528214500 +0000" stop="20260528235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Die Hard 4.0</title>
    <desc>Action thriller film sequel starring Bruce Willis and Justin Long, 2007. John McClane and a young hacker join forces to take down a master cyber terrorist in Washington, D.C.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260528235500 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shop on TV</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260529020000 +0000" stop="20260529025000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Soccer Aid: More Than Just a Game</title>
    <desc>Brand-new documentary that looks back at the legacy of Soccer Aid for UNICEF as the match celebrates a milestone 20 years.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260529025000 +0000" stop="20260529031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Assembly</title>
    <desc>Aitch faces the grilling of a lifetime from autistic and learning-disabled interviewers. From his lyrics to his bank balance, nothing is off the table.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts the exciting and iconic gameshow as another of his brave contestants steps up to take on the infamous Banker for a chance at a life-changing cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard returns to pit four players against a mesmerising machine. There are mystery prizes and a jaw-dropping jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard returns to pit four players against a mesmerising machine. There are mystery prizes and a jaw-dropping jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard returns to pit four players against a mesmerising machine. There are mystery prizes and a jaw-dropping jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>The game of words hosted by Adil Ray - trying to Lingo all the way this time are best friends Kiran and Sarah, partners Dan and Jono, and mother and daughter Kelly and Georgia.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>A team of five friends play to take home 125,000 pounds by answering a series of Top 10 list questions in the quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beat the Chasers</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as the Sensational Six - The Sinnerman, The Beast, The Governess, The Menace, The Vixen and The Dark Destroyer - come together to take on more contestants.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the quiz where contestants take on the Riddlemaster in a bid to solve his riddles - how will Faisal and Daniel, Sara and Kaitlin, and Vicki and Richard cope.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts another episode of the exciting and iconic gameshow as a brave contestant takes on the infamous Banker for a chance at winning a life-changing cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>The game of words hosted by Adil Ray - crossing words against the reigning Lingo champions this time are mother and daughter Valerie and Sarah and siblings Michael and Shanice.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced game of words hosted by Adil Ray - playing this time are the reigning Lingo champions alongside Daniella and Charlotte from London and Nathan and Aarati from Kent.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>The game of words hosted by Adil Ray - trying to Lingo all the way this time are brother and sister Penny and Steve, sisters Allandah and Miah, and couple Alison and Mick.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ant and Dec's Limitless Win</title>
    <desc>Firefighting duo Harry and Ben try to cash out with some truly life-changing money before husband-and-wife team Ciaran and Louise try to hold their nerve and avoid crashing out.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard returns to pit four players against a mesmerising machine. There are mystery prizes and a jaw-dropping jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard returns to pit four players against a mesmerising machine. There are mystery prizes and a jaw-dropping jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528230000 +0000" stop="20260528235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard returns to pit four players against a mesmerising machine. There are mystery prizes and a jaw-dropping jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260528235500 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>A team of five friends play to take home 125,000 pounds by answering a series of Top 10 list questions in the quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260529005000 +0000" stop="20260529010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260529010000 +0000" stop="20260529060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260529060000 +0000" stop="20260529080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260529080000 +0000" stop="20260529090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts another episode of the exciting and iconic gameshow as a brave contestant takes on the infamous Banker for a chance at winning a life-changing cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260529090000 +0000" stop="20260529100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard returns to pit four players against a mesmerising machine. There are mystery prizes and a jaw-dropping jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260529100000 +0000" stop="20260529110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard returns to pit four players against a mesmerising machine. There are mystery prizes and a jaw-dropping jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260529110000 +0000" stop="20260529120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard returns to pit four players against a mesmerising machine. There are mystery prizes and a jaw-dropping jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528012000 +0000" stop="20260528015000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auto Mundial</title>
    <desc>The latest news and reviews from the world of cars.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528015000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528023000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorsport Mundial</title>
    <desc>This programme brings you up to date with the latest action from the world of motorsport and features race coverage, insights, and behind-the-scenes footage from the best series.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. Thomas uncovers a multi-million-dollar drugs racket when TC is arrested for smuggling a fellow Vietnam veteran into Hawaii.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528071000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. A woman enlists the investigator's help to find her missing father, but Thomas soon finds that he is not alone in his quest.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528071000 +0000" stop="20260528081500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Saint</title>
    <desc>Suave freelance troubleshooter Simon Templar embarks on another case involving action and intrigue. The Saint agrees to help a girl find her missing brother.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528081500 +0000" stop="20260528092000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boon</title>
    <desc>Classic drama. An attractive blonde biker comes to work for Texas Rangers, but she only has eyes for the man who intends to repossess her father's stately home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528092000 +0000" stop="20260528103500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sweeney</title>
    <desc>Tough 1970s police drama series. Carter winds up behind bars when he attempts to find the proceeds of a jewellery robbery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528103500 +0000" stop="20260528114000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BattleBots</title>
    <desc>The Bull, the Dragon and the Frog: US robot combat series. Beta tries to hammer Kraken into submission, and the giant wheels of Huge go up against Blip in a tumultuous Main Event.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528114000 +0000" stop="20260528124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. The owner of a stud farm hires the investigator to find out who is behind threats that have been made to her expensive racehorse.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528124000 +0000" stop="20260528134500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. Thomas is instructed to pay a ransom demand without pursuing a case, but he is convinced into hunting the would-be blackmailer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528134500 +0000" stop="20260528145000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Saint</title>
    <desc>Troubleshooter Simon Templar embarks on another case. Four company directors die from heart attacks - or is it murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528145000 +0000" stop="20260528155000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boon</title>
    <desc>Classic drama. Harry becomes involved with his ex-wife Alison when she visits the Coaching Inn and loses money intended to settle her new boyfriend's debts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528155000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sweeney</title>
    <desc>Tough 1970s police drama series. Regan and Carter become involved in a plot to stop a foreign head of state gaining access to a pill that can fight heart disease.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Minder</title>
    <desc>Comedy-drama series. When Arthur falls out with Dave when a member of their boyhood gang reappears, tries setting up a rival club to the Winchester.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Pickers</title>
    <desc>US documentary series following a pair of travelling salvage experts. Mike and Frank turn on the charm as they try to buy a collection of rare motorbike parts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Junk and Disorderly</title>
    <desc>Henry Cole, Allen Millyard and Guy Willison pick up a pile of trinkets from a shed in Shrewsbury before travelling to an auction in Tewkesbury and their second Kempton autojumble.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Under Siege 2: Dark Territory</title>
    <desc>Action thriller film sequel starring Steven Seagal and Katherine Heigl, 1995. Ex-Navy SEAL Casey Ryback re-enters action when a train he is on is hijacked by nefarious mercenaries.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528210500 +0000" stop="20260528220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Under Siege 2: Dark Territory</title>
    <desc>Action thriller film sequel starring Steven Seagal and Katherine Heigl, 1995. Ex-Navy SEAL Casey Ryback re-enters action when a train he is on is hijacked by nefarious mercenaries.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528220500 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beat the Chasers</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as more contestants from across the UK take on the Sinnerman, the Beast, the Super Nerd, the Menace, the Vixen and the Dark Destroyer while hoping to win big.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260528230000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Berlin Station</title>
    <desc>The Station enlists Rafael Torres to track down missing comrade Daniel Miller's last known location, leading him to hostile territory. Kirsch visits an old friend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260529000000 +0000" stop="20260529005500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hell's Kitchen</title>
    <desc>US cooking competition. The chefs learn that influence can make or break their future when they prepare to impress Gordon's social media followers in a challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260529005500 +0000" stop="20260529014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Minder</title>
    <desc>Comedy-drama series. Shifty Uncle Arthur's search for a new motor ends in his arrest, but even DS Morley thinks he is innocent of the charge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Kelly sneaks her children back into Abby Lee Dance Company; Brooke's return threatens Payton's position on the team; Maddie helps to make a girl's dream come true.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women: LA</title>
    <desc>The women try to pick up the pieces of their friendship after a nasty brawl; Christy, Briana and Lila bring the girls together for a race, and wind up insulting Terra and Tonya; Lila throws a cocktail party to make peace.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women: LA</title>
    <desc>Terra treats the gang to a weekend on Catalina Island; the ladies go zip lining and later reward themselves with a fancy dinner in town; Lila lashes out at each of the girls.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Abby receives the remains of her beloved dog, Broadway Baby; Kelly secretly meets with the mothers; Maddie's star continues to fall, while Nia's is on the rise.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Kelly sneaks her children back into Abby Lee Dance Company; Brooke's return threatens Payton's position on the team; Maddie helps to make a girl's dream come true.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women: LA</title>
    <desc>The women try to pick up the pieces of their friendship after a nasty brawl; Christy, Briana and Lila bring the girls together for a race, and wind up insulting Terra and Tonya; Lila throws a cocktail party to make peace.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women: LA</title>
    <desc>Terra treats the gang to a weekend on Catalina Island; the ladies go zip lining and later reward themselves with a fancy dinner in town; Lila lashes out at each of the girls.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cindy Crawford talks about the latest breakthroughs in skincare</title>
    <desc>Join Cindy Crawford as she talks to real customers about the breakthrough skincare system that keeps them looking their best. Take a trip to the stunning French countryside to see the rare French melon that defies the aging process.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pain Relief Revealed</title>
    <desc>Discover the hidden story of OmegaXL with John Walsh. He dives deep into the groundbreaking supplement that promises hope and relief for millions battling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A father who is also a doctor tests the staff's patience; third-time parents hope to deliver a girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>An unplanned pregnancy forces a young father to learn how to be supportive; a mother endures a painful delivery without the help of an epidural.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>Mothers must decide how they would like to manage labor pains.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A loving couple must face a caesarian section; two teenagers cram for the test of parenthood; a first time mother tries to joke her way through labor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>Complications in labor and delivery; a woman who is pregnant with twins from two different fathers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A military family prepares for delivery; a woman with three boys at home hopes her baby is a girl; a newlywed couple is expecting their first child.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A woman forgets her birth plan at home; a mother of four boys hopes her next child is a girl; a surrogate mother gives birth.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>Two sportscasters make their first attempt at parenthood; a couple prepares for twins; a first-time mother experiences fear.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>In the first week of the competition, 12 children contend with topics including math and memory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>Eleven children return for week two of the competition, battling it out in the rounds of spelling and geography.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>The remaining 10 academic warriors compete in this week's rounds of U.S. history and logic to advance toward the prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>The remaining nine competitors must conquer this week's challenging topics of current events and the human body.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260528230000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>In week five of the competition, the eight remaining contestants prepare to do battle in the categories of literature &amp; fine arts and vocabulary.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop: On the Road</title>
    <desc>The Repair Shop experts are off on a road trip across the UK fixing historical treasures and precious objects that cannot be brought to the barn.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Game of Wool: Britain's Best Knitter</title>
    <desc>Ten amateur knitters vie for UK's first TV knitting champion title; Olympic diver Tom Daley hosts as judges Di Gilpin and Shelia Greenwell eliminate contestants weekly based on creativity and technique.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop: On the Road</title>
    <desc>The Repair Shop experts are off on a road trip across the UK fixing historical treasures and precious objects that cannot be brought to the barn.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>The team at the barn roll up their sleeves and tackle the damage on a 250-year-old antique anatomy book, a fragile diamond engagement ring, and a tired hat that belonged to a dedicated railway man.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Travelling Auctioneers</title>
    <desc>Will Kirk and Christina Trevanion take their mobile auction house on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Game of Wool: Britain's Best Knitter</title>
    <desc>Ten amateur knitters vie for UK's first TV knitting champion title; Olympic diver Tom Daley hosts as judges Di Gilpin and Shelia Greenwell eliminate contestants weekly based on creativity and technique.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes Makes It Right</title>
    <desc>Charmaine and Zephie discover their century home has a mysterious third floor sealed off by the previous homeowners decades ago.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">History by the Numbers</title>
    <desc>The annual worth of the world's black market economy is 2.2 trillion dollars; we reveal the inside scoop on those pulling the strings, five of the most notorious criminal bosses of the last century, and their notoriety has no bounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Below Zero Canada</title>
    <desc>Becky and Dene make upgrades to their new homestead; Kim and Pierre look to the land for a source of emergency food; Bentley tries his hand at some early season trapping; Jon takes to the sea in his on-going quest to pad his winter larder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brojects: Road House</title>
    <desc>Brothers Andrew and Kevin are stoked to finally be in British Columbia, the final stop on their cross-Canada journey.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528133000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Todd Talbot Builds: The Passive House Project</title>
    <desc>Kick off construction with Todd and his wife, Rebecca, who face challenges on Day 1 when a windstorm blocks the road. See what architect Monty Wood and designer Ami McKay have in store for this high-tech A-frame as they begin laying the foundation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blown Away</title>
    <desc>Planets collide and aliens give birth, as the artists conquer the final frontier, crafting dynamic sculptures that capture the majesty of outer space.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528143000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blown Away</title>
    <desc>In an emotional challenge, the three remaining glassblowers create pieces that represent their greatest fears and try out some risky techniques.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Drink Masters</title>
    <desc>In teams of three, the contestants develop drinks from gin, bourbon, and rum for a 1920s-themed challenge; guests at a cocktail party decide their fate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes Makes It Right</title>
    <desc>Charmaine and Zephie discover their century home has a mysterious third floor sealed off by the previous homeowners decades ago.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes Makes It Right</title>
    <desc>Charmaine and Zephie discover their century home has a mysterious third floor sealed off by the previous homeowners decades ago.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop: On the Road</title>
    <desc>The Repair Shop experts are off on a road trip across the UK fixing historical treasures and precious objects that cannot be brought to the barn.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260528230000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260529000000 +0000" stop="20260529010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great British Sewing Bee</title>
    <desc>The collection features baby doll dresses, asymmetrical overalls and Pop Art custom designs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528013000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>After overhearing Fry and the gang bickering over the superiority of the sexes, an annoyed alien tries to teach them a lesson by changing their sexual characteristics.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>A game show where taxi riders become instant contestants in a trivia game on wheels.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528023000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Passengers hail a taxi only to discover they're instant contestants in a trivia game show on wheels.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fear Factor USA</title>
    <desc>Contestants dine on horse rectum, enduring both the taste and stench.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>When Marge opens a franchise sandwich shop, the running of the business proves challenging, especially when a competitor opens another location across the street.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528043000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>After overhearing Fry and the gang bickering over the superiority of the sexes, an annoyed alien tries to teach them a lesson by changing their sexual characteristics.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Marvel</title>
    <desc>In the decades preceding the current Marvel Cinematic Universe, Marvel struggled through box office flops like "Howard the Duck," corporate skulduggery, and a bankruptcy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Passengers hail a taxi only to discover they're instant contestants in a trivia game show on wheels.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528063000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>A game show where taxi riders become instant contestants in a trivia game on wheels.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>A baby boy is scared of a vacuum cleaner; a crew drops a house from a crane; a bear settles in; mirrors fall.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528073000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>A bear stealing clothes; a stingray with an attitude; an elephant that sprays a woman; a bat that hides in an umbrella.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Featuring caught-on-camera videos that highlight the world of animals.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Caught-on-camera videos that highlight the outrageous and wacky world of animals, hosted by comic Andy Woodhull.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fear Factor USA</title>
    <desc>Contestants dine on horse rectum, enduring both the taste and stench.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>There's no sound, but there sure are plenty of laughs. This crazy Quebec-based troupe uses the city as its stage, and its inhabitants, or victims, as characters! People are caught in a twisted yet funny web of comedic deception. This updated "Candid Camera" is a tad more risque and a little kookier with its practical jokes. The little snippets last only a few minutes, and some look more painful th</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Featuring a jealous statue, a disappearing fence post, a peeing fish among others.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comedians Lori Ferguson-Ford, Diana Love, Larke Miller and Dawn Whitewill perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>John Hastings shares his travels as a telemarketer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>There's no sound, but there sure are plenty of laughs. This crazy Quebec-based troupe uses the city as its stage, and its inhabitants, or victims, as characters! People are caught in a twisted yet funny web of comedic deception. This updated "Candid Camera" is a tad more risque and a little kookier with its practical jokes. The little snippets last only a few minutes, and some look more painful th</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528133000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Featuring a jealous statue, a disappearing fence post, a peeing fish among others.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comedians Lori Ferguson-Ford, Diana Love, Larke Miller and Dawn Whitewill perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>John Hastings shares his travels as a telemarketer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>There's no sound, but there sure are plenty of laughs. This crazy Quebec-based troupe uses the city as its stage, and its inhabitants, or victims, as characters! People are caught in a twisted yet funny web of comedic deception. This updated "Candid Camera" is a tad more risque and a little kookier with its practical jokes. The little snippets last only a few minutes, and some look more painful th</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528163000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Featuring a jealous statue, a disappearing fence post, a peeing fish among others.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260528173000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unassuming people enter a taxi cab as simple passengers taking a normal ride, only to be shocked when they discover that they're instant contestants; passengers win money by answering trivia questions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528013000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Andy tries to jumpstart his comeback; after Robert drunkenly shuts down a local branch, Jim and Dwight join forces in hope of outsmarting a salesman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>A former boss helps Andy go undercover and stage a coup; a new opportunity arises for Robert.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528023000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Two new, young employees throw Dwight and Jim off balance; Andy returns from leadership training with a desire for revenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>A toast at Roy's wedding leads to Pam and Jim searching their relationships for buried secrets; Dwight reacts to Nellie's mandatory charity initiative.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528033000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>As Andy flaunts a discovery he made about his ancestry, Darryl struggles in his new role; Dwight teaches a language to Erin, who wants to impress her boyfriend's educated family; Jim reveals a secret.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo welcome "The Challenge" stars CT Tamburello and Johnny Bananas to celebrate BFF Overachievers; in Still Eating It?, they check out gross foods.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528043000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo talk about the meaning of the phrase "Turd on Top"; why snakes are just "Slithering Nightmares"; the condition known as "Loose Ducts.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Motoring with "Weekend Bikers"; trying to relax out back in "Decks of Doom"; watching for danger from above in "Falling Skies.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528053000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood hit the slopes in Snow Wheelin', challenge dads in No Longer Got It and get drenched by Waves of Sadness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Jenni JWoww Farley sees some nice drunks, champagne dangers and finds out who's too drunk.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528063000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood take some big falls with folks who are gravity-proof, celebrate romance with some weird love languages and speed towards disaster in too much momentum.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood assess the damage caused by some "Homewreckers," find out who is definitely high in "Clearly Cooked" and take a risky stroll with "Surprise Sidewalk Assaults.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528073000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo go logging with "Crappy Jacks," keep their cool around "Mildfires," and marvel at some people's "Fascinating Fingers.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Steve Wilkos; "Surprise T..."; "Stevecurity"; "Highest Rated Category Ever.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Bite-sized badasses; partying with moms gone wild; witnessing a few grand exits.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo talk about gym weirdos who make one ask "What's He Training For?"; people who've reverted to toddlerhood and are "Goin' Bottomless"; going to Japan.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Parking lot pandemonium; learning when to be more afraid; getting gross with babies picking doo-doo power.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo salute the troops in "Training Basics," discover a new sport called "Drunkour" and witness the majesty of "Hobo Wizards.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo deliver the pain in "Brown Down," see what not to do with some "Out of Pocket Parents," and feel the wet slap of "Reverse Bellyflops.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and guest host Lexi Rivera hit the moving stairs hard with "Escalated Pain"; meeting some killer kids that may be "Parent Assassins"; can't cross the road without getting "Crossed Wrecked.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo get hurt in the most picturesque places, fit in a little sleep at the gym and run from danger.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Lolo Wood joins Rob and Sterling where they learn about the zodiac and watch people rethink their choices.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528123000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and guest host Lolo Wood get wet and wild with water slider colliders, learn when to be quiet with gab smacked, and get bucked in horseback drops.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Chanel welcome rap superstar Tyga as they watch some people "Get a Taste" and witness what could go wrong when people "Make It Haute.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528133000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo try their luck in "Lotto Legends," get hurt at home in "Danger Rooms," and watch seniors get sauced in "Grandpa's Drunk Again.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo see who's off base in "Missin' Marks," see who's eating at "Trash Buffets," and explore "The Great Indoors.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Help I Sexted My Boss</title>
    <desc>William Hanson and Jordan North take on the hilarious challenges of life. Expect laugh-out-loud stories, brutally honest moments, and a friendship that's as unlikely as it is unfiltered.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528014500 +0000" stop="20260528023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master</title>
    <desc>Some of the remaining artists botch their portrait tattoos when they screw up important features, leaving their human canvasses with bad art.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528023500 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Cribs</title>
    <desc>MTV rings the bell on boxing superstar Tyson Fury. The gloves are off and this Morecambe mansion wins with a knockout. The VIP rope is unhooked and we scoot around Wes Nelson's crib.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528054500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>Shelby is preparing for the birth of her baby with her ex, who already has a baby with his girlfriend. Shelby is confident she can raise her baby on her own but the future looks uncertain.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528054500 +0000" stop="20260528063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>Amber worries she's developed a new addiction to food. Farrah decides to open a frozen yogurt shop, while Tyler's concerned that Catelynn is falling back into bad habits.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528063500 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528073000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Geek Australia</title>
    <desc>The last elimination of the competition decides who will make it to the grand finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bar Rescue</title>
    <desc>Jon Taffer heads to Kenosha, Wisconsin to rescue a long-standing bar whose owner has failed to update the business over the past 30 years.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: True Love</title>
    <desc>After a string of bad luck with women, Jeff believes he has finally found his dream girl in Megan. However, Megan is starting to sound off Catfish alarms.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: True Love</title>
    <desc>Colleen met Tony online and fell in love. Despite never meeting, Tony proposed over the phone and Colleen accepted! Nev and Max help her face reality to reveal the man she's engaged to.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: True Love</title>
    <desc>Alexis and Jaymes have been there for each other for 5 years. When Nev and Kamie uncover Jaymes may have a guy on the side, it leaves Alexis wondering who she's really fallen in love with.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: True Love</title>
    <desc>When Zak met Garret online he fell hard, but curious disappearances have Zak worried about who he really fell in love with. Will Nev and Max find Garret before he vanishes for good.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528153000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528163000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Geek Australia</title>
    <desc>After the most dramatic challenge of the competition, one couple will become the winners.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghosted: Love Gone Missing</title>
    <desc>Rachel and Travis help an aspiring New York stand-up track down the professed love of his life, but she may have had a good reason for ghosting him after six months.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bar Rescue</title>
    <desc>A historic bar in Sheboygan, Wisconsin faces closure because of an owner with a bad attitude whose staff is afraid to speak out against him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>The team heads to Fenway Park in Boston and also hit up a famous bar.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Geordie Shore: From The Beginning</title>
    <desc>It's Jay's birthday and Vicky's playing the dutiful 'girlfriend', Holly's boyfriend visits, Charlotte loses the battle to fight off Gaz and the house is rocked by a shock departure.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528012000 +0000" stop="20260528022500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Jeremy, who's 71, arrives at St George's in an air ambulance after crashing his bicycle at speed, and café worker Amy comes to the rescue of complete stranger James.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528022500 +0000" stop="20260528025500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Perfect Pitch</title>
    <desc>The final stop in North Yorkshire is The Dalesbridge campsite. The experience is dampened by bad weather, but the stunning scenery and live music keep the critics in good spirits.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528025500 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528075500 +0000" stop="20260528085500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Find It, Fix It, Flog It</title>
    <desc>In Whitby and Shipley in Yorkshire, Henry Cole builds a steampunk lamp from a copper pipe, while Simon O'Brien brings a dated Welsh dresser right up to date.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528085500 +0000" stop="20260528095500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Find It, Fix It, Flog It</title>
    <desc>The boys visit a military vehicle enthusiast. Henry Cole mirror polishes a decommissioned missile and Simon O'Brien repurposes a tank turret.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528095500 +0000" stop="20260528102500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>James and Jessica kick off the week at the Ship Inn in Dymchurch, Kent. Some of their guests lap up the luxury, but others uncover a bit of bother with their bedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528102500 +0000" stop="20260528105500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Mother and daughter Amanda and Becci host at Thompson Hall Retreat in Norfolk. Their guests are impressed by the stylish shepherd huts, but the DIY breakfast isn't to everyone's taste.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528105500 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The third visit is to The White House in Swansea, owned by Lloyd and Marta, where guests James and Jessica have a toilet encounter they'll never forget..</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The final visit is to Jacobs Plough in Bicester, Oxfordshire, run by manager Duncan and bar supervisor Ryan, who like to mix business with banter. But Lloyd and Marta pick the place apart.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528123500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time. After dramatic discoveries and frank exchanges, the payments are revealed and the winner is announced.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528123500 +0000" stop="20260528130500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Welfare team leader Jennie honours her city's fishing heritage with her under-the-sea theme, on a lively night of twerking and seal impressions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528130500 +0000" stop="20260528133500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Wrestling promoter James puts on a show with spicy Mexican food and a full-blown wrestling match with wrestling outfits for his guests.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528133500 +0000" stop="20260528141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Vegetarian Katrena plans a glamorous cruise ship theme. Will her unusual strawberry soup starter and towel-folding entertainment sink or swim.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528141000 +0000" stop="20260528144000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Super-confident mum-of-three Natalie's night is full of faux pas, about everything from Botox to cougars.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528144000 +0000" stop="20260528151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Retirement community manager George has talked the talk all week, and now expectations are high for his egg drop soup and flambéed crêpes Suzette.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528151500 +0000" stop="20260528155000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>A loo with a view provides cause for concern, as former art dealers Robin and Brenda Spence kick off the competition at Causilgey Manor in Truro, Cornwall.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528155000 +0000" stop="20260528162000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Retired politician Martin Perry and housekeeper Tracey Barrett like to keep things traditional at Elmfield B&amp;B in Devon. But their guests are unimpressed by the ageing heirlooms.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528162000 +0000" stop="20260528165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Leoni Wilton and Tish Broughton treat their rivals to chocolate-themed rooms and chocolate breakfasts, at The Chocolate Box in Bournemouth. But the DIY drinks don't go down well.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528165000 +0000" stop="20260528172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The final visit is to The Buckle Seaford in East Sussex, where B&amp;B newbies Julie and Jason Martin push the boat out with seaside luxe. And the guests are blown away by the bedrooms.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528172000 +0000" stop="20260528175000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time. There are accusations and awkward moments as the payments are revealed and the winner is announced.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528175000 +0000" stop="20260528185500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Location, Location, Location</title>
    <desc>In the Peak District, Kirstie Allsopp helps Anne and her son Vinnie find a new home, while Phil Spencer searches for a dream property for Andrea and James.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528185500 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PopMaster TV: Grand Final</title>
    <desc>Ken Bruce puts the finalists to the ultimate pop trivia test in the Grand Final. Who will reign supreme and be crowned PopMaster TV champion.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Great British Train Journeys from Above</title>
    <desc>From Whitby to Pickering, aerial views of the stunning North Yorkshire Moors Railway reveal the Stephenson steam revolution's profound impact.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Brooke, who's 12, has gone into respiratory arrest after having a severe asthma attack. Howard, who's 76, has burns from trying to put out an explosion in his shed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 must band together after a devastating fire catches them off guard; Vasquez continues his quest for answers; Violet and Novak face an unexpected roadblock in the new training protocol.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight teams up with an unlikely ally to take a killer off the streets while fighting to bring his Intelligence unit back together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528033400 +0000" stop="20260528043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Comic Colin Jost; actress Sienna Miller; AZ and Nas perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528043700 +0000" stop="20260528053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actress Charlize Theron; actor Jorma Taccone.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528053700 +0000" stop="20260528060700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528060700 +0000" stop="20260528063700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528063700 +0000" stop="20260528070700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Interviews with international music sensation Laufey, actress Selma Blair, and Dr. Sandra Lee ("Dr. Pimple Popper").</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528070700 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "Diamonds"; Rita Wilson; Sue Bird; Cat Cora; The Curb Free Foundation; Claire Rosinkranz performs; ice cream inspired by India.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York @ 6AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Water Safety Month with Bode and Morgan Miller; Robert De Niro and Jane Rosenthal on the Tribeca Festival 25th Anniversary; Today's Consumer: Underrated destinations; Today Food: Summer grilling with Mark Anderson and Ryan Fey.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>On the Money: AI &amp; Finances with Ted Jenkin. Take It Off Today: Minnesota man loses over 200 pounds through yoga and starts a food truck business; catching up with Fred Armisen; author David Sedaris; simple tricks to elevate your home for summer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Halle Berry Joins the chat; actor RuPaul and the Queens of "Stop! That! Train!.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528153000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Live</title>
    <desc>Celebrity interviews and discussing recipes, beauty, fashion and current events pertinent to the tri-state region.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>After a nurse and mother-of-three is murdered inside her Illinois home, investigators uncover security camera footage that could be key to solving the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "Day Late and a Buck Short"; Brendan Fraser; David Tennant; Marin Alsop; "Whole Lotta Woman" with Marin Alsop; Emily Kaufman, the Travel Mom; first lady of Iceland.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528203000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>A newly single woman wants help uncovering the identity of her new love, but she may have secrets of her own.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>A man receives an anonymous text warning him that his online love is not who she says she is, and he seeks help from Nev and Max.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) enrolls in an acting class taught by an accomplished actress (guest star Janet Hubert) who takes a strong liking to him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528033000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie struggles to keep the hotel together after rap trio Westside Connection hosts a raging house party.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie is (Jamie Foxx) excited when he lands a record deal, until he reads the fine print in his contract.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528043000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie and Braxton (Jamie Foxx, Christopher B. Duncan) end up hostages in a bank robbery; Jamie tries to ward off Fancy's (Garcelle Beauvais) new beau (Kristoff St. John).</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>Will looks forward to seeing his mother, until she announces plans to bring him back home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528053000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>Will and Carlton convince Geoffrey that he has won a multimillion-dollar lottery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>The house is robbed after Philip hires an ex-convict handyman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528063000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>As Vivian's delivery date approaches, the family fantasizes about what the baby will mean to each of them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon scheme to find a way to protect Dee from the con artist she is falling in love with.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528073000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn's (Shawn Wayans) landlady (Adrienne Barbeau) makes a pass at him and Shawn must decide how to deal with the unwanted attention.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) decides acting is in his future and wants to get out of the newsstand business. Los Angeles Clippers' Brent Barry guest stars.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>After breaking his leg in a fall at the newsstand, Marlon (Marlon Wayans) decides to sue Shawn (Shawn Wayans) for his injuries.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon let Grandma live with them, then find she's overbearing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>It's girl troubles for Shawn (Shawn Wayans) when his girlfriend decides Marlon (Marlon Wayans) is more her type.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>RSVP are off to New York's biggest Italian festival, San Gennaro to help find Vinny love; Ang wants to be a pop star; Nicole gets more information about her birth mom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>The guys head to Connecticut for Vinny's first out-of-state comedy show; Deena runs for pizza; Sammi talks to Ronnie.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>The group starts in Las Vegas, then heads back to the East Coast after partying; they celebrate milestones in Atlantic City, N.J., before settling in for an extended summer at the Shore.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Vinny thinks he has a fever; the girls take a PJ to see Pauly spin; the squad heads down south for a farming good time!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Angelina talks to ghosts; Mike puts everyone to work; the fam learns the true meaning of DTF.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>After an honest day of work on the farm; the gang goes farm to table. Can the roomies finally share a peaceful meal?</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Jordan ends a real-life relationship for a spark on Tinder; Nev and his wife Laura get on the case and uncover dark truths.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Danny wants to build a family with his online love in spite of her violent past, but Nev and Max discover possible ties to a former catfish.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Nev and co-host Slick Woods help 19-year-old Aubri search for her Snapchat love, Brian; Brian says he lives at Aubri's college but makes several excuses not to meet; with little to go on, Nev and Slick hit the campus in search of answers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528013000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Kyle, Lance Woods, Treasure Wilson, and BenDaDonnn take a look back at all the season's highlights, from the best trash talking to the worst performances, and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Loe Shimmy joins Big Bank, DJ Scream, and Baby Jade to discuss building relationships with some of the best in sports and music, how it feels to be on the charts, who he defines as family, and shares what keeps him hungry and motivated in life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Hope Flood; Mike Yard; Nick Lewis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528033000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Alonzo Jones (Hamburger); Chris Tucker; Bernie Mac; Kevin Anthony.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Loe Shimmy joins Big Bank, DJ Scream, and Baby Jade to discuss building relationships with some of the best in sports and music, how it feels to be on the charts, who he defines as family, and shares what keeps him hungry and motivated in life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Hope Flood; Mike Yard; Nick Lewis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528063000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Alonzo Jones (Hamburger); Chris Tucker; Bernie Mac; Kevin Anthony.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Big Oomp joins Big Bank, DJ Scream and Baby Jade to discuss how he got into the music business, the importance of Atlanta record stores in breaking artists, and shares how he's been able to have such a long career.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of A$AP Ferg</title>
    <desc>Paying tribute to A$AP Ferg with his latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Anderson .Paak</title>
    <desc>Paying tribute to Anderson .Paak with his latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Don Toliver</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Don Toliver with his latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Internationally Known</title>
    <desc>Highlighting emerging artists and the top hits in Africa, Latin America, the U.K., and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528163000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Kyle, Lance Woods, Treasure Wilson, and BenDaDonnn take a look back at all the season's highlights, from the best trash talking to the worst performances, and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Overtime Hustle</title>
    <desc>In the season premiere, Speedy heads to Los Angeles to meet up with gymnast Jordan Chiles for a crash course in gymnastics and a final performance in front of the judges.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528173000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A mix of the best hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos, from the hottest new releases to favorite throwbacks.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>Lynae Vanee breaks down top headlines from her distinct perspective and lived experience.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>Lynae Vanee breaks down top headlines from her distinct perspective and lived experience.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Baller Alert Show</title>
    <desc>Hosts Ferrari Simmons and You Know BT are joined by celebrity guests for the latest in pop culture news, hot gossip, and fresh takes in this extension of the mega-popular entertainment brand Baller Alert.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Featuring the short films "Sunflower" and "Thank (U).".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528013000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 7 PM</title>
    <desc>The latest in local breaking news, weather reports and feature stories covering the vast Southern California region.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528023000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Interviews with international music sensation Laufey, actress Selma Blair, and Dr. Sandra Lee ("Dr. Pimple Popper").</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brilliant Minds</title>
    <desc>A party girl on the run is rushed to the hospital where the doctors work to figure out exactly what she's running from; when Wolf doesn't show up for his shift, Carol -- already worried about his mental health -- goes on a mission to find him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 must band together after a devastating fire catches them off guard; Vasquez continues his quest for answers; Violet and Novak face an unexpected roadblock in the new training protocol.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight teams up with an unlikely ally to take a killer off the streets while fighting to bring his Intelligence unit back together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528063400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528063400 +0000" stop="20260528073700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Comic Colin Jost; actress Sienna Miller; AZ and Nas perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528073700 +0000" stop="20260528083700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actress Charlize Theron; actor Jorma Taccone.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528083700 +0000" stop="20260528090700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528090700 +0000" stop="20260528093700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528093700 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "Diamonds"; Rita Wilson; Sue Bird; Cat Cora; The Curb Free Foundation; Claire Rosinkranz performs; ice cream inspired by India.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 4AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 4:30AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 5AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 6AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Water Safety Month with Bode and Morgan Miller; Robert De Niro and Jane Rosenthal on the Tribeca Festival 25th Anniversary; Today's Consumer: Underrated destinations; Today Food: Summer grilling with Mark Anderson and Ryan Fey.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>On the Money: AI &amp; Finances with Ted Jenkin. Take It Off Today: Minnesota man loses over 200 pounds through yoga and starts a food truck business; catching up with Fred Armisen; author David Sedaris; simple tricks to elevate your home for summer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Halle Berry Joins the chat; actor RuPaul and the Queens of "Stop! That! Train!.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11am</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528183000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">California Live</title>
    <desc>A daily lifestyle show that takes a ride through all of California, discovering many of the hidden treasures the state and its people have to offer including beauty, glamour, fitness, food, health, and tech.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "Day Late and a Buck Short"; Brendan Fraser; David Tennant; Marin Alsop; "Whole Lotta Woman" with Marin Alsop; Emily Kaufman, the Travel Mom; first lady of Iceland.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kings of Leon: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The band performs in Denmark; songs include "On Call," "Fans," and "Knocked Up.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gnarls Barkley: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The group performs in Denmark; songs include "Crazy," "Smiley Faces," and "Going On.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Streets: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The band performs in Denmark; songs include "Fit But You Know It," "Dry Your Eyes," and "Could Be Well In.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kings of Leon: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The band performs in Denmark; songs include "On Call," "Fans," and "Knocked Up.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gnarls Barkley: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The group performs in Denmark; songs include "Crazy," "Smiley Faces," and "Going On.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260528230000 +0000" stop="20260529000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260529000000 +0000" stop="20260529003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Conor Maynard: MTV Brand New Live</title>
    <desc>Emerging British pop star Conor Maynard performs; songs include "Can't Say No" and "Vegas Girl"; live in London.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260529003000 +0000" stop="20260529010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>Silversun Pickups perform songs including "Lazy Eye," "Panic Switch," and "Well Thought Out Twinkles.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528013000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Gardens</title>
    <desc>Exploring the healing nature of gardens and the transformative power derived from the act of gardening.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>A land-owner is murdered, and the chief suspects are the couple he had been trying to evict; Wycliffe soon learns that blood ties have no patience for the process of law.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528033000 +0000" stop="20260528040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Visionary Gardeners</title>
    <desc>An orchardist shares his collection of hundreds of apple varieties with the community in an annual festival; a waterfront gardener celebrates the serendipity and wildness of her drought-resistant plants.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528040000 +0000" stop="20260528050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nick becomes the object of a fatal attraction.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528050000 +0000" stop="20260528053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Organic Panic</title>
    <desc>Homeowners are concerned with chemicals that could be leeching out of bedding, flooring, paint and cabinetry.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528053000 +0000" stop="20260528060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Chicken Soup</title>
    <desc>Thought-provoking messages.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528060000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beautiful Little Classics</title>
    <desc>Performances by classical musicians.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Chicken Soup</title>
    <desc>Thought-provoking messages.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Balance</title>
    <desc>Stunning videos of nature paired with soothing classical music create inspiration.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kabalah Yoga With Audi Gozlan</title>
    <desc>Audi Gozlan demonstrates a new system of yoga and meditation known as Kabbalah Yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: The Elemental Series</title>
    <desc>A series of classical hatha yoga, plus mediations and breath work.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528103000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Yoga that helps relieve mental fatigue.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anjelica's 22 Minute Workout</title>
    <desc>A revival of the '80s aerobics series offers workouts for a wide range of ages and abilities.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528113000 +0000" stop="20260528120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Namaste</title>
    <desc>A dynamic, yet gentle flow.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528120000 +0000" stop="20260528123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528123000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Yoga that focuses on aiding couples romantically.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shaolin Tai Chi</title>
    <desc>Learn how to control breathing to enhance energy levels, boost circulatory systems, and increase breathing capacity for stronger lungs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528133000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Namaste</title>
    <desc>A sequence that encourages a sense of ease.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pilates Pupil</title>
    <desc>Strengthening, stretching and toning with pilates.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528143000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Audi's Body Flow</title>
    <desc>Workout routines comprised of yoga, cardio, core workouts, stretching, fat burning movements, weight-lifting and toning exercises, hosted by Audi Gozlan.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528153000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shaolin Tai Chi</title>
    <desc>Exploring how various Shaolin Tai Chi exercises can help to heal the knees through gentle movement.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: The Elemental Series</title>
    <desc>A series of classical hatha yoga, plus mediations and breath work.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 must band together after a devastating fire catches them off guard; Vasquez continues his quest for answers; Violet and Novak face an unexpected roadblock in the new training protocol.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight teams up with an unlikely ally to take a killer off the streets while fighting to bring his Intelligence unit back together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528033400 +0000" stop="20260528043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Comic Colin Jost; actress Sienna Miller; AZ and Nas perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528043700 +0000" stop="20260528053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actress Charlize Theron; actor Jorma Taccone.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528053700 +0000" stop="20260528060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528060400 +0000" stop="20260528063900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528063900 +0000" stop="20260528073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "Diamonds"; Rita Wilson; Sue Bird; Cat Cora; The Curb Free Foundation; Claire Rosinkranz performs; ice cream inspired by India.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528073000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Interviews with international music sensation Laufey, actress Selma Blair, and Dr. Sandra Lee ("Dr. Pimple Popper").</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 5:00a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528093000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 5:30a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 6a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Water Safety Month with Bode and Morgan Miller; Robert De Niro and Jane Rosenthal on the Tribeca Festival 25th Anniversary; Today's Consumer: Underrated destinations; Today Food: Summer grilling with Mark Anderson and Ryan Fey.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>On the Money: AI &amp; Finances with Ted Jenkin. Take It Off Today: Minnesota man loses over 200 pounds through yoga and starts a food truck business; catching up with Fred Armisen; author David Sedaris; simple tricks to elevate your home for summer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Halle Berry Joins the chat; actor RuPaul and the Queens of "Stop! That! Train!.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 11a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>After a nurse and mother-of-three is murdered inside her Illinois home, investigators uncover security camera footage that could be key to solving the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "Day Late and a Buck Short"; Brendan Fraser; David Tennant; Marin Alsop; "Whole Lotta Woman" with Marin Alsop; Emily Kaufman, the Travel Mom; first lady of Iceland.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 4p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 5p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 6p</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528010000 +0000" stop="20260528020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 must band together after a devastating fire catches them off guard; Vasquez continues his quest for answers; Violet and Novak face an unexpected roadblock in the new training protocol.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528020000 +0000" stop="20260528030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight teams up with an unlikely ally to take a killer off the streets while fighting to bring his Intelligence unit back together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528030000 +0000" stop="20260528033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528033400 +0000" stop="20260528043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Comic Colin Jost; actress Sienna Miller; AZ and Nas perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528043700 +0000" stop="20260528053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actress Charlize Theron; actor Jorma Taccone.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528053700 +0000" stop="20260528061200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528061200 +0000" stop="20260528070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Top Story With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Reporting of breaking news and developing stories in real time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528070000 +0000" stop="20260528080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "Diamonds"; Rita Wilson; Sue Bird; Cat Cora; The Curb Free Foundation; Claire Rosinkranz performs; ice cream inspired by India.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528080000 +0000" stop="20260528083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528083000 +0000" stop="20260528090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 430A</title>
    <desc>Early morning news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528090000 +0000" stop="20260528100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528100000 +0000" stop="20260528110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528110000 +0000" stop="20260528130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Water Safety Month with Bode and Morgan Miller; Robert De Niro and Jane Rosenthal on the Tribeca Festival 25th Anniversary; Today's Consumer: Underrated destinations; Today Food: Summer grilling with Mark Anderson and Ryan Fey.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528130000 +0000" stop="20260528140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live with Kelly and Mark</title>
    <desc>Brendan Fraser and Caroline Rhea are here; Shopping Day at "Live" with Monica Mangin; simple summer switch-ups from Dr. Wendy Bazilian.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528140000 +0000" stop="20260528150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>On the Money: AI &amp; Finances with Ted Jenkin. Take It Off Today: Minnesota man loses over 200 pounds through yoga and starts a food truck business; catching up with Fred Armisen; author David Sedaris; simple tricks to elevate your home for summer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528150000 +0000" stop="20260528160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Halle Berry Joins the chat; actor RuPaul and the Queens of "Stop! That! Train!.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528160000 +0000" stop="20260528163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the local news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528163000 +0000" stop="20260528170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528170000 +0000" stop="20260528180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528180000 +0000" stop="20260528190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>After a nurse and mother-of-three is murdered inside her Illinois home, investigators uncover security camera footage that could be key to solving the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528190000 +0000" stop="20260528200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Cameoke: "Day Late and a Buck Short"; Brendan Fraser; David Tennant; Marin Alsop; "Whole Lotta Woman" with Marin Alsop; Emily Kaufman, the Travel Mom; first lady of Iceland.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528200000 +0000" stop="20260528210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 4</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528210000 +0000" stop="20260528213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528213000 +0000" stop="20260528220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5:30</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260528220000 +0000" stop="20260528223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 6</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-28</date>
  </programme>
</tv>