<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260715213203 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="FX.us">
    <display-name>US | FX East</display-name>
    <icon src="https://tlgrm.re/images/fx-us.png" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465357">
    <display-name lang="US">FXX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465331">
    <display-name lang="US">Freeform HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470910">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465105">
    <display-name lang="US">Fuse HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464897">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Family</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470509">
    <display-name lang="Canada">CTV LIFE CHANNEL</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465241">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465354">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="492942">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Mystery</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470820">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FXX Canada</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464774">
    <display-name lang="US">FYI Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470299">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Global Toronto</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465167">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Mystery HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="481954">
    <display-name lang="US">Haunt TV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486672">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486726">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486853">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486821">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV Quiz</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465290">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486720">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465002">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime Real Women</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470737">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Makeful TV SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470474">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Much Music HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486751">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">More4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465080">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV - Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486755">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">MTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464825">
    <display-name lang="US">MTVLIVE</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465207">
    <display-name lang="US">Revolt HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465113">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV2: Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467402">
    <display-name lang="US">WPTZ-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="469871">
    <display-name lang="US">KNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="468233">
    <display-name lang="US">WCAU-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467015">
    <display-name lang="US">WNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470330">
    <display-name lang="Canada">ONETV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260715163000 -0400" stop="20260715190000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Day After Tomorrow</title>
    <desc>After climatologist Jack Hall is largely ignored by U.N. officials when presenting his environmental concerns, his research proves true when a superstorm develops, setting off catastrophic natural disasters throughout the world; trying to get to his son, Sam, who is trapped in New York with his friend Laura and others, Jack and his crew must travel by foot from Philadelphia, braving the elements, to get to Sam before it's too late.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715190000 -0400" stop="20260715213000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Thor: The Dark World</title>
    <desc>In ancient times, the gods of Asgard fought and won a war against an evil race known as the Dark Elves. The survivors were neutralized, and their ultimate weapon -- the Aether -- was buried in a secret location. Hundreds of years later, Jane Foster (Natalie Portman) finds the Aether and becomes its host, forcing Thor (Chris Hemsworth) to bring her to Asgard before Dark Elf Malekith (Christopher Eccleston) captures her and uses the weapon to destroy the Nine Realms -- including Earth.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260715213000 -0400" stop="20260716000000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Thor: Love and Thunder</title>
    <desc>Thor embarks on a journey unlike anything he's ever faced -- a quest for inner peace. However, his retirement gets interrupted by Gorr the God Butcher, a galactic killer who seeks the extinction of the gods. To combat the threat, Thor enlists the help of King Valkyrie, Korg and ex-girlfriend Jane Foster, who -- to his surprise -- inexplicably wields his magical hammer. Together, they set out on a harrowing cosmic adventure to uncover the mystery of the God Butcher's vengeance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716000000 -0400" stop="20260716020000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Machete</title>
    <desc>After nearly being killed during a violent fight with a powerful drug lord, a former Mexican Federale known as Machete roams Texas streets as a vigilante and sometime day-laborer. Hired to perform a covert hit, he is double-crossed and forced to go on the run. Machete may be down, but not out, and he carves a path of blood, bullets and broken hearts in his quest to settle the score.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716020000 -0400" stop="20260716040000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Darkest Minds</title>
    <desc>When teens mysteriously develop powerful new abilities, they are declared a threat by the government and detained. One of the most powerful young people, Ruby, escapes from her camp and joins a group of runaways who are seeking a safe haven. Betrayed by the adults in power, this newfound family soon realizes that running is not enough -- they must use their collective powers to wage a resistance and take back their future.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716040000 -0400" stop="20260716043000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim has big plans for Ruby when she is hired for a cookies advertisement.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716043000 -0400" stop="20260716050000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Cheryl goes behind Jim's back and lends money to Andy for a down payment on a new condominium.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716050000 -0400" stop="20260716053000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716053000 -0400" stop="20260716060000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716060000 -0400" stop="20260716063000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>1776 - 2026 250th Anniversary Quarter Celebration Program</title>
    <desc>2026 will be one of the most historic years ever in U.S. coinage; join your host Mike Mezack to learn about the incredible U.S. Quarter program and get a chance at an exclusive P&amp;D Roll!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716063000 -0400" stop="20260716070000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716070000 -0400" stop="20260716090000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>This Means War</title>
    <desc>CIA operatives FDR Foster (Chris Pine) and Tuck (Tom Hardy) are inseparable best friends and partners. Together, their good looks, covert abilities and combat skills rank them among the CIA's elite, but their longstanding personal and professional bond is put to the test when they meet Lauren (Reese Witherspoon). FDR and Tuck both fall hard for the beautiful blonde, turning their deadly skills and an array of high-tech gadgetry against each other in an all-out battle for her love.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716090000 -0400" stop="20260716110000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Bringing Down the House</title>
    <desc>Lawyer Peter Sanderson (Steve Martin) wants to dive back into dating after his divorce and has a hard time meeting the right women. But he lucks out with online dating and meets a fellow lawyer. The two agree to meet in the flesh, but the woman he meets -- an escaped African-American convict named Charlene (Queen Latifah) -- is not what he expected. Peter is freaked out, but Charlene convinces him to take her case and prove her innocence, and along the way they learn to become friends.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260716110000 -0400" stop="20260716133000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>The Devil Wears Prada</title>
    <desc>Andy is a recent college graduate with big dreams. Upon landing a job at prestigious Runway magazine, she finds herself the assistant to diabolical editor Miranda Priestly. Andy questions her ability to survive her grim tour as Miranda's whipping girl without getting scorched.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>A bogus synchronized swimming independent study helps the kids avoid gym class; Bob adds a soft-serve ice cream machine to the restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Bob becomes obsessed with a burger-flipping video game after Jimmy Pesto gets a high score and insults Bob.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260715223000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Bob is talked into buying a food truck; the kids cause trouble at a food festival.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter broadcasts a television station out of the Griffin home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After writing a story for a local magazine, Brian gets a job at The New Yorker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Stewie steps up his efforts to kill Lois, who orders Peter to spend more time with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716003000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Lois learns she has a brother she has never met (Robert Downey Jr.), so she brings him home from a mental institution to live with her family.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When Peter's dad visits the Griffins, he tries to impose his religious beliefs on the family.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716013000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>A near-death experience lands Brian in the hospital but infuses him with a new passion for life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>At his high school reunion, Peter pretends to be a millionaire, but the truth comes out when he meets Tom Brady and loses all self-control.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716023000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When Peter goes on a TV game show and wins a maid for a week, Quagmire is smitten with her and ends up popping the question.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>After a pregnancy scare, Peter reluctantly agrees to get a vasectomy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716033000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>When Meg lands an internship with Mayor West, Brian argues that he is corrupt; a local talent show brings Peter and Lois back to their folk-singing days.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Leela becomes a Hollywood big shot after her series creation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716043000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Fry's good intentions backfire when he nurtures an alien egg that hatches into a monster.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The crew alters history when they travel back in time to the American Revolution.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Disaster ensues when a sneezing Fry inadvertently reintroduces the common cold to the world of the future, after it has been gone for 500 years.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>When the Rev. Stroup gives the Smith family the Hills' pew at the Arlen First Methodist Church, Hank and the family begin church-hopping.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>When Strickland finds himself banned from his favorite strip club, he refocuses on making Strickland Propane a fun place to work.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>Bobby meets a young freeloader when he gets a job to pay for a pair of trendy jeans and realizes there could be an easier way to get the pants.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Hill</title>
    <desc>The Hills get some liberal neighbors; Hank and Bobby try to put the neighborhood bully in his place.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1916 Gold Rarity</title>
    <desc>Own the first-ever Gold issue of the legendary 1916 Mercury Dime today. This special 2026 Gold Mercury Dime comes with a bonus Silver Medal, both dated 1916 in tribute to the classic coin and graded Perfect 70 condition in exclusive holders!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Have Thinning Hair? Keranique Can Help Regrow Beautiful, Thicker Hair!</title>
    <desc>If you have thinning hair or hair loss, Keranique can help regrow thicker, longer and fuller hair. Keranique is the number 1 hair regrowth system for women. Regain your confidence with beautiful, thicker and fuller hair in just 3 easy steps!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260715200000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aladdin</title>
    <desc>Aladdin is a lovable street urchin who meets Princess Jasmine, the beautiful daughter of the sultan of Agrabah. While visiting her exotic palace, Aladdin stumbles upon a magic oil lamp that unleashes a powerful, wisecracking, larger-than-life genie. As Aladdin and the genie start to become friends, they must soon embark on a dangerous mission to stop the evil sorcerer Jafar from overthrowing young</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cruella</title>
    <desc>Estella is a young and clever grifter who's determined to make a name for herself in the fashion world. She soon meets a pair of thieves who appreciate her appetite for mischief, and together they build a life for themselves on the streets of London. However, when Estella befriends fashion legend Baroness von Hellman, she embraces her wicked side to become the raucous and revenge-bent Cruella.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Million Dollar Nannies</title>
    <desc>Leadership is questioned as patience runs thin and clients run dry. A birthday trip promises a reset, but personal drama gets in the way, and what was meant as a celebration turns into a pressure cooker of hard truths.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Inspiring stories of miracles and answered prayers from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Andy asks Dana to join him in his therapy; broken promises are revealed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716043000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim is obsessed with bowling while Cheryl and their guests impatiently wait to start Thanksgiving dinner.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Andy announces he is becoming a vegetarian like his new girlfriend; Dana becomes frustrated with her dream date.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Cheryl is hurt when her visiting mother gives Dana a family heirloom for Christmas; Ruby and Gracie think Andy is Santa.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What's Your Injury Case Worth?</title>
    <desc>Legal professionals are standing by 24/7. Call now for a free case evaluation and learn what your injury case may be worth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Inspiring stories of miracles and answered prayers from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best Mattress Topper Ever!</title>
    <desc>Back Pain? Hip? Sleep well thanks to this cooling topper!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Million Dollar Nannies</title>
    <desc>The nannies demand answers from Leah about her past, causing tension among the group; competition rises over a new client; the biggest threat to the agency isn't from inside the house, but the realization may be too late.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Million Dollar Nannies</title>
    <desc>A confession forces Leah to decide a nanny's fate as the agency scrambles to get ahead of a scandal before it reaches other families. Under pressure, the nannies push for a risky move that could save them or blow everything up.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Amazing stories of people who have experienced God's blessings.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">CBN Newswatch</title>
    <desc>A half-hour daily news program reporting the latest national and international news from a Judea-Christian perspective; viewers can stay informed each weekday through the day's top headlines, analysis, and in-depth reports.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716143000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Andy resents a wealthy client (Nana Visitor), then ends up dating her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pinocchio</title>
    <desc>When the woodworker Geppetto (Christian Rub) sees a falling star, he wishes that the puppet he just finished, Pinocchio (Dickie Jones), could become a real boy. In the night, the Blue Fairy (Evelyn Venable) grants Geppetto's wish and asks Jiminy Cricket (Cliff Edwards) to serve as the wooden boy's conscience. But the naive and trusting Pinocchio falls into the clutches of the wicked Honest John (W</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716185000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Emperor's New Groove</title>
    <desc>Arrogant young Emperor Kuzco is transformed into a llama by his power-hungry advisor -- the devious diva Yzma. Stranded in the jungle, Kuzco's only chance to get back home and reclaim the high life rests with a good-hearted peasant named Pacha. Together, they must return Kuzco to the throne before Yzma tracks them down and finishes him off.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716185000 +0000" stop="20260716205500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hercules</title>
    <desc>Disney tackles Greek mythology in this animated feature. Hercules (Tate Donovan), a son of gods, was snatched as a baby by Hades (James Woods) and forced to live among mortals as a half-man, half-god. Now a teenager, Hercules needs to perform a rite of passage on Earth to prove himself worthy of living with the gods on Mount Olympus. With his plucky satyr sidekick, Philoctetes (Danny DeVito), alon</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716205500 +0000" stop="20260716230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Bug's Life</title>
    <desc>Flik is an inventive ant who's always messing things up for his colony. His latest mishap was destroying the food stores that were supposed to be used to pay off grasshopper Hopper. Now the strong-arming insect is demanding that the ants gather double the food or face annihilation. To avert disaster, Flik goes on a journey to recruit fighters to defend the colony. When he meets a band of high-flyi</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260716230000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ratatouille</title>
    <desc>Remy (Patton Oswalt), a resident of Paris, appreciates good food and has quite a sophisticated palate. He would love to become a chef so he can create and enjoy culinary masterpieces to his heart's delight. The only problem is, Remy is a rat. When he winds up in the sewer beneath one of Paris' finest restaurants, the rodent gourmet finds himself ideally placed to realize his dream.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a graduate student is found dead, Cosgrove and Shaw follow the evidence to a suspect with no clear motive; Price and Maroun uncover a money-grabbing scheme within a church; McCoy warns them to focus on the suspects and not the institution.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>After shots are fired in a popular nightclub, Cosgrove and Shaw suspect the spree was a ruse to target a sole victim; when security footage mysteriously disappears, Price and Maroun must rely on a witness who values reputation over facts.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A romantic date ends with a teenager fighting for her life in the hospital; Carisi can't help bringing the case home with him as he envisions the dangers ahead for his growing daughters.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A couple's dinner party ends with a violent home invasion and assault by masked men; Rollins suspects the crime is linked to her Intelligence investigation of an international gang of thieves.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716013500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nandor's search for love is finally successful; Nadja realizes her lifelong ambition of opening a vampire nightclub.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716013500 +0000" stop="20260716020500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Opening night of Nadja's vampire nightclub is threatened when the big musical guest cancels.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716020500 +0000" stop="20260716024000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires take a trip to the secret Night Market, where all the supernatural creatures gather to barter and haggle.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716024000 +0000" stop="20260716031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires endure the private school admissions interview process.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716031500 +0000" stop="20260716035000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nandor's search for love is finally successful; Nadja realizes her lifelong ambition of opening a vampire nightclub.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716035000 +0000" stop="20260716042000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Opening night of Nadja's vampire nightclub is threatened when the big musical guest cancels.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716042000 +0000" stop="20260716045500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires take a trip to the secret Night Market, where all the supernatural creatures gather to barter and haggle.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716045500 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires endure the private school admissions interview process.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716060500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nandor's search for love is finally successful; Nadja realizes her lifelong ambition of opening a vampire nightclub.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716060500 +0000" stop="20260716063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Opening night of Nadja's vampire nightclub is threatened when the big musical guest cancels.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716063500 +0000" stop="20260716071000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires take a trip to the secret Night Market, where all the supernatural creatures gather to barter and haggle.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716071000 +0000" stop="20260716080500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>The maid-of-honor winds up dead after a bachelorette party; it's up to Charlie and Rex to untangle the events of the night.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716080500 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When Rex finds a body with signs of foul play during Charlie and Sarah's romantic weekend getaway, they discover the community they're staying in may be more hostile than it looks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a popular physiotherapist is murdered, the team must investigate the victims of his alleged sexual assaults in order to track down the killer before they strike again.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie's Aunt Miranda and her friends are caught investigating an investment fraud scheme, so it's up to Charlie and Rex to get to the source of the fraud.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a starlet is killed onstage, Rex takes on a starring role while Charlie goes behind the scenes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When Jesse's sister contacts him for help, Jesse, Sarah and Rex head to Northern Ontario and find themselves in the middle of a deadly situation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a popular physiotherapist is murdered, the team must investigate the victims of his alleged sexual assaults in order to track down the killer before they strike again.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie's Aunt Miranda and her friends are caught investigating an investment fraud scheme, so it's up to Charlie and Rex to get to the source of the fraud.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a starlet is killed onstage, Rex takes on a starring role while Charlie goes behind the scenes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When Jesse's sister contacts him for help, Jesse, Sarah and Rex head to Northern Ontario and find themselves in the middle of a deadly situation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>After a popular physiotherapist is murdered, the team must investigate the victims of his alleged sexual assaults in order to track down the killer before they strike again.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Girl falling on the steps, ball dancing, baby plays with food, wheelbarrow race, cat being spun around on kitchen floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Funniest Pets and People is a solid half-hour of pure entertainment with a proven format featuring hysterical, fast-paced video clips submitted by viewers who share the funniest moments of their favorite Pets and People.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260715223000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Boy runs over a girl; birthday celebration; playing softball; fight in the mud; set falling; Doberman gives lady a ride on her chair.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cher: Life in the Spotlight</title>
    <desc>Tracing Cher's life from her childhood stage fright to her rise as an iconic star in music, TV and movies.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716003000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Bowie: Out of This World</title>
    <desc>Few artists marked the 20th century like David Bowie marked it. He was an astonishing and eclectic performer whose work brought a new dimension to the music scene and queer culture. Driven, fierce and always wanting to escape conformity, he was an outsider and was considered as a man from another planet.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Women That Made Elvis</title>
    <desc>Taking a look at the women who influenced Elvis Presley's life, from his mother, Gladys, to his true love, Priscilla.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Wendy Spring learns out why her husband is suddenly interested in yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716033000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Jasmine Washington is concerned about her boyfriend's backsliding behavior.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sex Clinic</title>
    <desc>Zach hopes to get answers about his problematic penis; Michelle wants to know more about the skin growths on her thighs; Taleela seeks some advice.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sex Clinic</title>
    <desc>A male stripper comes in to get a rash looked at, and Emily requests an STI test.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>OnlyFans top earner Lena the Plug invites Weezy to cameo in her first porn; the team at Evil Angel teaches Weezy the fundamentals of directing some of their most iconic scenes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>Weezy and rapper Freddie Gibbs stretch more than their imaginations when Jet Setting Jasmine drops by to explore their kinks; Weezy and her mom learn how to cowgirl while strengthening their pelvic floor with sex therapist Tyomi Morgan.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>Weezy and her best friend, Vinny, take a much-needed staycation at a high-class dungeon where domination is bought not earned; Weezy introduces a revolutionary sex toy that gives men a whole new role in the bedroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sex Sells</title>
    <desc>Weezy's mom gets rejuvenated with a visit to a doctor who specializes in sexual health; Weezy meets Chai, who has invested in their true sexual self and made it their own, giving them a priceless return.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob Marley: Roots of the Man</title>
    <desc>The life of Jamaican Robert Nesta Marley, known around the globe as reggae musician Bob Marley.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Shalyce hopes to gain insight into why Rod seems to be avoiding her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Hailey wants to know why Mike doesn't answer his phone when she calls.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Lindsey Johnson fears her unemployed boyfriend is not using his time wisely.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Mondo Brown discovers why his girlfriend has been so out of pocket lately.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>A water boarder hits a buoy; cat plays with a tent.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716113000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Girl falling on the steps, ball dancing, baby plays with food, wheelbarrow race, cat being spun around on kitchen floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Funniest Pets &amp; People</title>
    <desc>Funniest Pets and People is a solid half-hour of pure entertainment with a proven format featuring hysterical, fast-paced video clips submitted by viewers who share the funniest moments of their favorite Pets and People.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716123000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>Boy runs over a girl; birthday celebration; playing softball; fight in the mud; set falling; Doberman gives lady a ride on her chair.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deadly Love: Bobby &amp; Whitney</title>
    <desc>Exploring the romance of Whitney Houston and Bobby Brown; behind the glamour is a story of love, addiction and heartbreak that shaped their lives and legacies.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716143000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dolly Parton: Queen of Country</title>
    <desc>The story of multi-award winning country performer Dolly Parton.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blondie: Glass Heart</title>
    <desc>The story of Blondie and their rise from small clubs in New York City to selling out shows around the globe.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260715200000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wedding at Graceland</title>
    <desc>A country star on the rise has a short time to plan her wedding when a date opens up at Graceland Chapel.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth feels caught between overprotective Jack and new miner Billy Hamilton; when Jack tells her he has proof Billy lied to her, Elizabeth decides she's had enough; Abigail suggests Jack try a gentler approach to reach Elizabeth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Abigail is encouraged to reopen Coal Valley's dilapidated and abandoned café and make it her own after Elizabeth raves about Abigail's baking; Jack and Elizabeth are at odds after Elizabeth's brief romance with a dishonest miner.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth and Abigail move into rooms above Abigail's café; Elizabeth and her students put on the Coal Valley Founders' Day play; Jack surprises Elizabeth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Jack asks Elizabeth for a dinner date, finally making his romantic intentions clear; Elizabeth receives an unexpected visit from her younger sister, Julie; Elizabeth is swept away when Jack surprises her with a very romantic evening at the café.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>An elderly relative of James and Cassandra arrives in Walnut Grove with the news that he plans to sue for their custody.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Hester Sue's estranged husband arrives in Walnut Grove and convinces Charles and Caroline to help him win her back.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mr. Edwards almost alienates the Ingalls when he stays with them after alcoholism ruins his marriage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Amy is upset with Ty when he purchases a vintage motorcycle; Caleb leaves for a rodeo in Montana.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Amy discovers that Mr. Hanley has abandoned his horses and is on the brink of losing his farm.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>A country doctor's (Roscoe Lee Browne) dedication to his community's medical needs nearly ruins him physically and financially. With Renee Jones.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>A zealous district attorney tries for a felony conviction of a vagrant accused of stealing a bottle of wine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>An elderly relative of James and Cassandra arrives in Walnut Grove with the news that he plans to sue for their custody.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Hester Sue's estranged husband arrives in Walnut Grove and convinces Charles and Caroline to help him win her back.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mr. Edwards almost alienates the Ingalls when he stays with them after alcoholism ruins his marriage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Charles, Albert and Mr. Edwards follow the bank robbers who shot innocent bystander James.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>James and Alert are caught up in a nefarious gang's bank robbery while on a trip to Sleepy Eye.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Summer of Dreams</title>
    <desc>A fading pop star (Debbie Gibson) who is on the verge of losing everything finds inspiration when she relocates to suburban Ohio and begins teaching music to a talented group of misfit children.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wedding of Dreams</title>
    <desc>Debbie turns her back on the music business and finds true love. When her manager tries to pull her back into the limelight, she must decide whether music or love comes first.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Perfect Bride</title>
    <desc>Fitness instructor Molly runs the Bridal Boot Camp, helping prospective brides-to-be get in shape for the big day. Things get complicated when sparks start to fly between herself and Nick, the fiancé of one of her new clients.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260716220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Perfect Bride: Wedding Bells</title>
    <desc>After their wedding venue reserves the wrong date, Nick and Molly have six weeks to plan the wedding of their dreams. Things get even more complicated when Steven, who once left Molly at the altar, comes back into her life with a business offer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716220000 +0000" stop="20260716230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth is heartbroken after saying goodbye to Jack, but she tries to stay strong in front of her class; Abigail tries to outwit Henry Gowen by stealing a file from his office that could hold the clues to the cause of the mine explosion.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260716230000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Jack is thought of as a hero after putting away the Tolliver outlaws; he decides to return to Coal Valley; Jack's return to Elizabeth is complicated when a beautiful actress arrives; Bill Avery and Abigail try to make a case against Gowen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260717000000 +0000" stop="20260718000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">When Calls the Heart</title>
    <desc>Jack helps Bill Avery with his investigation into the mine explosion; a romance grows between Bill and Abigail; Elizabeth struggles to make a decision about the teaching offer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Frank is ordered to attend a parade honoring a man who conspired in a bombing against the police; Danny investigates the return of a teen who suspiciously disappeared 13 years ago; Jamie and Eddie try to help a woman they believe is being exploited.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monk</title>
    <desc>Capt. Stottlemeyer tries to think like Monk to determine why someone would want to kill the world's oldest man.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Denise Nurse helps a couple with a budget of £450,000 find their dream country home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Queen of the Castle</title>
    <desc>Viewers years and older Ann takes on the ultimate juggling act by hosting two weddings in one day, a lavish ceremony for a pair of pampered pups and a heartfelt celebration for Kev, a castle builder who gets to trade his hard hat for wedding bells.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef UK</title>
    <desc>Nine home cooks arrive for the second week of heats; their first test is the Audition Round; each must cook a signature dish, which John and Gregg judge solely on taste, and whose three favorite dishes earn a MasterChef apron.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716023000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Find My Country House: Canada</title>
    <desc>Sarah and Tate search for their dream home, nestled between the beautiful mountainscape of Blue River.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>In the first team challenge, the remaining cooks honor firefighting heroes in a rib cook-off.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Frank is ordered to attend a parade honoring a man who conspired in a bombing against the police; Danny investigates the return of a teen who suspiciously disappeared 13 years ago; Jamie and Eddie try to help a woman they believe is being exploited.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monk</title>
    <desc>Capt. Stottlemeyer tries to think like Monk to determine why someone would want to kill the world's oldest man.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Queen of the Castle</title>
    <desc>Viewers years and older Ann takes on the ultimate juggling act by hosting two weddings in one day, a lavish ceremony for a pair of pampered pups and a heartfelt celebration for Kev, a castle builder who gets to trade his hard hat for wedding bells.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie cooks sardines on the grill and serves them with watercress salad, figs and crispy halloumi; dessert is a thick chocolate mousse.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie prepares steak Indian-style, with spinach and paneer salad, naan breads, and a mango dessert.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>How to wear the top fashion trends; Bryan and Sarah Baeumler; buzzworthy tech; beauty trends; Myra Berg meets "MasterChef Canada's" home cooks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary shakes up a cocktail of recipes that use beer and wine to load up on flavor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Chef Spencer Watts makes a fresh Vietnamese meal for four for around 30 dollars.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>A Mystery Box Challenge requires the cooks to work together, and the winners give the assignments in the pantry challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>Racers wade into Smithers, B.C., where some have a smooth delivery and others struggle with the details; it's a delicate balance of the right ingredients during the detour, and teams put their knowledge of their partner to the test.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Mary's veg versions of meaty classics include burgers, nugs and even bacon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716123000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Chef Spencer Watts cooks up food truck inspired fare for the whole family in under 30 minutes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Erin's trial against a human trafficker is jeopardized when the presiding judge is found dead; Mayor Dutton opposes Frank's public safety initiative, but a plan is devised to bypass the mayor's veto.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Monk</title>
    <desc>Monk stars in a play while investigating an onstage murder witnessed by 300 theatergoers. Melissa George, Amy Sedaris and Betty Buckley guest star.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>A Mystery Box Challenge requires the cooks to work together, and the winners give the assignments in the pantry challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>How to wear the top fashion trends; Bryan and Sarah Baeumler; buzzworthy tech; beauty trends; Myra Berg meets "MasterChef Canada's" home cooks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Tasty crusted cod with 'my mushy peas', tartar sauce and warm garden salad.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716173000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Chicken skewers with satay sauce; a fiery noodle salad; fruit and mint sugar.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>Racers wade into Smithers, B.C., where some have a smooth delivery and others struggle with the details; it's a delicate balance of the right ingredients during the detour, and teams put their knowledge of their partner to the test.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260715200000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Small Town Christmas</title>
    <desc>Nell's last stop on a nationwide book tour takes her to Springdale, the hometown of Emmett, a young man she met while both were junior copy editors at a New York publishing company.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rocky Mountain Christmas</title>
    <desc>Sarah heads to her uncle's ranch to escape New York and the spotlight from a breakup. Returning home for the first time since her aunt passed, complications arise when Graham, a Hollywood star, arrives at the ranch to prepare for his next film.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">O Little Christmas Market</title>
    <desc>An artist fights to save her town's beloved Christmas market from a developer, but a budding romance with the architect tied to the deal may help bring about a Christmas miracle.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy and her former tennis rival play practical jokes during a reunion.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716023000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy and Blanche try to help Rose overcome a 30-year dependency on prescription medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose thinks her visiting sister is trying to steal her friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716033000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Sophia and Rose help a friend escape from an inadequate nursing home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy and her former tennis rival play practical jokes during a reunion.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716043000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy and Blanche try to help Rose overcome a 30-year dependency on prescription medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose thinks her visiting sister is trying to steal her friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Sophia and Rose help a friend escape from an inadequate nursing home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>When Van fails a history test due to the pressure of being a star football player, Reba steps in to tutor him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba's best friend returns to Houston and uncovers a photograph that hints at infidelity early in Reba and Brock's marriage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba celebrates her divorce with lunch and finds her credit card is declined; Reba is angered to find out Brock let Barbra Jean run up the shared credit card for her wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba's ex-husband becomes jealous when she calls a plumber to fix a faucet; Cheyenne "moons" Van's teammates.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Kyra does not want to spend time with her father since it includes Barbra Jean; Cheyenne and Van plan to move out.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>When Van fails a history test due to the pressure of being a star football player, Reba steps in to tutor him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba's best friend returns to Houston and uncovers a photograph that hints at infidelity early in Reba and Brock's marriage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba celebrates her divorce with lunch and finds her credit card is declined; Reba is angered to find out Brock let Barbra Jean run up the shared credit card for her wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba's parents visit and surprise everyone when they accept Barbra Jean into the family.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba returns to work but is fired when advice to a teen couple is misinterpreted as endorsing premarital sex.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>After Richard and Emily renew their vows, Lorelai, Luke and Christopher find Rory and Logan together.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>After the disastrous scene at the wedding, Lorelai begs Luke not to give up on their relationship, and his decision to be alone leaves her devastated.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>When Luke agrees to build sets for the elementary school's production of "Fiddler on the Roof," he knows that Lorelai is the costume designer and hopes that their paths will cross.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">An Ice Palace Romance</title>
    <desc>A journalist faces old fears when she returns to her hometown ice rink to cover a story. With the help of the owner and his young daughter, she begins to reevaluate her life's purpose.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping for Christmas</title>
    <desc>It's almost Christmas when busy realtor Abigail agrees to help her sister with the simple flip of a recently inherited home. Unfortunately, co-beneficiary Bo has other plans in mind.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Stone asks Benson to investigate a sexual encounter from his past that he feels guilt and uncertainty about; Rollins considers a proposal from Doctor Al.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The murder of an elusive, shy teenage author living a double life leads Benson and the rest of the SVU on an investigation that uncovers a situation beyond their wildest imaginations.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a young woman accuses a celebrity plastic surgeon and his girlfriend of sexual assault, Benson and the team must determine if the woman was attacked or if it was a night of sex games gone wrong.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A serial rapist strikes again after two decades of silence, and SVU is determined to uncover the elusive criminal and bring justice to his many victims; Stone discovers that his father worked on the case before it went cold.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the team investigate a father's murder after his teenage daughters call in a home burglary that turns into an attempted assault; when the team speaks with the medical examiner, the details don't add up.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson, Fin, Carisi and Rollins debate what they should and should not conjecture about a defendant's situation while waiting to testify at her murder trial.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the team investigate the death of a prostitute at a brothel; they wonder if there was foul play or if this could be a case of a junkie who relapsed, turned to tricking, got depressed and committed suicide.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and the SVU investigate the death of a man they believe to be a pedophile; when they dig deeper, they realize things are not what they seem and that the case actually hits really close to home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU pursues a suspect when a child is discovered in the trunk of an abandoned car.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When defense attorney Nikki Staines is raped after a police charity event, Benson reluctantly looks to her own for a suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">H2O X5 - Super Powerful 5-In-1 Multi-Use Steam Cleaner</title>
    <desc>Kills 99% of Bacteria, Viruses, and Germs with Steam! The 5-in-1 Lightweight, Fast, Powerful, And Completely Chemical Free Steam Cleaner! Lift and remove dirt and stains all around the home!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1776 - 2026 250th Anniversary Quarter Celebration Program</title>
    <desc>2026 will be one of the most historic years ever in U.S. coinage; join your host Mike Mezack to learn about the incredible U.S. Quarter program and get a chance at an exclusive P&amp;D Roll!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When a tutor who works with privileged students turns up dead, the team sifts through possible murderers; Bones wants to voice her own audiobook.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The investigation into the murder of a golfer-turned-lumberjack reveals numerous secrets that could have led to the victim's demise, including an affair with a married rival.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Corpses that are linked to Booth's former Army unit turn up around D.C.; Brennan's father hides a serious medical procedure from her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>A recent loss creates tension between Booth and Brennan as they each try to deal with their grief; an old flame from Brennan's past visits.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Booth, Brennan and Aubrey go undercover at a rowdy demolition derby to investigate the case of a young man who died in a horrendous hay baler accident; Dr. Gordon Wyatt returns and assists Hodgins and Cam when the Gormogon case hits a dead end.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After an investigative journalist is murdered, the team uncovers information linking the suspect to past cases; the victim's death strikes a chord with Maggie, leaving her desperate for answers in regard to a traumatic event in her personal life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>A serial bomber appears to be targeting Wall Street's elite; Maggie and OA search for a suspect who seems set on revenge; Dana deals with Spencer Briggs, a cocky profiler brought in to consult on the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The daughter of a wealthy family is kidnapped in an attempt to gain notorious internet fame; Maggie and OA discover the kidnapper's plans go far beyond abduction.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>Maggie and Dana struggle to find justice for victims murdered by a serial killer; the mayor limits the investigation to cut costs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>OA and Maggie team up with members of the FBI's Fugitives Department to track down a person wanted for murder who is also on America's Top 10 Most Wanted list.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When the BAU is called to negotiate a situation at a federal bank, one of their own becomes a hostage; Prentiss says goodbye.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU interviews candidates to take the opening left by Kate's departure; the team tracks a serial killer who leaves behind evidence that indicates a person intent on revenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team must find the person responsible for a sarin gas attack on a Los Angeles bus before a larger incident occurs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team suspects a jilted unknown subject is responsible when brides are murdered on the eve of their nuptials.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When a robbery-homicide leaves three restaurant employees dead, a cold case that occurred in the same town six years earlier could yield a lead.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A notorious street artist becomes a suspect when corpses are used in macabre graffiti art in Detroit; Dr. Lewis tries to balance work and her relationship with her fiancé.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A murder in a Florida community of sex offenders results in many possible suspects; a career opportunity could take Lewis away from the BAU.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Rossi's daughter, a journalist, investigates the disappearance of a college student; JJ comes back from maternity leave.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>An unknown subject in Phoenix abducts people and deprives them of sleep; Garcia and Hotch deal with a threat from hit men.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Listener</title>
    <desc>Toby is forced to use his telepathic abilities to keep himself and others alive when he becomes a hostage in a bank heist.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Listener</title>
    <desc>Toby struggles with Alvin Klein during his first official investigation: a 10-year-old murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Listener</title>
    <desc>A performer's life is threatened, so Toby poses as her assistant and helps to investigate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Listener</title>
    <desc>An African teenager, whose father is an alleged war criminal, is abducted.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Business becomes personal for Bull when TAC assists with a civil suit against the bank that funded the terrorists responsible for Cable's death; Marissa enlists her former homeland security co-worker Taylor Rentzel to help with the suit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Bull joins the defense team of a seemingly unwinnable case when a doctor is put on trial after his DNA links him to a homicide; Bull and Benny work on selecting jurors who are predisposed to trust their instincts instead of incontrovertible evidence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Bull and the TAC team must help when Marissa's restaurateur husband is charged with involuntary manslaughter after one of his employees dies, allegedly because of negligence; Bull and Benny aim to select jurors who will believe it was an accident.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Bull confronts his guilt over closing his psychiatric practice when a former patient goes on trial for killing her brother; Bull and Benny enter an insanity defense plea and aim to seat jurors that are sympathetic to mental illness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Bull takes on a pro bono client who was poorly advised by his public defender to plead guilty to a misdemeanor assault charge and is now facing felony manslaughter after the victim dies.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Danny looks to her colleagues for help when her boyfriend is arrested and threatened with deportation; Bull represents a German national who is being sued by a museum over possession of a valuable painting.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Bull represents a priest who knows, but cannot reveal, the identity of a driver involved in a fatal hit-and-run accident.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bull</title>
    <desc>Bull and his romantic rival, Diana Lindsay, join forces to create two defense teams when Diana's niece and her husband are charged with armed robbery; Bull's reunion with Diana is strained by his new post-heart attack regimen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When mummified remains are found at Halloween attractions, Brennan and Booth realize that they must find the killer by Halloween or there will be another death.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>The team suspects colleagues when the remains of a young Jeffersonian intern are found in the building's incinerator; Booth poses as Cam's boyfriend and accompanies her on a family get-together.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260716210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>When high-school classmates reunite to unearth a time capsule buried 20 years earlier, they find the corpse of an adolescent friend inside; while combing through the victim's life, the team members rehash their own teen years.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716210000 +0000" stop="20260716220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>After construction workers find an archbishop's body with the kneecaps surgically removed, the team returns to the case of the Widow's Son serial killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260716220000 +0000" stop="20260716230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bones</title>
    <desc>Three days before Christmas the body of a bearded man in a tailor-made Santa outfit turns up in a sewer; Brennan visits her father in prison and plots a nontraditional holiday reunion.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Unaware that Claire has a personal assistant, Phil cannot figure out how she is getting everything done; Jay and Gloria are sleep-deprived as Joe goes through a fussy phase; Cam and Mitch feel they are not treated well at a friend's wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>The effects of the supply chain shortages continue to impact the ED when Taylor's drug dealer reappears; one of the victims of the recent train crash needs a transplant, forcing Marcel to improvise; Charles and Cuevas help a patient with amnesia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Firehouse 51 hosts a Halloween open house; Kidd and Severide help a young girl after she gets kicked out of her home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Atwater's reactions during a tense arrest are called into question; the team must dig in to uncover key evidence that could aid in the ongoing investigation and clear Atwater's name.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang uses the Internet to cyber stalk their prey; Frank tries to drum up business for Paddy's with a viral video.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716013000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang designs a scheme to extract an artifact; their plans are jeopardized when the owners are still at home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Mac confesses to a confused priest that his weight gain is the fault of the other members of the gang.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716023000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang puts all its effort into seeing the hottest action movie of the summer; the president visits Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang uses the Internet to cyber stalk their prey; Frank tries to drum up business for Paddy's with a viral video.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716033000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang designs a scheme to extract an artifact; their plans are jeopardized when the owners are still at home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Mac confesses to a confused priest that his weight gain is the fault of the other members of the gang.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716043000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang puts all its effort into seeing the hottest action movie of the summer; the president visits Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang uses the Internet to cyber stalk their prey; Frank tries to drum up business for Paddy's with a viral video.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang designs a scheme to extract an artifact; their plans are jeopardized when the owners are still at home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Mac confesses to a confused priest that his weight gain is the fault of the other members of the gang.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>The gang puts all its effort into seeing the hottest action movie of the summer; the president visits Philadelphia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A man makes a pact with the devil for immortality then finds he doesn't get a kick out of living anymore.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>Convicted of murder, a man is sent to a deserted asteroid in space to serve a 50-year prison sentence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>Unique circumstances allow a meek bank teller to indulge his passion for reading. With Burgess Meredith.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A terrified man stumbles into a psychiatrist's office, afraid that if he falls asleep a woman in his dream will murder him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A passenger on board a wartime freighter has a premonition that the ship will be sunk by a Nazi submarine at 1:15 a.m., but no one believes him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>Three astronauts, returning from man's first space flight, can not remember the events of their trip; they begin to disappear one by one.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Charlie and Rex head into the woods to track a missing photographer, a mysterious organization throws the investigation off its trail.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate a fantasy role-playing game turned deadly when a player is found slain by a sword.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex are in deep water after a university rower is shot by a sniper during team practice.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>As Charlie and Rex head into the woods to track a missing photographer, a mysterious organization throws the investigation off its trail.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>An unfinished multimillion-dollar Las Vegas mansion could make or break Scott's career.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott purchases a home that has legal issues, but he soon needs legal help of his own to avoid federal drug charges.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott buys a small condo unit in a low-income neighborhood, only to learn some nasty surprises about his bargain-priced purchase.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott must use unusual methods after his latest purchase presents problems of an other-worldly nature.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott and his workers are stymied in their efforts to remove a nauseating stench during a house flip.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott develops chest pains following a dispute with Amie over the work required for a large home in a fancy golf community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716030100 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott learns that his latest project, an unassuming home on a public golf course, was previously used as a chop-shop junkyard.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott must use unusual methods after his latest purchase presents problems of an other-worldly nature.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott and his workers are stymied in their efforts to remove a nauseating stench during a house flip.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott develops chest pains following a dispute with Amie over the work required for a large home in a fancy golf community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716070100 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>Scott learns that his latest project, an unassuming home on a public golf course, was previously used as a chop-shop junkyard.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flipping Vegas</title>
    <desc>A golf course property with an accelerated construction schedule.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flawless 1776 Silver</title>
    <desc>Secure the first-ever dual-dated 1776-2026 Morgan &amp; Peace Silver Dollars celebrating America's 250th Anniversary; featuring the first-ever Enhanced Uncirculated issues, one-year-only Liberty Bell 250 privy marks and exceptionally low mintages.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pain Relief Revealed</title>
    <desc>Discover the hidden story of OmegaXL with John Walsh. He dives deep into the groundbreaking supplement that promises hope and relief for millions battling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rare Silver Kennedy</title>
    <desc>Add 31 silver Kennedy half dollars from 1992 to 2021 graded near perfect PF69 Ultra Cameo to your collection today; each coin features the highest eye appeal for their date and grade, including a bonus first year of issue 1964 Kennedy in PF69.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rare Silver Kennedy</title>
    <desc>Add 31 silver Kennedy half dollars from 1992 to 2021 graded near perfect PF69 Ultra Cameo to your collection today; each coin features the highest eye appeal for their date and grade, including a bonus first year of issue 1964 Kennedy in PF69.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joni Table Talk</title>
    <desc>Joni and guests tackle a wide range of relevant issues, controversial subjects and hard-hitting news topics with candor and wit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716113000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Winter descends on the mountains without mercy; Fifty-below weather traps Marty; Morgan and Tom forge new alliances; Rich battles a rogue grizzly.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Morgan races the ice to gather critical supplies; Eustace digs out from a devastating tornado; Marty takes to the air in a bid to win the season.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Morgan fights to stay afloat on a treacherous river run; Jason loses everything; routine training turns to live combat for Rich's dog team.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Morgan faces a gauntlet of frozen river crossings to get home; Tom strikes out; Marty's season begins to unravel.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>As winter strikes, Morgan hunts for riches in the ruins; Jason tackles a river giant; Eustace makes a breakthrough with black powder.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>A customer demands a discount when Jarrett fails to deliver a shipment of surfboards on time; Marc agrees to transport a monster truck, only to learn the vehicle has no "travel wheels.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716173000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Roy takes a ride on a submersible boat; Jennifer hauls a set of large window displays to a Hollywood candy store.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrett hauls a life-size version of a popular children's game and a hot-rod casket; Jennifer races the clock to transport a pregnant horse.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 5</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 6</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260715223000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goldbergs</title>
    <desc>With everyone preoccupied with the new baby on the way, Erica's graduation is met with lackluster enthusiasm from Beverly and Geoff; Adam's new job is in jeopardy; Barry tries to be the new man of the house.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Brother</title>
    <desc>The houseguests compete to win the power of veto; during the veto meeting, the winner of the competition can keep nominations the same or save someone from eviction for the week.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716013000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghosts</title>
    <desc>When new pressures threaten Sam and Jay's control over Woodstone, they're forced to navigate unexpected challenges to protect its future; a long-absent ghost returns, reopening emotional connections that complicate new relationships.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Burger Battle</title>
    <desc>Three chefs put it all on the line to win the title of Big Burger Battle Champion and the cash prize of $25,000.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 11</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716033500 +0000" stop="20260716040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716040500 +0000" stop="20260716050500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>A young woman disappears in Calgary, Canada, and a 911 call results in the discovery of an older couple dead in their home, leading police to uncover the tragic connection between the two cases as they discover evidence of a senseless killing spree.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716050500 +0000" stop="20260716053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716053500 +0000" stop="20260716063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>Things get off to a smoky start in the Wildfire Round; the chefs fish for a win in the Crossfire Round; in the Feast of Fire, it's a BBQ battle of superfoods.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716063500 +0000" stop="20260716073500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masters of Flip</title>
    <desc>Kortney and Dave flip a rundown property into a stunning home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716073500 +0000" stop="20260716083500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Brother Canada</title>
    <desc>Fifteen people share an isolated home and try to avoid being evicted by their housemates.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716083500 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SIGN OFF</title>
    <desc>Sign off.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Today</title>
    <desc>Daniel Kolenda, the global evangelist and author of "Furious," unpacks the battle between legalism and the Gospel in Paul's day to see how it applies in the church today.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News Morning</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast to start your day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Morning Show</title>
    <desc>Viewers from across the country are welcomed in for an hour of smart conversation, lifestyle segments, big-name guests and live performances.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tamron Hall</title>
    <desc>"The Real Housewives of New Jersey's" Paul Connell and Dolores Catania open up about his recent eyelid lift surgery and breaking the stigma around men and cosmetic procedures; plastic surgeon Dr. Mark Karolak; the viral trend around men's fertility; viral barber Edgar Hernandez; how men are embracing makeup as part of their everyday routines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Property Brothers: Forever Home</title>
    <desc>A family in Las Vegas takes time to heal after a recent loss; now it's time star over and renovate multiple rooms.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716163000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Save My Reno</title>
    <desc>It's up to Samantha and Sebastian to crank up the heat on savings for Karen and Keith's open-concept dream kitchen and insulation overhaul.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Making It Home With Kortney &amp; Kenny</title>
    <desc>A young family of five are world travelers and have never owned a real home; after deciding it is time to settle down, they purchase a massive house; Kortney enlists Kenny's help to open up the walls and make room for this growing family.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goldbergs</title>
    <desc>Erica asks Beverly for help to find Barry a date for the Sadie Hawkins dance; Adam and Pops get into an argument.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>Ben recalls the '60s, when he resigned as judge to defend a black cook (Stan Shaw) accused of killing a bullying white sheriff.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hannah Swensen Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When a suspect in a forgery case is murdered and the prosecutor goes missing, Hannah and Chad must uncover how the two cases are connected and solve them in time for the trial.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hailey Dean Mysteries: Death on Duty</title>
    <desc>A psychologist and former prosecutor helps a detective investigate the murder of a former Marine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A jealous mystery-writer (Jean Simmons) creates havoc for Jessica when her own publisher tells her that her work is slipping.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Eudora admits she stole Jessica's notes, but denies poisoning the apples she brought or murdering the detective who was following her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica becomes involved in a dangerous espionage case in Athens, Greece, after a chance encounter in Paris with British agent Michael Haggerty (Len Cariou).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A parishioner confesses murder to a pastor, who cannot divulge the truth when an innocent man is accused.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>The death of a venerable female mystery writer takes Jessica back to a 1947 murder aboard the Queen Mary.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica can't make sense of clues surrounding a real-estate developer's murder and his wife's suicide.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A jealous mystery-writer (Jean Simmons) creates havoc for Jessica when her own publisher tells her that her work is slipping.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Eudora admits she stole Jessica's notes, but denies poisoning the apples she brought or murdering the detective who was following her.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica becomes involved in a dangerous espionage case in Athens, Greece, after a chance encounter in Paris with British agent Michael Haggerty (Len Cariou).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A parishioner confesses murder to a pastor, who cannot divulge the truth when an innocent man is accused.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>Mark investigates an arson blaze in the Malibu hills that kills an unpopular ecology activist who was preventing a businessman's planned housing development.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>Mark sets out to discover who tried to kill a high-profile millionairess only to learn that she was not the intended victim.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>Mark (Dick Van Dyke) attempts to solve the murder of a famous basketball player. Ken Howard, Malik Sealy and Pooh Richardson guest star.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>When a young model dies after a workout, Jesse and Mark learn she wasn't the all-natural person she appeared to be.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diagnosis Murder</title>
    <desc>A network president is murdered and so is her successor; Michele Greene; Erik Estrada; Doug E. Doug; Jane Seymour; Fred Willard; John Aniston; Jaleel White; Reginald VelJohnson; Stephen J. Cannell; Dr. Joyce Brothers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>At a beach resort to attend a high-school sweetheart's funeral, Ben is drawn into the investigation of two men's deaths.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>Ben defends a man against murder charges stemming from a date-rape shakedown scheme.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>A murder case involves two stars of a local theater production and an argument Ben thought he saw from his hotel window.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260716210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>Milton Berle guest stars as a mouthy comic who stands accused of murdering an equally mouthy young comedian.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716210000 +0000" stop="20260716220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>A con artist facing execution for murder exasperates Ben while having his case appealed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260716220000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hailey Dean Mysteries: Deadly Estate</title>
    <desc>After her fiancé is murdered, Hailey Dean becomes one of the country's most revered felony prosecutors. When she helps her close friend Pam sell the estate of Pam's grandparents, she falls headfirst into a harrowing mystery.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260717000000 +0000" stop="20260718000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Harmony Mysteries</title>
    <desc>A new teacher at an Irish prep school is shocked to find a ghost in her house. She decides to help solve his murder in the hopes that it will allow him to move on.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260715210200 +0000" stop="20260715215300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>APRA ambitiously conducts its most ambitious investigation to date; a full-scale paranormal experiment during a once-in-a-lifetime eclipse.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260715215300 +0000" stop="20260715224600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>Study a physical scratch that could be linked to a haunting love story.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260715224600 +0000" stop="20260715233500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alien Files Reopened</title>
    <desc>Billy Meier claims he's traveled through time and space with an alien race from the Pleiades star cluster; in the decades following his revelation, both skeptics and ufologists say it's a hoax despite Meier providing photographic evidence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260715233500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Patterns in fields, which appear overnight and without any warning; examining crop circles, why they appear and what they could possibly signify.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716002500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>During the renaissance, advances were made in both science and the arts, but many paintings have a mysterious UFO.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716002500 +0000" stop="20260716012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unexplained: Caught on Camera</title>
    <desc>A look at a silent spirit stalker in the Bay State; a look at an English family that hears their floorboards squeak even when no one is there; a look at a Scottish seaside village, where the aurora borealis attracts unwanted visitors.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716012000 +0000" stop="20260716020900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alien Files Reopened</title>
    <desc>Billy Meier claims he's traveled through time and space with an alien race from the Pleiades star cluster; in the decades following his revelation, both skeptics and ufologists say it's a hoax despite Meier providing photographic evidence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716020900 +0000" stop="20260716023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Patterns in fields, which appear overnight and without any warning; examining crop circles, why they appear and what they could possibly signify.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716023500 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>During the renaissance, advances were made in both science and the arts, but many paintings have a mysterious UFO.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716032500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A look at this English town in Buckinghamshire and why so many spirits of the past haunt its streets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716032500 +0000" stop="20260716041800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unexplained: Caught on Camera</title>
    <desc>A look at a silent spirit stalker in the Bay State; a look at an English family that hears their floorboards squeak even when no one is there; a look at a Scottish seaside village, where the aurora borealis attracts unwanted visitors.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716041800 +0000" stop="20260716050900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>Revisit Karric-Parks House, where the team is keen to determine if the cavern behind the home is its source of supernatural power; watch as they team up with local investigators to replicate the finds from their first visit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716050900 +0000" stop="20260716055900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>Probe the eerie Civil War apparitions inside a Confederate general's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716055900 +0000" stop="20260716065000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>The APRA collaborates with the mayor of West Point, Ky., who's invested in the preservation of the town; the team assesses paranormal activity in two purportedly haunted locations -- the Lynch House and Hardy Hotel.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716065000 +0000" stop="20260716074100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>APRA ambitiously conducts its most ambitious investigation to date; a full-scale paranormal experiment during a once-in-a-lifetime eclipse.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716074100 +0000" stop="20260716083400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries</title>
    <desc>Study a physical scratch that could be linked to a haunting love story.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716083400 +0000" stop="20260716092300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Alien Files Reopened</title>
    <desc>Billy Meier claims he's traveled through time and space with an alien race from the Pleiades star cluster; in the decades following his revelation, both skeptics and ufologists say it's a hoax despite Meier providing photographic evidence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716092300 +0000" stop="20260716094800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Patterns in fields, which appear overnight and without any warning; examining crop circles, why they appear and what they could possibly signify.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716094800 +0000" stop="20260716101400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>During the renaissance, advances were made in both science and the arts, but many paintings have a mysterious UFO.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716101400 +0000" stop="20260716110600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unexplained: Caught on Camera</title>
    <desc>A look at a silent spirit stalker in the Bay State; a look at an English family that hears their floorboards squeak even when no one is there; a look at a Scottish seaside village, where the aurora borealis attracts unwanted visitors.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716110600 +0000" stop="20260716113200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries: Family Spirits</title>
    <desc>Learn how caregiver Beth Deering puts her ability to see the dead to work in her job as a death doula; explore the extraordinary paranormal power that she inherited and see why it allows her to provide comfort to patients in their final hours.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716113200 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haunted Discoveries: Family Spirits</title>
    <desc>Revisit a series of paranormal encounters that have helped reassure a family of a mother's enduring love; learn why Andy believes that his ex-wife, Cat, continues to visit both him and his son Trey long after her tragic passing.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716125200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unexplained: Caught on Camera</title>
    <desc>A Massachusetts sailor is shocked to his core when a sinister sound calls out at sea. In the UK, a lifelong paranormal believer reveals her collection of ghost pictures you need to see to believe. It's all unexplained and all caught on camera.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716125200 +0000" stop="20260716134500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unexplained: Caught on Camera</title>
    <desc>The dark energies have turned a woman's home upside down and targeted her children in the dead of night; meeting a couple who swear they can summon UFOs; tamping down the fear when a graveyard ghoul pops into view.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716134500 +0000" stop="20260716143800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unexplained: Caught on Camera</title>
    <desc>A face-off with an angry demon who scratches a Canadian couple exploring a haunted mansion; meeting a pushy pub poltergeist in the UK; seeing strange footage captured by an Australian man who swears that a ghost has been walking his beloved pooch.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260716143800 +0000" stop="20260716150400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A mass-produced series of paintings of crying children, a popular artwork in many houses in the 1980s, is believed to be related to a mysterious series of house fires at the time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260715214500 +0000" stop="20260715235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jack Reacher</title>
    <desc>Mystery action thriller film starring Tom Cruise and Rosamund Pike, 2012. When five people are gunned down by a sniper, only one man has the skills to take the true criminals out.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260715235500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shop on TV</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716025000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Noel Edmonds' Kiwi Adventure</title>
    <desc>Noel and Liz face new challenges in New Zealand as they fight to turn their business around and Noel's love for cars and his legacy project are put to the test.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716025000 +0000" stop="20260716040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716040500 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dickinson's Real Deal</title>
    <desc>The Duke takes off to Aerospace Bristol, where Mark Stevens hits turbulence when he attempts to land a pair of luxury watches.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Morning Britain</title>
    <desc>News, current affairs and lively debate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">This Morning</title>
    <desc>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real-life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716113000 +0000" stop="20260716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716123000 +0000" stop="20260716125500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Lunchtime News</title>
    <desc>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716125500 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dickinson's Real Deal</title>
    <desc>David and his dealers visit Crewe. It's a jungle in the den as new dealer Laurie Scully faces a cheeky chimp, and Fay Rutter goes wild about autographs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern as Kelly gets her chance to open the iconic red boxes and tries to hold her nerve until just the right moment to beat the Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which three players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as Julie from West Yorkshire, Charlie from Bognor Regis, Catherine from Manchester and Anuj from London join forces in the hope that they can beat a Chaser.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716173000 +0000" stop="20260716183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Evening News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716183000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tom Kerridge Cooks Italy</title>
    <desc>Tom is in Italy's Deep South, discovering the secrets behind beloved Calabrian chillies and Puglia's grapes, before cooking up delicious dishes that celebrate them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>DS Reid arrives to ask Vanessa questions about Todd. Aaron is deeply suspicious about Serena. Robert is struck by a runaway trainer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716193000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Lisa refuses to let Dylan shirk the blame for what happened to Betsy, Kit urges Sarah to get hold of Gary's phone, and Ross and Tracy ignore the naysayers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260716210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase Around the World</title>
    <desc>The Chase Around The World sees Bradley and The Chasers escape the studio and challenge contestants in a bid to win £100,000. First up, it's the eternal city: Rome.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716210500 +0000" stop="20260716213500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News at Ten</title>
    <desc>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716213500 +0000" stop="20260716215000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716215000 +0000" stop="20260716222500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">G'wed</title>
    <desc>Aimee's big theatre debut is upended by family truths, Mia-Louise must choose her footballing future, and the boys' antics run wildly out of control.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716222500 +0000" stop="20260716230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Password</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mangan hosts the word-based gameshow as team captains Daisy May Cooper and Alan Carr play the lively guessing game with contestants Adisa and Jo to win 10,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260716230500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shop on TV</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder in Provence</title>
    <desc>Antoine and Marine investigate a murder at a university and question the professors and students, but they uncover more crimes the further they delve.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260715225000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trial and Retribution</title>
    <desc>The conclusion of this case of the crime drama. When a documentary suggests police misconduct and portrays McCready as innocent, Walker is suspended and takes a trip to Glasgow.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716012500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George and Mildred</title>
    <desc>Domestic sitcom. George's brother Charlie arrives with a document which suggests that Mildred is married to an Army deserter.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716012500 +0000" stop="20260716013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716013000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George and Mildred</title>
    <desc>70s sitcom. Mildred's dreams of a cheap holiday clash with George's political allegiances.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716053500 +0000" stop="20260716060500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George and Mildred</title>
    <desc>Sitcom. When Mildred discovers that George has been writing love letters to another woman, a marriage counsellor is brought in over his refusal to discuss it.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716060500 +0000" stop="20260716063500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Jo is disturbed to learn the extent of Andy's sabotage, Nicola finds herself homeless again, and the Kings remove the last of their belongings from Home Farm.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716063500 +0000" stop="20260716070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Jo leaves to start a new life, Lexi becomes envious of Carl and Chas's close relationship, and Ashley discovers that the church is set to close on Boxing Day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716070500 +0000" stop="20260716074000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Gary and Len keep the Platts' house under observation, and Darryl discovers Dev is buying the kebab shop. Graeme asks Ashley for a job, while Emily offers Jed a place to stay.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716074000 +0000" stop="20260716081000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Hayley tells Roy she is considering going back to Africa, while Amber is furious with Dev for buying the kebab shop and takes revenge by telling Tara about his affair with Nina.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716081000 +0000" stop="20260716102000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Touch of Frost</title>
    <desc>Police drama series. Frost investigates the disappearance of a local environmental health officer, and faces domestic problems with the arrival of a new lodger.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716102000 +0000" stop="20260716112500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series set in a 1960s Yorkshire village. A hit-and-run accident leads to a conflict of interest for Sergeant Craddock.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716112500 +0000" stop="20260716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series set in a 1960s Yorkshire village. Jackie uncovers a case for the police when she represents a man injured in an industrial accident.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716123000 +0000" stop="20260716143500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>When a butterfly collector and founding member of an elite IQ society is found murdered, DCI Barnaby and DS Winter are called upon to catch the culprit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716143500 +0000" stop="20260716154000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Donna and Charlotte break into Shane's flat and decide to question Jasmine about his mysterious disappearance. Andy and Diane are stunned to find Butler's Farm abandoned.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716154000 +0000" stop="20260716161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Amber reveals she is going to visit her mother in Finland, and Becky seeks an assurance that Steve will support her in court.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716161500 +0000" stop="20260716165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Becky makes a difficult decision and Amber walks out on Dev, while Gary Windass is annoyed to discover he did David and Graeme a favour by getting rid of the stolen car.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716165000 +0000" stop="20260716175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Drama. The police are called in when an elderly woman suspects that prowlers are trying to force her off her farm, and Vernon takes up a hot rod racing challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716175500 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Mike and Jackie discover what a handful teenagers can be like when Mike's niece comes to stay, and Vernon plays bodyguard to an emigre Russian prince.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Vera</title>
    <desc>DCI Vera Stanhope investigates the mysterious death of a businessman found floating in the water under the Gateshead Millennium Bridge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716210000 +0000" stop="20260716225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder in Provence</title>
    <desc>Now working as a consultant for the police, Marine helps Antoine and Helene investigate the death of an aristocrat found dead at his crumbling chateau.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260716225000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trial and Retribution</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the discovery of a young woman's skeleton in the yard of what used to be a boarding house in north London.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bullseye</title>
    <desc>Freddie Flintoff hosts a festive special of the classic darts-based game show and is joined by former world champion 'Mighty' Michael van Gerwen for a charity challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Collision</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting action from AEW's newest show, featuring stars including Kyle Fletcher, Kazuchika Okada, Megan Bayne, Tommaso Ciampa and Claudio Castagnoli.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Minder</title>
    <desc>Drama series about the shady dealings of a loveable rogue and his sidekick. Terry is hired out by Arthur to act as a minder for a newsagent who is being threatened.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Champions</title>
    <desc>Fantasy espionage series. When the crew of a nuclear submarine are found dead, the Champions reconstruct its last voyage to find the truth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716023000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorsport Mundial</title>
    <desc>This programme brings you up to date with the latest action from the world of motorsport and features race coverage, insights, and behind-the-scenes footage from the best series.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. Higgins, TC and Rick witness an armed robbery at the King Kamehameha Club, but Thomas's investigation is hampered by their lurid accounts.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Part One: The first part of a two-part episode of the classic US action drama series. Thomas becomes involved in a bizarre situation involving a pair of twins.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716070500 +0000" stop="20260716081000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dempsey and Makepeace</title>
    <desc>Classic detective series. Dempsey shows Makepeace another side of his nature when her best friend is murdered, and the duo also investigate a man's kidnapping.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716081000 +0000" stop="20260716091500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boon</title>
    <desc>Classic drama. Women spell trouble for Ken and Harry when an Irish builder asks Ken to investigate a break-in and theft of cash at his office while Harry moves house.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716091500 +0000" stop="20260716102000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Champions</title>
    <desc>Fantasy espionage series. When the crew of a nuclear submarine are found dead, the Champions reconstruct its last voyage to find the truth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716102000 +0000" stop="20260716112500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BattleBots</title>
    <desc>US robot combat series. An all-star cast of BattleBots' brightest minds go behind the scenes to count down the most outrageous moments in its history.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716112500 +0000" stop="20260716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Part Two: The concluding part of a two-part episode of the classic US action drama series. Thomas is shocked by the arrival of Diane's twin sister.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716123000 +0000" stop="20260716133500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. Thomas reluctantly agrees to help a retired bank robber find the crooks responsible for kidnapping his grandchild.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716133500 +0000" stop="20260716144500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dempsey and Makepeace</title>
    <desc>Classic detective series. Dempsey and Makepeace go downmarket when an isolated petrol station is attacked by masked raiders and a major company is blackmailed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716144500 +0000" stop="20260716155000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boon</title>
    <desc>Classic drama starring Michael Elphick. Ken finds himself being interrogated about a crime he did not commit thanks to a jilted lover and a lying husband.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716155000 +0000" stop="20260716165500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Champions</title>
    <desc>Fantasy espionage series. The Champions are enlisted to help when the body of a top Pentagon official is found in Wales.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716165500 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Minder</title>
    <desc>Drama series about a loveable rogue and his reluctant sidekick. Terry and Arthur meet a Greek Cypriot and become involved in a battle for a Greek restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">River Monsters</title>
    <desc>Extreme fisherman Jeremy Wade takes a trip to Mongolia to investigate a giant fish that is said to be one of the world's strongest fighters on a line.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716183000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">River Monsters</title>
    <desc>Extreme angler Jeremy Wade travels to the Himalayas to investigate a fresh spate of savage river attacks and learns that the suspected culprit is a sacred animal.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sharpe</title>
    <desc>Action-adventure series. Sharpe returns to England with his reputation restored and is ordered to the north of England to command a troublesome local militia force.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716211000 +0000" stop="20260716221000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Motorbike Show</title>
    <desc>Henry Cole enters his first-ever motorbike race and goes training with BSB rider Chris 'The Stalker' Walker before going off-road riding with Dakar Rally competitor Lyndon Poskitt.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260716221000 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Berlin Station</title>
    <desc>Mere hours remain before enemy forces topple the Estonian government. Berlin Station acts alone in a last desperate push to prevent the fall of a nation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260715235500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>A team of five friends from the Wirral get their chance to win a bumper prize by answering a series of Top 10 list questions in the quiz hosted by Warwick Davis.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716005000 +0000" stop="20260716013500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the rapid and ruthless quiz as contestants Bea and Martha, Daniel and Gaz, and Siobhan and Ian take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716013500 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts as Brian, the show's longest-serving wing player, gets his turn to take on the Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Fighting it out this time are sisters Rachel and Carla from Leicester, brothers Sulayman and Aasim from Manchester, and cousins Chelsea and Alain from Northampton and Manchester.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Warwick Davis hosts as a team of five get their chance to win a bumper cash prize by answering Top 10 list questions, but can they take home 125,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Wants to Be a Millionaire</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Clarkson hosts as six more players go head-to-head for a place in the Millionaire chair - 15 correct answers is all they need to win the ultimate prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Riddiculous</title>
    <desc>Ranvir Singh hosts the rapid-fire quiz as contestants Stephanie and Jill, Hussein and Alex, and Holly and Ben take on Riddlemaster Henry Lewis in a bid to solve his riddles.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts as Brian H gets his chance to open the iconic red boxes and goes up against the Banker in a bid to take home a huge cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Looking to Lingo all the way this time are couple Michelle and Callum from Aberdeen, pals Chris and Mark from Gateshead, and neighbours Lindsay and Jordan from Shropshire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Fighting it out this time are married couple Daphne and Peter from Bognor Regis, neighbours Sarah and Sarah from Wales, and mates Charlie and Paige from Reading.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Working out words this time are two married couples - Londoners Nestor and Andrew, and John and Sue from Liverpool - plus sisters Meg and Holly from Bolton and Chesterfield.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260716210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Wants to Be a Millionaire</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Clarkson hosts the quiz as the Millionaire chair, 15 questions and four lifelines are all that stand between six hopeful contestants and one million pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716210000 +0000" stop="20260716220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716220000 +0000" stop="20260716230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716230000 +0000" stop="20260716235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260716235500 +0000" stop="20260717000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Warwick Davis hosts as a team of five get their chance to win a bumper cash prize by answering Top 10 list questions, but can they take home 125,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>When talk show host Bobby Mann (Tom Bergeron) mysteriously dies, Castle is convinced that there was foul play; a guest on Bobby Mann's show (Kelly Carlson) seduces Castle.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>The team tries to find a witness to the contract killing of a woman outside a nightclub; Jane puts herself in the line of fire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>The team's skills are tested when the mummified remains of a woman are found; Jane tries to recover from a devastating loss.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>The team helps Korsak investigate a cold case; Jane refuses to believe that she is not ready to go back on duty.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>Jane and Maura find a man who died in a bathtub full of ice; while trying to stay cool during a heatwave, Angela discovers a spicy tea that brings unexpected romantic consequences.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716020300 +0000" stop="20260716030300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A notable county prosecutor is arrested for murder; when Angela hears that Maura is planning to meet Jack's daughter, she sets out to educate Maura about the interests of children today.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716030300 +0000" stop="20260716040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>After Jane jumps from a bridge to save a prosecutor, Maura worries that she has lost her best friend; Angie enlists Frankie's help to apply for new jobs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716040100 +0000" stop="20260716050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>The team helps Korsak investigate a cold case; Jane refuses to believe that she is not ready to go back on duty.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716050100 +0000" stop="20260716060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>Jane and Maura find a man who died in a bathtub full of ice; while trying to stay cool during a heatwave, Angela discovers a spicy tea that brings unexpected romantic consequences.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716060400 +0000" stop="20260716070400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A notable county prosecutor is arrested for murder; when Angela hears that Maura is planning to meet Jack's daughter, she sets out to educate Maura about the interests of children today.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716070400 +0000" stop="20260716080200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>After Jane jumps from a bridge to save a prosecutor, Maura worries that she has lost her best friend; Angie enlists Frankie's help to apply for new jobs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716080200 +0000" stop="20260716083200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716083200 +0000" stop="20260716090200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716090200 +0000" stop="20260716093200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716093200 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Jeremiah</title>
    <desc>In this weekly program, Dr. David Jeremiah delivers practical messages to the congregation at the Shadow Mountain Community Church in San Diego. Also featured is music from the Shadow Mountain Community Church Choir and Orchestra, as well as performances by musical guests that have included Steve Green and Charles Billingsley. Men and women who have been impacted by the Turning Point ministry also</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Creflo Dollar</title>
    <desc>Dr. Creflo Dollar ministers to people from all backgrounds with hopes for change; Creflo helps viewers find ways to renew their faith, mind, and spirit; based on the belief that the Bible is the written and inspired Word of God, the show is meant to invoke change in the lives of people across the globe; Creflo and his wife, Taffi, share their vision for everyone to hear the Word and gain understan</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Today</title>
    <desc>James Robison was a former preacher who changed directions in his life and began hosting this television show alongside his wife, Betty, in order to reach out to help more people. This daily religious and self-help program welcomes guests who tell how they have successfully overcome difficulties in their lives by following God's word -- with the hope of encouraging others to do the same and look t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joyce Meyer Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Noted for her humanitarian ministry efforts to aid suffering people around the world, Bible teacher Joyce Meyer reaches out to both Christians and non-Christians as she illustrates how to make each day better by applying biblical principles to every activity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716113000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Military Makeover</title>
    <desc>Purple Heart Homes shines a well-deserved spotlight on our dedicated Volunteers. Learn about financial and disability services to help all veterans. Matthew reignites his love for power sports and Luna gets pup-worthy pampering.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Vanished in an Instant</title>
    <desc>Megan's teenage daughter, Whitney, disappears after their car breaks down at a gas station. As a shadowy figure traps Whitney in a deadly game of survival, Megan scrambles to uncover the truth before she's lost forever.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Behind Closed Doors</title>
    <desc>A murder suspect on the run forces his way into Morgan's home and holds her family captive. She does everything she can to keep them safe, but it seems his arrival at her door may not have been so random after all.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Tim receives a strange message, launching a larger investigation into the dark web; Celina works to take down a popular podcast; Miles helps update the department's training videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Documentary filmmakers interview the LAPD on a complicated missing person's case connected to John.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>The team has mixed feelings when a familiar face returns hoping to prove himself; an influencer gets his fans to come after Wesley; Tim supports Lucy as she prepares for the sergeant's exam.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>Castle and Beckett find that Esposito has a personal connection to a suspected killer; Beckett connects with an attractive new detective.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260716210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Castle</title>
    <desc>A well-known chef is found frozen to death in the kitchen of a New York restaurant; Castle shares an attraction with a former classmate of Beckett's.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260715210500 +0000" stop="20260715213500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Island: The Debrief</title>
    <desc>Your daily drop of hot Love Island tea, and all the Villa gossip. With Shakira Khan, Toni Laites and Yasmin Pettet, nothing is off-topic or out of the question.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260715213500 +0000" stop="20260715220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Bango Was His Name Oh! Part 2: Animated comedy about family life. Stewie and Brian visit San Francisco to look for a man that Stewie believes is his real father.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260715220500 +0000" stop="20260715223500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy about family life. After reading an erotic novel, Peter gets the idea to write one himself. Carter is sued for publishing Peter's book on tape.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260715223500 +0000" stop="20260715230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Stan is seeking a promotion at work, but he faces convincing the dictator of Isla Island to sign a treaty in order to promote his case.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260715230500 +0000" stop="20260715233500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated series about bumbling CIA man Stan Smith. Steve is teased at school about the back brace he has to wear, so Stan reveals that he wears a wig to cover his baldness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260715233500 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. When Linda takes to caring for an injured raccoon, she makes a mistake during a neighbourhood block party that could endanger its life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716000500 +0000" stop="20260716003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. Gene tries to remember a perfect song that he wrote in his sleep, and Louise and Tina try to catch a cricket that is keeping Linda up at night.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716003000 +0000" stop="20260716005500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Transaction</title>
    <desc>Lively sitcom. When Liv reveals a terrible secret, the team must lie their way through to midnight at a fancy New Year's Eve gala before Liv's shame is unveiled.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716005500 +0000" stop="20260716012500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Piglets</title>
    <desc>Sitcom. B Group learn how to restrain awkward suspects, but Danni feeling strangely sensitive makes things potentially embarrassing when physical contact is required.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716012500 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716052500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Farm-to-Table: Home improvement programme. Brian and Sarah make a couple's dreams come true with a vegetable garden, a dining room, a BBQ zone and a play space.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716052500 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join Stephen Mulhern for the game show with only one question as Monz gets to open the red boxes and tries to beat the Banker.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716072500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dress to Impress</title>
    <desc>Connor, otherwise known to many as Mr Wigan, is hoping to be impressed by the style choices of three potential suitors in Manchester.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716072500 +0000" stop="20260716082500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Georgia and Tommy: Baby Steps</title>
    <desc>As Georgia and Tommy prepare to celebrate their ninth anniversary as a couple, Georgia confides in her friend Lydia about how she really feels about marrying Tommy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716082500 +0000" stop="20260716092500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Only Way is Essex</title>
    <desc>Gatsby finds out about Courtney's allegation that he was texting girls behind Dani's back. Diags is determined to give his world record attempt another try.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716092500 +0000" stop="20260716101500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Salt Lake City</title>
    <desc>An RV girls' trip descends into chaos as Bronwyn spreads rumours about Lisa's business, Britani confronts Whitney, and Heather and Bronwyn feud.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716101500 +0000" stop="20260716111000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Orange County</title>
    <desc>Reality show. The reunion continues with Jenn questioning her rocky friendship with Tamra and Emily addressing Heather about the fashion show.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716111000 +0000" stop="20260716121000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dinner Date</title>
    <desc>Christian from Leicester is going to be given five menus, each put together by a potential blind date.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716121000 +0000" stop="20260716131000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Supermarket Sweep</title>
    <desc>Rylan Clark-Neal hosts a revamp of the iconic game show as three pairs of shoppers go wild in the aisles and compete to win a 3,000-pound prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716131000 +0000" stop="20260716141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Floor US</title>
    <desc>Rob Lowe hosts the fast-paced game show. Contestants test their knowledge of natural history, Real Housewives, space travel, TV chefs and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716141000 +0000" stop="20260716151000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Only Way is Essex</title>
    <desc>Chloe Sims has made her life drama-free, but there's just one loose end she needs to tie up - finding closure with Pete. Dan gives Gatsby a lesson in anger management.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716151000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Salt Lake City</title>
    <desc>Lisa returns to confront Angie and Bronwyn over the gossip about her legal and business issues, while old friendships are cautiously tested and repaired. S6 Ep.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Orange County</title>
    <desc>Reality show. The reunion concludes with a heated face-off between Shannon and Alexis and unseen footage of John Janssen's interview.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mulhern hosts a celebrity special of the classic game show with Kadeena Cox, Adam James, and Ellie Taylor all trying to guess well-known phrases in aid of charity.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Floor US</title>
    <desc>Rob Lowe hosts the fast-paced game show. Contestants test their knowledge of pasta, crayon colours, Tony Award winners, and hunting and camping.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Abby returns from Hollywood to find that many of her dancers have been slacking; the mothers make a pact to turn down Abby's invitation for their daughters to perform on national television; Abby pits Maddie against Chloe.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Abby is nervous about the annual Abby Lee Dance Company recital; Kelly is upset when Abby assigns Paige the only new solo for the recital; the girls compete to appear on the cover of a dance magazine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Abby gets a tip that her dancers will be competing against Cathy's dancers, so she creates three new dances in order to win; Kelly, Brooke and Paige have not shown up; Abby punishes Maddie by taking away her solo.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Abby receives the remains of her beloved dog, Broadway Baby; Kelly secretly meets with the mothers; Maddie's star continues to fall, while Nia's is on the rise.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Kelly sneaks her children back into Abby Lee Dance Company; Brooke's return threatens Payton's position on the team; Maddie helps to make a girl's dream come true.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women: LA</title>
    <desc>The women try to pick up the pieces of their friendship after a nasty brawl; Christy, Briana and Lila bring the girls together for a race, and wind up insulting Terra and Tonya; Lila throws a cocktail party to make peace.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women: LA</title>
    <desc>Terra treats the gang to a weekend on Catalina Island; the ladies go zip lining and later reward themselves with a fancy dinner in town; Lila lashes out at each of the girls.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Abby receives the remains of her beloved dog, Broadway Baby; Kelly secretly meets with the mothers; Maddie's star continues to fall, while Nia's is on the rise.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dance Moms</title>
    <desc>Kelly sneaks her children back into Abby Lee Dance Company; Brooke's return threatens Payton's position on the team; Maddie helps to make a girl's dream come true.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women: LA</title>
    <desc>The women try to pick up the pieces of their friendship after a nasty brawl; Christy, Briana and Lila bring the girls together for a race, and wind up insulting Terra and Tonya; Lila throws a cocktail party to make peace.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Women: LA</title>
    <desc>Terra treats the gang to a weekend on Catalina Island; the ladies go zip lining and later reward themselves with a fancy dinner in town; Lila lashes out at each of the girls.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pain Relief Revealed</title>
    <desc>Discover the hidden story of OmegaXL with John Walsh. He dives deep into the groundbreaking supplement that promises hope and relief for millions battling joint pain and inflammation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A father who is also a doctor tests the staff's patience; third-time parents hope to deliver a girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>An unplanned pregnancy forces a young father to learn how to be supportive; a mother endures a painful delivery without the help of an epidural.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>Mothers must decide how they would like to manage labor pains.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A loving couple must face a caesarian section; two teenagers cram for the test of parenthood; a first time mother tries to joke her way through labor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>Complications in labor and delivery; a woman who is pregnant with twins from two different fathers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A military family prepares for delivery; a woman with three boys at home hopes her baby is a girl; a newlywed couple is expecting their first child.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>A woman forgets her birth plan at home; a mother of four boys hopes her next child is a girl; a surrogate mother gives birth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Born Every Minute</title>
    <desc>Two sportscasters make their first attempt at parenthood; a couple prepares for twins; a first-time mother experiences fear.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Child Genius: Battle of the Brightest</title>
    <desc>In the first week of the competition, 12 children contend with topics including math and memory.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose, Blanche and Dorothy take a vacation at a resort that doesn't live up to its reputation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Dressing up a bedraggled toy lamb with Amanda and Julie; Dom and Brenton get a cool Uruguayan kitchen gadget turning again; Mark unsticks a vintage music machine for a man who's keen to hear his grandmother's tunes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Travelling Auctioneers</title>
    <desc>Will Kirk and Christina Trevanion take their mobile auction house on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop: On the Road</title>
    <desc>The Repair Shop experts are off on a road trip across the UK fixing historical treasures and precious objects that cannot be brought to the barn.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Antiques Roadshow</title>
    <desc>Animals abound with fish teapots, bear umbrella stands and horse pictures.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop: On the Road</title>
    <desc>The Repair Shop experts are off on a road trip across the UK fixing historical treasures and precious objects that cannot be brought to the barn.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose, Blanche and Dorothy take a vacation at a resort that doesn't live up to its reputation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba learns she will be spending Christmas Eve alone; Cheyenne and Van try to start a holiday tradition, but their plan backfires.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Dressing up a bedraggled toy lamb with Amanda and Julie; Dom and Brenton get a cool Uruguayan kitchen gadget turning again; Mark unsticks a vintage music machine for a man who's keen to hear his grandmother's tunes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Travelling Auctioneers</title>
    <desc>Will Kirk and Christina Trevanion take their mobile auction house on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Craftsmen pool their talents and resources to restore heirlooms and treasured antiques such as music boxes, vases and clocks to prove that anything can be restored to their former glory.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes 911</title>
    <desc>Mike and the Make It Right crew start a new home that was left half done by a contractor, finding all sorts of problems hiding behind the walls; Michael and designer Kimm go shopping for flooring with some furry friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Park for All Seasons</title>
    <desc>The Gulf Island National Park sits between the development of Vancouver Island and British Columbia.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716113000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Park for All Seasons</title>
    <desc>The remote Auyuittuq National Park is home to polar bears, glaciers and Mount Thor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Below Zero Canada</title>
    <desc>In search of a steady supply of dog food, Becky and family establish a Fish Camp on Great Slave Lake; Kim and Pierre work on a new shelter; Bentley and newcomer Jon Grenier attempt to secure essential sources of meat before winter sets in.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Scenic River Journeys</title>
    <desc>Bill Nighy leads a magical journey in the Norfolk Broads along England's holiday river, the River Bure; discovering a watery world where both wildlife and recreation go hand in hand.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blown Away</title>
    <desc>The artists design sculptures that celebrate what they wanted to be when they were kids, with pieces inspired by botanists, stunt performers and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716143000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blown Away</title>
    <desc>The glassblowers take cues from natural wonders with vivid, gravity-defying installations while working in teams.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>While Dorothy is laid off from teaching, she finds work at the same museum where Blanche goes to work.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716153000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Everyone takes turns in front of the camera to create a video family album for Cheyenne's baby, Elizabeth.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes 911</title>
    <desc>Mike and the Make It Right crew start a new home that was left half done by a contractor, finding all sorts of problems hiding behind the walls; Michael and designer Kimm go shopping for flooring with some furry friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Observing Julyan's delicate surgery on a ukulele that helped a man court his future bride; Amanda and Julie make over a lipstick-stained plaything; Steve goes out of his comfort zone to fix a 1960s split-flap clock that won't flip.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The crew is trapped aboard the ship with a terrifying alien creature.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include an officer stuck on a fence, the return of the T. rex and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260715223000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include quarrelling newlyweds, an ejecting dish tray and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Marvel</title>
    <desc>Kevin Feige assembles his team and maps out the road to the Avengers; Marvel must figure out how to integrate Thor into the world of Iron Man, as well as creating a worthy villain.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Jerry feels betrayed when his method of pleasing a woman is used on Elaine by a friend (Patrick Warburton).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716003000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Jerry plans to meet a supermodel at an airport lounge; Mr. Pitt tells Elaine he has mentioned her in his will; George tries to prove he isn't racist; Kramer gambles with a Texan.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>The Flanders rent their rumpus room to a pair of college-age women who use it to run a soft-core webcam, making Ned so embarrassed that he moves his family to Humble, Pa.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716013000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The crew is trapped aboard the ship with a terrifying alien creature.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716023000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fear Factor USA</title>
    <desc>Contestants swap revolting lumps of so-called food, then devour their final gift; players must swim underwater in a lake of fire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>The Flanders rent their rumpus room to a pair of college-age women who use it to run a soft-core webcam, making Ned so embarrassed that he moves his family to Humble, Pa.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716043000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The crew is trapped aboard the ship with a terrifying alien creature.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Marvel</title>
    <desc>Kevin Feige assembles his team and maps out the road to the Avengers; Marvel must figure out how to integrate Thor into the world of Iron Man, as well as creating a worthy villain.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>We gawk at a man with all-powerful feet on his day at the beach, and enjoy a temperamental ventriloquist who speaks through a cheese sandwich.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>We catch clumsy high-divers making a big splash by the pool, blow bubbles and swim with some outrageous ocean life below the surface.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Video clips from the pet world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Video clips from the pet world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fear Factor USA</title>
    <desc>Contestants swap revolting lumps of so-called food, then devour their final gift; players must swim underwater in a lake of fire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Features pranks such as glued fruits and fake manicure.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include whipped cream coming out of ears, Jesus resurrecting a trout, and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic Debra DiGiovanni performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716113000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Many Canadian performers and writers, make inroads in the comedy world by appearing on this star-making stand-up series.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comic Nick Beaton performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Grandmother Rose, who's 80, has fluid on her lungs and is having trouble breathing, and 55-year-old trucker Kevin has serious injuries after his lorry rolled down a verge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260715220500 +0000" stop="20260715231000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Neil is flown in by helicopter after a head-on road collision, and Matias needs help after trapping his hands in a train door and being dragged along the platform.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260715231000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">999: On the Front Line</title>
    <desc>Paramedics are called to a man who's bleeding from his ears, a woman who's recently had bowel surgery and is losing blood, and an eight-month-old with a fever.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716001500 +0000" stop="20260716012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Grandmother Rose, who's 80, has fluid on her lungs and is having trouble breathing, and 55-year-old trucker Kevin has serious injuries after his lorry rolled down a verge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716012000 +0000" stop="20260716022500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Neil is flown in by helicopter after a head-on road collision, and Matias needs help after trapping his hands in a train door and being dragged along the platform.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716022500 +0000" stop="20260716025500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Place in the Sun</title>
    <desc>Ben Hillman house-hunts around Gran Alacant on the Costa Blanca with Mick and Dianne from Newcastle. With a £120,000 budget, the couple are ready to make a permanent move to the sun.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716025500 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716075500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discover Must Have Ideas: Shopping</title>
    <desc>Discover the very latest must-haves for your home and garden with Must Have Ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716075500 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heir Hunters</title>
    <desc>A sole heir is discovered on a valuable treasury case worth almost half a million pounds. Can the hunters beat the other firms to sign him up and break the news of the windfall.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The first visit is to the Oxenham Arms in Devon, where Simon and Lyn help their guests brush up on the local pastime of broom dancing. But one guest's feedback has the hosts vowing revenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716093500 +0000" stop="20260716100500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>John Brady likes to stand out from the crowd in Liverpool with his unique B&amp;B, Elegant House. But his eclectic style and alternative breakfast aren't to everyone's taste.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716100500 +0000" stop="20260716103500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Peter and Amanda introduce their guests to the world of glamping at Hidden Valley Yurts in Monmouthshire. But the shared bathroom facilities and DIY breakfast aren't to everyone's taste.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716103500 +0000" stop="20260716111000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>David and Nikki host the final visit at Cley Hall Hotel in Spalding, Lincolnshire. But there's clock-watching at breakfast, and some of the guests' comments leave the hosts fuming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716111000 +0000" stop="20260716114000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time to discover how much they've been paid and confront their critics, before the winner is announced.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716114000 +0000" stop="20260716121000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Enthusiastic business consultant James plans a complex Italian menu, a 1960s Italian dress code and a fun photoshoot. But he spends most of the night in the kitchen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716121000 +0000" stop="20260716124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Former mental health nurse Ronnie Imlah shocks her guests with a revelation about her past, and guests JP and Amanda don't see eye to eye over plastic surgery.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716124000 +0000" stop="20260716131500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>JP Goodyear-Martinez treats his guests to Jamaican food, on a night of wacky wigs, alarming Lycra outfits and a hula-hooping drag queen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716131500 +0000" stop="20260716135000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Football coach and first-time cook Tim Travers plans an American menu, with his mum on the other end of the phone to help him every step of the way.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716135000 +0000" stop="20260716142000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>There are high hopes for recruitment consultant Amanda's sophisticated evening. But an accident at the table has her guests in hysterics.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716142000 +0000" stop="20260716145000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The competition kicks off at The Unicorn Inn in Ludlow, where Zoe and Lee hope that their glamorous, fairy-tale rooms will become the stuff of legend. And Zoe wows the guests at breakfast.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716145000 +0000" stop="20260716152000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The second visit is to the East Walls Hotel in Chichester, which owners Celia and Damon describe as 'bespoke'. Their guests go crazy for the continental, but there's loo brush controversy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716152000 +0000" stop="20260716155000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>There's toilet brush controversy for the second time in the week. And the battle of the bangers continues, as ambitious Jake and Chris welcome their rivals to The Wheatsheaf in Cheshire.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716155000 +0000" stop="20260716162000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The final visit is to Shawries Hotel in Blackpool, run by Allison and Dave. The décor takes Jake and Chris back to their childhood, but Celia and Damon aren't fans of the 1980s look.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716162000 +0000" stop="20260716165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time. After strong opinions are aired and differences debated, the winner is announced.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716165000 +0000" stop="20260716175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">George Clarke's Old House New Home</title>
    <desc>Up a long garden path in Leeds lies a Victorian villa that's been a labour of love for Jawad and Charlie. And in Brixton, George hopes for a clean sweep with a redundant chimney.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260716175500 +0000" stop="20260716185500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Location, Location, Location</title>
    <desc>Kirstie and Phil head to South Wales to help Chris and Laura, who want to get out of their Bristol rental, and Bob and Lara, who've been outbid 10 times in competitive Cardiff.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon and Amy visit Penny and Leonard after the holidays and tell them about their terrible trip to Texas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Penny thinks Leonard is taking her for granted and decides to go on a spa weekend with Amy; Wolowitz and Koothrappali try to fix a squeaky floorboard in the baby's room.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260715223000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon tests an MIT invention after hearing it can help him read people's emotions; Leonard finds out Penny's brother is coming to town; Raj asks his ex-girlfriends to give him dating advice.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Andy drives across the country to get Erin; Nellie shows up and tries to claim the manager position.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Robert forces the office to throw a welcome party for Nellie; Erin helps Andy practice how he will break up with Jessica.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>After returning from his romantic quest, Andy battles with Nellie for the manager's chair; Kelly has a difficult time choosing between Ryan and a perfect man (Sendhil Ramamurthy).</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716003000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Andy crashes a fundraiser and ends up adopting 12 dogs; Dwight learns that an auction winner loses money; Nellie learns how to eat a taco.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Andy tries to jumpstart his comeback; after Robert drunkenly shuts down a local branch, Jim and Dwight join forces in hope of outsmarting a salesman.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716013000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>A former boss helps Andy go undercover and stage a coup; a new opportunity arises for Robert.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Two new, young employees throw Dwight and Jim off balance; Andy returns from leadership training with a desire for revenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716023000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>A toast at Roy's wedding leads to Pam and Jim searching their relationships for buried secrets; Dwight reacts to Nellie's mandatory charity initiative.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>As Andy flaunts a discovery he made about his ancestry, Darryl struggles in his new role; Dwight teaches a language to Erin, who wants to impress her boyfriend's educated family; Jim reveals a secret.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716033000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>When Jim convinces Dwight the building is unsafe, Dwight rents a bus to use as his office; Nellie asks for Andy's help; Jim uses pie to cheer Pam.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Andy invites his old a cappella group to perform for Halloween, which leads to a confrontation with his frenemy; Dwight tries to track down a madman in the office; Jim and Pam fight over his new job.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716043000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office</title>
    <desc>Andy must step up when his dad loses all his family's money; when Dwight is a guest on a radio show, his co-workers call in to torture him; Kevin learns a secret about Oscar.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Big Black; "Makeshift Thrill Rides"; "Bieber Hair"; "Coming in Hot"; human scorpions; spider.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get swept off their feet in "Gettin' Tableclothed," celebrate over nothing in "Bored to Cheers," and vacation with some "All-Inclusive Pain.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>B. Simone lends a spot to people who are "Gym Dumb" and get a first-hand look out the windshield with "Dashcam Diaries.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo battle extreme weather in "Hail No", witness major leaks in "Busted Pipes" and have a bit of fun at work with some "Office Pranks.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Post Malone; "Really White Iversons"; "Saucin' on You"; "Knuckle Tats.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo avert their eyes from some "Fedora Freakiness," listen to the pain sounds of "Owgasms," and learn why you "Don't Feed the Animals.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood fail to juggle with Juggle Struggles; hanging with tiny party animals in Born to Party; witnessing some sisterly spite in Sister Attacks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood check out unskilled thieves who are Shoplifting, watching people fight with Random Weaponry and seeing a collective brain fart in Vocab Lapse.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood figure out their all terrain boat of choice in "Land Kayaking"; finding out all the ways a kid can get stuck in "Toddler Traps"; meeting inattentive folks in "Spa.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo do some spring cleaning with "Mr. Cleans," discover that athletic ability is genetic in "Momletes," and realize they know nothing about cars in "Auto Ignorant.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tattoo Fixers</title>
    <desc>The artists cover Zoe's tattoo dedicated to her favourite food, Sean's lewd leprechaun that his wife wants rid of, and Chantal's pop portrait that looks like a famous footballer.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Geordie Shore: From The Beginning</title>
    <desc>The gang return from Prague to a turbulent Toon. The house is in total meltdown as Charlotte and Gary finally come to blows, and it looks like it could be the end for Vicky and Ricci.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood are totally 'not into it', taste some 'fail fries' and get a little 'too close to the action'.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>On this episode of Ridiculousness, Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood take a foul in 'ref down', fail to achieve 'crew coordination' and see which couples are 'worse together'.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master: Master vs Apprentice</title>
    <desc>Professional football players call the shots in the elimination tattoo, knocking the Artists off their game. Superfans get inked with permanent autographs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master: Master vs Apprentice</title>
    <desc>With a spot in the top four on the line, loyalties are put to the test. Artists feel the pressure when they must tattoo portraits on active military and their loved ones.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716014500 +0000" stop="20260716021000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>One of Ink Master's most divine Artists returns with three unhappy Canvases. Can he achieve redemption or will his dark side prevail.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716021000 +0000" stop="20260716023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Veteran artists Dave Clarke and E.S. return to the Ink Master shop looking for another shot at Redemption.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716023500 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just Tattoo Of Us USA</title>
    <desc>Bitter exes throw down their baggage in an all-out ink war, and a couple airs its dirty laundry when a girlfriend tries to lock down her man, who counters with an ultimatum.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Cribs</title>
    <desc>Meet twins Allayla and Ciara as they take us on a tour of their Saratoga, New York, house of fun. Then jet over to the west coast farm that Connery calls home.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716052000 +0000" stop="20260716061000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>Arianna from Georgia was your typical high school girl. After becoming pregnant with Maurice's child, the two began fighting. Maurice eventually steps up but will Arianna forgive him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716061000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bar Rescue</title>
    <desc>Jon Taffer sends his long-time expert, Phil Wills to lead the rescue of a bar in San Marcos, California that is suffering from an identity crisis.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>It's time to announce the DCC squad but first Kelli and Judy put the candidates through a final field rehearsal at Cowboys Stadium.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Kailani has fallen for Sam, her gay friend's online ex-boyfriend. Sam claims to love Kailani, but has been acting strange since she has tried to meet up with him. Nev and Max investigate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Solana wants to take her relationship with her boyfriend to the next level but she can't stop thinking about her online love Elijah. But Solana has to know if the online persona is real.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>When Jay met Vegas girl Anna, he thought he had hit the jackpot! Before he can cash in his chips, Nev and Kamie find that Anna may hold secrets that could place her across the globe.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Since Leuh saw surfer Justin it's been insta-love. But after two failed attempts to meet up, she wants to know if he's the man of her dreams or is she one in a long line of online lovers.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>The Scorpions perform acoustically in Athens, Greece; songs include "Sting in the Tail," "Rock You Like a Hurricane," and "Wind of Change.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kings of Leon: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The band performs in Denmark; songs include "On Call," "Fans," and "Knocked Up.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gnarls Barkley: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The group performs in Denmark; songs include "Crazy," "Smiley Faces," and "Going On.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716180000 +0000" stop="20260716190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716190000 +0000" stop="20260716200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Streets: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The band performs in Denmark; songs include "Fit But You Know It," "Dry Your Eyes," and "Could Be Well In.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716200000 +0000" stop="20260716210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kings of Leon: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The band performs in Denmark; songs include "On Call," "Fans," and "Knocked Up.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260716210000 +0000" stop="20260716220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gnarls Barkley: Live at Roskilde Festival '08</title>
    <desc>The group performs in Denmark; songs include "Crazy," "Smiley Faces," and "Going On.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Featuring the short films: "Red Wine," "No Cap," "Love Letter to Savannah," and "Momma.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>Lynae Vanee breaks down top headlines from her distinct perspective and lived experience.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Internationally Known</title>
    <desc>Highlighting emerging artists and the top hits in Africa, Latin America, the U.K., and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Mike Majlak, JayKindaFunny, and NLE Choppa take their shots in the 3-point contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Featuring the short films: "Red Wine," "No Cap," "Love Letter to Savannah," and "Momma.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Summer Walker</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Summer Walker with her latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716013000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Sexyy Red</title>
    <desc>Paying a tribute to Sexyy Red with her music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Atlanta legends DJ Scream and Big Bank welcome the biggest names in hip hop culture for unfiltered conversations you won't hear anywhere else.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Carl Strong; Adele Givens; Cortez W. Jackson (Cortez); Dave Edwards.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716033000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Reynaldo Rey; Eddie Griffin; Darcel Blagmon (Fat Doctor); Arceneaux &amp; Mitchell.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A mix of the best hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos, from the hottest new releases to favorite throwbacks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Atlanta legends DJ Scream and Big Bank welcome the biggest names in hip hop culture for unfiltered conversations you won't hear anywhere else.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Carl Strong; Adele Givens; Cortez W. Jackson (Cortez); Dave Edwards.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Reynaldo Rey; Eddie Griffin; Darcel Blagmon (Fat Doctor); Arceneaux &amp; Mitchell.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Atlanta legends Big Bank and DJ Scream welcome the biggest names in hip-hop culture for unfiltered conversations.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Joey Bada$$</title>
    <desc>Paying tribute to Joey Bada$$ with his recent music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Kali Uchis</title>
    <desc>Paying a tribute to Kali Uchis with her music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Don Toliver</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Don Toliver with his latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Summer Walker</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Summer Walker with her latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260716163000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Sexyy Red</title>
    <desc>Paying a tribute to Sexyy Red with her music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>After a year and a half of chatting with her online, Tyler thinks he may have a future with Amanda; Amanda may not be a girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>When a woman's friend urges her to sign up for a dating website, Nev and Max become suspicious of the love of her life.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Sunny, a nursing student, is in love with the man of her dreams; Jamison is a model, a TV writer, and also studying to be an anesthesiologist; Sunny and Jamison have never met.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>A man cannot escape his online ex, whose stalking has caused his real girlfriend to break up with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Nev and Max receive a request to help track down a missing online love, and they discover the involvement of a former catfish.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>After meeting in a chat room seven years ago, a woman is eager to find someone before they disappear.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) must prove his love for Fancy (Garcelle Beauvais) when her well-to-do parents (guest stars Billy Davis Jr. and Marilyn McCoo) come to town.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716033000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie is afraid of Fancy's reaction when he secretly woos the company's top client, a beautiful young woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) accepts delivery of Fancy's (Garcelle Beauvais) new BMW convertible and takes it out for a spin with his friends (guest stars Alex Thomas, Chris Spencer, Vibe and Suli McCullough). Traci Bingham also guest stars.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716043000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jamie Foxx Show</title>
    <desc>Jamie (Jamie Foxx) encourages Fancy (Garcelle Beauvais) to stand up for herself when she is pressured into throwing a bridal shower.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>Will and Lisa discuss spending more time with their friends, but end up at the same party after lying about their plans.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>Will is shot by a robber and Carlton is traumatized, reacting excessively; Will asks Lisa to marry him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>As Will recuperates, Lisa agonizes over his marriage proposal.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716063000 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air</title>
    <desc>Will and Lisa meet the bickering George and Louise Jefferson when they attend couples' counseling.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Dee (Shawn Wayans, Anna Maria Horsford) get together at a concert by Missy "Misdemeanor" Elliott, for dancing and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn (Shawn Wayans) suspects Marlon's (Marlon Wayans) new movie-star friend is having a bad influence on his brother.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon is drugged and chained by a woman claiming to be his biggest fan.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon's (Marlon Wayans) family must rescue him when he falls in with a cult after signing up for a class.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Pops and the boys learn the real meaning of Christmas when they visit rural relatives living in poverty.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn agrees to marry a woman who needs a husband to avoid deportation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>A beef between the roomies is upstaged only by an unforgettable talent show hosted by Vinny Guadagnino, featuring an out of this world performance by Snooki, and a speech from Angelina that gives new meaning to the word "bombing.".</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>With the trip coming to an end, Snooki's left to clean up the mess made by Dren; Mike plans a second gender reveal even though everyone knows he's having a boy; Angelina "accidentally" shoots off a gender reveal powder cannon in her husband's face.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>The new year means new beginnings; Pauly returns to touring; the arrival of Deena's Baby Meatball #2 approaches; Mike prepares to officially become Big Daddy Sitch, but what happens next still catches everyone by surprise.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>No longer pregnant, Deena has a meatball day with Snooki; Vinny is no longer bi-coastal, Angelina is fed up, and Mike is struggling as he awaits the moment he can bring Baby Romeo home from the hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Vinny's realizes there's no place like home, Mike swaps out the prosciutto for placenta, and a rumor wreaks havoc on the girls' big West Coast trip.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5:30</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 6</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260715223000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>In a classic game-show version of "Hangman," contestants solve word puzzles for cash and prizes.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>Dr. Charles grapples with his own mental health following a harrowing experience working the suicide prevention line.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>While in the field, Violet and Novak are thrust into a dangerous and rapidly escalating situation, forcing them to rely on their instincts to protect both themselves and a vulnerable patient.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Torres investigates the conspiracy surrounding the Morgan case, leading Intelligence into a tangled web of secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716033400 +0000" stop="20260716043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Zendaya; actress Chrissy Metz.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716043700 +0000" stop="20260716053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Jon Bernthal; actress Stephanie Hsu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716053700 +0000" stop="20260716061200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716061200 +0000" stop="20260716070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Top Story With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Reporting of breaking news and developing stories in real time.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716070000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A murder case considered closed by North Dakota detectives is suddenly reopened when a confidential informant comes forward with a tip about an unlikely suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 430A</title>
    <desc>Early morning news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Actors Anne Hathaway and Tom Holland ("The Odyssey"); author Jay Shetty; Adam Lambert performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live with Kelly and Mark</title>
    <desc>Molly Shannon and Meg Stalter are here.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>Skin health with Dr. Saranya Wyles; actor Jake Johnson; shopping expert Adrianna Brach; summer road trip ice cream flavors with Jamila Robinson.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>The cast of "The Hawk"; Today Food with Mika Leon; Adam Lambert performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the local news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716163000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260716170000 +0000" stop="20260716180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "In My Head"; Jamie Lee Curtis; Josh Groban; Jo Koy and Gabriel Iglesias; Simon Baker; "Murder, She Wrote" Festival; Waylon Wyatt performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 3pm</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260715223000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 4pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 5pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC 4 News at 6pm</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716013000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 7 PM</title>
    <desc>The latest in local breaking news, weather reports and feature stories covering the vast Southern California region.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716023000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>"The Odyssey" New York City red carpet premiere and cast interviews; summer beauty glam on-the-go.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>Dr. Charles grapples with his own mental health following a harrowing experience working the suicide prevention line.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>While in the field, Violet and Novak are thrust into a dangerous and rapidly escalating situation, forcing them to rely on their instincts to protect both themselves and a vulnerable patient.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Torres investigates the conspiracy surrounding the Morgan case, leading Intelligence into a tangled web of secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716063400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716063400 +0000" stop="20260716073700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Zendaya; actress Chrissy Metz.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716073700 +0000" stop="20260716083700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Jon Bernthal; actress Stephanie Hsu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716083700 +0000" stop="20260716090700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716090700 +0000" stop="20260716093700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716093700 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "In My Head"; Jamie Lee Curtis; Josh Groban; Jo Koy and Gabriel Iglesias; Simon Baker; "Murder, She Wrote" Festival; Waylon Wyatt performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 4AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716113000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 4:30AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 5AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 6AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Actors Anne Hathaway and Tom Holland ("The Odyssey"); author Jay Shetty; Adam Lambert performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>Skin health with Dr. Saranya Wyles; actor Jake Johnson; shopping expert Adrianna Brach; summer road trip ice cream flavors with Jamila Robinson.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 5p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 6p</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260715223000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 7p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>"The Odyssey" New York City red carpet premiere and cast interviews; summer beauty glam on-the-go.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>Dr. Charles grapples with his own mental health following a harrowing experience working the suicide prevention line.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>While in the field, Violet and Novak are thrust into a dangerous and rapidly escalating situation, forcing them to rely on their instincts to protect both themselves and a vulnerable patient.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Torres investigates the conspiracy surrounding the Morgan case, leading Intelligence into a tangled web of secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716033400 +0000" stop="20260716043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Zendaya; actress Chrissy Metz.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716043700 +0000" stop="20260716053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Jon Bernthal; actress Stephanie Hsu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716053700 +0000" stop="20260716060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716060400 +0000" stop="20260716063300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716063300 +0000" stop="20260716073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>Reality TV star Abby Lee Miller; wrestler Braun Strowman (USA's "Everything on the Menu with Braun Strowman"); beauty expert Daniel McFadden; Like this? Add that! recs; Daily feed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716073000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>"The Odyssey" New York City red carpet premiere and cast interviews; summer beauty glam on-the-go.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 5:00a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 5:30a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 6a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Actors Anne Hathaway and Tom Holland ("The Odyssey"); author Jay Shetty; Adam Lambert performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>Skin health with Dr. Saranya Wyles; actor Jake Johnson; shopping expert Adrianna Brach; summer road trip ice cream flavors with Jamila Robinson.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>The cast of "The Hawk"; Today Food with Mika Leon; Adam Lambert performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 11a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260715213000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 6</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260715223000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 7</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>"The Odyssey" New York City red carpet premiere and cast interviews; summer beauty glam on-the-go.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>Dr. Charles grapples with his own mental health following a harrowing experience working the suicide prevention line.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>While in the field, Violet and Novak are thrust into a dangerous and rapidly escalating situation, forcing them to rely on their instincts to protect both themselves and a vulnerable patient.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Torres investigates the conspiracy surrounding the Morgan case, leading Intelligence into a tangled web of secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716033400 +0000" stop="20260716043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actress Zendaya; actress Chrissy Metz.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716043700 +0000" stop="20260716053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actor Jon Bernthal; actress Stephanie Hsu.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716053700 +0000" stop="20260716060700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716060700 +0000" stop="20260716063600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716063600 +0000" stop="20260716070500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>"The Odyssey" New York City red carpet premiere and cast interviews; summer beauty glam on-the-go.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716070500 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "In My Head"; Jamie Lee Curtis; Josh Groban; Jo Koy and Gabriel Iglesias; Simon Baker; "Murder, She Wrote" Festival; Waylon Wyatt performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York @ 6AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Actors Anne Hathaway and Tom Holland ("The Odyssey"); author Jay Shetty; Adam Lambert performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>Skin health with Dr. Saranya Wyles; actor Jake Johnson; shopping expert Adrianna Brach; summer road trip ice cream flavors with Jamila Robinson.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716140000 +0000" stop="20260716150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>The cast of "The Hawk"; Today Food with Mika Leon; Adam Lambert performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716150000 +0000" stop="20260716153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716153000 +0000" stop="20260716160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Live</title>
    <desc>Celebrity interviews and discussing recipes, beauty, fashion and current events pertinent to the tri-state region.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260716160000 +0000" stop="20260716170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260715210000 +0000" stop="20260715220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Ruth has a mystery admirer who unnerves her; Louisa gets in trouble with Bert when one of her students writes about getting food poisoning at his restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260715220000 +0000" stop="20260715230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Craddock angers farmers when he cracks down on the local vet's drunken driving.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260715230000 +0000" stop="20260715233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Keeping Up Appearances</title>
    <desc>Everyone is in shock when an eccentric woman moves into Daddy's bedroom, claiming to be his fiancée and the sisters' stepmother-to-be, and it's up to Hyacinth to break up the insane engagement and get rid of the woman for good.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260715233000 +0000" stop="20260716000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ageless Gardens</title>
    <desc>Gardens used to maintain emotional balance.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-15</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716000000 +0000" stop="20260716010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Ruth has a mystery admirer who unnerves her; Louisa gets in trouble with Bert when one of her students writes about getting food poisoning at his restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716010000 +0000" stop="20260716013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Keeping Up Appearances</title>
    <desc>Everyone is in shock when an eccentric woman moves into Daddy's bedroom, claiming to be his fiancée and the sisters' stepmother-to-be, and it's up to Hyacinth to break up the insane engagement and get rid of the woman for good.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716013000 +0000" stop="20260716020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ageless Gardens</title>
    <desc>A protected woodland and public cultivated garden welcome year-round volunteers, students, and visitors; a rural gardener and lily connoisseur identifies hidden and rare plants left by the previous owner.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716020000 +0000" stop="20260716030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>Wycliffe and Kersey have words when a blackmail investigation is put in jeopardy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716030000 +0000" stop="20260716033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716033000 +0000" stop="20260716040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ZoomerLife: Health, Wellness &amp; Longevity</title>
    <desc>The world's leading artists, doctors, filmmakers and scientists participate in a panel discussion.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716040000 +0000" stop="20260716050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Craddock angers farmers when he cracks down on the local vet's drunken driving.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716050000 +0000" stop="20260716053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Longevity Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Sonia and Lennox travel to Lobitos to teach children how to speak English and about ecology and being community leaders.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716053000 +0000" stop="20260716060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Scriptures</title>
    <desc>Nature videography and classical music with passages of scripture from the world's religions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716060000 +0000" stop="20260716080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beautiful Little Classics</title>
    <desc>Performances by classical musicians.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716080000 +0000" stop="20260716083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Chicken Soup</title>
    <desc>Thought-provoking messages.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716083000 +0000" stop="20260716090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Balance</title>
    <desc>Stunning videos of nature paired with soothing classical music create inspiration.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716090000 +0000" stop="20260716093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kabalah Yoga With Audi Gozlan</title>
    <desc>Audi Gozlan demonstrates a new system of yoga and meditation known as Kabbalah Yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716093000 +0000" stop="20260716100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716100000 +0000" stop="20260716103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: Blissful Living</title>
    <desc>A series of yoga designed to calm the nerves and strengthen the spirit.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716103000 +0000" stop="20260716110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Yoga for grandparents.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716110000 +0000" stop="20260716113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anjelica's 22 Minute Workout</title>
    <desc>A revival of the '80s aerobics series offers workouts for a wide range of ages and abilities.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716113000 +0000" stop="20260716120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kabalah Yoga With Audi Gozlan</title>
    <desc>Audi Gozlan demonstrates a new system of yoga and meditation known as Kabbalah Yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716120000 +0000" stop="20260716123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716123000 +0000" stop="20260716130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Yoga to strengthen the upper back.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260716130000 +0000" stop="20260716133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shaolin Tai Chi</title>
    <desc>Exploring how various Shaolin Tai Chi exercises can help to heal the knees through gentle movement.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-16</date>
  </programme>
</tv>