<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260522084502 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="FX.us">
    <display-name>US | FX East</display-name>
    <icon src="https://tlgrm.re/images/fx-us.png" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465331">
    <display-name lang="US">Freeform HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464897">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Family</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464774">
    <display-name lang="US">FYI Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465357">
    <display-name lang="US">FXX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470299">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Global Toronto</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465167">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Mystery HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470910">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FX HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465105">
    <display-name lang="US">Fuse HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465241">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark Channel HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470509">
    <display-name lang="Canada">CTV LIFE CHANNEL</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470820">
    <display-name lang="Canada">FXX Canada</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486672">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465290">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465354">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="492942">
    <display-name lang="US">ION Mystery</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="481954">
    <display-name lang="US">Haunt TV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486720">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV2 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486726">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV3 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486853">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486821">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">ITV Quiz</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465002">
    <display-name lang="US">Lifetime Real Women</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467402">
    <display-name lang="US">WPTZ-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470474">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Much Music HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486755">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">MTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470737">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Makeful TV SD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="486751">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">More4 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="467015">
    <display-name lang="US">WNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465080">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV - Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464825">
    <display-name lang="US">MTVLIVE</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465113">
    <display-name lang="US">MTV2: Music Television HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="469871">
    <display-name lang="US">KNBC-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465207">
    <display-name lang="US">Revolt HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="468233">
    <display-name lang="US">WCAU-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470330">
    <display-name lang="Canada">ONETV</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260522043000 -0400" stop="20260522050000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Accident? Start here.</title>
    <desc>After an accident, discover your options, avoid costly mistakes, and learn how to connect with an attorney to review your case.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522050000 -0400" stop="20260522053000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>1776 - 2026 250th Anniversary Quarter Celebration Program</title>
    <desc>2026 will be one of the most historic years ever in U.S. coinage; join your host Mike Mezack to learn about the incredible U.S. Quarter program and get a chance at an exclusive P&amp;D Roll!</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522053000 -0400" stop="20260522060000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522060000 -0400" stop="20260522063000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522063000 -0400" stop="20260522070000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522070000 -0400" stop="20260522073000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim fears that Cheryl's romantic expectations will increase as Ryan (Mitch Rouse) showers Dana with gifts, until he learns a secret about a special tape Cheryl may have made.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522073000 -0400" stop="20260522103000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Star Wars: Return of the Jedi</title>
    <desc>Luke Skywalker (Mark Hamill) battles horrible Jabba the Hutt and cruel Darth Vader to save his comrades in the Rebel Alliance and triumph over the Galactic Empire. Han Solo (Harrison Ford) and Princess Leia (Carrie Fisher) reaffirm their love and team with Chewbacca, Lando Calrissian (Billy Dee Williams), the Ewoks and the androids C-3PO and R2-D2 to aid in the disruption of the Dark Side and the defeat of the evil emperor.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522103000 -0400" stop="20260522133000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Star Wars: The Force Awakens</title>
    <desc>Thirty years after the defeat of the Galactic Empire, the galaxy faces a new threat from the evil Kylo Ren (Adam Driver) and the First Order. When a defector named Finn crash-lands on a desert planet, he meets Rey (Daisy Ridley), a tough scavenger whose droid contains a top-secret map. Together, the young duo joins forces with Han Solo (Harrison Ford) to make sure the Resistance receives the intelligence concerning the whereabouts of Luke Skywalker (Mark Hamill), the last of the Jedi knights.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522133000 -0400" stop="20260522170000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Star Wars: The Last Jedi</title>
    <desc>Luke Skywalker's peaceful and solitary existence gets upended when he encounters Rey, a young woman who shows strong signs of the Force. Her desire to learn the ways of the Jedi forces Luke to make a decision that changes their lives forever. Meanwhile, Kylo Ren and General Hux lead the First Order in an all-out assault against Leia and the Resistance for supremacy of the galaxy.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522170000 -0400" stop="20260522200000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Star Wars: The Rise of Skywalker</title>
    <desc>When it's discovered that the evil Emperor Palpatine did not die at the hands of Darth Vader, the rebels must race against the clock to find out his whereabouts. Finn and Poe lead the Resistance to put a stop to the First Order's plans to form a new Empire, while Rey anticipates her inevitable confrontation with Kylo Ren.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522200000 -0400" stop="20260522230000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Solo: A Star Wars Story</title>
    <desc>Young Han Solo finds adventure when he joins forces with a gang of galactic smugglers and a 190-year-old Wookiee named Chewbacca. Indebted to the gangster Dryden Vos, the crew devises a daring plan to travel to the mining planet Kessel to steal a batch of valuable coaxium. In need of a fast ship, Solo meets Lando Calrissian, the suave owner of the perfect vessel for the dangerous mission -- the Millennium Falcon.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260522230000 -0400" stop="20260523020000 -0400" channel="FX.us">
    <title>Rogue One: A Star Wars Story</title>
    <desc>Former scientist Galen Erso lives on a farm with his wife and young daughter, Jyn. His peaceful existence comes crashing down when the evil Orson Krennic takes him away from his beloved family. Many years later, Galen becomes the Empire's lead engineer for the most powerful weapon in the galaxy, the Death Star. Knowing that her father holds the key to its destruction, Jyn joins forces with a spy and other resistance fighters to steal the space station's plans for the Rebel Alliance.</desc>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joe Lando joins Jane Seymour - New Crepe Erase show with 3 FREE Gifts!</title>
    <desc>TV stars Joe Lando and Jane Seymour reveal the secret to smoother, younger-looking skin with Crepe Erase. Plus, receive 3 FREE gifts with this limited-time offer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>Eric wants to appear on a TV dating show to win over a college girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>Cory assumes Shawn is involved with a classmate when she stays overnight.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>Cory tries to be in two places at once when Topanga's birthday party falls on the night of a wrestling match.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boy Meets World</title>
    <desc>The Matthewses dine at the Hunters' trailer home for Thanksgiving when Cory and Shawn urge the families to become friendly.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Meet ordinary people who have experienced the extraordinary power of prayer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">700 Club Interactive</title>
    <desc>Highlighting current events and stories that will help bring encouragment to people.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522143000 +0000" stop="20260522153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">That Thrifting Show with Lara Spencer</title>
    <desc>Lara Spencer dares the teams to go Hollywood Regency vs. Worldly Eclectic in their living room designs. From bold thrift finds to wild design choices, the duos mix patterns, flaunt animal prints, and pull off jaw-dropping transformations.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522153000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Gracie and Ruby have nightmares after Jim takes them to a scary movie.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lyle, Lyle, Crocodile</title>
    <desc>When the Primm family moves to New York City, their young son, Josh, struggles to adapt to his new school and friends. All of that changes when he discovers Lyle, a singing crocodile that loves baths, caviar and great music. The two become fast friends, but when evil neighbor Mr. Grumps threatens Lyle's existence, the Primms must band together to show the world that family can come from the most u</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522183000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Raya and the Last Dragon</title>
    <desc>Long ago, in the fantasy world of Kumandra, humans and dragons lived together in harmony. However, when sinister monsters known as the Druun threatened the land, the dragons sacrificed themselves to save humanity. Now, 500 years later, those same monsters have returned, and it's up to a lone warrior to track down the last dragon and stop the Druun for good.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lilo &amp; Stitch</title>
    <desc>A tale of a young girl's close encounter with the galaxy's most wanted extraterrestrial. Lilo is a lonely Hawaiian girl who adopts a small ugly "dog," whom she names Stitch. Stitch would be the perfect pet if he weren't in reality a genetic experiment who has escaped from an alien planet and crash-landed on Earth. Through her love, faith and unwavering belief in ohana, the Hawaiian concept of fami</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mulan</title>
    <desc>Fearful that her ailing father will be drafted into the Chinese military, Mulan takes his spot -- though, as a girl living under a patriarchal regime, she is technically unqualified to serve. She cleverly impersonates a man and goes off to train with fellow recruits. Accompanied by her dragon, Mushu, she uses her smarts to help ward off a Hun invasion, falling in love with a dashing captain along </desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Beast</title>
    <desc>An arrogant young prince and his castle's servants fall under the spell of a wicked enchantress, who turns him into the hideous Beast until he learns to love and be loved in return. The spirited, headstrong village girl Belle enters the Beast's castle after he imprisons her father Maurice. With the help of his enchanted servants, including the matronly Mrs. Potts, Belle begins to draw the cold-hea</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Meet ordinary people who have experienced the extraordinary power of prayer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>A successful guy that Jim went to high school with gives him a big contracting job and makes a pass at Cheryl over dinner.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523043000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim does more harm than good when he stands up to Dana's boss; Andy has trouble making arrangements for his birthday party.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim must decide between helping Cheryl through surgery or meeting his hero, Bo Diddley.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523053000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">According to Jim</title>
    <desc>Jim and Cheryl's new friends turn out to be obnoxious, but they benefit from the relationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523060000 +0000" stop="20260523063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America 250th Anniversary Coins: Enduring Liberty Half Dollars</title>
    <desc>Join Mike Mezack for a special presentation of the 1776-2026 Enduring Liberty Half Dollars-one-year-only U.S. Mint issues honoring America's 250th Anniversary, including rare rolls and certified MS67 collectibles.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523063000 +0000" stop="20260523070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Have Thinning Hair? Keranique Can Help Regrow Beautiful, Thicker Hair!</title>
    <desc>If you have thinning hair or hair loss, Keranique can help regrow thicker, longer and fuller hair. Keranique is the number 1 hair regrowth system for women. Regain your confidence with beautiful, thicker and fuller hair in just 3 easy steps!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523070000 +0000" stop="20260523080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 700 Club</title>
    <desc>Meet ordinary people who have experienced the extraordinary power of prayer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465331" start="20260523080000 +0000" stop="20260523083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1776 USA Gold Rarity</title>
    <desc>Secure a 1oz Gold 1776-2026 American Gold Eagle graded PF70UCAM in a special Holder, honoring 250 years of American Freedom! Included as a bonus is a free 2026 1oz Silver Eagle also featuring the iconic Liberty Bell to create a one of a kind pair!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>Mark's friendship with a former police partner is threatened when the officer asks him to lie about a racist crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura tries to convince Almanzo she is mature and her love for him is not just infatuation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura wants to pass the teaching exam to prove her maturity, but romantic rival Nellie has other ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>The Ingalls go to court to adopt Albert, but his father reappears and demands custody.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mary must get help when a stagecoach accident traps Adam and endangers a pregnant woman; Laura and Albert offer a beehive to their rivals.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Laura becomes jealous when Almanzo dates another girl; Mr. Oleson learns that the fat lady in a visiting circus is his sister.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rise and Shine, Benedict Stone</title>
    <desc>Benedict Stone's life gets turned upside down when his teenage niece arrives on his doorstep. However, he soon realizes that she may be the change that he so desperately needs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fashionably Yours</title>
    <desc>After three years of organizing fashion collections at a top magazine, Lauren is passed up for a promotion and decides it is finally time to throw in the towel and move home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Second Honeymoon</title>
    <desc>The children of a couple (Roma Downey, Tim Matheson) on the brink of divorce send their parents on a trip in hopes of rekindling the romance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love by Chance</title>
    <desc>Claire, the owner of a new restaurant, is too busy to focus on relationships. Her mother decides to fix this by finding Claire the perfect man -- without telling Claire.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Gift of Peace</title>
    <desc>Traci is a once-devout Christian who stopped believing in God after her husband tragically died despite her prayers. As her second Christmas without him approaches, she tries going to a support group for inspiration and comfort.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two Turtle Doves</title>
    <desc>Dr. Sharon Hayes returns home to search for a beloved family heirloom. With the help of an adorable little girl and her dispirited father, together they rediscover the magic of Christmas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mrs. Oleson demands the Rev. Alden's resignation when she discovers a woman parishioner spent the night in his room.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Albert dreams that he and Laura have been captured by Indians who want him to lead an attack against the U.S. Army.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Charles and Laura rush to the aid of an old friend when they learn that a disabling accident has destroyed his will to live.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>Ty is asked to mentor a troubled kid, but finding common ground proves harder than he expected.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523060000 +0000" stop="20260523070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartland</title>
    <desc>While on Lyndy's first camping trip, Amy and Ty find an injured animal.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523070000 +0000" stop="20260523080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>Jonathan must deal with the anger and frustration of losing his supernatural powers after he rejects an assignment from God; Jonathan falls for a beautiful woman who helps him cope.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523080000 +0000" stop="20260523090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway to Heaven</title>
    <desc>Jonathan, now mortal, has trouble finding a job, and Jennifer doesn't share his wish for a long-term relationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523090000 +0000" stop="20260523100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Mrs. Oleson demands the Rev. Alden's resignation when she discovers a woman parishioner spent the night in his room.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523100000 +0000" stop="20260523110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Albert dreams that he and Laura have been captured by Indians who want him to lead an attack against the U.S. Army.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523110000 +0000" stop="20260523120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>Charles and Laura rush to the aid of an old friend when they learn that a disabling accident has destroyed his will to live.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523120000 +0000" stop="20260523130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>A con artist (Ray Walston) and a wrestler convince Jonathan he could be a champion and urge the town to bet on him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523130000 +0000" stop="20260523140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little House on the Prairie</title>
    <desc>A charismatic preacher (James Olson) entices residents from the Rev. Alden's teachings.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523140000 +0000" stop="20260523160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Away &amp; Back</title>
    <desc>Hostility between a widowed farmer (Jason Lee) and a pushy ornithologist (Minka Kelly) who comes to his farm to save a family of swans turns into something else.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464897" start="20260523160000 +0000" stop="20260523180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sarah, Plain and Tall</title>
    <desc>In 1910 Kansas, widowed farmer Jacob Witting (Christopher Walken) is having a hard time raising his children and running his farm without the help of a wife. He puts an ad in the paper for a bride to help him, and gets a response from a woman named Sarah (Glenn Close), who only describes herself as "plain and tall." Sarah travels to the farm for a one-month trial period, but finds Jacob's stubborn</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shipping Wars</title>
    <desc>Jenn attempts to dismantle a butter sculpture in the Texas heat; Jessica's tardiness spoils the dress rehearsal of a middle-school play.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Silver Coin Rarities</title>
    <desc>Secure a First Day of Issue Complete 2024 Morgan and Peace Dollar Set in perfect 70 condition for your collection. With Mint State mintages of 300,000, 275,000 for Proof, and 262,500 for Reverse Proofs, these coins are incredible absolute rarities!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Silver Coin Rarities</title>
    <desc>Secure a First Day of Issue Complete 2024 Morgan and Peace Dollar Set in perfect 70 condition for your collection. With Mint State mintages of 300,000, 275,000 for Proof, and 262,500 for Reverse Proofs, these coins are incredible absolute rarities!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Iconic Silver Set</title>
    <desc>Secure a complete 2025 Set of the iconic Morgan and Peace Silver Dollars, struck from .999 pure silver; this set contains 2 of each coin in Mint State, Proof, and Reverse Proof 70 condition with each mintage among the lowest of the modern series.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Iconic Silver Set</title>
    <desc>Secure a complete 2025 Set of the iconic Morgan and Peace Silver Dollars, struck from .999 pure silver; this set contains 2 of each coin in Mint State, Proof, and Reverse Proof 70 condition with each mintage among the lowest of the modern series.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joni Table Talk</title>
    <desc>Joni and guests tackle a wide range of relevant issues, controversial subjects and hard-hitting news topics with candor and wit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Tom builds an authentic Native American bull boat; Jake goes back on the hunt for the bus stop bandit; Morgan struggles to haul a ton of greenhouse supplies; Eustace and Raleigh tackle a rush order for lumber.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>As winter descends in the mountains, Jake's first lion hunt ends in a near-deadly dust up; Tom and Nancy face a surge in the local coyote population; Jason comes face to face with a marauding black bear; Mike fights predators on land and sea.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Eustace and Raleigh try to restore an antique buzz saw; Tom takes on a massive new dugout canoe project; Jake's quest for winter meat takes him on a dangerous high-altitude hunt; Kidd and Harry race against a winter storm to round up rogue cattle.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Tom and Sean search for better trapping grounds; Jake seeks revenge on the lion that injured his hound; Eustace and Raleigh struggle to fix a storm-damaged bridge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Jason's bladesmithing business suffers a critical setback when his hand is badly cut on the job; Jake's latest lion hunt turns into a rescue mission; Kidd and Harry break a colt; Josh scavenges a wolf-killed bison.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Mike's scouting trip for bears turns into an alpine goat hunt; Jake brings in the big dogs to settle an old score with a problem lion; Tom and Sean check beaver sets to see if their new trapping grounds will pay off.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Jake tracks a dangerous mother lion and her young; Kidd and Harry go on the offensive against a pack of coyotes that is targeting their cattle; Eustace and Raleigh track a rogue black bear that's been raiding a neighbor's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mountain Men</title>
    <desc>Mike returns to the bear-infested crags of Kodiak to reclaim his mountain goat kill; Jason hunts down a wild hog to feed his family; Kidd and Harry blow up a beaver dam to save their water supply; Josh goes on the offensive against wolves.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>A three-ring circus erupts when the buyers head to Irvine, Calif.; Darrell speculates that Dave has gone broke.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522203000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers are in Upland, Calif.; Barry brings an advantage; Darrell gets shut out; Jarrod and Brandi fall in love with a furniture locker; Dave goes all out on a jewelry unit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Dave doesn't buy; Jarrod and Brandi uncover rare Depression-era art; Barry's art goes back to the Mayan culture; Darrell uncovers a possible Wells Fargo stagecoach gun.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders descend upon Laguna Hills, Calif.; Dave scores a furniture unit; Jarrod and Brandi stroll down memory lane.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers venture into downtown Los Angeles, where they participate in a vault auction; Jarrod and Brandi put all their marbles in some mystery boxes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers visit Ontario, Calif., where Darrell wants to take son Brandon to the next level of the business; Barry's unit is anything but chicken feed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260522233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Barry questions his judgment as the bidders hunt for deals in Azusa, Calif.; Darrell scores a timeless unit; Jarrod and Brandi seek quality over quantity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260522233000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>In Hemet, Calif., Jarrod and Brandi locate a tattoo locker and Dave hopes for a big payday; Barry showers Dave with kindness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers journey to the affluent neighborhood of Westminster, Calif.; Barry discovers an antique medical device.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>In Simi Valley, Calif., the buyers deal with safes, a pirate's booty and a vintage motorcycle; Dave is left with a broken heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464774" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers return to Long Beach, Calif., where Darrell manages to turn a profit and Barry finds a unique race car.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rare USA Silver Set</title>
    <desc>This patriotic Set of 29 American Silver Eagles features every annual release of the series from the first year of issue in 2000 to 2026, each coin graded MS69. This set includes the final 2021 Type 1 and first Type 2 with a bonus 2025 Eagle Privy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Last Full Measure</title>
    <desc>Airman William H. Pitsenbarger Jr. is awarded the Medal of Honor for his service and actions on the battlefield.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522133000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Red Tails</title>
    <desc>During World War II, the Civil Aeronautics Authority selects 13 black cadets to become part of an experimental program at the Tuskegee Institute in Alabama. The program aims at training colored personnel to become fighter pilots for the Army. However, discrimination, lack of institutional support and the racist belief that these men lacked the intelligence and aptitude for the job dog their every </desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pearl Harbor</title>
    <desc>This sweeping drama, based on real historical events, follows American boyhood friends Rafe McCawley (Ben Affleck) and Danny Walker (Josh Hartnett) as they enter World War II as pilots. Rafe is so eager to take part in the war that he departs to fight in Europe alongside England's Royal Air Force. On the home front, his girlfriend, Evelyn (Kate Beckinsale), finds comfort in the arms of Danny. The </desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When Louise is accused of a theft at school, Linda uses her position as school office volunteer to try to solve the case from the inside.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522203000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When the coolest teens she's ever seen start coming into the restaurant, Tina decides she needs to be just like them; Gene and Louise get into a battle of wills over stinky socks.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Louise brings Tina along on a mission to find the perfect item for her last-ever show-and-tell; Teddy goes overboard trying to impress a date at the restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Mr. Fischoeder challenges Bob to successfully prank him on April Fool's Day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Tina drags Bob along on a desperate quest to earn her bird-watching badge for ThunderGirls; Louise and Gene try to keep their new restaurant game a secret from Linda.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>When a customer leaves a $100 gift card as a tip, Bob, Linda and the kids go on a shopping spree; Gene has an awkward run-in with a former friend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260522233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter attends a business conference in Atlantic City with Preston; Stewie helps Chris prepare for his role in Adam West High School's rendition of "Romeo and Juliet.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260522233000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>The Griffins perform a retelling of three Oscar-winning stories: "Silence of the Lambs," "American Beauty" and "Forrest Gump.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Resolved to enjoy a family movie night, the Griffins take a road trip to Bend, Ore., to rent a VHS from the last Blockbuster in existence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Joe accidentally sees Lois naked, leading to a reinvigoration of his sex life with Bonnie; Stewie is gifted an electric SUV and quickly embodies the "Range Rover" lifestyle.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Lois hypnotizes Peter into satisfying her sexual proclivities; Stewie renovates his treehouse in an attempt to win over Brian and Chris.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523013000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Cleveland is fired as a mailman after a mishap, but flourishes in his new job at the brewery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter makes a hologram of himself to get out of menial household duties.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523023000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>During a game of hide-and-seek, Stewie takes refuge in Quagmire's suitcase, only to wind up in Paris; Peter and Lois take a getaway to Vermont, where Lois is intent on breaking Bonnie's Instagram likes record.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Stewie finds himself in public disgrace after a pop star unleashes her fan base on him for a benign comment; Peter gets lap band surgery and enjoys the merriment of excess skin.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523033000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Peter and Chris finish last in a "Generation Gap" game at a carnival, forcing them to try to reconnect; Brian starts to date a carny, whom he can't break up with even after witnessing some of her crude habits.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The guys are sentenced to death on Planet Amazonia by a race of giant women. Voices of Billy West, Katey Sagal, John DiMaggio, Phil LaMarr and Lauren Tom. Guest voice: Bea Arthur.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465357" start="20260523043000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>The crew is injected into Fry's body to fight off parasites he picked up from an egg-salad sandwich. Voices of Billy West, Katey Sagal, John DiMaggio, Phil LaMarr and Lauren Tom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522083700 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">SIGN OFF</title>
    <desc>Sign off.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Today With James Robison</title>
    <desc>Sheila Walsh looks through the eyes of mothers whose children are suffering to see the need and opportunity to share the love of God in word and deed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News Morning</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast to start your day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Morning Show</title>
    <desc>Viewers from across the country are welcomed in for an hour of smart conversation, lifestyle segments, big-name guests and live performances.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tamron Hall</title>
    <desc>Actress Keke Palmer and director Boots Riley ("I Love Boosters"); Keke performs "2-D"; author Emma Straub ("American Fantasy").</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Property Brothers: Forever Home</title>
    <desc>After 15 years of memories in their cozy home, this family can't imagine living anywhere else; with only two bedrooms for five people and limited storage, Drew and Jonathan arrive to revamp the space so they can stay in the home they love.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522163000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Save My Reno</title>
    <desc>Melissa and Ben suffer a second floor with a host of problems, but their wants may be bigger than their budget.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Masters</title>
    <desc>Three chefs enter the arena in the Wildfire Round; in the Crossfire Round, it's steak versus pork; In the Feast of Fire, the judges are served steakhouse feasts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Masters of Flip</title>
    <desc>With the color pink as her inspiration, Kortney tries to balance masculine and feminine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>Sunny Anderson joins Drew and Ross to hit the headlines and has a twist on a Key lime pie.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522193000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>Comic Alex Edelman chats and helps Jake Cohen whip up something in the kitchen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Young and the Restless</title>
    <desc>Drama revolves around three families in Genoa City.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 5</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 6</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260522233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Goldbergs</title>
    <desc>Beverly convinces Murray to get a hot tub to spark romance and spend time together; Geoff decides to try out a new look for himself, which is not well received by Barry.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260522233000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>Stephen Colbert's final episode of "The Late Show"; "Propeller One-Way Coach"; Dorit Kemsley (memoir "Unburdened"); the 52nd American Music Awards; Tony Awards nominees; Kenan Thompson surprises acting teacher Freddie Hendricks; Pedro Pascal ("Star Wars: The Mandalorian and Grogu"); Sonequa Martin-Green ("Boston Blue"); Clint Black and Lisa Hartman Black (movie "When I Said I Do"); Miley Cyrus' Wa</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sheriff Country</title>
    <desc>With her department under scrutiny and tensions rising across Edgewater, Sheriff Mickey Fox faces the fallout from a major investigation that threatens to upend everything she's built.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fire Country</title>
    <desc>After a catastrophic dam failure unleashes historic floodwaters across Edgewater, Station 42 and Three Rock battle rising waters and dwindling resources.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>In the summer of 2000, 40-year-old Michelle Charette goes missing; when she's found dead in a remote area, police have little to go on; they think they know who did it but can't prove it; what's more they believe the suspected killer may be responsible for the deaths of three other women found in Lake Ontario 500 km away.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523033500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global News at 11</title>
    <desc>Greater Toronto's top local news stories and latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260523033500 +0000" stop="20260523040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Global National</title>
    <desc>The top stories from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260523040500 +0000" stop="20260523050500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crime Beat</title>
    <desc>Crime reporter Nancy Hixt reviews the case of Meika Jordan, a six-year-old girl whose life was tragically cut short; Nancy reveals the details of this case and the evidence uncovered by investigators in their quest for justice.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470299" start="20260523050500 +0000" stop="20260523053500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>Stephen Colbert's final episode of "The Late Show"; "Propeller One-Way Coach"; Dorit Kemsley (memoir "Unburdened"); the 52nd American Music Awards; Tony Awards nominees; Kenan Thompson surprises acting teacher Freddie Hendricks; Pedro Pascal ("Star Wars: The Mandalorian and Grogu"); Sonequa Martin-Green ("Boston Blue"); Clint Black and Lisa Hartman Black (movie "When I Said I Do"); Miley Cyrus' Wa</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Fresh blood stains indicate foul play when Seth (William Windom) disappears; a proliferation of strangers in town raises Jessica's suspicions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A Texas trucker (Earl Holliman) is charged with insurance fraud; his son (Patrick Cassidy) is accused of murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Internal strife at an earthquake-shaken California zoo culminates in an employee's death from snake bite.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's probe of a friend's kidnapping in Amsterdam leads to two murders and a diamond-smuggling ring.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's discovery that Cabot Cove's Revolutionary War hero was actually a traitor results in a TV director's murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica's vacation to Honolulu becomes chaotic when the son of her host, power broker Matt Kinkaid, vanishes during a hotly contested U.S. Senate election.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica investigates when, during a visit to San Francisco, an advice columnist (Eileen Brennan) falls victim to a crazed gunman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Accidentally tapped into a closed-circuit video surveillance system, Jessica's neighbor witnesses scheming, a robbery and then a murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>While vacationing in Martinique, Jessica is called on to help an acquaintance (Wayne Rogers) accused of a woman's (Cassie Yates) murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>The mysterious deaths of a winery matriarch's son and a rival vintner lead Jessica into a world of greed and betrayal.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hannah Swensen Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Hannah's favorite reality show takes over The Cookie Jar; when the producer is found dead, Hannah and Norman team up to track down the killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hannah Swensen Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When Hannah's customer and Delores' theater rival is murdered, Hannah must find her killer in order to save her mother's reputation; Chad and Hannah's romance blossoms.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hannah Swensen Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Hannah finds a body at the grand re-opening of the Lake Eden Inn; when a storm traps everyone inside, Hannah must find the culprit before the road clears and the killer escapes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hannah Swensen Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When a suspect in a forgery case is murdered and the prosecutor goes missing, Hannah and Chad must uncover how the two cases are connected and solve them in time for the trial.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica seeks a link between the electrocution of the town bully and the hanging of a teacher who was his lover.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>While working on an infomercial, Jessica helps a detective friend (George DiCenzo) probe a strangulation, and tries to find out why a member of her studio audience (Gale Hansen) is found dead during the taping.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica helps a Russian police officer (David Ogden Stiers) capture the elusive mastermind behind the theft of a Fabergé egg.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>The pervasive stench of death looms over Jessica and Seth's visit to his cousin's South Carolina plantation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523060000 +0000" stop="20260523070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica takes a trip to Egypt to finalize a cultural exchange program and ends up searching for a killer and a stolen artifact.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523070000 +0000" stop="20260523080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica seeks a link between the electrocution of the town bully and the hanging of a teacher who was his lover.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523080000 +0000" stop="20260523090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>While working on an infomercial, Jessica helps a detective friend (George DiCenzo) probe a strangulation, and tries to find out why a member of her studio audience (Gale Hansen) is found dead during the taping.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523090000 +0000" stop="20260523100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica helps a Russian police officer (David Ogden Stiers) capture the elusive mastermind behind the theft of a Fabergé egg.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523100000 +0000" stop="20260523110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A stalker threatens a gifted soprano (Khrystyne Haje) about to make her debut, and Jessica steps in to help with the investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523110000 +0000" stop="20260523120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Pressured by corporate sponsors, a Nobel Prize-winning scientist (Bruce Weitz) fakes his death, then turns up dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523120000 +0000" stop="20260523130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Homicide haunts the release of a restored movie, and Jessica investigates the current crime and the 1960 murder that prevented the original release.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465167" start="20260523130000 +0000" stop="20260523140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>The murder of a French designer's estranged son leads Jessica into the world of smuggling and sweatshops.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>An arsonist begins terrorizing a neighborhood with car bombs; Charlie and Rex race to find the next target before the case goes up in smoke.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a murder appears to mimic an infamous crime spree from the past, Charlie and Rex rush to stop the culprit from continuing a serial killer's legacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie lets Rex take the lead as they investigate a murder at a prestigious dog show.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Trapped in an isolated mansion during a storm, Charlie and Rex uncover a wannabe-killer after the hostess is drugged; Sarah fights to keep her alive.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Jesse's friend vanishes; Charlie and Rex discover the man was living two separate lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a murder appears to mimic an infamous crime spree from the past, Charlie and Rex rush to stop the culprit from continuing a serial killer's legacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie lets Rex take the lead as they investigate a murder at a prestigious dog show.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Trapped in an isolated mansion during a storm, Charlie and Rex uncover a wannabe-killer after the hostess is drugged; Sarah fights to keep her alive.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Jesse's friend vanishes; Charlie and Rex discover the man was living two separate lives.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>When a murder appears to mimic an infamous crime spree from the past, Charlie and Rex rush to stop the culprit from continuing a serial killer's legacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie lets Rex take the lead as they investigate a murder at a prestigious dog show.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>After a teenager is killed, Cosgrove and Shaw discover what lengths kids will go to become internet famous; Price and Maroun take a risk to go after whom they believe to be the real criminal in the case, but they wind up back where they started.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Agent Sykes struggles to cope on the anniversary of her sister's disappearance; Benson suspects a cold case from Manhattan could help her get closure.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>After a teenager is killed, Cosgrove and Shaw discover what lengths kids will go to become internet famous; Price and Maroun take a risk to go after whom they believe to be the real criminal in the case, but they wind up back where they started.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Agent Sykes struggles to cope on the anniversary of her sister's disappearance; Benson suspects a cold case from Manhattan could help her get closure.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a graduate student is found dead, Cosgrove and Shaw follow the evidence to a suspect with no clear motive; Price and Maroun uncover a money-grabbing scheme within a church; McCoy warns them to focus on the suspects and not the institution.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The SVU searches for a pattern assailant before his crimes escalate to murder; Fin must contend with a suspect's aggrieved son; Carisi is pressured to close the case quickly to ease public concern.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523013500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Baby Colin reaches that awkward age.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523013500 +0000" stop="20260523020500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires discover the mall.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523020500 +0000" stop="20260523024000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nandor and Laszlo have a night out with Sean and his friends; Nadja discovers the source of her bad luck.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523024000 +0000" stop="20260523031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires help Sean host a Pride parade; Nadja helps her doll achieve a long-held dream.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523031500 +0000" stop="20260523035000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Baby Colin reaches that awkward age.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523035000 +0000" stop="20260523042000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires discover the mall.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523042000 +0000" stop="20260523045500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Nandor and Laszlo have a night out with Sean and his friends; Nadja discovers the source of her bad luck.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523045500 +0000" stop="20260523053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>The vampires help Sean host a Pride parade; Nadja helps her doll achieve a long-held dream.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470910" start="20260523053000 +0000" stop="20260523060500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">What We Do in the Shadows</title>
    <desc>Baby Colin reaches that awkward age.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prince: My Name Is</title>
    <desc>An inside look at Prince's life, his innovative music, his mysterious persona, and his influence on the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Excited to go on a date with her crush, Carlita is surprised to end up at his mother's house instead; "RuPaul's Drag Race" contestant Vanessa Vanjie Mateo goes on a date in Texas and when her date starts ignoring her, all hell starts breaking loose.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Dating Stories</title>
    <desc>Alex goes on a karaoke date with Kevin, but is sad to learn that Kevin invited some friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Diana Ross: Supreme Sensation</title>
    <desc>From being the queen of Motown to taking on the world stage, Diana Ross has sold over 100 million records worldwide; her career spans decades, attracting generation after generation of loyal fans.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Freedia: Queen of Bounce</title>
    <desc>Freedia performs a tribute concert to her mother at the historic Howard Theater in Washington, D.C.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Freedia: Queen of Bounce</title>
    <desc>Freedia records one of her dirtiest songs with her best friend Katey Red and has a showbiz talk with Faith Evans.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Freedia: Queen of Bounce</title>
    <desc>Boyfriend troubles back home threaten to ruin Freedia's good time in Hawaii.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Freedia: Queen of Bounce</title>
    <desc>After returning to New Orleans and ending the Just Be Free Tour, Freedia makes a life-changing decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Michael Jackson: Chase the Truth</title>
    <desc>Close friends, former staff and researchers paint an intimate portrait of pop star Michael Jackson's complicated world and put allegations of sexual abuse under the microscope.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522143000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deadly Love: Bobby &amp; Whitney</title>
    <desc>Exploring the romance of Whitney Houston and Bobby Brown; behind the glamour is a story of love, addiction and heartbreak that shaped their lives and legacies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Life and Death of Tupac Shakur</title>
    <desc>Seen as a poet whose tales of urban alienation captivated young people of all races and backgrounds, Tupac Shakur sets the stage for the current and continuing evolution of the hip-hop phenomenon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522173000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Last 24 Hours: Michael Jackson</title>
    <desc>Michael Jackson, the "King of Pop," spends his last hours battling insomnia and pleading with his personal physician.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Alex Montoya discovers her girlfriend models with and without her clothes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522193000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Pedro Green worries about his girlfriend's shady ways after she moves in with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>LaShan Hudson finds out why her girlfriend only wants to work out alone.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522203000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Nadia Freeman discovers the reason behind her boyfriend's unbalanced behavior.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Brittany wants to find out why her boyfriend, Taylor, has become distant.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Kesha wants to find out what's going on with Duke.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Nicholas is worried about his relationship with Ava.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cheaters</title>
    <desc>Jill wants to know why Rose constantly wants alone time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Luau</title>
    <desc>A man who owes a large sum of cash throws a party that soon spirals out of control just to raise some money.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Malibooty</title>
    <desc>Three buddies (Brian Hooks, Sticky Fingaz, J.T. Jackson) leave their Arizona town and head to California for a wild beach party.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Extraordinary Journey of the Fakir</title>
    <desc>An Indian street magician travels to France to find his estranged father.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hollywood: No Sex, Please</title>
    <desc>Exploring how Hollywood has evolved to reflect society's changing attitudes towards sex over the decades, from "Basic Instinct" and "Body Heat" to "Mad Men" and "Sex and the City.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260523063000 +0000" stop="20260523073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">101 Body Shocks</title>
    <desc>A tour of the human body from head to toe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465105" start="20260523073000 +0000" stop="20260523080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Big Boobs</title>
    <desc>Podcaster and body confidence advocate Jackie Adedeji meets women with big breasts to explore the growing issue living with larger breasts and the increased demand for reduction surgery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Waltons</title>
    <desc>John-Boy's feelings of inadequacy are washed away when circumstances lead to the publishing of a book of his short stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>A counselor encourages all to share their feelings during a workshop; Reba packs Kyra's things to send to Brock's house.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba convinces Barbra Jean her house is haunted by the previous owner, but the joke wears thin when Barbra Jean moves in with her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Kyra and Barbra Jean hide a stray cat in the attic since Brock is allergic; Reba and Brock ply Jake with outrageous gifts.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>When Van and Cheyenne go out of town for Van's football game, Reba is upset to find they have asked Barbra Jean to take care of Elizabeth.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Van insists on coaching Reba after she agrees to compete against Brock in a 5K race to raise money for Jake's school.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Van announces he is quitting school to try out for arena football, but Reba's disapproval causes him to blow his chance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Over Brock and Barbra Jean's objections, Reba gives Kyra permission to go on her first date, then discovers the boy is 17 years old.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Cheyenne suspects Van of cheating on her with a sexy publicist and kicks him out of the house.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Sophia seeks a swinging senior through the personals column; Rose can't recall an old beau who comes to visit her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522133000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>A teacher breathes life into Dorothy's decades-old crush on him; Rose makes her debut as a TV producer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche fails to seduce her date and is heartbroken; Dorothy goes bananas over a "Beatlemania" cast member.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522143000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy dreams she is a contestant on "Jeopardy!" but the game is fixed in favor of neighbor Charlie Dietz.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Lorelai invites Rory to dinner to tell her that she and Christopher got married in Paris; Logan invites Rory to his new Internet company's launch party; frantic Luke turns to Lorelai for help when April faces a medical emergency.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Lorelai admits her concern that her old friends may not accept Christopher; Lorelai brings Christopher to the town's knit-a-thon, where his well-intentioned gesture ends the event early.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Luke and Lorelai share a sweet moment; Christopher worries that Lorelai is not fully committed to their marriage; Luke and Christopher have an ugly confrontation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Strikes Twice</title>
    <desc>Stuck in a stale marriage, a woman magically wakes up 15 years earlier and gets to decide if she'll choose the same man all over again.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Because of Cupid</title>
    <desc>Best friends Naomi and Marcus participate in a Valentine's Day mocktail competition but things go awry when Cupid interferes with a love potion that affects Marcus and several of their friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Long Lost Christmas</title>
    <desc>Hayley is an interior designer who plans to surprise her recently widowed mother with the perfect holiday present -- the extended family she knows her mom yearns for.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">You, Me &amp; the Christmas Trees</title>
    <desc>An arborist falls in love with a farmer as she tries to save his trees before the town tree lighting.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>While choking, Sophia has an out-of-body experience; Blanche protests the demolition of the family's plantation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260523023000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>A soldier returning from the Persian Gulf sweeps Blanche off her feet.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Sophia accidentally comes away with the visiting pope's ring, then refuses to return it.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260523033000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Sophia seeks a swinging senior through the personals column; Rose can't recall an old beau who comes to visit her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>A teacher breathes life into Dorothy's decades-old crush on him; Rose makes her debut as a TV producer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465241" start="20260523043000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche fails to seduce her date and is heartbroken; Dorothy goes bananas over a "Beatlemania" cast member.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>Chef Chuck Hughes spotlights new restaurants in Canada; time-saving tech; viral kitchen hacks tested; actress Lauren Ash ("Superstore").</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>Hosted by chef and two-time Canadian Screen Award-winner Mary Berg takes viewers step-by-step through recipes that solve everyday cooking conundrums.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Chef Spencer Watts cooks up an affordable Thai dinner in around 30 minutes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>In the series' 100th episode, the Top Seven must bake it to the top with show-stopping cakes; one home cook wins big, while another goes home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>Teams travel to Tofino and Ucluelet, B.C., where things get icy before they take a dive.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mary Makes It Easy</title>
    <desc>To reduce food waste, Mary Berg shares how to use compost castoffs in recipes; using flavorful scraps like corn cobs and potato peels, Mary makes Parmesan corn chowder, twice baked potato casserole and cinnamon oat pancakes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spencer's BIG 30</title>
    <desc>Chef Spencer Watts makes fast and affordable Japanese food for four in around 30 minutes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Jackie and Danny think a young woman was forced to commit suicide; Frank clashes with Mayor Poole over a threat to the city; Henry has a heart attack.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>A dangerous ex-mobster helps Danny with cold cases in exchange for leniency for his son; Jamie searches for a secret about the Sanfino family.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>In the series' 100th episode, the Top Seven must bake it to the top with show-stopping cakes; one home cook wins big, while another goes home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Stuff With Mary Berg</title>
    <desc>Mary Berg explores lifestyle trends, do-it-yourself projects, home renovations, recipes and more; featuring celebrity guests, influencers and everyday heroes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 15 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie prepares sausage gnocchi with warm kale and bean salad and Mexican chicken with wicked mole sauce, veg and rice.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522173000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jamie's 15 Minute Meals</title>
    <desc>Jamie Oliver cooks Asian sea bass, sticky rice and dressed greens; chorizo carbonara and Catalan market salad.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Amazing Race Canada</title>
    <desc>Teams travel to Tofino and Ucluelet, B.C., where things get icy before they take a dive.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Pet Ate What?</title>
    <desc>One feline has an appetite that's shockingly on the money, while another's taste for stringy oddities appears to be insatiable; while Ben is back home visiting family, an exotic bird with questionable peckishness puts Dr. G out of his comfort zone.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522193000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Pet Ate What?</title>
    <desc>A pet owner who is a nurse gets a front-row seat as Dr. G explores a troublesome appetite; a feline at risk for a dangerous blockage means a high-pressure game of cat and mouse.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>Eight social media chefs kick off the competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Jackie and Danny think a young woman was forced to commit suicide; Frank clashes with Mayor Poole over a threat to the city; Henry has a heart attack.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>A dangerous ex-mobster helps Danny with cold cases in exchange for leniency for his son; Jamie searches for a secret about the Sanfino family.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Helping prospective buyers find their dream home in the country.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef</title>
    <desc>The chefs must create a signature dish that they feel defines them, but there is a hidden catch.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Australia</title>
    <desc>Contestants compete in a service challenge at the prestigious Vue de Monde restaurant in Melbourne.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Nicki Chapman helps a couple from London search for their dream home in the countryside.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MasterChef Canada</title>
    <desc>In the series' 100th episode, the Top Seven must bake it to the top with show-stopping cakes; one home cook wins big, while another goes home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Jackie and Danny think a young woman was forced to commit suicide; Frank clashes with Mayor Poole over a threat to the city; Henry has a heart attack.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470509" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>A dangerous ex-mobster helps Danny with cold cases in exchange for leniency for his son; Jamie searches for a secret about the Sanfino family.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>After Seamus threatens Kevin, Holt devises an elaborate plan to hide him in a safe house, using Jake as his guard; Kevin is miserable as the 99 works overtime to find Seamus and take him down.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A couple is awakened in the middle of the night by the cries of their six-year-old daughter who has fallen through a mysterious door into another dimension.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A man awakens one morning to find that no one recognizes him, not even his mother.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex head underground into an allegedly haunted mine after a crew member turns up dead during a horror film shoot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate the long list of enemies surrounding a vitriolic celebrity chef after a finger turns up in his Beef Wellington.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex head underground into an allegedly haunted mine after a crew member turns up dead during a horror film shoot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate the long list of enemies surrounding a vitriolic celebrity chef after a finger turns up in his Beef Wellington.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex head underground into an allegedly haunted mine after a crew member turns up dead during a horror film shoot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hudson &amp; Rex</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Rex investigate the long list of enemies surrounding a vitriolic celebrity chef after a finger turns up in his Beef Wellington.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>When Jake is asked to negotiate a hostage situation with a jewel thief, he learns that the culprit seems to be a familiar face; Gina and Amy help Charles manage the high demands of his food truck.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522163000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brooklyn Nine-Nine</title>
    <desc>Jake surprises Amy with an investigation into arson cases connected to her favorite crossword puzzle author; Gina helps Holt jazz up his commissioner candidate speech; Terry, Rosa, Hitchcock and Scully argue over who deserves the new detective car.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parks and Recreation</title>
    <desc>Chris sends Leslie and Ben on a trip to the capital; Ron teaches a student about his views; Tom's new game; April hurts Andy's feelings.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522173000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Parks and Recreation</title>
    <desc>The parks department is unhappy when Chris makes big changes; Leslie is surprised when Ben has a meeting with her mother.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 Rock</title>
    <desc>Liz and Jenna decide to get serious about their dating lives but, unexpectedly, find themselves switching their typical roles.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522183000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">30 Rock</title>
    <desc>Liz accompanies Jack to a birthday celebration for a prince (Paul Reubens); Tracy tempts Pete with a beer-filled party at the office.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>The family struggles with goodbyes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522193000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay has grown children, grandchildren and a gorgeous young wife, who has a preteen son of her own; all together they must bridge generational, cultural and social gaps.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Phil is determined to help Luke prove he is responsible enough to have a new bike; Jay and Manny have some father and son time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522203000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay reluctantly takes Phil on a model-airplane excursion, and Gloria goes shopping with Alex. Meanwhile, Claire and Manny get to know each other as siblings.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Jay's ex-wife, Dede (Shelley Long), tries to make amends with everyone she offended at Jay and Gloria's wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Tensions rise during a day of barbecue and football at Jay and Gloria's in the wake of an incident between Manny and Luke at school.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Med</title>
    <desc>Halstead and Marcel facilitate a trans-organ exchange; Asher and Cuevas help a sexual assault survivor; Choi and Archer treat a patient whose case could expose a fraudulent doctor; Grant and Maggie take a trip down memory lane.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Detective Pryma asks for Severide's help on a case involving explosives; Gallo and Carver clash.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>An unexpected visitor causes disruption for Ruzek and Burgess amidst an emotional investigation involving an unidentified young girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Marital bliss turns into business, as the gang experiences the emotional and economic hardships of divorce.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470820" start="20260523013000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia</title>
    <desc>Mac, Charlie and Dennis use some extra income to purchase a boat; the gang sets sail on the open sea.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lorraine</title>
    <desc>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">This Morning</title>
    <desc>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real-life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Loose Women</title>
    <desc>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip and the latest showbiz news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522125500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Lunchtime News</title>
    <desc>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522125500 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dickinson's Real Deal</title>
    <desc>David sets up shop in Middlesbrough, where Karen Dalmeny is shaken but not stirred as she tries to buy a Bond book.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>Crossing words this time are Angie and her daughter Kirsty from Hertfordshire and two teams of mates, Ben and Paul from West Yorkshire and Jan and Gillian from Warwick.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Chase</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as four strangers - Bob from Macclesfield, Lea from Colchester, Phil from the Wirral and Namuli from London - take on a Chaser.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522173000 +0000" stop="20260522183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Evening News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522183000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bradley and Barney Walsh: Breaking Dad</title>
    <desc>The boys have arrived in the bustling city of Brisbane and put their acting skills to use as they immerse themselves in medieval fantasy role-play.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Kammy looks alarmed. Pollard encourages Cain to deal with his problems head-on.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522193000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Summer names a witness who will back up her alibi, George makes a confession to Todd, Will misconstrues Bethany's compassion, and Daniel buys Jodie a drink for her birthday.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beat the Chasers - Celebrity Special</title>
    <desc>Bradley Walsh hosts as Stephen Mangan, Grace Dent, Sam Quek and Nile Wilson hope to win big for charity by taking down the greatest quiz team that ever was.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News at Ten</title>
    <desc>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News London</title>
    <desc>The latest news and weather from London and the South East.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260522214500 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Batman</title>
    <desc>Epic action crime drama film reboot starring Robert Pattinson and Zoe Kravitz, 2022. A sadistic serial killer causes a superhero to investigate the corruption of his home city.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shop on TV</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Family Next Door</title>
    <desc>Australian mystery drama. Tension around Lulu and Holly's parenting choices comes to the surface just as Isabelle's investigation zones in on Lulu and her daughter Elvis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523034500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Family Next Door</title>
    <desc>Australian mystery drama. Struggling with her husband's depression, Fran is put in a compromised position when Isabelle leverages her guilt to access confidential files.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260523034500 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dermot's Taste of Ireland</title>
    <desc>In Game of Thrones country, Dermot fishes wild mackerel, discovers a local twist on the classic dessert rhubarb and custard, and tastes whiskey magic at the Giant's Causeway.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260523053000 +0000" stop="20260523072500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Your Weekend with Alan Titchmarsh</title>
    <desc>Joining Alan at Manor Farm are actor Neil Stuke and singing sensation Marisha Wallace. Plus, florist Jonathan Moseley celebrates the delights of the Chelsea Flower Show.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260523072500 +0000" stop="20260523082500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ainsley's Fantastic Flavours</title>
    <desc>Inspired by nature, Ainsley cooks vibrant seasonal dishes, from celeriac steaks to orange cake, while Tony Hadley makes garden pasta and Ainsley visits a Maltese potato farm.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486672" start="20260523082500 +0000" stop="20260523083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV News</title>
    <desc>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522083200 +0000" stop="20260522090200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NECTAR TRI-PILLOW -Cooler, Comfy, Better Sleep! Buy One Get One FREE!</title>
    <desc>Discover the Nectar Tri-Comfort Cooling Pillow for the ultimate sleep experience! Adjustable to three firmness levels to provide customized support and cooling all night long. Order NOW to get a second pillow FREE, plus a 30-night home trial!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522090200 +0000" stop="20260522093200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522093200 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Jeremiah</title>
    <desc>In this weekly program, Dr. David Jeremiah delivers practical messages to the congregation at the Shadow Mountain Community Church in San Diego. Also featured is music from the Shadow Mountain Community Church Choir and Orchestra, as well as performances by musical guests that have included Steve Green and Charles Billingsley. Men and women who have been impacted by the Turning Point ministry also</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Creflo Dollar</title>
    <desc>Dr. Creflo Dollar ministers to people from all backgrounds with hopes for change; Creflo helps viewers find ways to renew their faith, mind, and spirit; based on the belief that the Bible is the written and inspired Word of God, the show is meant to invoke change in the lives of people across the globe; Creflo and his wife, Taffi, share their vision for everyone to hear the Word and gain understan</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Today With James Robison</title>
    <desc>James Robison is a former preacher who changed directions in his life several years ago and began hosting this television show alongside his wife, Betty, in order to reach out to help more people. This daily religious and self-help program welcomes guests who tell how they have successfully overcome difficulties in their lives by following God's word -- with the hope of encouraging others to do th</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joyce Meyer Enjoying Everyday Life</title>
    <desc>Noted for her humanitarian ministry efforts to aid suffering people around the world, Bible teacher Joyce Meyer reaches out to both Christians and non-Christians as she illustrates how to make each day better by applying biblical principles to every activity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Designing Spaces</title>
    <desc>Pest control for the whole house; convert a sunroom to a year-round oasis; tips on pool care--time to open your pool! Smarter financing for today's homeowners.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Meet, Marry, Murder</title>
    <desc>A respected lawyer kills the woman he can't bear to lose, then goes on the run across two countries.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Meet, Marry, Murder</title>
    <desc>When a wife and an intruder are found dead in Las Vegas, her husband's story of self-defense unravels to reveal a serial killer hiding in plain sight.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Meet, Marry, Murder</title>
    <desc>A respected family man murders his wife and children, then claims it was her doing a desperate bid to preserve his fantasy of perfection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Meet, Marry, Murder</title>
    <desc>A decorated husband says he killed his wife by accident, but the evidence suggests he planned her death all along.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>As the team investigates a Mossad officer's murder in Virginia, Tony and Ziva pursue her father's killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Ignoring orders from Homeland Security, the team searches for Bodnar in order to avenge the murders of Eli David and Jackie Vance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>An investigator (Colin Hanks) from the Department of Defense scrutinizes the team's response to the Bodnar case; the team must determine whether a petty officer is suffering from paranoia when he claims he is being followed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>As the international hunt for Eli David and Jackie Vance's killer continues, questions are raised about the unconventional methods employed by Gibbs and the team.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Gibbs must take desperate measures to protect his loved ones with Paloma Reynosa still on the loose.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>A girl's kidnapping turns into something bigger when her grandfather complicates the investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a bomb tech's guarded personal life after she is attacked.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team hopes to avoid an international incident when an American officer is killed on a British ship.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team uncovers a sinister plan when a controversial DJ and a naval officer are shot to death.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Abby becomes fixated on solving a murder; DiNozzo's latest fling leads to an interesting Halloween.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260523020300 +0000" stop="20260523030300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Dinozzo's father (Robert Wagner) returns and plays an important role in a murder investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260523030300 +0000" stop="20260523040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team must protect Ziva's father when his attendance at a convention leads to surprises.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260523040100 +0000" stop="20260523050100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team uncovers a sinister plan when a controversial DJ and a naval officer are shot to death.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260523050100 +0000" stop="20260523060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Abby becomes fixated on solving a murder; DiNozzo's latest fling leads to an interesting Halloween.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465290" start="20260523060400 +0000" stop="20260523070400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Dinozzo's father (Robert Wagner) returns and plays an important role in a murder investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Through the Bible With Les Feldick</title>
    <desc>Les Feldick, an Oklahoma farmer and rancher with a special gift for teaching the Bible; his simple and nondenominational approach on the program "Through the Bible with Les Feldick" has reached millions around the world with the Gospel of Grace.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Historic USA Gold</title>
    <desc>Secure the only .9999 fine pure gold coin with the dual date featuring 1776, the year of our nation's founding and the Liberty Bell privy; this unique 1776-2026 American Gold Buffalo comes graded perfect PF70UCAM in an exclusive 1 of 250 holders.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Health and Wellness Insights for Older Adults Dr. Roberts</title>
    <desc>At Oak Street Health, our doctors take the time to get to know you and your needs. We can help you get the most out of your Medicare coverage, set up mail-order prescriptions, and coordinate healthcare &amp; social services. VISITOAKSTREETHEALTH.COM.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Amazing Facts With Doug Batchelor</title>
    <desc>Near-death experiences reinforce the popular belief that souls go to heaven or hell as soon as the body dies; but in the Bible, the soul is said to be a living being and can die; scripture describes death as sleep from which we awake at resurrection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Xploration Animal Science</title>
    <desc>Creatures of Asia: the snow leopard; the Komodo dragon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Xploration Animal Science</title>
    <desc>The seahorse; the Thomson's gazelle.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Xploration Awesome Planet</title>
    <desc>Iceland: waterfalls and geysers, a volcanic mountain that may erupt at any time, producing electricity with geothermal and hydro power, a large glacier.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Xploration Awesome Planet</title>
    <desc>Red rock formations in Sedona, Ariz.; Hawaii's red, black and green beaches; colorful hot springs in Yellowstone National Park; colorful animals include the octopus, who can change color in an instant.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Xploration Awesome Planet</title>
    <desc>Hawaiian Islands: traditional methods of catching fish and collecting sea salt, sea creatures along the coral reef, a limestone cave where ancient artifacts are preserved.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522133000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Xploration Awesome Planet</title>
    <desc>Croatia's waterfalls and caves; Plitvice Lakes National Park; stalactites and stalagmites; the island of Brac's limestone quarries; a stone masonry school.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Hondo reunites with an old flame when the SWAT team works with the FBI to bring in a separatist group that has weapons-grade plutonium; the team worries it will lose an annual law enforcement charity competition to the Los Angeles Fire Department.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The SWAT team pursues a group of unknown assailants responsible for a patrol officer's death; Chris reels from the revelation that she knew the patrol officer who was killed; Deacon and his wife prepare to welcome their newest child.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The SWAT team struggles to maintain peace on the eve of an LGBTQ pride festival after a hate crime sparks citywide anger that ignites further violence; Hicks reunites with his estranged gay son; Street worries his mother will be sent back to prison.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The SWAT team tries to zero in on the next target of a carjacking ring that's using deadly force to boost luxury vehicles; Hondo takes a big step to help his childhood friend's incarcerated son; Mumford weighs a major decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Hondo has a tense reunion with a fellow Marine, Ruiz, when the team hunts an escaped convict who was broken out of prison by criminals using stolen military weapons; Chris prepares for a difficult goodbye when her former K-9 partner becomes ill.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The abduction of Luca and Street's neighbor sends the SWAT team in pursuit of a home invasion crew targeting domestic workers to gain entry into upscale homes; the SWAT division prepares to help Mumford mark a major career milestone.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The team discovers a new version of PCP with ties to an escaped drug dealer who created a version that ravaged the city decades earlier; Chris weighs a major decision regarding her romantic relationship with Kira and Ty.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The SWAT team finds itself under internal investigation when a civilian is killed while they are trying to bring in the city's most wanted criminal; internal affairs calls Hondo's leadership into question.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>The team races to locate the next place a lone gunman will strike; Hondo takes some time away from the team to pursue an investigation that hits close to home; Jessica is presented with an unexpected opportunity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260522233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA on ION Pregame Show</title>
    <desc>Studio coverage of the Women's National Basketball Association.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260522233000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>The Golden State Valkyries travel to Gainbridge Fieldhouse to face the Indiana Fever. Golden State seeks to rebound after losing to Chicago, while Indiana beat Seattle 89-78 behind 21 points from Caitlin Clark in an early-season matchup.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260523013000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA On ION Game Break Show</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>The WNBA regular-season continues as the Sun take on the Storm at Climate Pledge Arena. Seattle leads the season series 1-0 after beating the Sun, 89-82 behind Seattle guard Lexie Brown exploded for 17 points, draining five crucial 3-pointers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <desc>Magnum must help his defense attorney girlfriend when she realizes a client she successfully defended in a murder trial is actually guilty; TC confronts Kamekona about stealing his helicopter business.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465354" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum P.I.</title>
    <desc>Magnum investigates the death of a hotel guest who was thrown from her room's balcony while working on a secret investigation of her own; Icepick is released from jail and is trying to keep a secret from Rick.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Listener</title>
    <desc>Toby and Olivia learn that Oz's parents' restaurant is in trouble; Toby uses his telepathy to try to solve a missing persons case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Listener</title>
    <desc>When a patient dies after a hit-and-run accident, Toby discovers that the man was convicted of embezzling millions of dollars.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team heads to Los Angeles in search of a suspect who kidnaps nannies and the children they care for.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team tracks a suspect targeting people in Detroit; Blake receives a life-changing proposition from her husband (D.W. Moffett).</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a series of deaths in Manhattan that seem to be related to ecstasy overdoses; Hotch makes a discovery about his estranged brother.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When the Replicator returns, a member of the BAU team is targeted.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team tracks an increasingly devolving killer to Arizona; the team suspects Hotch is in the running to be the unit chief.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>As the hunt for a ritualistic killer continues, a bizarre familial connection could help the team zero in on the suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team must determine if the anniversary of the Kennedy assassination is a motivating factor when a sniper strikes Dallas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team meets the new section chief (Esai Morales), who shares a long history with J.J.; an unknown subject leaves victims unable to communicate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>As Hotch fights for his life after being stabbed, he has visions of his late wife and his nemesis; when a teen goes missing, suspicions arise about her estranged father.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Ritualistic murders lead the team to believe their suspect may have a fascination with the Salem witch trials; Garcia plans a Day of the Dead celebration.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A series of strangulations leads the team to look for a killer who keeps mementos of his victims; Rossi's favorite bar is in danger of closing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team searches for missing teens who are suspects in a series of mass murders in Chicago.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When skeletons are discovered in the backyard of a home in Virginia, family secrets and past racial divisions are brought to light.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When a young boy disappears from his home in St. Louis, the team examines a similar cold case for clues.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Blake must work with her retired police captain father and her detective brother to solve a series of murders in Kansas City.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A murder investigation results in Garcia delving into her hacker past -- and reconnecting with a former flame.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>As the team searches for a vigilante killer in Cleveland, Rossi's former Marine sergeant goes missing in Los Angeles; J.J.'s secret catches up with her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU learns of JJ's kidnapping, they discover that Cruz has also been abducted and delve into the files of a classified assignment; the team uncovers details of INTEGRITY, the covert database born out of the operation to find Osama bin Laden.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a pair of suspects responsible for several murders near Pittsburgh; Morgan and Garcia make Valentine's Day plans with their significant others.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU makes startling discoveries as they search for a 4-year-old girl who went missing while staying with a relative.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523060000 +0000" stop="20260523070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>When Russ' first love, Emilia, is kidnapped by the same rebels he fought during his private military contract days, he takes the Phoenix team to a small, impoverished town to rescue her and rid the town of the rebels for good.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523070000 +0000" stop="20260523080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>A double date descends into chaos when Mac and Desi witness a murder in the back of the restaurant; as they work to find the killer, Riley tries to keep the secret about her and her friends' "day jobs' from her new boyfriend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523080000 +0000" stop="20260523090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>After Oversight is almost killed in a bombing, he recruits Mac to help him find the suspected bomber; Mac meets his Aunt Gwendolyn.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="492942" start="20260523090000 +0000" stop="20260523100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MacGyver</title>
    <desc>Los Angeles' power grid is taken hostage in a ransomware attack resulting in a citywide blackout; the team discovers the ransomware code used was written by Riley years ago.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522082200 +0000" stop="20260522085200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>During the renaissance, advances were made in both science and the arts, but many paintings have a mysterious UFO.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522085200 +0000" stop="20260522091800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A mass-produced series of paintings of crying children, a popular artwork in many houses in the 1980s, is believed to be related to a mysterious series of house fires at the time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522091800 +0000" stop="20260522094400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A famous inscription leads some to believe that a real curse haunts the original discoverers of Tutankhamun.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522094400 +0000" stop="20260522101000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Investigating a strange creature seen in a wooded area of rural Massachusetts by three different people who all give similar descriptions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522101000 +0000" stop="20260522103900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A hoard of golden coins is found in the prospecting district of California; a valuable find in an old piano in rural England.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522103900 +0000" stop="20260522110500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A mysterious book that is 500 years old, almost 300 pages long, full of handwritten notes and illustrations and so far no one can translate a word of it.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522110500 +0000" stop="20260522113100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>For over 1,000 years, people worldwide claim to develop injuries spontaneously.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522113100 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Most Unexplained</title>
    <desc>Jimmy Hoffa makes enemies easily.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522122600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State: The New Class</title>
    <desc>Ryan Buell's Paranormal Research Society help people who have nowhere to turn.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522122600 +0000" stop="20260522125200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>Ryan and the Paranormal Research Society head to a grieving woman's farmhouse where she suspects her late son fell victim to the "Dark Man.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522125200 +0000" stop="20260522132200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>The PRS visits a graveyard where a jealous spirit haunts the caretaker's new wife.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522132200 +0000" stop="20260522134400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>Ryan investigates the claim of a student who says she has seen a ghost in her dorm room.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522134400 +0000" stop="20260522141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>Ryan and the team help a family whose home was once part of the underground railroad.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522141000 +0000" stop="20260522143600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>The PRS travels to Las Vegas to investigate a 14-year-old medium who claims to be visited by a spirit called "Emily.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522143600 +0000" stop="20260522150600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paranormal State</title>
    <desc>Ryan and the PRS investigate the haunting of a woman and her dog in Waterboro, Maine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522150600 +0000" stop="20260522153300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>A woman buries her mother's ring on her grave, only to have it turn up hours later; a woman is surprised by a message from her dead father.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522153300 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>Meeting two people who are especially susceptible to supernatural experiences.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522162700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>A woman sees the ghost of a vaudeville performer in a Trenton theater; a man comes face to face with the spirit of a young man who died in a tragic accident.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522162700 +0000" stop="20260522165800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>A man is driven from his home and onto the road in a yearlong battle with a spirit that pushes him to the edge of sanity.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522165800 +0000" stop="20260522172500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>A woman meets an unusual man in a diner; a trucker helps a mysterious colleague out of a storm, receiving a comforting message in return.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522172500 +0000" stop="20260522175200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>A house's long and storied past comes to light when a family starts to renovate it.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522175200 +0000" stop="20260522182200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghostly Encounters</title>
    <desc>A guide for a ghost tour is surprised to learn there is more truth to the stories he tells than he originally believed; a man turns a childhood tormented by ghosts into an interesting career.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522182200 +0000" stop="20260522191700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A Russian soldier describes being lured into a swamp by an unnatural entity; an Ohio military base with a UFO connection; an interview with a US Air Force colonel whose alien-craft sightings are finally confirmed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522191700 +0000" stop="20260522201200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission Unexplained</title>
    <desc>An Infantryman encounters an otherworldly presence on a training mission.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522201200 +0000" stop="20260522211100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission Unexplained</title>
    <desc>An intelligence analyst on a secret mission makes an unearthly discovery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="481954" start="20260522211100 +0000" stop="20260522220500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission Unexplained</title>
    <desc>A Navy seaman experiences strange events in the heart of the Bermuda Triangle; an Air Force Staff Sergeant is confronted by an otherworldly being in Iraq; a tech sergeant discovers a haunting visitor in her air base house.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522082000 +0000" stop="20260522092000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Only Way is Essex</title>
    <desc>Tom couldn't have been clearer: stop flirting with Sam or they're done. Tom's a nice guy, but there's no denying the chemistry she has with Sam.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522092000 +0000" stop="20260522101500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Salt Lake City</title>
    <desc>US reality series. Heather wants to get everyone together for a fresh start as Angie introduces her friend Monica to the ladies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522101500 +0000" stop="20260522110500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of New Jersey</title>
    <desc>When All Is Said and Done: US reality series. The ladies agree to sit down and lay their issues out in the open - without holding back - as the group is about to implode.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522110500 +0000" stop="20260522120500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ant and Dec's Limitless Win</title>
    <desc>There's more life-changing money on offer and surprises in store as Ant and Dec introduce father and daughter Paul and Tegan - and friends Abbi and Amy - to the Limitless Ladder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522120500 +0000" stop="20260522130500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Aisling Bea, Chris Packham, and Kate Lawler join Stephen Mulhern hoping to 'say what they see' and guess well-known phrases for a chance to win 50,000 pounds for their charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522130500 +0000" stop="20260522141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>Graham Norton invites customer experience manager Phil, HR manager Jamie-Lee, and hair salon owner Helen to spin the Wheel and avoid the bankrupts for a possible 50,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522141000 +0000" stop="20260522151000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Only Way is Essex</title>
    <desc>Tom and Miss Tribble split when Sam re-enters the scene, causing a big drama among the former love birds. Celia is feeling let down by Shelby.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522151000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of Salt Lake City</title>
    <desc>US reality series. Lisa and Meredith meet to talk out their issues before Meredith plans a trip to Palm Springs that leaves one Housewife out.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real Housewives of New Jersey</title>
    <desc>US reality series. The ladies of the Garden State reconvene for the first time to watch and react to the highly anticipated 14th series finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Celebrity Catchphrase</title>
    <desc>Stephen Mangan, Kemi Rodgers and Tom Allen join Stephen Mulhern as they 'say what they see' and guess well-known phrases for a chance to win 50,000 pounds for their charities.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>Graham Norton invites operations manager Emma, partnerships manager Ebona, and consultant Dan to spin the Wheel, solve puzzles, and play for a chance to win up to 50,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The 1% Club</title>
    <desc>Lee Mack presents the ultimate leveller of a quiz show where it doesn't matter if you're not usually good at quizzes because the questions are all about logic and common sense.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days</title>
    <desc>Romantic comedy film starring Kate Hudson and Matthew McConaughey, 2003. An advertising executive and ladies' man bets that he can make a woman fall in love with him in ten days.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522210500 +0000" stop="20260522211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FYI Daily</title>
    <desc>Latest news from the world of entertainment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522211000 +0000" stop="20260522222500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days</title>
    <desc>Romantic comedy film starring Kate Hudson and Matthew McConaughey, 2003. An advertising executive and ladies' man bets that he can make a woman fall in love with him in ten days.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522222500 +0000" stop="20260522225500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>..: Animated comedy. Peter overcompensates when he finds Chris is better endowed than he is, while Meg plots revenge after being humiliated by the school in-crowd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522225500 +0000" stop="20260522232500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family Guy</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. Peter's little white lie about Chris having done his homework snowballs into far bigger lies - until Peter is worshipped as a god.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522232500 +0000" stop="20260522235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated series about CIA agent Stan Smith. Stan develops anorexia when embarking on a strict exercise and dieting regime.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260522235500 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy series. Francine idolises a group of women who seem to have it all, but they are not as perfect as they first seem.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260523002500 +0000" stop="20260523005000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. Gene is upset when he breaks his favourite Christmas album, and Teddy's idea for a compact neighbourhood Secret Santa turns into a mess.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260523005000 +0000" stop="20260523011000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bob's Burgers</title>
    <desc>Animated comedy. An old photo that brings up unhappy memories and a Tina-Louise conflict over a desk leads Linda to enrol them in a loft bed-building effort.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260523011000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523055500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Next Level Chef USA</title>
    <desc>The final of the first series of the American version of the reality TV show. The three remaining contestants must create dishes on all three levels in 90 minutes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260523055500 +0000" stop="20260523062500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Craft Studio: Brian and Sarah build a stylish lounge space and convert a garage into a multi-purpose place for crafting and playing guitar.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486720" start="20260523062500 +0000" stop="20260523064000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Bonkers Guinness World Records</title>
    <desc>Matt Edmondson writes and narrates this series about the most entertaining Guinness World Records and the brilliant characters who set them as captured by TV shows.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522080500 +0000" stop="20260522101500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inspector Morse</title>
    <desc>Morse investigates a case of foul play at a brewery and learns that employees and family would stand to gain from the death of the brewery's manager.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522101500 +0000" stop="20260522112000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series set in a 1960s Yorkshire village. Nick is plagued by an alcoholic aristocrat as Greengrass entertains grand designs for Ashfordly Hall.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522112000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic drama series set in a 1960s Yorkshire village. Ashfordly Police investigate thefts from a fur factory, and Greengrass thinks that he has struck gold.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522143500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Barnaby's wife is unsure if she might be responsible for a dead body found in a cemetery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522143500 +0000" stop="20260522154000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Emmerdale</title>
    <desc>Debbie accepts Eli's proposal on the condition that their union will be a marriage of convenience and nothing more. David and Nicola decide to try to find a home together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522154000 +0000" stop="20260522161500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Jerry finds a flat for Teresa, Bill resolves to get Audrey back and David takes a risky step in his perfect boyfriend campaign. Dev begins to feel used.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522161500 +0000" stop="20260522165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Coronation Street</title>
    <desc>Darryl's comments land David in hot water with Tina. Ken is engrossed in writing his novel, and Kevin refuses to consider Tony's offer - leaving Sally worried about their finances.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522165000 +0000" stop="20260522175500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series set in a 1960s Yorkshire village. A schoolgirl witnesses a shooting on the local moors, and Greengrass sets up a pool competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522175500 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heartbeat</title>
    <desc>Nostalgic police drama series. Nick and Jo's wedding day finally arrives, but the groom is stranded on the moors as the church fills up.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Comedy-drama series. Martin and Louisa get into double trouble when they host a disastrous dinner party and their new childminder walks out on them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Comedy-drama series. Ruth has an unnerving mystery admirer, and Bert and Al demand action after one of Louisa's pupils gives a bad review of their restaurant.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Grantchester</title>
    <desc>When a suspicious death interrupts an Easter fete in the parish, Alphy attempts to use the case as a distraction from the recent lovelorn nature of his personal life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Grantchester</title>
    <desc>A death at the university plunges Geordie and Alphy into a world of academic adversaries while Alphy encounters a complication in his newfound romantic life with Meg.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522225000 +0000" stop="20260522235000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scott and Bailey</title>
    <desc>DCI Gill Murray, DC Janet Scott and DC Rachel Bailey find themselves working alongside the formidable DCI Julie Dodson when two badly burned bodies are found in woodland.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260522235000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Scott and Bailey</title>
    <desc>The team finally break down the wall of silence maintained by their four murder suspects. Meanwhile, Rachel cannot fight her attraction to Sean.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523005000 +0000" stop="20260523012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">On the Buses</title>
    <desc>Sitcom about a bus driver and his conductor pal. The inspector and Jack are the only contestants in a gardening competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523012000 +0000" stop="20260523013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523013000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523071000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inspector Morse</title>
    <desc>A body is found in Oxford's canals and the only clue to its identity points to a college - which of the respected contenders for a prestigious post is the killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523071000 +0000" stop="20260523092500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inspector Morse</title>
    <desc>Morse investigates the death of a member of the Clarets XI old boys' cricket team and realises that the players have more than cricket on their minds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523092500 +0000" stop="20260523112000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Endeavour</title>
    <desc>Crime drama series. Endeavour and Thursday must overcome corruption in Oxford's corridors of power when the death of a journalist threatens to expose past horrors.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523112000 +0000" stop="20260523132500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Agatha Christie's Marple</title>
    <desc>Crime thriller. Miss Marple arrives at Bertram's Hotel to find that secrets lurk there - however, things take an even more sinister turn when a maid is murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523132500 +0000" stop="20260523151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>When a pub landlady is crushed to death during a magic show, Barnaby and Nelson uncover conflict between the village church and ancient pagan traditions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523151500 +0000" stop="20260523171000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Barnaby investigates whether a ballad made famous by a late lamented folk singer could have been the inspiration for a murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523171000 +0000" stop="20260523190500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Barnaby tries to find out just who is targeting the Midsomer Vinae Winery - what does the attack have to do with the death of a child in a hit-and-run accident.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486726" start="20260523190500 +0000" stop="20260523210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Crime drama series. DCI Barnaby, DS Nelson, and new forensic pathologist Kam Karimore seek to identify the culprit when a wealthy landowner's body goes missing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522084500 +0000" stop="20260522095000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sweeney</title>
    <desc>Classic 1970s police drama series. Regan and Carter try to catch a blackmailer when Eddie Monk wins the pools but then receives threats about a historic robbery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522095000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BattleBots</title>
    <desc>US robot combat series. The temperature is rising as fan favourites return to the BattleBox and Golden Bolt winner End Game takes on Blip in the Main Event.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>Classic US action drama series. Magnum is hired to investigate the suspicious shotgun suicide of a film star.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522120500 +0000" stop="20260522130500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum, P.I.</title>
    <desc>.. Never Again: Classic US action drama series. Magnum follows a trail of duplicity and multiple murders as he investigates the disappearance of a man taken by a gang.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522130500 +0000" stop="20260522141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Saint</title>
    <desc>Freelance troubleshooter Simon Templar embarks on another adventure. The Saint joins the ranks of a mercenary army in order to prevent a hijacking.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522141000 +0000" stop="20260522151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Boon</title>
    <desc>Classic drama. A psychic predicts a motorbike crash, blood and an operating table for Ken - all of this comes true, but in a different way to how he expected it.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522151500 +0000" stop="20260522162500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sweeney</title>
    <desc>Tough 1970s police drama series. Regan is determined to nail a modern-day Bonnie and Clyde partnership who have already made fools of the police.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522162500 +0000" stop="20260522173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Minder</title>
    <desc>No Way to Treat a Daley: Comedy-drama series. Arthur acquires a hot-air balloon in a bid to break into the aerial advertising game, but the venture falls flat when it's hijacked.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522173000 +0000" stop="20260522183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Pickers</title>
    <desc>US documentary series. Mike and Frank search through a burnt-out warehouse and a collection of school buses before going head to head to identify a mystery item.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522183000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">EPCR Challenge Cup Final 2026 Montpellier v Ulster</title>
    <desc>Action from the final of the European rugby competition, as Montpellier go up against Ulster at San Mames Stadium in Bilbao.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting action from the world of All Elite Wrestling - the roster features world-class talent including Jon Moxley, MJF, Ricochet and Adam Page.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522214500 +0000" stop="20260522234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Dynamite</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting action from the world of All Elite Wrestling - the roster features world-class talent including Jon Moxley, MJF, Ricochet and Adam Page.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260522234500 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">All Elite Wrestling: Collision</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting action from AEW's newest show, featuring stars including Kyle Fletcher, Kazuchika Okada, Megan Bayne, Tommaso Ciampa and Claudio Castagnoli.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523004500 +0000" stop="20260523011000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two and a Half Men</title>
    <desc>American sitcom about a well-off bachelor. Charlie convinces Alan to take a trip to Las Vegas when he gets apprehensive about an upcoming medical procedure.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523011000 +0000" stop="20260523014000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Two and a Half Men</title>
    <desc>American sitcom about a well-off bachelor. Charlie goes to hospital after suffering back pain and hits on the doctor who treats him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523014000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523023000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Auto Mundial</title>
    <desc>The latest news and reviews from the world of cars.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523051500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of the 90s</title>
    <desc>A look back at the wide variety of sports covered by ITV during the 1990s - from the 1990 World Cup to athletics and Euro '96 to snooker - that includes many memorable moments.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523051500 +0000" stop="20260523062000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>Brian Moore introduces football highlights from August 1975 including Queens Park Rangers against West Ham, Leeds United against Sheffield United, and Sunderland against Blackpool.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523062000 +0000" stop="20260523072000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>Brian Moore introduces First Division highlights from September 1975 including Arsenal against Leicester City, Middlesbrough against Stoke City, and Derby County against Burnley.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523072000 +0000" stop="20260523083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Minder</title>
    <desc>Comedy-drama series. Arthur's new dispatch business is a runaway success, but Ray thinks it's all too good to be true and not that kosher either.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523083000 +0000" stop="20260523093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ITV Racing: The Opening Show</title>
    <desc>Oli Bell and the team are at Haydock ahead of a busy weekend of racing, plus all the latest news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523093000 +0000" stop="20260523103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Match Revisited</title>
    <desc>Brian Moore introduces FA Cup 4th round highlights from February 1972, including Reading against the holders Arsenal and Huddersfield Town against Fulham.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486853" start="20260523103000 +0000" stop="20260523113500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Sweeney</title>
    <desc>Tough 1970s police drama series. Regan is determined to nail a modern-day Bonnie and Clyde partnership who have already made fools of the police.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>It's Stephen's turn to join Stephen Mulhern and open the famous red boxes in the hope of leaving the Banker 100,000 pounds worse off.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>There are mystery prizes and a cash jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz for any player with the skill to see off their human rivals and conquer the machine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>There are mystery prizes and a cash jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz for any player with the skill to see off their human rivals and conquer the machine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>There are mystery prizes and a cash jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz for any player with the skill to see off their human rivals and conquer the machine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced game of words hosted by Adil Ray - crossing words this time alongside the reigning Lingo champions are sisters Harriet and Ella and best mates Steve and Dave.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Warwick Davis hosts as a team of five get their chance to win a bumper cash prize by answering Top 10 list questions, but can they take home 125,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ant and Dec's Limitless Win</title>
    <desc>There's more life-changing money on offer and surprises in store as Ant and Dec introduce father and daughter Paul and Tegan - and friends Abbi and Amy - to the Limitless Ladder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Time is Money</title>
    <desc>Sara Davies hosts the quick-fire quiz where contestants are given their prize money upfront but must race to keep hold of it while coping with pressure.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join host Stephen Mulhern for one of the most exciting gameshows of all time as one of his contestants takes on the infamous Banker for a life-changing cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced game of words hosted by Adil Ray - battling this time alongside the reigning Lingo champions are husband and wife Sue and Wayne and cousins Serena and Neha.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>The game of words hosted by Adil Ray - trying to Lingo all the way alongside the reigning Lingo champions are Brighton couple Louis and Jack and Nipula and her husband Kishor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>The fast-paced game of words hosted by Adil Ray - taking on the reigning Lingo champions this time are partners Jen and James and brothers-in-law Nish and Chris.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Millionaire Hot Seat</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Clarkson hosts the quiz where six players race to answer timed questions and hope to win one million pounds, but it all comes down to who's in the Hot Seat at the end.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522203000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Millionaire Hot Seat</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Clarkson hosts the quiz where six players race to answer timed questions and hope to win one million pounds, but it all comes down to who's in the Hot Seat at the end.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>There are mystery prizes and a cash jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz for any player with the skill to see off their human rivals and conquer the machine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>There's mystery prizes and a cash jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz for any player with the skill to see off their human rivals and conquer the machine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260522235500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts a quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a jaw-dropping cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260522235500 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tenable</title>
    <desc>Warwick Davis hosts as a team of five get their chance to win a bumper cash prize by answering Top 10 list questions, but can they take home 125,000 pounds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260523005000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unwind with ITV</title>
    <desc>Your daily escape designed to calm the mind and encourage relaxation and reflection.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260523060000 +0000" stop="20260523080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Shopping from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260523080000 +0000" stop="20260523090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deal or No Deal</title>
    <desc>Join host Stephen Mulhern for one of the most exciting gameshows of all time as one of his contestants takes on the infamous Banker for a life-changing cash prize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260523090000 +0000" stop="20260523100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>There are mystery prizes and a cash jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz for any player with the skill to see off their human rivals and conquer the machine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260523100000 +0000" stop="20260523110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>There's mystery prizes and a cash jackpot up for grabs in this thrill-packed quiz for any player with the skill to see off their human rivals and conquer the machine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260523110000 +0000" stop="20260523120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tipping Point</title>
    <desc>Ben Shephard hosts a quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a jaw-dropping cash jackpot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486821" start="20260523120000 +0000" stop="20260523130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lingo</title>
    <desc>The game of words hosted by Adil Ray - trying to Lingo all the way alongside the reigning Lingo champions are Brighton couple Louis and Jack and Nipula and her husband Kishor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cindy Crawford talks about the latest breakthroughs in skincare</title>
    <desc>Join Cindy Crawford as she talks to real customers about the breakthrough skincare system that keeps them looking their best. Take a trip to the stunning French countryside to see the rare French melon that defies the aging process.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>JD splits the rappers into two groups for a performance; the Migos visit to critique the rappers on collaboration; the parents clash about managing their artists in a group.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Jermaine Dupri takes the children to an underground battlerap to see which of the young rappers will step up to the plate; the rappers must catch the beat in front of an audience; the parents get heated as the end of the competition grows near.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>The rappers must create a stage show in front of a huge audience for their final assignment; Flo Rida and Mariah Carey stop by to give the children advice before their big performance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>The rappers perform in front of a huge audience that includes Da Brat and the contestants from Season 1; Jermaine Dupri chooses the winner.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Five artists join Jermaine Dupri for his 13-week rapper boot camp to compete for a contract with So So Def; the rappers try to make a good first impression on Fabolous; one young rapper shocks everyone.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Rick Ross joins Jermaine Dupri as he challenges the rappers to write about their work ethic; two rappers butt heads; one manager becomes suspicious.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Jermaine Dupri challenges the rappers to write a 12-bar verse about their dream; two managers go head to head; one artist struggles to keep it together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Celebrity stylist April Roomet and rapper Jeezy inspire the rappers to amp up their style; the rappers must earn money to shop for a photo shoot; one rapper copies another; an artist struggles to break free from a celebrity comparison.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Rappers iHeartMemphis and iAmDLOW give the contestants a lesson on generating buzz; the artists are challenged to create a signature dance that they must write, record and shoot a viral video for; one young artist struggles with dancing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>After the rappers get feedback from a focus group, one gets overconfident while another experiences a reality check; mentor Jadakiss tries to help the young rappers turn haters into fans.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>JD brings the group to his interview with the Durtty Boyz, where they throw the rappers an unexpected challenge; one rapper is shaken to the core.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>JD mixes up the management teams and then challenges the rappers to write, record and shoot a music video with past winners of "The Rap Game," Miss Mulatto and Mani.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>JD splits the young rappers into two teams and challenges them to perform at a high school halftime show.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Kelly Rowland and her personal trainer visit the five young rappers; JD tests the children on both their mental and physical stamina in the "Catch the Beat" challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Bow Wow helps hone the young rappers' media skills to prepare them for a press conference, television interview and photo shoot; Nova throws another artist under the bus.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Before signing, JD tests the young rappers in a battle rap; John John Da Don, Arsonal, Charlie Clips, DNA and Calicoe prepare the group; a rapper makes an unforgettable decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>After thirteen weeks of challenges, the artists prepare for their final performance; JD makes a decision, and awards one rapper the chain and the contract.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Kelly Rowland and her personal trainer visit the five young rappers; JD tests the children on both their mental and physical stamina in the "Catch the Beat" challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Bow Wow helps hone the young rappers' media skills to prepare them for a press conference, television interview and photo shoot; Nova throws another artist under the bus.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260523060000 +0000" stop="20260523070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>Before signing, JD tests the young rappers in a battle rap; John John Da Don, Arsonal, Charlie Clips, DNA and Calicoe prepare the group; a rapper makes an unforgettable decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465002" start="20260523070000 +0000" stop="20260523080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rap Game</title>
    <desc>After thirteen weeks of challenges, the artists prepare for their final performance; JD makes a decision, and awards one rapper the chain and the contract.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 430A</title>
    <desc>Early morning news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News Today</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Bleachers perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live with Kelly and Mark</title>
    <desc>Craig Ferguson stops by; Ariel Winter talks with the hosts about Disney's "Sofia the First: Royal Magic"; it's time for summer cooking!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>Mindfulness and meditation with Dora Kamau; style expert Melissa Garcia; singer-songwriter Jack Antanoff; Bleachers perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Actor Lakeith Stanfield; choreographer Fatima Robinson; summer travel with Mark Ellwood; Memorial Day entertaining with Meaghan Murphy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at Noon</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the local news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522163000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>An investigation into the poisoning of Wisconsin mother-of-two Julie Jensen takes a surprising turn when detectives learn that she wrote a letter days before her death pointing to a possible suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "Coraline"; Brooke Shields; Ella Bright; Clint Black; Pawsitively: Pawz Photo Studio; the NHL's Matthew Schaefer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 4</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 5:30</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 6</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260522233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>The Emmy-winning quiz show features a unique answer-and-question format.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260522233000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>In a classic game-show version of "Hangman," contestants solve word puzzles for cash and prizes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Showtime</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the latest storylines and news from across the NBA featuring in-depth analysis and highlights.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Western Conference Finals, Game 3.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260523033400 +0000" stop="20260523043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actor Robert De Niro; producer Jane Rosenthal; Maluma talks and performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260523043700 +0000" stop="20260523053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actress Lisa Kudrow; actor Nicholas Braun.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260523053700 +0000" stop="20260523061200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC5 News at 11</title>
    <desc>Staying informed with the news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467402" start="20260523061200 +0000" stop="20260523070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Top Story With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Reporting of breaking news and developing stories in real time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Wacky animal clips.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anthony Bourdain: Parts Unknown</title>
    <desc>Anthony Bourdain takes a wide-angle look at the culture and history of Armenia, heavily influenced by Europe and Russia; his guides include musician Serj Tankian (System of a Down), and historian-Armenian resident Richard Giragosian.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include an exploding portable toilet and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>A group of pranksters does a prank called Bagels Thrown at Crippled Man's Face in public and record people's reactions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comedian Jeff McEnery performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comedian and actor Roman Danylo performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include an exploding portable toilet and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522133000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>A group of pranksters does a prank called Bagels Thrown at Crippled Man's Face in public and record people's reactions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comedian Jeff McEnery performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Comedy Now!</title>
    <desc>Comedian and actor Roman Danylo performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>Gags include an exploding portable toilet and many more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522163000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>A group of pranksters does a prank called Bagels Thrown at Crippled Man's Face in public and record people's reactions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>A game show featuring passengers in a specially outfitted taxi who are surprised and offered the chance to win money by correctly answering a series of general knowledge or trivia questions on the way to their destination; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522173000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cash Cab</title>
    <desc>Unsuspecting members of the public climbing into an apparently normal taxicab, only to find themselves on national television, with a chance to win a small fortune; hosted by Adam Growe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Caught-on-camera videos that highlight the outrageous and wacky world of animals, hosted by comic Andy Woodhull.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522183000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Totally Funny Animals</title>
    <desc>Caught-on-camera videos that highlight the outrageous and wacky world of animals, hosted by comic Andy Woodhull.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>Riding the rails; a hunting we will go; a warning to watch out as objects in motion come to sudden stops.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522193000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Funniest Videos: Top 10 Countdown</title>
    <desc>The family we were born into can be our closest confidants, our partners in crime, and the people who know us best.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Star Wars</title>
    <desc>"Star Wars" takes its toll on George Lucas; while his marriage, relationships and physical health are breaking down, expectations are higher than ever for the series finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>When Lisa praises Homer's integrity, he is asked to be a World Cup referee; a slick gangster tests Homer's honesty.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Futurama</title>
    <desc>Sent underground for being a mutant, Leela leads an army of sewer-dwelling mutants in a rebellion against the surface people.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>There's no sound, but there sure are plenty of laughs. This crazy Quebec-based troupe uses the city as its stage, and its inhabitants, or victims, as characters! People are caught in a twisted yet funny web of comedic deception. This updated "Candid Camera" is a tad more risque and a little kookier with its practical jokes. The little snippets last only a few minutes, and some look more painful th</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Just for Laughs: Gags</title>
    <desc>There's no sound, but there sure are plenty of laughs. This crazy Quebec-based troupe uses the city as its stage, and its inhabitants, or victims, as characters! People are caught in a twisted yet funny web of comedic deception. This updated "Candid Camera" is a tad more risque and a little kookier with its practical jokes. The little snippets last only a few minutes, and some look more painful th</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Icons Unearthed: Star Wars</title>
    <desc>"Star Wars" takes its toll on George Lucas; while his marriage, relationships and physical health are breaking down, expectations are higher than ever for the series finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Jerry is shocked to hear the naughty suggestions on his tape recorder; George sees Elaine in a new light.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470474" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Seinfeld</title>
    <desc>Jerry straddles the fence regarding his latest flame (Tawny Kitaen); George's attention is focused on his date's (Susan Diol) nose.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Geek Australia</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bar Rescue</title>
    <desc>Jon Taffer sends Phil Wills and Danny Trejo to Houston, TX to rescue a business whose owner prefers to drink in the bar while his retired wife is left to pick up the pieces.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: OMG Moments</title>
    <desc>Cassie was on a downward spiral until she got a friend request from a rapper named Steve. Two and a half years later, Cassie and Steve are engaged - but they have yet to meet.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: OMG Moments</title>
    <desc>Jamey fell for Ari online, and he will do anything to meet her, but she will only do it on TV! Nev and Max help Ari share her story, and she hopes Jamey will accept her as she is.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: OMG Moments</title>
    <desc>Lucille led a simple life until she was asked to work for music producer Kidd Cole. Companies were never paid and one day Kidd couldn't be found. Will she get the answers she needs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: OMG Moments</title>
    <desc>Kiaira and Cortney had a baby despite Kiaira never meeting Cortney or the baby! Nev and Max try to bring the family together, but is this the greatest manipulation in Catfish history.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522153000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522163000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Judge Judy</title>
    <desc>Judge Judy Sheindlin, a former judge from New York, tackles actual, small claims cases with her no-nonsense attitude in which damages of no more than $5,000 can be awarded.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Geek Australia</title>
    <desc>When the Beauties and Geeks are tasked with swapping lives for a day, there are unexpected consequences.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Cribs UK</title>
    <desc>The cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around a host of famous faces pads. This week featuring the homes of reality King Joey Essex and chip loving Charlotte Dawson.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522183000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Friendzone</title>
    <desc>Chris doesn't know that Nicole likes him more than just friends. She puts her friendship on the line as she reveals her crush to him at a fun park.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Mom UK</title>
    <desc>Amber gets upset speaking to her mum about Ste's behaviour. Mia and Manley try to discuss Marliya's attitude which ends in another argument.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bar Rescue</title>
    <desc>Jon Taffer attempts to rescue a bar in Kingwood, TX whose owners have neglected both the business and the staff over the last several years.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pearl Jam: MTV Unplugged</title>
    <desc>Riding high on the success of their debut album, Pearl Jam taped this Unplugged episode at midnight at the Kaufman Astoria Studios in March of 1992.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aerosmith: MTV Unplugged</title>
    <desc>Enjoy this acoustic Unplugged set from legendary rock band Aerosmith, performed at the Ed Sullivan Theatre in New York, on 11th August 1990.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Help I Sexted My Boss</title>
    <desc>William Hanson and Jordan North take on the hilarious challenges of life. Expect laugh-out-loud stories, brutally honest moments, and a friendship that's as unlikely as it is unfiltered.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tattoo Fixers</title>
    <desc>Jay covers paramedic Anthony's tattoo, which is putting the frighteners on his patients. Alice disguises Sonny's unwanted present from his mates. Sketch tackles Alex's teddy bear design.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish UK</title>
    <desc>Alex has been chatting to Matt for a year and thinks he could be the one. But after several failed attempts to meet, Alex wants Julie and Oobah to track him down.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523014500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Help I Sexted My Boss</title>
    <desc>William Hanson and Jordan North take on the hilarious challenges of life. Expect laugh-out-loud stories, brutally honest moments, and a friendship that's as unlikely as it is unfiltered.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260523014500 +0000" stop="20260523023500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ink Master</title>
    <desc>Photo Realism tattoos turn disastrous when Bili has difficulty with muscle structure and Heather's art goes up in flames. A fourth artist is eliminated from the competition.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260523023500 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Cribs</title>
    <desc>Snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week featuring The Vamps singer Brad, supermodel Caprice and athletes Perri Shakes-Drayton and Mike Edwards.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523052000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teen Cribs</title>
    <desc>We take a look at ordinary teenagers Lindy and Anthony who live in extraordinary homes, and hear from the parents who give them whatever they want.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486755" start="20260523052000 +0000" stop="20260523061000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>Maddie and her mum were best friends until Maddie met her boyfriend. Crystal sees him as a bad influence and there's tension between the two. Maddie only wants what's best for her baby.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Travelling Auctioneers</title>
    <desc>Will Kirk and Christina Trevanion take their mobile auction house on the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Homes With George Clarke</title>
    <desc>Look inside homes that push the limits of design under this island's extreme conditions; ramble through a modernized courtyard, a house based on a love of circles, and an open-plan sculptural marvel inspired by the harsh, weather-beaten coastline.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes Makes It Right</title>
    <desc>After a student passes away, his teacher and class renovate his family's basement.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Life Below Zero Canada</title>
    <desc>In search of a steady supply of dog food, Becky and family establish a Fish Camp on Great Slave Lake; Kim and Pierre work on a new shelter; Bentley and new comer Jon Grenier attempt to secure essential sources of meat before winter sets in.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blown Away</title>
    <desc>The hot shop meets the big top in a circus-themed challenge filled with whimsical creatures, from a bearded dragon lady to a dapper walrus.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blown Away</title>
    <desc>The glassblowers split up into pairs; one team collaborates on a troll-like tree baby, while the other forges flames and fiery chili peppers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Drink Masters</title>
    <desc>Using all-natural ingredients, the mixologists pair up to construct botanical cocktails as industry pioneer Dale DeGroff joins the judges.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brink of Disaster</title>
    <desc>The coastal metropolis of Miami faces a triple threat of crumbling limestone bedrock, ferocious superstorms and relentless rising oceans.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lakefront Luxury</title>
    <desc>Amanda and Shawn are best friends and work colleagues; they are looking to pool their money together to buy a vacation lakefront property that gives them each space of their own; first, they view a fully restored house that was built in the 1960s.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522153000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lake Front Luxury</title>
    <desc>Newly engaged couple Michelle and Phil are looking for a lakefront home where they can entertain family and friends; Phil, a chef, is looking for a property with a great kitchen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes Makes It Right</title>
    <desc>After a student passes away, his teacher and class renovate his family's basement.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>Art conservator Lucia Scalisi is fascinated by an unusual religious artefact, Richard Talman works on a broken silver locket, and optics expert Richard Biggs is eager to get to work on a pair of vintage binoculars.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Separate trash from treasure with experts Raj and Stephanie and find out if Team Red or Team Blue makes a bigger killing at auction; pay a visit to the International Aviation Academy with Charlie to see a student-built electric airplane.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holmes Makes It Right</title>
    <desc>After a student passes away, his teacher and class renovate his family's basement.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great British Sewing Bee</title>
    <desc>Britain's best home sewers are tested on their sewing and dressmaking skills.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Landscape Artist of the Year</title>
    <desc>Joan Bakewell and Frank Skinner find the nation's best landscape painter.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Landscape Artist of the Year</title>
    <desc>Joan Bakewell and Frank Skinner find the nation's best landscape painter.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>Two teams of amateur collectors have an hour at an antiques fair to acquire the best bargains.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon, Gino and Fred's Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Watch Gordon, Gino, and Fred head to Scotland, where they try to impress Clan Ramsay with their bespoke kilts; laugh along as the guys dive for icy scallops, fail miserably at the Highland Games, and cook up a feast for a very important chieftain.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Unravel the history of Australia's top game at the Sherrin factory in Melbourne; see how leather, laces, and over a century of craftsmanship produce the perfect Aussie rules football, then join a local club as they test some game-changing new tech.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260523013000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Dr. Karl learns how cheese is made at the Bega factory; we find out that he knows more about String Theory than he does string cheese.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Millionaire Hoarders</title>
    <desc>Experts sift through homes crammed with potential treasure to unearth prized items that could raise life-changing sums of cash for their owners; can the hoarders and collectors bear to part with their possessions for the vital funds they need?</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gordon, Gino and Fred's Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Watch Gordon, Gino, and Fred head to Scotland, where they try to impress Clan Ramsay with their bespoke kilts; laugh along as the guys dive for icy scallops, fail miserably at the Highland Games, and cook up a feast for a very important chieftain.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Unravel the history of Australia's top game at the Sherrin factory in Melbourne; see how leather, laces, and over a century of craftsmanship produce the perfect Aussie rules football, then join a local club as they test some game-changing new tech.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470737" start="20260523043000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr Karl's How Things Work</title>
    <desc>Dr. Karl learns how cheese is made at the Bega factory; we find out that he knows more about String Theory than he does string cheese.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522075500 +0000" stop="20260522085500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Find It, Fix It, Flog It</title>
    <desc>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien visit Surrey and Middlesex, where Henry restores a pair of racing go-karts, and Simon repurposes an old butcher's block into a coffee table.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522085500 +0000" stop="20260522095500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Find It, Fix It, Flog It</title>
    <desc>Henry Cole refurbishes a classic Ford Mustang and a neon garage sign, while Simon O'Brien restores a classic Chopper bicycle and turns a bass guitar into a chair.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522095500 +0000" stop="20260522102500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The competition kicks off at Genice Hall and Cathy Hudson's Holland Hall Hotel in Upholland, Lancashire. There's a battle of the breakfasts and feedback that cuts deep.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522102500 +0000" stop="20260522105500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Lydia Perkins and Luke Mainprize host at The Railway Inn near Hull. Their guests find little to complain about, but the pressure is on for Luke's breakfast.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522105500 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Sarah and Pete Healey welcome their rivals to The Driftwood B&amp;B in Weymouth. Cathy and Genice find the place shipshape, and Lygia prepares to party when she spots disco balls.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The final visit is to The Bull Hotel in Wrotham, Kent, where owner Lygia Fontanella-Deadman and breakfast chef Mary Murray pride themselves on a luxury stay. But emotions run high.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522123500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;Bers meet for one last time to find out how much they've been paid. There's some surprising feedback before the winner is announced.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522123500 +0000" stop="20260522130500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>House-proud Charlotte plans a menu that reflects her personality and a rugby choir performance in her living room.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522130500 +0000" stop="20260522133500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Electrician and bachelor Steve serves soup, lasagne and homemade wine, on a lively night featuring a shocking revelation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522133500 +0000" stop="20260522141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Occupational nurse Christine serves up a menu of family favourites and a rock band performance. But then Ainsley tells Christine that she looks like one of her exes..</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522141000 +0000" stop="20260522144000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Retired French teacher Meic plans an authentic French menu. But what will he make of Charlotte turning up wearing an onion necklace.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522144000 +0000" stop="20260522151500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Dine with Me</title>
    <desc>Teaching assistant Ainsley hosts with an authentic Russian theme. Can her vodka-infused pavlova and some Russian dancing compensate for the cantankerous mood at the table.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522151500 +0000" stop="20260522155000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>John Whitworth welcomes his guests to the quirky The Edge Accommodation in Huddersfield. But a revelation about what's behind some of the doors makes the group feel uneasy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522155000 +0000" stop="20260522162000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Best friends Sally and Teresa pride themselves on the community spirit at Darwin Lake Holiday Village in Matlock. But accusations of cheating fly when the guests compete in a sports day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522162000 +0000" stop="20260522165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>The third visit is to Sands Resort Hotel and Spa in Newquay, where father and son Nicholas and Tom Malcolm's facilities include a maze. But John gets in a lather over bubble bath.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522165000 +0000" stop="20260522172000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>Phil Gilbert takes his guests back to basics at the Oak Tree Lane Yurt Site in Bratton Clovelly, Devon. They're wowed by the Mongolian yurts, but there are some home truths at dinner.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522172000 +0000" stop="20260522175000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four in a Bed</title>
    <desc>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time. There are tears, name-calling and bitter rebukes as the payments are revealed and the winner is announced.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522175000 +0000" stop="20260522185500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Location, Location, Location</title>
    <desc>We catch up with Liz and Carl, who secured a Victorian end-of-terrace, but was it just a fling in Tring? And in Bangor, was it a case of home is where the heart is for Lynne.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522185500 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PopMaster TV</title>
    <desc>Ken Bruce hosts the fifth heat, testing more music lovers from across the UK, all hoping to give a smash hit performance and book their spot in the Grand Final.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Panda</title>
    <desc>Panda Horror Show: Comic French crime drama from Walter Presents. What dark games have been played that led to a man's death in a forest? In French/subs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522210500 +0000" stop="20260522221000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Mum-of-six Lillian has extremely low blood pressure. Carolyn bruised her neck and face when she slipped on wet decking on a night out. Dennis is having difficulty breathing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522221000 +0000" stop="20260522231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>This episode meets patients whose visions of the world are rocked by life-changing events. Sergio, who's 44, and Alan, who's 71, have both been badly injured in cycling accidents.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260522231500 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">999: On the Front Line</title>
    <desc>Paramedics treat a woman with a broken leg, a man who's passed out in the street, a woman who's had a seizure on a bus, and a man who's collapsed in his bathroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260523002000 +0000" stop="20260523012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Mum-of-six Lillian has extremely low blood pressure. Carolyn bruised her neck and face when she slipped on wet decking on a night out. Dennis is having difficulty breathing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="486751" start="20260523012000 +0000" stop="20260523022500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">24 Hours in A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>This episode meets patients whose visions of the world are rocked by life-changing events. Sergio, who's 44, and Alan, who's 71, have both been badly injured in cycling accidents.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York</title>
    <desc>The local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in New York @ 6AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Bleachers perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>Mindfulness and meditation with Dora Kamau; style expert Melissa Garcia; singer-songwriter Jack Antanoff; Bleachers perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Actor Lakeith Stanfield; choreographer Fatima Robinson; summer travel with Mark Ellwood; Memorial Day entertaining with Meaghan Murphy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522153000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Live</title>
    <desc>Celebrity interviews and discussing recipes, beauty, fashion and current events pertinent to the tri-state region.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>An investigation into the poisoning of Wisconsin mother-of-two Julie Jensen takes a surprising turn when detectives learn that she wrote a letter days before her death pointing to a possible suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "Coraline"; Brooke Shields; Ella Bright; Clint Black; Pawsitively: Pawz Photo Studio; the NHL's Matthew Schaefer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522203000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 4:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 5:30</title>
    <desc>NY news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 6</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260522231500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">News 4 NY at 7</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522231500 +0000" stop="20260522233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Live</title>
    <desc>Celebrity interviews and discussing recipes, beauty, fashion and current events pertinent to the tri-state region.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260522233000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Individual on-set interviews with John Stamos, Demi Lovato, Valerie Bertinelli and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Showtime</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the latest storylines and news from across the NBA featuring in-depth analysis and highlights.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Western Conference Finals, Game 3.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: News 4 NY at 11</title>
    <desc>Local and regional news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="467015" start="20260523033400 +0000" stop="20260523043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actor Robert De Niro; producer Jane Rosenthal; Maluma talks and performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo have their grocery trip ruined by "Market Volatility," learn some interesting "New Information," and pamper themselves with "Adult Accidents.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood stand up to bird bullies, pledge to be rush wrecked and find out why you don't press that.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood pull out all of the Face Breaks, see how people are when they get Egg-Gressive and learn how soothing hips can be in Emotional Hip Support.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>On this episode of Ridiculousness, Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood get attacked by an ANGRY OSTRICH, bust out some COUNTERTOP CHOREOGRAPHY and try to JUST LET IT GO.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>On this episode of Ridiculousness, Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood pull out their big swords while going FROM ZERO TO MACHETE, get tricked by some moms that are fluent in MOM-NIPULATION and get their pimples popped because sometimes Z.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Dana White; "Banned-Kinis"; "Hot Heads.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo talk about things that are "Built to Break," diving for "Perfect Zeroes," and certain things that are "Absolutely Alabama.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get a kick out of people going "Lace To Face," cook up some questionable "Street Food," and come down with a case of "Big City Blues.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Carly Aquilino share a fear of falling into wells with "One in the Hole"; Rob reveals a new plan for exchanging insurance info in "Dent My Ride.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo welcome rap superstar Chief Keef; some people are "Back from the Dead"; some "Four Wheel Fun.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522133000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo fly in Big Little Air, eat whatever and whenever with Anythingterians, and learn that sometimes the smallest creatures are the weirdest in Ants, Man.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo scratch away at their "Dog Tendencies," get harassed by "Bro Blockers" and knock down valuables "Off the Wall.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522143000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo hit the pool and fail to fly in "dive dumb," meet some tiny terrors who were just "born bad," and get in the dirt with "first time gardeners.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Chanel welcome Anderson .Paak to check out some "SoCal Slams," celebrate people with "Signature Smiles" and party down at some "Wild Weddings.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522153000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo grab a good opportunity in "Seize the Moment," feel the terror of "Death Rides," find some funky feet in "Toe-Wareness.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Lolo Wood go to the carnival for some Sketchy Rides, catch and accidentally release in Fish Escape and get hit by Gender Reveal Shrapnel.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522163000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob Dyrdek, Steelo Brim and Lolo Wood meet some on the clock baddies in Action Packed Job Sites; they see some slowpokes in Sloth Blooded and check out some denials in Power Rejections.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Hip hop duo Rae Sremmurd; "SremmLife"; "Worse Than It Looks"; "Come Get Her.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522173000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob and Sterling are joined by Brittney Elena, and they get started by "Breaking the Ice" before moving on to Australian wildlife in "Danger Down Under," then they try to clear up some "Communication.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Maddy Smith try to interpret the behavior of some bizarre beasts, watch people ruin the fun for everyone, and look for a cure for some kids who are S.C.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522183000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob Dyrdek, Steelo Brim and Lolo Wood fall hard for the unanchored rung climbers in Free Laddering, run smack-dab into some happy but painful Joy Bolts and watch people throw their lives away.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo sit down with two-time Olympian Miles Chamley-Watson and cut right to the chase with "Swordplay," get a little creative with "Behind the Back," and watch people draw "First Blood.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522193000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Kripke has proof that Dr. Pemberton plagiarized his thesis in college, and Sheldon and Amy aren't sure if they should turn him in or not; Wolowitz learns that Bernadette wasn't the only waitress at the Cheesecake Factory who had a crush on him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Leonard is pleasantly surprised when Beverly comes to visit, and she's genuinely kind to him, until he finds out the real reason she's there; Denise and Stuart overstay their welcome at the Wolowitz house.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465080" start="20260522203000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Big Bang Theory</title>
    <desc>Sheldon and Amy await big news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522193000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Conor Maynard: MTV Brand New Live</title>
    <desc>Emerging British pop star Conor Maynard performs; songs include "Can't Say No" and "Vegas Girl"; live in London.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>Silversun Pickups perform songs including "Lazy Eye," "Panic Switch," and "Well Thought Out Twinkles.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522203000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unplugged</title>
    <desc>All Time Low performs in New York City; songs include "Weightless," "Dear Maria, Count Me In," and "Damned If I Do Ya (Damned If I Don't).".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MTV Live</title>
    <desc>John Legend performs in Rome; songs include "Used to Love U," "Save Room" and "Green Light.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic.Awesome.Videos</title>
    <desc>Features the hottest and most current music videos available.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Damiano David</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Push Showcase: Jordan Adetunji</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Ayra Starr</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260523013000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Shaboozey</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: The Warning</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260523023000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH Showcase: Flyana Boss</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464825" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PUSH: Chappell Roan Interview</title>
    <desc>Chappell Roan loves her whole debut album.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Shawn and Marlon (Shawn and Marlon Wayans) believe Pops (John Witherspoon) is dying, so they arrange for him to meet singer Gloria Gaynor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Music trio En Vogue sues Marlon after he sells an innocent picture of the group to a tabloid magazine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Wayans Bros.</title>
    <desc>Marlon (Marlon Wayans) witnesses a bank robbery and his cooperation with the police puts him in danger. With Shawn Wayans and John Witherspoon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>After falling for a single mother, a man wants to take their online relationship to the next level.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Derek, a veteran and single father, meets Kristen on Facebook; after developing a deep love, Derek's ready to meet her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Even though a young woman faces heartache from an Instagram lover, and moves on, she is still eager to meet.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>A woman from Long Island, N.Y., prepares to relocate to Tennessee for her internet love.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>After meeting on an LGBT site four years ago, a couple has yet to even engage in a video chat, raising red flags.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>After five years of talking to Matt, Kim is ready to meet up; as Max and Nev try to bring the two together, they uncover buried secrets that threaten to drive a wedge between the couple.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Lauren met Derek through MySpace eight years ago; Lauren, now 21 and a single mother, is ready to meet him for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Although always there for him online, Cierra always blows off Lawrence when they try to meet in person.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>After a year and a half of chatting with her online, Tyler thinks he may have a future with Amanda; Amanda may not be a girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Dylan has fallen for a beautiful model with an elusive secret; with all the standard red flags, Nev and Max assume it's an open and shut case, but the truth is far stranger than they imagined.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catfish: The TV Show</title>
    <desc>Love letters and voice messages have kept a couple together for a decade, in spite of having never met.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo break down the newest sport, known as "Drunning," salute "The Oddest Couples" and following the advice of some tutorials, they learn "How To: F... Up Your Head.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522213000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rapper Lil Jon joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to end the party in "Turn Down for This," have the hardest Christmas ever in "Merry Crunk-Mas," and to say "I do" in "Unique Proposals.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Chanel take a ride in some "Self-Crashing Cars," light a match to some "Fuel Fools" and mock some criminals with "No Getaway Plan.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Tami Roman; "Ratnaphobia"; "Street Dumb"; "Butt Regret.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260522233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo learn where it hurts in "Slam-natomy," make things appear in "Summoners," and take a gander at some evil geese in "Honk if You're Angry.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260522233000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Tommy Lee joins Rob, Steelo and Chanel as they enter "Total Mayhem," get blown away by "Industrial Size Fans" and roll around "In the Dirt.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Chanel try to dry off some "Soggy Boys," hire the "Extrasterminators" and discover the power of "Druggernauts.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Marcus Lemonis; "Lemonis Face"; "People, Process, Pain"; "They Do Exist.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Chanel and Steelo take a trip down the "Stair Slopes"; celebrating "Happy Brawlidays"; learning how bad getting air can be when the "Math Was Off.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260523013000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Schoolboy Q joins Rob, Steelo and Chanel to get wild on the "Numb Numb Juice," golf hard with "Hole Lotta Stress" and watch football dreams disappear in "Shattered Chances.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465113" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Chanel get high with some "Baked Beasts," barely slip through in "Threading the Needle" and get romanced by some "Unique Chivalry.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522083700 +0000" stop="20260522090700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522090700 +0000" stop="20260522093700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522093700 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "Take Me Home"; Paul Bettany and Will Sharpe; Michaela Jaé Rodriguez; Mýa; Rad Human: Foster Love; Jobi Riccio performs; Katherine Legge, Indy and NASCAR driver.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 4AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 4:30AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 5AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today in LA @ 6AM</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Bleachers perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>Mindfulness and meditation with Dora Kamau; style expert Melissa Garcia; singer-songwriter Jack Antanoff; Bleachers perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Actor Lakeith Stanfield; choreographer Fatima Robinson; summer travel with Mark Ellwood; Memorial Day entertaining with Meaghan Murphy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 11am</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522183000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">California Live</title>
    <desc>A daily lifestyle show that takes a ride through all of California, discovering many of the hidden treasures the state and its people have to offer including beauty, glamour, fitness, food, health, and tech.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "Coraline"; Brooke Shields; Ella Bright; Clint Black; Pawsitively: Pawz Photo Studio; the NHL's Matthew Schaefer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 3pm</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News at 4pm</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting the community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Showtime</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the latest storylines and news from across the NBA featuring in-depth analysis and highlights.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Western Conference Finals, Game 3.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC4 News</title>
    <desc>Breaking news, local stories, weather reports and events taking place in Southern California.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">California Live</title>
    <desc>Previously recorded; lifestyle show featuring the latest in travel, food and fashion.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260523043000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Individual on-set interviews with John Stamos, Demi Lovato, Valerie Bertinelli and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="469871" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline NBC</title>
    <desc>Anchored by Lester Holt, "Dateline" is NBC's signature newsmagazine, bringing viewers storytelling at its best by putting the pieces together to present the full picture of real-life events. NBC News correspondents cover compelling stories and issues of the day, ranging from mystery and crime to in-depth investigations and breaking-news events.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522080000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big Facts</title>
    <desc>Quando Rondo joins Big Bank for a special edition of "Big Facts" to discuss his current feelings and mental state, the importance of taking accountability for his decisions, and what being sober has helped him realize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos</title>
    <desc>A morning mix of jams to start the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Travis Scott</title>
    <desc>Travis Scott's latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of Future 2</title>
    <desc>REVOLT pays tribute to Future with his latest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Best of 21 Savage</title>
    <desc>A tribute to 21 Savage with his latest and greatest music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Out the Mud</title>
    <desc>NBA legends Zach Randolph and Tony Allen welcome a star-studded lineup of athletes and artists for can't-miss conversations about the journey to success.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">REVOLT Sports Weekly</title>
    <desc>In the series premiere, host Mariah Rose covers Micah Parsons' big return to Dallas, the Giants benching Russell Wilson, Kawhi Leonard's wild contract requests, and more. Presented by Levi's®.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522173000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Who got next? 310babii takes his shots in the 3-point contest before the season's winner is revealed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>In the season finale, Lynae Vanee reflects on the season with a live audience, chats with Ayanna Gregory, Guy Davis, Ashley Sharpton, and Lanny Smith about their famous parents, civil rights, and Actively Black at NYFW.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Out the Mud</title>
    <desc>NBA legends Zach Randolph and Tony Allen welcome a star-studded lineup of athletes and artists for can't-miss conversations about the journey to success.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Baller Alert Show</title>
    <desc>Hosts Ferrari Simmons and You Know BT are joined by celebrity guests for the latest in pop culture news, hot gossip, and fresh takes in this extension of the mega-popular entertainment brand Baller Alert.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Featuring the short films like "For Richard or Poorer" and "5-Star Rating.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">REVOLT Sports Weekly</title>
    <desc>In the series premiere, host Mariah Rose covers Micah Parsons' big return to Dallas, the Giants benching Russell Wilson, Kawhi Leonard's wild contract requests, and more. Presented by Levi's®.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Crew League: 3-Point Contest</title>
    <desc>Who got next? 310babii takes his shots in the 3-point contest before the season's winner is revealed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The People's Brief With Lynae Vanee</title>
    <desc>Lynae Vanee discusses the phenomenon of Black athletes choosing white partners; she talks dating within your race with journalist Shari' Nycole and podcaster Deanté Kyle and explains the importance of Black people loving out loud.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Short &amp; Fresh</title>
    <desc>Featuring the short films like "For Richard or Poorer" and "5-Star Rating.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260523010000 +0000" stop="20260523020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wrist Check Pod</title>
    <desc>Close friends and watch-collecting enthusiasts Perri Dash and Rashawn Smith welcome celebrities, friends, and fellow collectors for a deep dive into the booming business and culture of the global watch community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260523020000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untapped</title>
    <desc>Viewer-submitted music videos highlight untapped indie artists.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Mike Bonner; George Willborn; Sonya D. Scales (Sonya D.).</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260523033000 +0000" stop="20260523040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Def Comedy Jam</title>
    <desc>Comics: Geoff Brown; Tony Woods; Arceneaux &amp; Mitchell; Alex Thomas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260523040000 +0000" stop="20260523050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Verified Videos: After Hours</title>
    <desc>A late-night mix of the best raw and uncut hip-hop and R&amp;B music videos.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465207" start="20260523050000 +0000" stop="20260523060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untapped</title>
    <desc>Viewer-submitted music videos highlight untapped indie artists.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Early Today</title>
    <desc>This early-morning news covers overnight events, breaking domestic and international news as well as a preview of the day's anticipated events. The program also presents regular reports from the worlds of business, entertainment and sports.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 5:00a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 5:30a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 6a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today</title>
    <desc>Bleachers perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today 3rd Hour</title>
    <desc>Mindfulness and meditation with Dora Kamau; style expert Melissa Garcia; singer-songwriter Jack Antanoff; Bleachers perform.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Today With Jenna &amp; Sheinelle</title>
    <desc>Actor Lakeith Stanfield; choreographer Fatima Robinson; summer travel with Mark Ellwood; Memorial Day entertaining with Meaghan Murphy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News Today at 11a</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC News Daily</title>
    <desc>NBC News provides viewers with the latest national and international news; consumer, health and personal finance reporting; up-to-the-minute local news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>An investigation into the poisoning of Wisconsin mother-of-two Julie Jensen takes a surprising turn when detectives learn that she wrote a letter days before her death pointing to a possible suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Daily With Mario &amp; Kit</title>
    <desc>The daily one-hour syndicated entertainment news and lifestyle talk show co-hosted by Mario Lopez, Kit Hoover and Scott Evans features celebrity interviews and gives viewers insider access to Hollywood's biggest stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Kelly Clarkson Show</title>
    <desc>Kellyoke Encore: "Coraline"; Brooke Shields; Ella Bright; Clint Black; Pawsitively: Pawz Photo Studio; the NHL's Matthew Schaefer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 4p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 5p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522220000 +0000" stop="20260522223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 6p</title>
    <desc>Stay informed with the latest breaking news and headlines.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522223000 +0000" stop="20260522230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522230000 +0000" stop="20260522233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 7p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260522233000 +0000" stop="20260523000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Access Hollywood</title>
    <desc>Individual on-set interviews with John Stamos, Demi Lovato, Valerie Bertinelli and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260523000000 +0000" stop="20260523003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Showtime</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the latest storylines and news from across the NBA featuring in-depth analysis and highlights.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260523003000 +0000" stop="20260523030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>Western Conference Finals, Game 3.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260523030000 +0000" stop="20260523033400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260523033400 +0000" stop="20260523043700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Tonight Show Starring Jimmy Fallon</title>
    <desc>Actor Robert De Niro; producer Jane Rosenthal; Maluma talks and performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260523043700 +0000" stop="20260523053700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Late Night With Seth Meyers</title>
    <desc>Actress Lisa Kudrow; actor Nicholas Braun.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260523053700 +0000" stop="20260523060400 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC10 News at 11p</title>
    <desc>The latest local news, weather and investigative stories impacting your community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="468233" start="20260523060400 +0000" stop="20260523063300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NBC Nightly News With Tom Llamas</title>
    <desc>Tom Llamas anchors the latest news, going beyond the headlines to see how lives are affected by the world around them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-23</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522083000 +0000" stop="20260522090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Believe: Balance</title>
    <desc>Stunning videos of nature paired with soothing classical music create inspiration.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522090000 +0000" stop="20260522093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kabalah Yoga With Audi Gozlan</title>
    <desc>Audi Gozlan demonstrates a new system of yoga and meditation known as Kabalah Yoga.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522093000 +0000" stop="20260522100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ideacity</title>
    <desc>Presentations, keynotes and debates with some of the smartest people with big ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522100000 +0000" stop="20260522103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: The Elemental Series</title>
    <desc>A series of classical hatha yoga, plus mediations and breath work.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522103000 +0000" stop="20260522110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Relieving irritability.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522110000 +0000" stop="20260522113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anjelica's 22 Minute Workout</title>
    <desc>A revival of the '80s aerobics series offers workouts for a wide range of ages and abilities.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522113000 +0000" stop="20260522120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Namaste</title>
    <desc>Strengthening and aligning sequence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522120000 +0000" stop="20260522123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522123000 +0000" stop="20260522130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Yoga for improving asthma.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522130000 +0000" stop="20260522133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shaolin Tai Chi</title>
    <desc>Momentum qi, a basic energy that is the building block of everything in the body.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522133000 +0000" stop="20260522140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Namaste</title>
    <desc>Testing shoulder and leg flexibility.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522140000 +0000" stop="20260522143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pilates Pupil</title>
    <desc>Strengthening, stretching and toning with pilates.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522143000 +0000" stop="20260522150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522150000 +0000" stop="20260522153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Audi's Body Flow</title>
    <desc>Workout routines comprised of yoga, cardio, core workouts, stretching, fat burning movements, weight-lifting and toning exercises, hosted by Audi Gozlan.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522153000 +0000" stop="20260522160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Shaolin Tai Chi</title>
    <desc>Exercises to improve awareness of the body's internal signals for balance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522160000 +0000" stop="20260522163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Padma Yoga: The Elemental Series</title>
    <desc>A series of classical hatha yoga, plus mediations and breath work.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522163000 +0000" stop="20260522170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Anjelica's Dance Workout</title>
    <desc>Hip-hop, belly dance and flamenco combine into a cardio and body toning workout.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522170000 +0000" stop="20260522173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Yoga</title>
    <desc>Yoga for improving asthma.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522173000 +0000" stop="20260522180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pilates Pupil</title>
    <desc>Strengthening, stretching and toning with pilates.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522180000 +0000" stop="20260522183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Divine Intervention</title>
    <desc>Rabbi Shmuley talks with Sara about her panic attacks and why she feels she can't do anything without failing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522183000 +0000" stop="20260522190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ageless Gardens</title>
    <desc>A printmaker turns her lush garden into a living art gallery, where dancers, visual artists, and musicians all come together; a cosmopolitan artist combines floral imagery in playful and complex works, and finds inspiration growing in his back alley.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522190000 +0000" stop="20260522193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Healing Gardens</title>
    <desc>Exploring the healing nature of gardens and the transformative power derived from the act of gardening.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522193000 +0000" stop="20260522200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">BollyFit!</title>
    <desc>Host Reshmi Chetram combines her love of Bollywood and fitness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522200000 +0000" stop="20260522210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wycliffe</title>
    <desc>Wycliffe and Kersey have words when a blackmail investigation is put in jeopardy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470330" start="20260522210000 +0000" stop="20260522220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc Martin</title>
    <desc>Though Martin has opened his surgery, his patients seem to treat it more as a social hangout; Martin is forced to fire Elaine for incompetence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-22</date>
  </programme>
</tv>