<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260719051724 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="465053">
    <display-name lang="US">Syfy HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465138">
    <display-name lang="US">SundanceTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464919">
    <display-name lang="US">TLC HD (US)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465114">
    <display-name lang="US">TNT HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464987">
    <display-name lang="US">truTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719050000 +0000" stop="20260719073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Freaky</title>
    <desc>Seventeen-year-old Millie Kessler spends her days trying to survive high school and the cruel actions of the popular crowd. But when she becomes the latest target of the Butcher, the town's infamous serial killer, her senior year becomes the least of her worries. When the Butcher's mystical dagger causes him and Millie to magically switch bodies, the frightened teen learns she has just 24 hours to</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719073000 +0000" stop="20260719100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Play</title>
    <desc>A monster named Larry manifests itself through smartphones and mobile devices. Feature film version of the 2017 short film.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719100000 +0000" stop="20260719103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NECTAR TRI-PILLOW -Cooler, Comfy, Better Sleep! Buy One Get One FREE!</title>
    <desc>Discover the Nectar Tri-Comfort Cooling Pillow for the ultimate sleep experience! Adjustable to three firmness levels to provide customized support and cooling all night long. Order NOW to get a second pillow FREE, plus a 30-night home trial!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719103000 +0000" stop="20260719110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719110000 +0000" stop="20260719113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719113000 +0000" stop="20260719120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Freedom to Leave the House! Inogen Portable Oxygen</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719120000 +0000" stop="20260719143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Come Play</title>
    <desc>A monster named Larry manifests itself through smartphones and mobile devices. Feature film version of the 2017 short film.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719143000 +0000" stop="20260719163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Men in Black 2</title>
    <desc>Kay and Jay reunite to provide our best line of defense against a seductress who levels the toughest challenge yet to the MIB's mission statement: protecting the earth from the scum of the universe. While investigating a routine crime, Jay uncovers a plot masterminded by Serleena, a Kylothian monster who disguises herself as a lingerie model. When Serleena takes the MIB building hostage, there is </desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719163000 +0000" stop="20260719190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Men in Black 3</title>
    <desc>Even though agents J and K have been protecting the Earth from alien scum for many years, J still does not know much about his gruff partner. However, J soon gets an unexpected chance to find out what makes K tick when an alien criminal called Boris the Animal escapes, goes back to 1969, and kills K. With the fate of the planet at stake, J goes back in time and teams up with K's younger self to pu</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719190000 +0000" stop="20260719213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Freaky</title>
    <desc>Seventeen-year-old Millie Kessler spends her days trying to survive high school and the cruel actions of the popular crowd. But when she becomes the latest target of the Butcher, the town's infamous serial killer, her senior year becomes the least of her worries. When the Butcher's mystical dagger causes him and Millie to magically switch bodies, the frightened teen learns she has just 24 hours to</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260719213000 +0000" stop="20260720000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Willow</title>
    <desc>Enter the world of "Willow." Journey to the far corners of your imagination, to a land of myth and magic, where dream and reality live side by side ... to a place that never existed, a time that never was. It is a world where a young man named Willow lives out an adventure that explodes beyond the boundaries of his own hopes and fears.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720003000 +0000" stop="20260720023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mask</title>
    <desc>When timid bank clerk Stanley Ipkiss (Jim Carrey) discovers a magical mask containing the spirit of the Norse god Loki, his entire life changes. While wearing the mask, Ipkiss becomes a supernatural playboy exuding charm and confidence which allows him to catch the eye of local nightclub singer Tina Carlyle (Cameron Diaz). Unfortunately, under the mask's influence, Ipkiss also robs a bank, which a</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720023000 +0000" stop="20260720043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jumanji</title>
    <desc>A magical board game unleashes a world of adventure on siblings Peter and Judy Shepherd. While exploring an old mansion, the youngsters find a curious, jungle-themed game called Jumanji in the attic. When they start playing, they free Alan Parrish, who's been stuck in the game's inner world for decades. If they win Jumanji, the kids can free Alan for good, but that means braving giant bugs, ill-ma</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720043000 +0000" stop="20260720070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big</title>
    <desc>At a carnival, young Josh Baskin wishes he were big, only to wake up the next morning and discover his wish came true. But the more Josh experiences life as an adult, the more he longs for the simple joys of childhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720070000 +0000" stop="20260720100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Willow</title>
    <desc>Enter the world of "Willow." Journey to the far corners of your imagination, to a land of myth and magic, where dream and reality live side by side ... to a place that never existed, a time that never was. It is a world where a young man named Willow lives out an adventure that explodes beyond the boundaries of his own hopes and fears.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720100000 +0000" stop="20260720110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ark</title>
    <desc>An unexpected visitor wreaks havoc on the ship's electrical system.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720110000 +0000" stop="20260720120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ark</title>
    <desc>Two theories on what could and shouldn't have been are revealed when two realities intertwine.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720120000 +0000" stop="20260720140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jumanji</title>
    <desc>A magical board game unleashes a world of adventure on siblings Peter and Judy Shepherd. While exploring an old mansion, the youngsters find a curious, jungle-themed game called Jumanji in the attic. When they start playing, they free Alan Parrish, who's been stuck in the game's inner world for decades. If they win Jumanji, the kids can free Alan for good, but that means braving giant bugs, ill-ma</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720140000 +0000" stop="20260720163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big</title>
    <desc>At a carnival, young Josh Baskin wishes he were big, only to wake up the next morning and discover his wish came true. But the more Josh experiences life as an adult, the more he longs for the simple joys of childhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720163000 +0000" stop="20260720183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jumanji</title>
    <desc>A magical board game unleashes a world of adventure on siblings Peter and Judy Shepherd. While exploring an old mansion, the youngsters find a curious, jungle-themed game called Jumanji in the attic. When they start playing, they free Alan Parrish, who's been stuck in the game's inner world for decades. If they win Jumanji, the kids can free Alan for good, but that means braving giant bugs, ill-ma</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720183000 +0000" stop="20260720203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Mask</title>
    <desc>When timid bank clerk Stanley Ipkiss (Jim Carrey) discovers a magical mask containing the spirit of the Norse god Loki, his entire life changes. While wearing the mask, Ipkiss becomes a supernatural playboy exuding charm and confidence which allows him to catch the eye of local nightclub singer Tina Carlyle (Cameron Diaz). Unfortunately, under the mask's influence, Ipkiss also robs a bank, which a</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260720203000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Man on Fire</title>
    <desc>In a Mexico City wracked by a recent wave of kidnappings, ex-CIA operative John Creasy (Denzel Washington) reluctantly accepts a job as a bodyguard for 9-year-old Lupita (Dakota Fanning), the daughter of wealthy businessman Samuel Ramos (Marc Anthony). Just as Creasy begins to develop a fondness for the young girl, a bloodthirsty gunman (Jesús Ochoa) kidnaps her. Now, Creasy must pick off a succes</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I, Robot</title>
    <desc>In 2035, highly intelligent robots fill public service positions throughout the world, operating under three rules to keep humans safe. Despite his dark history with robotics, Detective Del Spooner (Will Smith) investigates the alleged suicide of U.S. Robotics founder Alfred Lanning (James Cromwell) and believes that a human-like robot (Alan Tudyk) murdered him. With the help of a robot expert (Br</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260719023000 +0000" stop="20260719053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sahara</title>
    <desc>Seasoned adventurer Dirk Pitt (Matthew McConaughey) sets out for the African desert with his sarcastic companion (Steve Zahn) in search of a ship rumored to have vanished long ago, the main draw being the treasure supposedly hidden within the lost vessel. When the daring duo come across a beautiful scientist (Penélope Cruz) who is juggling an escape from a warlord and a mission to stop the spread </desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260719053000 +0000" stop="20260719073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crocodile Dundee</title>
    <desc>A New York reporter heads to Australia to interview the living legend Mike Dundee (Paul Hogan). When she finally locates him, she is so taken with him that she brings him back with her to New York. In New York, Mike Dundee is amazed by the wonders of the city and the interesting people there.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260719073000 +0000" stop="20260719100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Crocodile Dundee II</title>
    <desc>Mick "Crocodile" Dundee (Paul Hogan) is settling into his new Manhattan home when a South American drug dealer (Hechter Ubarry) abducts his girlfriend, Sue Charlton (Linda Kozlowski). The drug dealer thinks images of his criminal activities, taken by Sue's photographer ex-husband, are now in her hands. The dealer takes Sue to Colombia and threatens her, hoping that she'll give up the evidence. But</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260719100000 +0000" stop="20260719130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unforgiven</title>
    <desc>When prostitute Delilah Fitzgerald (Anna Thomson) is disfigured by a pair of cowboys in Big Whiskey, Wyoming, her fellow brothel workers post a reward for their murder, much to the displeasure of sheriff Little Bill Daggett (Gene Hackman), who doesn't allow vigilantism in his town. Two groups of gunfighters, one led by aging former bandit William Munny (Clint Eastwood), the other by the florid Eng</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260719130000 +0000" stop="20260719160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Air Force One</title>
    <desc>After making a speech in Moscow vowing to never negotiate with terrorists, President James Marshall boards Air Force One with his family and advisers. When a group of terrorists led by Ivan Korshunov hijacks the flight, the President's principles are put to the test. Feigning escape, ex-solider Marshall stows away in the aircraft and must race against time to rescue his family and everyone else on</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260719160000 +0000" stop="20260719190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Captain Phillips</title>
    <desc>In April 2009, the U.S. container ship Maersk Alabama sails toward its destination on a day that seems like any other. Suddenly, Somali pirates race toward the vessel, climb aboard and take everyone hostage. The captain of the ship, Richard Phillips, looks to protect his crew from the hostile invaders, and their leader, Muse. The pirates are after millions of dollars, and Phillips must use his wit</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260719190000 +0000" stop="20260719230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Saving Private Ryan</title>
    <desc>Captain John Miller (Tom Hanks) takes his men behind enemy lines to find Private James Ryan, whose three brothers have been killed in combat. Surrounded by the brutal realties of war, while searching for Ryan, each man embarks upon a personal journey and discovers their own strength to triumph over an uncertain future with honor, decency and courage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260719230000 +0000" stop="20260720000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Apollo 13</title>
    <desc>This Hollywood drama is based on the events of the Apollo 13 lunar mission, astronauts Jim Lovell (Tom Hanks), Fred Haise (Bill Paxton) and Jack Swigert (Kevin Bacon) find everything going according to plan after leaving Earth's orbit. However, when an oxygen tank explodes, the scheduled moon landing is called off. Subsequent tensions within the crew and numerous technical problems threaten both t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720020000 +0000" stop="20260720050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Few Good Men</title>
    <desc>Lt. Daniel Kaffee (Tom Cruise) is a military lawyer defending two U.S. Marines charged with killing a fellow Marine at the Guantánamo Bay Naval Base in Cuba. Although Kaffee is known for seeking plea bargains, a fellow lawyer, Lt. Cdr. JoAnne Galloway (Demi Moore), convinces him that the accused marines were most likely carrying out an order from a commanding officer. Kaffee takes a risk by callin</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720050000 +0000" stop="20260720080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Apollo 13</title>
    <desc>This Hollywood drama is based on the events of the Apollo 13 lunar mission, astronauts Jim Lovell (Tom Hanks), Fred Haise (Bill Paxton) and Jack Swigert (Kevin Bacon) find everything going according to plan after leaving Earth's orbit. However, when an oxygen tank explodes, the scheduled moon landing is called off. Subsequent tensions within the crew and numerous technical problems threaten both t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720080000 +0000" stop="20260720083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night Court</title>
    <desc>A magazine votes Harry (Harry Anderson) one of New York's 10 most interesting men. With Markie Post and John Larroquette.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720083000 +0000" stop="20260720090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night Court</title>
    <desc>Christine's (Markie Post) ex-husband Tony (Ray Abruzzo) disrupts her blossoming romance with Harry (Harry Anderson). With John Larroquette.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720090000 +0000" stop="20260720093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night Court</title>
    <desc>Harry is arrested after spying on Christine and Tony in the park; Dan is swindled out of his "Phil's Foundation" funds.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720093000 +0000" stop="20260720100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night Court</title>
    <desc>The replacement (Gilbert Gottfried) for Dan (John Larroquette) is even more objectionable; Harry and Christine (Harry Anderson, Markie Post) face breaking up.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720100000 +0000" stop="20260720103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night Court</title>
    <desc>Dan, costumed as the "Phantom of the Courthouse," hides out in the subterranean levels of the building.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720103000 +0000" stop="20260720110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Night Court</title>
    <desc>Dan (John Larroquette) is humiliated by appearing in dog court when he returns to work. With Harry Anderson.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720110000 +0000" stop="20260720140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Captain Phillips</title>
    <desc>In April 2009, the U.S. container ship Maersk Alabama sails toward its destination on a day that seems like any other. Suddenly, Somali pirates race toward the vessel, climb aboard and take everyone hostage. The captain of the ship, Richard Phillips, looks to protect his crew from the hostile invaders, and their leader, Muse. The pirates are after millions of dollars, and Phillips must use his wit</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720140000 +0000" stop="20260720180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Saving Private Ryan</title>
    <desc>Captain John Miller (Tom Hanks) takes his men behind enemy lines to find Private James Ryan, whose three brothers have been killed in combat. Surrounded by the brutal realties of war, while searching for Ryan, each man embarks upon a personal journey and discovers their own strength to triumph over an uncertain future with honor, decency and courage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720180000 +0000" stop="20260720210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Few Good Men</title>
    <desc>Lt. Daniel Kaffee (Tom Cruise) is a military lawyer defending two U.S. Marines charged with killing a fellow Marine at the Guantánamo Bay Naval Base in Cuba. Although Kaffee is known for seeking plea bargains, a fellow lawyer, Lt. Cdr. JoAnne Galloway (Demi Moore), convinces him that the accused marines were most likely carrying out an order from a commanding officer. Kaffee takes a risk by callin</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720210000 +0000" stop="20260720220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team works to collect all the evidence they can in an effort to stop Ari.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Ari continues to wreak havoc on the team until Gibbs gets the face-off he has been awaiting.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>When a dead staff sergeant is found encased in a Civil War-era tomb, a cell-phone within it leads investigators to a safe deposit box.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>Members of the NCIS squad investigate when a petty officer with a double life is gunned down on a freeway.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719050000 +0000" stop="20260719060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Pao is upset that Russ hasn't done his therapy homework; Patrick reveals new information about Thais' trip to Brazil; sumit confesses why he and Jenny can't move out; Shekinah interrupts Rebecca, which sparks a huge fight between Rebecca and Zied.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719060000 +0000" stop="20260719070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>After surprising Baylen with a wedding day change, the couple goes to their menu tasting and Colin drops another bombshell; Julie worries the mounting pressure on Sammi to pull off the perfect celebration could further strain her relationship with Baylen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719070000 +0000" stop="20260719080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>Baylen's bridal shower finally arrives, but the celebration takes a turn when she reveals shocking future plans; later, Baylen and Sammi confront the tension that's been lingering; Baylen and Colin's trip to Myrtle might be over before it begins.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719080000 +0000" stop="20260719090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doubling Down with the Derricos</title>
    <desc>Karen and Deon remain at odds over Darian's college decision; when the boys take step class, they try to impress some girls with their moves; GG tells the children about her decision to stop chemotherapy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719090000 +0000" stop="20260719100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doubling Down with the Derricos</title>
    <desc>For Valentine's Day, the Derricos teach the children about dating; Dior's toothache triggers a trip to the dentist for all the children; when Deon hides the issues in the new house from Karen, it escalates their tension.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719100000 +0000" stop="20260719110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>Sammi's planned surprises lead to Baylen and Julie making some permanent decisions and spending an evening at a funeral home; Baylen reveals a worrisome medical concern; then, strong opinions during wedding planning put the sisters at odds again.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719110000 +0000" stop="20260719120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>Baylen returns from Kansas City still hurt by Sammi's Bridezilla comment; hoping to lift Baylen's spirits, Colin plans a Valentine's Day surprise while the couple meets a wedding officiant; Colin reveals another surprise she never saw coming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719120000 +0000" stop="20260719130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>After surprising Baylen with a wedding day change, the couple goes to their menu tasting and Colin drops another bombshell; Julie worries the mounting pressure on Sammi to pull off the perfect celebration could further strain her relationship with Baylen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719130000 +0000" stop="20260719140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>Baylen's bridal shower finally arrives, but the celebration takes a turn when she reveals shocking future plans; later, Baylen and Sammi confront the tension that's been lingering; Baylen and Colin's trip to Myrtle might be over before it begins.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719140000 +0000" stop="20260719150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>Krista's roaring 20s birthday bash brings glamour, jealousy, and surprise guests as Sammy and Steph's messy love triangle creates new suspicions; JJ confronts her past, and Krista takes a big climb toward independence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719150000 +0000" stop="20260719160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>Krista's birthday party sparks drama as Sammy distances himself from Steph after their kiss; Anthony pursues Krista, while JJ and John grow closer; after a night of Drag Bingo, John shares a shocking secret that leaves JJ stunned.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719160000 +0000" stop="20260719170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>Steph and John come clean about the secret relationships complicating their lives; Steph's Greek-themed celebration spirals into chaos when Krista confronts Sammy about the messy love triangle threatening to tear the group apart.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719170000 +0000" stop="20260719180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jay &amp; Pamela</title>
    <desc>Jay and Pamela brave New York City to make their runway debut during fashion week; they also want to take in all that NYC has to offer, but sightseeing has its challenges; Raphael and Rene are overwhelmed helping Jay and Pamela shop for a new bed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719180000 +0000" stop="20260719190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jay &amp; Pamela</title>
    <desc>With Jay turning 30, Pamela plans to celebrate this milestone birthday by giving him the party he always dreamt of as a child. And she has some surprises for him including one that makes him blush!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719190000 +0000" stop="20260719200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Steven and Olga navigate their new lives apart; Caesar travels across the country to meet his new love interest face-to-face; Anna reaches her breaking point as she questions Mursel's lack of intimacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719200000 +0000" stop="20260719210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Cortney and her fiancé have a major disagreement while wedding planning; Tyray goes to drastic lengths to improve his appearance; Armando faces high stakes as he tries for his U.S. visa again.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719210000 +0000" stop="20260719220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Ed makes a daring move towards a new romance; Kim searches for answers about her long-distance romance; Elise uncovers troubling information that could change everything with Josh; Gabe must confront the difficult next stage in his split from Isabel.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719220000 +0000" stop="20260719230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé</title>
    <desc>Marissa grapples with doubts; Mido is unsure about staying in the U.S.; Rasit bickers with Brandon at his first baseball game; Maxwell's family is shocked to learn Ashia's age; Annabelle is upset at Shea's drunken flirting; Catie meets up with Ryan.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260719230000 +0000" stop="20260720000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé</title>
    <desc>Marissa grapples with doubts; Mido is unsure about staying in the U.S.; Rasit bickers with Brandon at his first baseball game; Maxwell's family is shocked to learn Ashia's age; Annabelle is upset at Shea's drunken flirting; Catie meets up with Ryan.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720000000 +0000" stop="20260720020300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé</title>
    <desc>Edward struggles to fit in with Marissa's friends; Catie's mom is concerned about her recent behavior; Debby asks Mido for a decision; Anabelle offends Shea's daughter; Ashia seeks her mother-in-law's approval; Rasit makes an unlikely bond.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720020300 +0000" stop="20260720030300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth drops a shocking ultimatum when Andrei refuses to expand their family; Chloe is pushed to grow up fast with her mother moving away; Ashley and Manuel's explosive fights push their marriage to the breaking point.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720030300 +0000" stop="20260720040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jay &amp; Pamela</title>
    <desc>Pamela braces for family drama when she and Jay head to Kansas City for her grandmother's funeral; Rene and Raphael are caught completely off guard when Jay and Pamela reveal plans for the future; a visit to a fertility clinic has Pamela on edge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720040000 +0000" stop="20260720060300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé</title>
    <desc>Edward struggles to fit in with Marissa's friends; Catie's mom is concerned about her recent behavior; Debby asks Mido for a decision; Anabelle offends Shea's daughter; Ashia seeks her mother-in-law's approval; Rasit makes an unlikely bond.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720060300 +0000" stop="20260720070300 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth drops a shocking ultimatum when Andrei refuses to expand their family; Chloe is pushed to grow up fast with her mother moving away; Ashley and Manuel's explosive fights push their marriage to the breaking point.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720070300 +0000" stop="20260720080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jay &amp; Pamela</title>
    <desc>Pamela braces for family drama when she and Jay head to Kansas City for her grandmother's funeral; Rene and Raphael are caught completely off guard when Jay and Pamela reveal plans for the future; a visit to a fertility clinic has Pamela on edge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720080000 +0000" stop="20260720090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doubling Down with the Derricos</title>
    <desc>The Derricos head to the mountains to prove that black people ski too; determined to enjoy the vacation, GG hides her latest health symptoms from Deon, but fun on the slopes is cut short by a medical emergency.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720090000 +0000" stop="20260720100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doubling Down with the Derricos</title>
    <desc>The family deals with Karen's medical emergency; GG must come clean about her latest symptoms; the boys want to have their first ever hang out with girls they're crushing on at a skating rink.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720100000 +0000" stop="20260720110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jennifer Hudson Show</title>
    <desc>Jennifer welcomes back Aldis Hodge to talk about the new season of his show "Cross"; Jack Koltes, 15, is an autistic singer who has received more than 130 million views on social media in less than four months; his dad, Eric, accompanies him on guitar and says performing has helped Jack evolve, gain confidence, and form close friendships.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720110000 +0000" stop="20260720113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>When Gloria's mother and sister visit, they bring traditions, baby names and family baggage; Phil helps the kids with their problems; Mitchell and Cameron try to correct Lily's bad habits.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720113000 +0000" stop="20260720120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>When the lead in the school's production of "Phantom of the Opera" gets sick, Manny is willing to do anything to land the lead; Phil and Jay wind up in a golf-off with Mitch and Pepper; Gloria and Alex visit a psychic.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720120000 +0000" stop="20260720123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Claire and Phil's Valentine's Day romp ends with Claire in the hospital; Jay and Gloria's attempts at romance are interrupted by the kids; after hosting a wild party, Cam and Mitch are left with hangovers and a new housemate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720123000 +0000" stop="20260720130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Things get awkward when Phil shows up at Claire's college reunion; Jay is fixated on winning a big bowling tournament; a wig malfunction during an elaborate photo shoot with Joe leads to unfortunate results.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720130000 +0000" stop="20260720140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four Weddings</title>
    <desc>Kate has an eco-friendly party; Jennifer has chocolate handcuff favors; Erika's guests hop to a German polka; Roula's guests circle for traditional Greek dancing.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720140000 +0000" stop="20260720150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four Weddings</title>
    <desc>Solimar's bridesmaids choose their own rainbow-hued dresses; Kim's party is assigned all black; Melissa makes her entrance on a yacht; Sheneka impresses with Hollywood impersonators.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720150000 +0000" stop="20260720160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Steven and Olga navigate their new lives apart; Caesar travels across the country to meet his new love interest face-to-face; Anna reaches her breaking point as she questions Mursel's lack of intimacy.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720160000 +0000" stop="20260720170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Cortney and her fiancé have a major disagreement while wedding planning; Tyray goes to drastic lengths to improve his appearance; Armando faces high stakes as he tries for his U.S. visa again.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720170000 +0000" stop="20260720180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Ed makes a daring move towards a new romance; Kim searches for answers about her long-distance romance; Elise uncovers troubling information that could change everything with Josh; Gabe must confront the difficult next stage in his split from Isabel.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720180000 +0000" stop="20260720190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>John uncovers the truth about Steph and Sammy's history, but Sammy's flirting with Krista pushes tensions to the edge; when Steph invites Krista's potential love interest Anthony into the mix, jealousy erupts, ending in a blowout fight.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720190000 +0000" stop="20260720200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>Krista's roaring 20s birthday bash brings glamour, jealousy, and surprise guests as Sammy and Steph's messy love triangle creates new suspicions; JJ confronts her past, and Krista takes a big climb toward independence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720200000 +0000" stop="20260720210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>Krista's birthday party sparks drama as Sammy distances himself from Steph after their kiss; Anthony pursues Krista, while JJ and John grow closer; after a night of Drag Bingo, John shares a shocking secret that leaves JJ stunned.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720210000 +0000" stop="20260720220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>Steph and John come clean about the secret relationships complicating their lives; Steph's Greek-themed celebration spirals into chaos when Krista confronts Sammy about the messy love triangle threatening to tear the group apart.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Sarper braces himself for never-before-seen footage of his confrontation outside the bar; Kara explains her secret hallway conversation with Guillermo; the cast deliberates over who they would eat to survive in the wilderness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Thais becomes emotional while watching never-before-seen footage of her camp therapy session with Patrick and Dr. Tyrone, while Zied doubles down on wanting Rebecca to be a real wife; inspired by Russ and Pao, the cast plays Mouth Mayhem.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Tension amongst the couples reaches new heights at wilderness therapy. Guillermo draws a line in the sand with Kara. Pao is tired of waiting for Russ to be the man she wants. Shekinah and Sarper get exiled from the group.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719040000 +0000" stop="20260719060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rush Hour 2</title>
    <desc>After an explosion at the US Embassy in Hong Kong kills two customs agents investigating currency smuggling, Inspector Lee (Jackie Chan) and James Carter (Chris Tucker) search for the mastermind. Ricky Tan (John Lone), head of the Fu-Cang-Long Triad, sends out his minions to insure that Carter and Lee don't solve the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719060000 +0000" stop="20260719080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rush Hour 3</title>
    <desc>East meets West when the assassination of Ambassador Han leads to the reunion of Lee and Carter. In Paris, the pair must stay one step ahead of Chinese gangsters and Lee's childhood friend, as they track down an envelope containing the identity of a powerful crime lord.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719080000 +0000" stop="20260719090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team searches for an abducted college coed; Jubal has a tense encounter with Rina's mother.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719090000 +0000" stop="20260719100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>Maggie goes undercover working in a bar to investigate an anti-government group that regularly gathers there; a single father on the periphery of the group begins to fear he's in danger of becoming collateral damage.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719100000 +0000" stop="20260719110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a wealthy accountant is gunned down for secretly testifying against a notorious drug lord, the team's investigation leads Tiffany to ask for help from a friend who was formerly with the NYPD and is related to the dangerous crime boss.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719110000 +0000" stop="20260719120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>As the team works to rescue a 5-year-old kidnapping victim, Scola suspects the boy's mother isn't being forthcoming about why her son was targeted; Nina struggles to open up to Scola about matters in their relationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719120000 +0000" stop="20260719130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>Maggie returns from medical leave and helps the team investigate two homicides: a law student and a young man with possible gang ties; an inadvertent revelation from Maggie causes OA to worry that she is rushing back into the job too quickly.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719130000 +0000" stop="20260719140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a deadly truck heist arms the killers with enough ammonium nitrate to construct a massive bomb, the team discovers a link to a terrorist group Maggie is working to infiltrate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719140000 +0000" stop="20260719150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>A teen shows up at FBI headquarters with a large bag of fentanyl, seeking the team's protection from the men who shot his father; Nina goes to Scola with a proposal he is hesitant to accept.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719150000 +0000" stop="20260719160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The abduction of a young woman leads the team back to a cold case from 18 years ago, which pushes Isobel to reconnect with her old partner Jake and take another shot at solving one of her first cases at the bureau.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719160000 +0000" stop="20260719190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King Richard</title>
    <desc>Armed with a clear vision and a brazen, 78-page plan, Richard Williams is determined to write his two daughters, Venus and Serena, into history. Training on tennis courts in Compton, Calif., Richard shapes the girls' unyielding commitment and keen intuition. Together, the Williams family defies seemingly insurmountable odds and the prevailing expectations laid before them.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719190000 +0000" stop="20260719220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gran Turismo</title>
    <desc>The true story of a team of unlikely underdogs -- a working-class gamer, a former race car driver, and an idealistic motorsport executive -- who risk it all to take on the most elite sport in the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719220000 +0000" stop="20260719230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NASCAR Nation Pre-Race</title>
    <desc>From North Wilkesboro Speedway. Dale Earnhardt Jr., Jimmie Johnson, Jamie McMurray and Marty Smith set the stage for the Window World 450.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260719230000 +0000" stop="20260720000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NASCAR Cup Series</title>
    <desc>The 2026 Window World 450 of the NASCAR Cup Series gets underway at North Wilkesboro Speedway. This race returns after nearly 30 years and features drivers Ross Chastain, Austin Cindric and Austin Dillon on the 0.625-mile asphalt short track.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720020000 +0000" stop="20260720023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NASCAR Nation Post Race</title>
    <desc>From North Wilkesboro Speedway. Dale Earnhardt Jr., Jimmie Johnson, Jamie McMurray and Marty Smith recap the Window World 450.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720023000 +0000" stop="20260720053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gran Turismo</title>
    <desc>The true story of a team of unlikely underdogs -- a working-class gamer, a former race car driver, and an idealistic motorsport executive -- who risk it all to take on the most elite sport in the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720053000 +0000" stop="20260720060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers pretend to be bellhops and need to do and say what they're told while assisting unsuspecting guests to their rooms. Then, the guys need to give away tickets to an absurd made-up show they can no longer see.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720060000 +0000" stop="20260720070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Prue undergoes a supernatural sex change to stop a succubus who is slaying men; Piper books the Cranberries to play at her club.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720070000 +0000" stop="20260720080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>The sisters must turn to a reluctant teenage warlock for help when an evil witch escapes the confines of her 200-year-old prison.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720080000 +0000" stop="20260720090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>The sisters rally to protect a young man who has cracked an ancient code from a band of warlocks bent on draining the contents of his brain.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720090000 +0000" stop="20260720100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>At the summer camp where her mother drowned, Prue must follow in her mother's footsteps to protect the returning campers from a watery demon.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720100000 +0000" stop="20260720110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>The sisters are targeted by a hit woman known as Ms. Hellfire, and Prue goes undercover to find out who hired her, flirting with a cold-blooded criminal.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720110000 +0000" stop="20260720120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>A demon sets out to destroy Cupid and all his recent love matches, putting the relationships of the Charmed Ones in danger.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720120000 +0000" stop="20260720130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Phoebe protects an abandoned baby boy from a vengeful spirit that has methodically killed all the men in the child's family.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720130000 +0000" stop="20260720140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Prue and Phoebe break a code of conduct to cure Piper when she is hospitalized with a deadly disease, but the illness is spread to other patients.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720140000 +0000" stop="20260720145900 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>In light of a new fatality, a cult member's 1978 suicide is re-examined.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720145900 +0000" stop="20260720155800 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>A referee's deathbed confession leads to the reopening of a 1976 case in which an over-matched fighter died during a bout.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720155800 +0000" stop="20260720165700 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>A murder weapon is found during the city's gun recovery program, prompting detectives to take another look at the accidental 1987 drive-by shooting of a little girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720165700 +0000" stop="20260720175600 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>Lilly reopens the case of a young woman found murdered in her lover's apartment after the victim's brother gathers more information and finds more than one suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720175600 +0000" stop="20260720185500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>When drawings depicting the murder of a child from 1993 are found next to the victim's grave, the detectives reopen the case, and the child's former caregiver becomes the prime suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720185500 +0000" stop="20260720210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deep Blue Sea</title>
    <desc>On an island research facility, Dr. Susan McAlester is harvesting the brain tissue of DNA-altered sharks as a possible cure for Alzheimer's disease. When the facility's backers send an executive to investigate the experiments, a routine procedure goes awry and a shark starts attacking the researchers. Now, with sharks outnumbering their human captors, McAlester and her team must figure out a way t</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720210000 +0000" stop="20260720233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Godzilla: King of the Monsters</title>
    <desc>Members of the crypto-zoological agency Monarch face off against a battery of god-sized monsters, including the mighty Godzilla, who collides with Mothra, Rodan, and his ultimate nemesis, the three-headed King Ghidorah. When these ancient super-species-thought to be mere myths-rise again, they all vie for supremacy, leaving humanity's very existence hanging in the balance.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260720233000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Meg 2: The Trench</title>
    <desc>Jonas Taylor leads a research team on an exploratory dive into the deepest depths of the ocean. Their voyage spirals into chaos when a malevolent mining operation threatens their mission and forces them into a high-stakes battle for survival. Pitted against colossal, prehistoric sharks and relentless environmental plunderers, they must outrun, outsmart and outswim their merciless predators.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719050000 +0000" stop="20260719053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Kicking good people out and stealing from strangers is what's on the agenda for the Jokers; one of them ruins the entire night of a whole sports bar.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719053000 +0000" stop="20260719060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are snagging tips and spinning the Wheel of Doom to determine who will be the losing Joker, who will be excusing his bad behavior with a very generous compensation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719060000 +0000" stop="20260719063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>From bombing job interviews to trashing their Nona's sauce, the Jokers are not on their game; one Loser is punished by confronting cellphone users.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719063000 +0000" stop="20260719070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Busy week for the Jokers as they fake their marriage and interview folks for an upcoming lifestyle article, but one Loser couldn't keep up and will be forced to curse out in tonight's punishment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719070000 +0000" stop="20260719073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Reporting crimes and disrupting mealtimes in new challenges, but in the end, one Joker has to shed light onto something or someone important to complete his punishment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719073000 +0000" stop="20260719080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are hiding from their boss; they try to get away with sending bizarre emails; one loser won't make it through and is caught red-handed messing with women's purses.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719080000 +0000" stop="20260719090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Dumbest ...</title>
    <desc>A thief in a hijacked backhoe; a trucker using Flintstones-style technology; an Amish buggy driver who doesn't care about the rules of the road.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719090000 +0000" stop="20260719100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">World's Dumbest ...</title>
    <desc>Twenty stupid performers are in a countdown for a laugh.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719100000 +0000" stop="20260719103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers come in hot and correct rude behavior but not before adding an unusual fee to customers' bills; one of them couldn't wrap his mind around winning, so he must wrap his legs around something else.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719103000 +0000" stop="20260719110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are at Raising Cane's, and following that, asking for help to carry some furniture; one of them will be strapped to a speeding race car for his punishment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719110000 +0000" stop="20260719113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The team scouts for the next child star while trying not to laugh as Dan Jost reads his honest movie reviews in a focus group.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719113000 +0000" stop="20260719120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are breaking and entering a home for a commercial where they showcase their wackiest and over the top performances; to top it off, one loser will be trolling his way through the Liberty Science Center's Touch Tunnel!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719120000 +0000" stop="20260719123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Looks like the guys are selling sunsets, while later asking for help to film a bizarre video; one must lose and that one, must help a horse lose something from down under.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719123000 +0000" stop="20260719130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>One-star reviews are what Sal, Q, and Murr will be combating, and then testing their acting chops with special celebrity guest, Richard Kind; at the end, one of them will be forced to cut the line at a grocery store, over, and over, and over, and over.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719130000 +0000" stop="20260719133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>It's mayhem as the guys work as mall janitors with an out-of-control trash can and then devise a plan of revenge on our producer Dan Cast; in the end, two Jokers lose this episode race and will be getting the refill of a lifetime.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719133000 +0000" stop="20260719140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>From being overprotective parents to disclosing perplexing side effects, one Joker can't handle the challenges and will learn that all that glitters is not gold.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719140000 +0000" stop="20260719143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Q, Murr and Sal throw and catch grocery items in the Joker vs. Joker challenge with special celebrity guest, Jax.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719143000 +0000" stop="20260719150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Murr, Q and Sal sit alongside a stranger to participate in a documentary-style interview; they try to upcharge guests again as hotel concierge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719150000 +0000" stop="20260719153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers bring their plastic newborns to the grocery store; they pitch new community programs that the local community will find quite strange.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719153000 +0000" stop="20260719160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Sal and Murr air out their dirty laundry by sorting out the whites and colors of their relationship through past clips from the "Couples Therapy Special" with Casey Jost, unlicensed therapist.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719160000 +0000" stop="20260719183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Road House</title>
    <desc>An ex-UFC fighter tries to escape his dark past and penchant for violence by taking a job in a Florida roadhouse.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719183000 +0000" stop="20260719220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dune: Part Two</title>
    <desc>Paul Atreides unites with Chani and the Fremen while seeking revenge against the conspirators who destroyed his family. Facing a choice between the love of his life and the fate of the universe, he must prevent a terrible future only he can foresee.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719220000 +0000" stop="20260719230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NASCAR Nation Pre-Race</title>
    <desc>From North Wilkesboro Speedway. Dale Earnhardt Jr., Jimmie Johnson, Jamie McMurray and Marty Smith set the stage for the Window World 450.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260719230000 +0000" stop="20260720000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NASCAR Cup Series</title>
    <desc>The 2026 Window World 450 of the NASCAR Cup Series gets underway at North Wilkesboro Speedway. This race returns after nearly 30 years and features drivers Ross Chastain, Austin Cindric and Austin Dillon on the 0.625-mile asphalt short track.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720020000 +0000" stop="20260720023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NASCAR Nation Post Race</title>
    <desc>From North Wilkesboro Speedway. Dale Earnhardt Jr., Jimmie Johnson, Jamie McMurray and Marty Smith recap the Window World 450.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720023000 +0000" stop="20260720030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Q, Sal, Murr, and Joe help jobseekers land their next big gig; then, they meet with a focus group to pitch their memoirs; the losing joker must deliver the news.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720030000 +0000" stop="20260720033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Murr and Q are going on a trip down memory lane and watching extended never-been-seen-before clips from the last few years.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720033000 +0000" stop="20260720040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Sal, Q and Murr kick off another season of antics by getting themselves stuck in a vent system and confusing customers at a bagel shop; our losing Joker will face humiliation in a punishment that's tough to swallow.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720040000 +0000" stop="20260720043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are back working as dry cleaners and TV producers, but one of them can't keep it together and must endure concertgoers who have escaped their enclosures.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720043000 +0000" stop="20260720050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers face off by recording voiceover for a fake video game and playing the concerned parent writing to their kid's school; but one Joker burns out with a punishment that's gotta sting.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720050000 +0000" stop="20260720053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Joey Fatone interviews the Jokers for a fake documentary; the guys react to an overly emotional phone call for an underwhelming reason; one Joker checks out and is forced into being the world's worst grocery store employee in his punishment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720053000 +0000" stop="20260720060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers hit the grocery store aisles dressed in absurd disguises, then train someone in using aggressive phone tactics for charity donations; the losing Joker must subject themselves to scientific probing into their hidden emotions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720060000 +0000" stop="20260720063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers can't contain the laughs as they answer survey questions for a new snack food and present the world's worst pharmaceutical ads; the loser will work up a sweat in a punishment that's all pain, no gain.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720063000 +0000" stop="20260720070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Attention shoppers; the Jokers make mischief by taking unflattering pictures of grocery store patrons, then posing as horrible employees at the Yeti store; tonight's loser must meet his fate in a punishment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720070000 +0000" stop="20260720073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers play unprofessional actors in a fake commercial then make wild assumptions about other mall goers; one Joker breaks and is tasked with becoming the strictest security guard imaginable in his punishment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720073000 +0000" stop="20260720080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers pretend to be medical students in training with standardized patient actors, then play the hero and break up a public fight, hoping to earn applause; one Joker has to put his hips where his mouth is and settle a bet of his own making.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720080000 +0000" stop="20260720083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720083000 +0000" stop="20260720090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Never Scrub Your Floors Again</title>
    <desc>See why this cleaning tool replaces chemicals and hard labor!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720090000 +0000" stop="20260720093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Overwhelmed with IRS Debt? Keys to Resolving Tax Debt</title>
    <desc>See how one company is changing people's lives by helping them put their tax problems to rest.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720093000 +0000" stop="20260720100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Never Scrub Your Floors Again</title>
    <desc>See why this cleaning tool replaces chemicals and hard labor!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720100000 +0000" stop="20260720103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The jokers are asking strangers to send an important text to their loved ones and hunting for their missing kid using crazy descriptions.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720103000 +0000" stop="20260720110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers hatch horrible revenge schemes on their office bullies, then put one poor contractor through the wringer as they attempt home improvement projects; tonight's loser will be gifted the world's finest douchemobile.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720110000 +0000" stop="20260720113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are back as wacky inventors pitching a whole new line of AI-themed gadgets; they fill out bogus incident reports with unsuspecting deli customers; the loser will be forced to demonstrate mentally absurd and physically grueling apps.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720113000 +0000" stop="20260720120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers pretend to be bellhops and need to do and say what they're told while assisting unsuspecting guests to their rooms. Then, the guys need to give away tickets to an absurd made-up show they can no longer see.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720120000 +0000" stop="20260720123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers' mothers visit as overprotective parents meeting a Joker's girlfriend; a Joker must convince a stranger to pose as his girlfriend for a Broadway outing with his mother.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720123000 +0000" stop="20260720130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are back playing lawyers, trying to convince unsuspecting focus group participants to sign off on ridiculous terms and conditions before they go in. Then they put their family businesses to the test by asking strangers if their radio ad is good to stay on the air. Later, one joker will be getting revenge in an elaborate punishment that the other two are really going to feel.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720130000 +0000" stop="20260720133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are hitting the floor as restaurant owners of a New York Pizzeria, forced to say and do whatever wacky things the other guys tell them to. Later, they're back at Tompkins Square bagels trying to hunt down a customer that left a scathing review. Then, the losing joker is in for a punishment that really sucks.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720133000 +0000" stop="20260720140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are back at Colonial Diner, offering some new bizarre specials to unsuspecting patrons; they take a ride through the park; after a nasty fall, the Joker must get park goers to help them out from underneath their bike.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720140000 +0000" stop="20260720143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers are unsympathetic store managers, forced to throw out a disruptive customer before dealing with the wrath and disdain of fellow patrons; thus the guys must get a bystander to take their side during a heated argument with their fake spouses.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720143000 +0000" stop="20260720150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys pose as unreceptive receptionists, then head to a world-famous wax museum; tonight's losers are taken on a chopper ride from hell.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720150000 +0000" stop="20260720153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys conduct focus groups where they try to sell illogical inventions and clash with shoppers at a shoe store.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720153000 +0000" stop="20260720160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Joe, Sal, Murr and Q play a game of copycat at the park while babysitting children who are being told what to do and say by the other guys; catch and release battle at the supermarket.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720160000 +0000" stop="20260720163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys pose employees at a copy center, then conduct bizarre exit interviews for moviegoers; tonight's big loser becomes the least popular guy at the party.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720163000 +0000" stop="20260720170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys pose as inhospitable restaurant hosts, then beg strangers to babysit their grandfathers; the longest punishment in the show's history.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720170000 +0000" stop="20260720173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys play helpless oddballs in a waiting room, then ask grocery shoppers for cash; tonight's loser becomes the number one enemy of women everywhere.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720173000 +0000" stop="20260720180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys make passes at supermarket shoppers, then pose as reporters; with a painfully invasive punishment, tonight's loser is the butt of the joke.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720180000 +0000" stop="20260720183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Joe, Sal, Q and Murr go face-to-face at a clothing store; the loser crashes a classy book reading, learning that silence is golden.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720183000 +0000" stop="20260720190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Murr, Joe, Sal and Q go head-to-head in a focus group; the loser gets hunted down during a walk of shame.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720190000 +0000" stop="20260720193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys take name-calling to new heights and ask for bogus donations; the night's big loser gets a shave that's too close for comfort.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720193000 +0000" stop="20260720200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys show who's boss at a fast food joint, and whisper sweet nothings at a grocery store; the big loser helps a cow in labor, and almost buys the farm.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720200000 +0000" stop="20260720203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Joe, Sal, Murr and Q ask strangers to help them bury bizarre items, then go head-to-head to see who can cling the longest to a stranger's car; the Joker makes a room full of enemies at an auction house.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720203000 +0000" stop="20260720210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys pose as cranky NY cab drivers, then solicit undeserved congrats in the park; tonight's loser is sheriff of an old Nevada town.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720210000 +0000" stop="20260720213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys pose as crummy cashiers at a grocery store and then play with laser pointers at a mall; a loser gets soaked with embarrassment.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720213000 +0000" stop="20260720220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys bark up the wrong tree at a pet store; tonight's big loser virtually loses his mind after entering a world he's never visited before.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys look for partners in crime at a supermarket and throw caution to the wind as helpless romantics; tonight's loser has a serious wardrobe malfunction.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720223000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys spin a wheel and creep out shoppers at the mall; tonight's punishment leaves one Joker soaked, enraged, and totally shocked.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Field of Dreams</title>
    <desc>When Iowa farmer Ray hears a mysterious voice one night in his cornfield saying "If you build it, he will come," he feels the need to act. Despite taunts of lunacy, Ray builds a baseball diamond on his land, supported by his wife, Annie. Afterward, the ghosts of great players start emerging from the crops to play ball, led by "Shoeless" Joe Jackson. But, as Ray learns, this field of dreams is abou</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
</tv>