<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260624090016 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="464919">
    <display-name lang="US">TLC HD (US)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465138">
    <display-name lang="US">SundanceTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465053">
    <display-name lang="US">Syfy HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464987">
    <display-name lang="US">truTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465006">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465114">
    <display-name lang="US">TNT HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="12517">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Max HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465278">
    <display-name lang="US">Start TV Network</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9577">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Witness+1</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465234">
    <display-name lang="US">Vice HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465206">
    <display-name lang="US">VH1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465208">
    <display-name lang="US">TV ONE HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624080000 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way</title>
    <desc>Shekinah confronts Sarper about his ex; James' promises to Meitalia's parents come back to haunt him; Josh's jealousy issues frustrate Lily; Statler and Dempsey's reunion is overshadowed by Statler's anxiety.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way</title>
    <desc>Chaos ensues after James and Tatha tell her family they are staying in Indonesia; Joanne and Sean plan how to reveal they have been married for two years; Corona tells Ingi she has been hiding her anger from him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jennifer Hudson Show</title>
    <desc>Holly Robinson Peete (series "Kings Court") discusses the HollyRod Foundation; "American Idol" Season 23 winner Jamal Roberts tells of the upcoming Brandy and Monica tour and performs; Victoria Garrick Browne (podcast "Real Pod").</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Mitchell plants an idea in Jay's head; Manny's date gets a makeover from Gloria.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624113000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>A visit from an old friend (Minnie Driver) leaves Claire feeling inadequate; Mitchell tries to help Gloria with some legal issues.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Claire and Phil plan a Valentine's Day excursion; Jay takes Gloria to a comedy show; Cameron and Mitchell try to play cupid for Manny.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624123000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Phil tries to conquer his fear of the dark when he and Luke go on a discovery expedition underneath the house; Mitchell and Cameron invite Lily's pediatrician over for brunch.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untold Stories of the E.R.</title>
    <desc>A newlywed's hand gets stuck in a kitchen appliance; a student with an injury down under; a heavy drinker has complications.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Untold Stories of the E.R.</title>
    <desc>An ER doctor's friend arrives at the hospital combative and out of control; a cyclist's throat is torn open when a driver opens a car door in her path; a nursing student is found passed out on the hospital floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr. Pimple Popper</title>
    <desc>Cedric has a bump on his eye and a painful lump on his neck that have kept him from working; Katherine's large ear cluster puts her neighborhood watch job at risk; Andrea uses makeup to cover the white spots all over her face and body.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr. Pimple Popper</title>
    <desc>Jimmy's flaky, raised alligator skin feels like an itchy hell, and he wants it cured so he can find love; Djuka is a stubborn guy with a stubborn bump; Talina has hundreds of tumors all over her body, causing embarrassment and discomfort.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr. Pimple Popper</title>
    <desc>Tyler's hands are so dry, cracked and painful that he considers getting them amputated; Ebonee covers the tiny bumps around her eyes with sunglasses; Ralph feels like a cyst factory with painful cysts covering his back.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dangerously Obese</title>
    <desc>Natalie and her bedridden mother, Felicia, have been plagued with obesity for most of their lives; Dr. Procter vows to give them both weight loss surgery if Natalie can lose weight and Felicia can walk again.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dangerously Obese</title>
    <desc>Keith's big size is on the verge of ruining his marriage and his health; he must fight the temptations of a cruise vacation in order to make weight for life-saving bariatric surgery.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Face Doctors</title>
    <desc>After enduring years of torment over her looks, Holly wants a straighter nose; Leo has become isolated since losing his left eye to cancer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Face Doctors</title>
    <desc>Alex becomes a prisoner in his own home after having his nose surgically removed; Tracey struggles with an infected gaping hole in her neck due to an insect bite.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Most Extreme Humans</title>
    <desc>Mark's hands are 20 times bigger than a normal adult male's. After learning that his condition may require amputation, Mark stopped seeing doctors. Now troubling changes to his hands means he must go back. If not for himself, then for his young daughter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625000000 +0000" stop="20260625010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Most Extreme Humans</title>
    <desc>Winner of the Uganda's Ugliest Man contest, Godfrey has a rare disorder that has left him disfigured; with 10 children, a new baby on the way, and his condition worsening, he is seeking medical answers that will determine his future.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625010000 +0000" stop="20260625020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Most Extreme Humans</title>
    <desc>Following people from around the globe living with rare and remarkable physical conditions.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Face Doctors</title>
    <desc>After falling off a balcony, part of Alfie's skull is missing, and his brain is unprotected; Sue hopes an artificial eye will bring back her confidence.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625030000 +0000" stop="20260625040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Face Doctors</title>
    <desc>Brenda seeks help for her one-sided paralyzed face to get her smile back; surgeon Vijay attempts a difficult procedure to straighten Meghan's jaw.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625040000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Most Extreme Humans</title>
    <desc>Winner of the Uganda's Ugliest Man contest, Godfrey has a rare disorder that has left him disfigured; with 10 children, a new baby on the way, and his condition worsening, he is seeking medical answers that will determine his future.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Most Extreme Humans</title>
    <desc>In Brazil, Claudio lives with a condition that bent his head backward. Ahead of his 50th birthday, he wants to climb a sacred mountain. In Norway, Birgitte lives with a different presentation of the same condition. She's training for the next Paralympics.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Face Doctors</title>
    <desc>After falling off a balcony, part of Alfie's skull is missing, and his brain is unprotected; Sue hopes an artificial eye will bring back her confidence.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Face Doctors</title>
    <desc>Brenda seeks help for her one-sided paralyzed face to get her smile back; surgeon Vijay attempts a difficult procedure to straighten Meghan's jaw.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way</title>
    <desc>Joanne reveals the truth to her mom before leaving for Ireland; James and Tatha end up in tears when things get lost in translation; Lily's sister presses Josh on his lack of income; Statler and Dempsey face a frigid first night in their van.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé: The Other Way</title>
    <desc>Corona has a surprising first encounter with Ingi's parents; Joanne and her sons leave for Ireland to meet Sean; Statler and Dempsey hit the open road; an argument between Sarper and Shekinah ruins their birthday.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jennifer Hudson Show</title>
    <desc>Brittany Snow (show "The Hunting Wives," series "The Beast in Me").</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Phil invites his high school girlfriend (Judy Greer) to the house; Jay accidentally kills Manny's pet turtle, then goes to extremes to cover his tracks; overworked Mitchell stands up to his boss.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625113000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Claire and Phil each take on one of the kids' school projects; Gloria and Cameron bond during a night out.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>The release of a new product Phil wants coincides with his birthday; Mitchell has a newfound desire to toughen up; Cameron gets involved in a neighbor's marital problems.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625123000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Luke and Manny's hot-tempered basketball coach quits during a game, causing Jay and Phil to jockey to fill the position; Mitchell takes Cameron along to meet a prospective employer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four Weddings</title>
    <desc>A backyard bash for Jenean; Lauren's guests are treated to a black-tie affair; RhiAnna has a horse and carriage entrance; Lisa's year of meticulous planning.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four Weddings</title>
    <desc>Mirian's father is officiating; a hand puppet carries Kim's rings; Jen throws a five-hour cocktail party; Colleen has an alcohol-free reception.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>Baylen's tics are in full swing as she and Colin embrace the holiday spirit by taking Christmas photos with Santa and the dogs; Allen plans a heartfelt surprise for his and Julie's 25th anniversary; Baylen and Colin reveal a major wedding decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>Baylen and Colin's wedding announcement sends everyone into planning overdrive; with the help of her mom and grandmothers, Baylen heads to Florida to find her perfect wedding dress; Allen receives major news that could uproot the entire family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>Baylen's search for her dream wedding dress yields too many contenders. Anxiety goes into overdrive as Baylen and Julie head to Kansas for a girls' weekend with Sammi. And Sammi's surprise outing pushes Baylen outside her comfort zone.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Ashley has a romantic proposal for Chantel; Corey and Evelin make a life-changing move from Ecuador to the United States where Evelin experiences winter for the first time; Sam struggles with addiction and risks losing his family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Meghan is ready to give birth, but John wants a paternity test to find out if he's the father. Natalie opens up about insecurities as she takes the stage in a beauty pageant. Evelin already wants to leave Washington and worries marriage won't survive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Jovi and Yara's marriage reaches a breaking point. John and Meghan brace themselves for paternity test results that could change everything. Tania searches for both a lesbian partner and a sperm donor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Shekinah and Sarper remain distant; Jenny reveals why she doesn't trust Sumit; Rebecca and Zied unravel over control; Kara and Guillermo face painful truths; Patrick and Thais disagree on how to spend their time; Pao questions her future with Russ.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Kara and Guillermo's fight over her explicit content pushes him to make a big decision, Russ and Pao spiral after a blowout, Patrick and Thais clash over his high sex drive, and Sumit drops a surprising confession in therapy that leaves Jenny stunned.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>With bonus scenes; Russ and Pao face brutal intimacy truths; Jenny and Sumit try to reignite desire; Kara hopes their sexual connection brings her and Guillermo back together; Sarper holds a grudge against Rebecca.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624074500 +0000" stop="20260624094500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Enforcer</title>
    <desc>Police officer "Dirty Harry" Callahan (Clint Eastwood) is reassigned from homicide to personnel after his latest use of excessive force. Meanwhile, a terrorist group calling themselves the People's Revolutionary Strike Force organizes a series of crimes in San Francisco, hoping to enrich themselves. When they kidnap the mayor (John Crawford) and steal rockets and rifles for their next attack, Harr</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624094500 +0000" stop="20260624101500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Fred asks a professional gambler to teach Lamont and his friends a lesson.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624101500 +0000" stop="20260624104500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>When Lamont falls for an older woman, Fred schemes to show him how ridiculous it is.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624104500 +0000" stop="20260624111500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Lamont and Rollo mistakenly think Fred has only six months to live and set him up on a date with Lena Horne.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624111500 +0000" stop="20260624114500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Grady feels out of place when he moves in with his daughter and her family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624114500 +0000" stop="20260624121500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Fred puts his home and business up for sale when he hears an intense earthquake will hit and looks for a shelter in Las Vegas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624121500 +0000" stop="20260624143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dirty Harry</title>
    <desc>Cop Harry Callahan (Clint Eastwood) attempts to track down a psychopathic rooftop killer before a kidnapped girl dies. When he is found Harry abuses the murderer's civil rights putting him back on the streets. Once he is released he hijacks a school bus and Harry must go after him again. The only way to stop this vicious killer is in cold blood.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624143000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Magnum Force</title>
    <desc>A maverick cop, Callahan, investigates the slaying of some of the West Coast's most powerful criminals. Dismissing the theory that the murders are the result of underworld squabbling, Callahan learns that each of the victims was killed by a slug from a.357 Magnum, the most powerful handgun in the world and a weapon widely used by the San Francisco Police Department.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Enforcer</title>
    <desc>Police officer "Dirty Harry" Callahan (Clint Eastwood) is reassigned from homicide to personnel after his latest use of excessive force. Meanwhile, a terrorist group calling themselves the People's Revolutionary Strike Force organizes a series of crimes in San Francisco, hoping to enrich themselves. When they kidnap the mayor (John Crawford) and steal rockets and rifles for their next attack, Harr</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Stone must combat the emotional testimony of an estranged wife on trial for the murder of her husband and his lover.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Concluding that a young suicide was forced into pornography by her mother, Stone charges the woman with manslaughter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A convicted murderer argues to be set free because detectives unlawfully searched his home, a cardboard box.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A couple who refused treatment on religious grounds for their gravely ill child are charged with murder later.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>An apparent attack on a pregnant woman who then miscarried is part of a blackmail scheme against her boss.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625000000 +0000" stop="20260625010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A child's corpse reopens a 31-year-old missing-persons case and forces a woman to delve into painful memories.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625010000 +0000" stop="20260625020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>While investigating a college student's rape accusation, Cerreta and Logan find evidence indicating she might be trying to hide her own sexual promiscuity.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>An ex-football star's murder over gambling debts is in doubt because of a double-indemnity policy on him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625030000 +0000" stop="20260625040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A catastrophic fire at a dance club leads to the prosecution of an immigrations officer who supplied bogus papers to aliens.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625040000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The corpse of a sleazy producer found in a meat locker leads to an investigation of his co-producer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A celebrity's obsessive fan claims insanity as a defense tactic, so Stone sets out to prove the stalker is mentally competent.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Stone's fervor to defeat an old adversary (George Grizzard) jeopardizes his case against the murderer of an FBI witness.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Stone may need an 11-year-old girl to testify against her father, who has been charged with murdering his wife.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Aunt Bee scolds Opie and tells him to stay away from the courthouse after he handcuffs a classmate to a flagpole; Opie, annoyed at the situation, decides to run away from home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625083000 +0000" stop="20260625090500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy must cancel a big date with Helen when he has to confer with a lawyer in Raleigh, N.C.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625090500 +0000" stop="20260625094000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy sends Opie to an exclusive camp for boys, where he makes a wealthy friend.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625094000 +0000" stop="20260625101500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Millie's former boyfriend threatens to beat up Howard if the two don't break up.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625101500 +0000" stop="20260625105000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Aunt Bee, summoned for jury duty, disagrees with fellow jurors on her first case.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625105000 +0000" stop="20260625112500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Opie disobeys Andy and tape-records a bank robber's confession.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625112500 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Opie joins a rock 'n' roll group and starts getting failing grades in school.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625123500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Aunt Bee goes picnicking and dining out with a charming lecturer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625123500 +0000" stop="20260625131000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy opens a coin laundry to save money for Opie's college education.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625131000 +0000" stop="20260625134500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Howard proposes marriage to Millie at the bakery where she works.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625134500 +0000" stop="20260625142000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy learns the truth when he sees his cousin alight from a freight train.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625142000 +0000" stop="20260625145500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Goober takes over at the office when Andy comes down with the flu.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625145500 +0000" stop="20260625153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Howard quits his boring job as county clerk and becomes a Caribbean island beachcomber.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625153000 +0000" stop="20260625160500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Goober buys the gas station with financial backing from Andy and Emmett.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625160500 +0000" stop="20260625164000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy and Opie are thrilled when a station owner offers Aunt Bee a job as a television chef.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625164000 +0000" stop="20260625171500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Emmett's wife and his brother-in-law needle him to become an insurance salesman.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625171500 +0000" stop="20260625175000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Opie breaks a bottle of expensive perfume at his new job as a drugstore clerk.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625175000 +0000" stop="20260625182500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>A $500 bequest to the Mayberry church almost provokes a schism over how to spend it.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625182500 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Barney is on the spot when he gets Andy to let him use the Taylor home for an East-West summit meeting.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A teen who claimed his shooting of a friend was accidental was involved in a similar incident years earlier.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A murder suspect faces the death penalty if the victim's parents can get him extradited to Connecticut.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A rehabilitation center staffed by Catholic nuns faces closure after an investigation into allegations of sexual molestation leads to rape charges.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Stone brings charges against an apartment building's landlord and superintendent after a baby freezes to death.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The murder of a Jewish diamond merchant apparently because of bias turns out to be a cover-up of embezzlement.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>As the detectives search for a racial motive in the slaying of a Chinese honor student, they receive a tip leading them to the boy's scholastic rival.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260624075800 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Insidious: Chapter 3</title>
    <desc>When teenager Quinn Brenner (Stefanie Scott) senses that her late mother is trying to contact her, she seeks help from gifted psychic Elise Rainier (Lin Shaye). However, Elise's tragic past makes her reluctant to use her abilities. After Quinn is attacked by a malevolent entity, her father (Dermot Mulroney) pleads with Elise for help. With support from two parapsychologists, Elise ventures deep in</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2012</title>
    <desc>Earth's billions of inhabitants are unaware that the planet has an expiration date. With the warnings of an American scientist (Chiwetel Ejiofor), world leaders begin secret preparations for the survival of select members of society. When the global cataclysm finally occurs, failed writer Jackson Curtis (John Cusack) tries to lead his family to safety as the world starts falling apart.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260624133000 +0000" stop="20260624163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pacific Rim</title>
    <desc>Long ago, legions of monstrous creatures called Kaiju arose from the sea, bringing with them all-consuming war. To fight the Kaiju, mankind developed giant robots called Jaegers, designed to be piloted by two humans locked together in a neural bridge. However, even the Jaegers are not enough to defeat the Kaiju, and humanity is on the verge of defeat. Mankind's last hope now lies with a washed-up </desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260624163000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">2012</title>
    <desc>Earth's billions of inhabitants are unaware that the planet has an expiration date. With the warnings of an American scientist (Chiwetel Ejiofor), world leaders begin secret preparations for the survival of select members of society. When the global cataclysm finally occurs, failed writer Jackson Curtis (John Cusack) tries to lead his family to safety as the world starts falling apart.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom</title>
    <desc>Three years after the destruction of the Jurassic World theme park, Owen Grady and Claire Dearing return to the island of Isla Nublar to save the remaining dinosaurs from a volcano that's about to erupt. They soon encounter terrifying new breeds of gigantic dinos while uncovering a conspiracy that threatens the entire planet.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spider-Man: Homecoming</title>
    <desc>Thrilled by his experience with the Avengers, young Peter Parker returns home to live with his Aunt May. Under the watchful eye of mentor Tony Stark, Parker starts to embrace his newfound identity as Spider-Man. He also tries to return to his normal daily routine -- distracted by thoughts of proving himself to be more than just a friendly neighborhood superhero. Peter must soon put his powers to t</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spider-Man: Homecoming</title>
    <desc>Thrilled by his experience with the Avengers, young Peter Parker returns home to live with his Aunt May. Under the watchful eye of mentor Tony Stark, Parker starts to embrace his newfound identity as Spider-Man. He also tries to return to his normal daily routine -- distracted by thoughts of proving himself to be more than just a friendly neighborhood superhero. Peter must soon put his powers to t</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pompeii</title>
    <desc>In 79 A.D., Pompeii, a bustling port city, stands in the shadow of Mount Vesuvius. Milo (Kit Harington), a former slave, is a gladiator who has caught the eye of Cassia (Emily Browning), a wealthy merchant's daughter. However, their difference in social status is not the only obstacle to their love; Cassia has been promised to Corvus (Kiefer Sutherland), a corrupt Roman senator. When the eruption </desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625073000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>An obsessed Oliver Crangle (Theodore Bikel) tells an FBI agent that a drastic transformation will take place on all the evil people in the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>The disreputable patter of a used-car dealer changes when he buys a haunted car from an old man and finds he is suddenly unable to lie to his customers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625083000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A bad-tempered writer is convinced the machines in his home are conspiring to destroy him.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>Elva Keene, confined to her bed and wheelchair, is driven to distraction by mysterious telephone calls on a dead line.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625093000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>A group of neighbors turns into a hostile mob when they try to invade one family's bomb shelter, believing a UFO attack is imminent.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Twilight Zone</title>
    <desc>The leader (James Whitmore) of a colony stranded on an asteroid resists rescue. With James Broderick.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pompeii</title>
    <desc>In 79 A.D., Pompeii, a bustling port city, stands in the shadow of Mount Vesuvius. Milo (Kit Harington), a former slave, is a gladiator who has caught the eye of Cassia (Emily Browning), a wealthy merchant's daughter. However, their difference in social status is not the only obstacle to their love; Cassia has been promised to Corvus (Kiefer Sutherland), a corrupt Roman senator. When the eruption </desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Edward Scissorhands</title>
    <desc>A scientist (Vincent Price) builds an animated human being -- the gentle Edward (Johnny Depp). The scientist dies before he can finish assembling Edward, though, leaving the young man with a freakish appearance accentuated by the scissor blades he has instead of hands. Loving suburban saleswoman Peg (Dianne Wiest) discovers Edward and takes him home, where he falls for Peg's teen daughter (Winona </desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625153000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Pompeii</title>
    <desc>In 79 A.D., Pompeii, a bustling port city, stands in the shadow of Mount Vesuvius. Milo (Kit Harington), a former slave, is a gladiator who has caught the eye of Cassia (Emily Browning), a wealthy merchant's daughter. However, their difference in social status is not the only obstacle to their love; Cassia has been promised to Corvus (Kiefer Sutherland), a corrupt Roman senator. When the eruption </desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spider-Man: Homecoming</title>
    <desc>Thrilled by his experience with the Avengers, young Peter Parker returns home to live with his Aunt May. Under the watchful eye of mentor Tony Stark, Parker starts to embrace his newfound identity as Spider-Man. He also tries to return to his normal daily routine -- distracted by thoughts of proving himself to be more than just a friendly neighborhood superhero. Peter must soon put his powers to t</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone</title>
    <desc>Adaptation of the first of J.K. Rowling's popular children's novels about Harry Potter, a boy who learns on his eleventh birthday that he is the orphaned son of two powerful wizards and possesses unique magical powers of his own. He is summoned from his life as an unwanted child to become a student at Hogwarts, an English boarding school for wizards. There, he meets several friends who become his </desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Van Helsing</title>
    <desc>After spending years in a coma, Vanessa is thrust into a post-apocalyptic world ruled by vampires; Vanessa makes a discovery that could save humanity, but makes her a target for vampires.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624083000 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624093000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Overwhelmed with IRS Debt? Keys to Resolving Tax Debt</title>
    <desc>See how one company is changing people's lives by helping them put their tax problems to rest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys swipe food off diners' plates, tutor students in languages they don't speak and try to start a dance party.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624103000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys conduct a focus group with unique consumer questioning, are totally unfit as trainers in a gym class, and pretend to work at a famous New York bakery.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guy's serve up a new round of mischief at White Castle, pose as bouncers and offer phony horoscope readings.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624113000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys try to sell diamonds to unsuspecting couples ready to tie the knot and pose as members of an unwelcoming committee down at the boardwalk.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys share humiliating text messages in a quiet waiting room, shampoo women's hair and teach a driver's ed course.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624123000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys put their green thumbs to the test as workers in a garden center, demonstrate how not to save lives as CPR instructors, and they're full of bologna working a deli counter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys bark up the wrong tree at a pet store, pose as golf instructors and give their regards to Broadway.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624133000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys raise money for absurd charities, join diners mid-meal; offer unsolicited advice to shoppers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys toy with customers at a candy store using bizarre party props, they all try their hands at nosing, and they break the rules of appropriate elevator etiquette.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624143000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys relive their best hidden camera hijinks, offer behind the scenes insight, and reveal the hidden cameras to one unsuspecting victim.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys discuss their most shocking incidents, the best reactions, and reveal never before seen moments from the cutting room floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624153000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys relive the moments that made them cringe, crack under pressure, and reveal behind the scenes info on the surprises that came out of left field.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys work as dental assistants; work at a movie theater snack counter and participate in a photo shoot at a public park for their blogs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624163000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys try to hold strangers' hands in the park, get touchy-feely with patrons in a comic book store, and race through the aisles of a grocery store.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys say all the wrong things when conducting sensitivity training, have unexpected celebrity sightings on the street, and are forced into being unreceptive receptionists in a busy office.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624173000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys share shameful secrets in the park; don headsets at a fast food drive-through; try to convince unsuspecting strangers to dance with them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys enlist shoppers to settle senseless debates in the mall; scream for ice-cream as patrons in a parlor; protest unconventional causes in the park.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624183000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys debut uninspiring inventions to stunned focus groups, use people for pillows, talk shoppers out of their desired products; then the loser has his laptop make noises in a coffee shop.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys search for imaginary places with a little help from strangers, pick their own poison in the park, and there's a surprise behind every door in the horrifying hunt for a house-sitter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624193000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys endure a shakedown at a discount store, test fate with the "Wheel of Doom" and attempt to become Hibachi chefs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys face off as optometrists, they break each other's banks giving bad financial advice, and push outrageous political platforms in a fruitless hunt for votes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624203000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys host a taste test with embarrassing survey questions, haggle over priceless pieces of junk at a flea market, and tank as attendants at a gas station.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys test fate with the "Wheel of Doom"; Joe and Sal act as mall janitors; dental assistants; Sal faces his fear of cats.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624213000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Joe, Sal, Murr, and Q try their hands at giving palm readings, manicures, and much more in a humiliating quest to avoid facing the ultimate punishment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys lose sight of social etiquette with strangers in the park, present disastrous timeshare opportunities to future vacationers, and get sneaky with people's pockets in the grocery store.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624223000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys hug it out with strangers in the park, go head-to-head pitching wacky inventions to confused consumers, and launch a manhunt for their imaginary wives.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Moneyball</title>
    <desc>Billy Beane (Brad Pitt), general manager of the Oakland A's, one day has an epiphany: Baseball's conventional wisdom is all wrong. Faced with a tight budget, Beane must reinvent his team by outsmarting the richer ball clubs. Joining forces with Ivy League graduate Peter Brand (Jonah Hill), Beane prepares to challenge old-school traditions. He recruits bargain-bin players whom the scouts have label</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">DAZN Boxing</title>
    <desc>An all-access look at the upcoming fight between Xander Zayas and Jaron Ennis, scheduled for Saturday June 27th.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625023000 +0000" stop="20260625030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">DAZN Boxing</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625030000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cinderella Man</title>
    <desc>During the Great Depression, ex-boxer James J. Braddock (Russell Crowe) works as a day laborer until his former manager Joe Gould (Paul Giamatti) offers him a one-time slot against a rising young contender. After he wins a shocking upset, Braddock goes back into the ring full time, against the wishes of his frightened wife, Mae (Renée Zellweger). Dubbed "The Cinderella Man" for his rags-to-riches </desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers: Inside Jokes</title>
    <desc>Sal's true weakness is revealed; female staffers line up to watch Q's punishment.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625063000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers: Inside Jokes</title>
    <desc>Sal surprises the guys when he wins a challenge; Joe's play space punishment takes up a number of buildings.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers: Inside Jokes</title>
    <desc>The guys go barefoot for their "Feets of Strength" challenge; Q's Death Chair punishment inspires fear among the Jokers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625073000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers: Inside Jokes</title>
    <desc>Murr appears as an extra in a movie; wrestler Bully Ray's real-life beef with Sal; a feline fiasco halts filming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inogen Portable Oxygen - No More Tanks!</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625083000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625093000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Overwhelmed with IRS Debt? Keys to Resolving Tax Debt</title>
    <desc>See how one company is changing people's lives by helping them put their tax problems to rest.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys paint themselves into a corner teaching an art class, face the dartboard of destiny at a local bar, and tonight's loser stresses out over a Joker home invasion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625103000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Joe, Sal, Q and Murr must think on their feet at a podiatrist's office; burying unusual objects in the park; grocery store race.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys promote office safety to stunned employees, and dabble in online dating with humiliating profiles.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625113000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys are challenged to hold in their laughter during presentations designed to crack them up; when Joe, Sal, and Murr try to gang up on Q, he turns the tables.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys strike out with patrons in a bowling alley and try to force-feed unsuspecting diners; a surprise visit by Rosie O'Donnell has tonight's loser seeing double.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625123000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The Jokers ask absurd survey questions at the zoo and are forced to whisper sweet nothings to grocery store patrons.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Joe, Sal and Q get creative with French fries; compete to see whose invention will win over a focus group; serve up burgers at the Jersey Shore.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625133000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys compete to attach the most balloons to unsuspecting grocery shoppers; absurd tasks at a music store; trying to get compliments on some unique outfits.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys blindly follow each other's humiliating directions at a water park, compete to sell their ridiculous book ideas.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625143000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys get eaten alive leading a business luncheon, and trip over their own feet selling running shoes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys strike the wrong chord as music instructors and try to save face in a humiliating focus group face-off.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625153000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys call it quits with a cringe-worthy public announcement, and act as dinosaur experts with preposterous prehistoric lessons.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys meet to talk about their favorite moments; the most uncomfortable, most embarrassing, most humiliating and most outrageous.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys fumble through the aisles of a grocery store, and re-gift the kooky contents of a mystery bag; the guys must seek out the chosen one, in an embarrassing needle-in-a-haystack challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Joe, Murr, Sal and Q serve up tasks as deli waiters; deli customers are asked to settle debates; an embarrassing toast leaves everyone speechless.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys are forced to look for love in all the wrong places at a singles' event, and make embarrassing calls on strangers' cells; there's no happily-ever-after for tonight's big loser when his storybook ending becomes a humiliating sob story.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>It's the grand reopening of the old Langley Falls boardwalk, and no one's more pumped than the Smiths.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Steve feels isolated when he dislikes a new fast food restaurant popular among his friends; Stan and Francine attempt to return misdelivered mail.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>After Hayley is deemed a big child by The Lady from The Hamster Rescue Society, she gets involved with two Roger personas who have a complicated family dynamic in an effort to prove that she is an adult woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>After a nearly fatal interaction with one of Roger's personas, Steve and Stan work together to uncover the persona's mysterious past; Jeff, Hayley and Francine explore new hobbies.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Jeff gets a job after the family calls him out for being a mooch; when he unexpectedly strikes it rich, Hayley must protect Jeff from the family's greed.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Bullock throws a private, star-studded Christmas party the same night as the CIA work party; Stan and Klaus are determined to get in, by any means necessary.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Hayley scores an internship at Morning Mimosa but finds herself on thin ice when she tries to inject real journalism into the show. Meanwhile, the rest of the family suffers through a ravaging case of food poisoning.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Francine joins Tuttle's gardening club, but he wants her gone; the rest of the family practice the power of yes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Francine and Roger become addicted to peeping in on people at a mysterious motel.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">American Dad!</title>
    <desc>Forces of evil beyond human comprehension bully Hayley into doing a Space Jam.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Endurance Uncovered</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cinderella Man</title>
    <desc>During the Great Depression, ex-boxer James J. Braddock (Russell Crowe) works as a day laborer until his former manager Joe Gould (Paul Giamatti) offers him a one-time slot against a rising young contender. After he wins a shocking upset, Braddock goes back into the ring full time, against the wishes of his frightened wife, Mae (Renée Zellweger). Dubbed "The Cinderella Man" for his rags-to-riches </desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624080000 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>An abused foster child (Jae Head), apprehended while driving a runaway van, leads the detectives to re-examine a case involving a rape victim (Sara Gilbert).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detective Stabler's job and personal life intertwine when his daughter Kathleen becomes a suspect in a case; after learning that Kathleen may have an emotional disorder, he turns to his estranged mother (Ellen Burstyn) for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When a man opens fire on a patrol car and wounds Roman, Burgess pursues the shooter; with no gun found at the scene, Burgess faces the accusation of shooting an unarmed man; the man who sent Voight to prison is assigned to help defend Burgess.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Lindsay and Halstead discover the youngest daughter is the only survivor of a shooting at a family home; Antonio and Olinsky investigate a pyramid scheme self-help group; Platt tries to convince Crowley that Burgess and Roman should remain partners.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>When the body of a single mother is found in the trunk of her car, the team is shocked to learn the victim had contact with Voight's reformed son.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>The victim of a murder-arson case is discovered to have been wearing a CPD issued wire at the time of his death; Burgess meets her new partner; Cmdr. Crowley questions Lindsay about the night intelligence pursued Justin's killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Voight and the team search for answers after discovering a man badly beaten and learning that his fiancée is missing; Lindsay asks Halsted a surprising question; Platt is berated by Vogel for going over his head.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>After Platt is physically assaulted while getting into her car, she's rushed to Chicago Med, where Mouch finds himself being questioned; Antonio and the team look for previous threats against Platt.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago P.D.</title>
    <desc>Lindsay and Ruzek respond when a car crashes through a crowd of concert-goers and a gunman opens fire; Burgess sees Atwater's brother somewhere he shouldn't be.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A series of freeway car accidents leads to a catastrophic overpass collapse that endangers the lives of civilians and members of the 118.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena and Bobby set off on their honeymoon cruise, but when duty calls, their vacation is put on hold; a fighter jet traps a civilian; an unusual incident leaves a couple stuck together.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The disastrous cruise continues when Bobby and Athena respond to the ship's explosion, racing to aid injured passengers; Hen questions her instincts in a life-taking call and grows concerned about Athena and Bobby's whereabouts.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>With each moment becoming critical as the ship flips upside down, Athena and Bobby take charge, seeking methods for rescue while navigating efforts to guide survivors to safety; Hen defies protocols in her search for Bobby and Athena.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Upon her return to shore, Athena's son finds himself in trouble with the law; Buck grows envious as Eddie forms a close bond with someone else; the team rescues a woman who's stuck on receiving a rose at an iconic mansion.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Hen and Karen welcome a new addition to their family; a call unfolds involving a person's limb that's taken on a mind of its own; Eddie and Marisol take a closer look at their relationship; Buck navigates his new feelings.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260624233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Wednesdays on USA - Pregame</title>
    <desc>Pregame expert analysis ahead of tonight's marquee WNBA Wednesday night action.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260624233000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>The Indiana Fever host the Phoenix Mercury in a regular-season WNBA basketball game. Indiana relies on guard Caitlin Clark following her 26-point performance against Atlanta, while Phoenix counters with Alyssa Thomas to lead the offense.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: WNBA Basketball</title>
    <desc>The Golden State Valkyries face the Atlanta Dream as Gabby Williams anchors the offense. The home squad counts on Angel Reese following her 11.9 rebounds per game, while the visiting lineup counters with Janelle Salaün to establish paint presence.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625043000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">How I Met Your Mother</title>
    <desc>Robin, desperate to find a job before she is deported, agrees to let Barney produce a video resume for her.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">How I Met Your Mother</title>
    <desc>Barney tries to prove Ted wrong by completing every task on Ted's list of things he thinks the gang is too old to do.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625053000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">How I Met Your Mother</title>
    <desc>Barney takes matters into his own hands when Robin is hesitant to end things with Nick; Marshall and Lily desperately want some private time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>In Pembroke Pines, Fla., a rookie detective reopens a 15-year-old case about the disappearance of young father David Jackson.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>Investigators are suspicious when a wealthy former radio DJ mysteriously disappears from his yacht in the Pacific Ocean.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A look back at the 1997 murder of fashion designer Gianni Versace, including interviews with his long-time partner Antonio D'Amico, model Beverly Johnson, fashion journalist Hal Rubenstein, author Maureen Orth and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dateline</title>
    <desc>A look back at the 1997 murder of fashion designer Gianni Versace, including interviews with his long-time partner Antonio D'Amico, model Beverly Johnson, fashion journalist Hal Rubenstein, author Maureen Orth and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>When a gunnery sergeant moonlighting as a security guard at a decommissioned nuclear power plant suffers radiation poisoning, the team goes undercover to investigate.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>A tech entrepreneur and venture capitalist who secretly developed a computer program that stealthily collects data is murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS: Los Angeles</title>
    <desc>Kensi and Deeks announce that they are moving in together right before they are assigned to protection detail for Kensi's ex-fiancé, who has a list of important contacts that people are willing to kill for.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>ADA Novak calls upon detective Benson, still undercover in Oregon, to present evidence that will strengthen the case against a brutal rapist.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When detective Benson gets into the middle of an investigation of her brother, the case begins to threaten her career.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A troubled teen (David Del Rio) is the first suspect when a money manager is found murdered in his loft, but a hidden video camera leads detectives to a star football player whose agent is willing to do almost anything to protect his client.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detectives suspect a wealthy family of coffee traders when a pregnant woman is found raped and murdered in her burned-out loft.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Detective Lake, wounded in a gunfight prompted by the reopening of an old murder case, escapes from the hospital and takes hostage the original case's only witness (Victoria Cartagena).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman is found in Riverside Park, beaten and raped with no memory of what happened; during the investigation, Olivia must face the fact that she still thinks like a victim.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler begin to question the story of a missing teenager (Ellen Woglom) who returns home after four years, claiming to have been kept as a sex slave in a concrete cell.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the body of a 14-year-old girl is found in the Hudson River, Benson and Stabler think she was smuggled into the country by sex traffickers; in an attempt to identify her, Benson poses as a madam.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A man is found badly beaten in a parking lot, with no memory of what happened, and detectives suspect his transgender teen may be responsible.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A pediatrician found guilty of sexually assaulting four of his patients is murdered; after three years in the Witness Protection Program, Alexandra Cabot returns.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A former dancer (Carol Burnett) is caught up in the murder of a young couple.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">White House Down</title>
    <desc>Capitol police officer John Cale has just been denied his dream job of protecting President James Sawyer as a member of the Secret Service. Not wanting to disappoint his young daughter with the bad news, Cale takes her on a tour of the White House. While he and his daughter are there, a heavily armed paramilitary group attacks and seizes control. As the nation's government dissolves in chaos, only</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624080000 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>Rush and Valens reopen the 1985 case of a wealthy stockbroker killed during an apparent carjacking gone awry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Leo learns that the Charmed Ones' conflict-free world comes with a high price, so he teams with Zankou (Oded Fehr) to stop the Avatars and reverse the change.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>When Paige tries to hire a new professor for the Magic School, one of the candidates, Drake (Billy Zane), turns out to be an ex-demon who made a deal with a sorcerer to become human.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>When Inspector Morris believes his friend is possessed, the Charmed Ones investigate and find that a victim of a fire in 1899 has taken control of Mike.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Piper is attacked by demons and winds up in a coma, and as she hovers between life and death, her spirit meets Cole (Julian McMahon), who says he is trying to help restore Phoebe's faith in love.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Zankou uses his underlings to lure the sisters out of their house, so he can search for the Nexus and release the Shadow, the ultimate power.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>The team reopens the case of an innocent teenage inmate, killed in a juvenile detention center; Lilly reconnects with former love Saccardo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the death of an accomplished 45-year-old jockey who disappeared within hours of losing a race that he had planned to be his last before retiring.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the 1991 murder of a 14-year-old foster child who was starting to establish herself as a talented rapper.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>The team searches for the killer of a champion debater whom people believed had committed suicide after losing a debate.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>The team reopens the 1980 case of a hockey player who was killed at his team's ice rink in Philadelphia the day the U.S. hockey team beat the Soviet team at the Winter Olympics.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King</title>
    <desc>The culmination of nearly 10 years' work and conclusion to Peter Jackson's epic trilogy based on the timeless J.R.R. Tolkien classic, "The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King" presents the final confrontation between the forces of good and evil fighting for control of the future of Middle-earth. Hobbits Frodo and Sam reach Mordor in their quest to destroy the `one ring', while Aragorn leads </desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260624233000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aquaman and the Lost Kingdom</title>
    <desc>After failing to defeat Aquaman the first time, Black Manta wields the power of the mythic Black Trident to unleash an ancient and malevolent force. Hoping to end his reign of terror, Aquaman forges an unlikely alliance with his brother, Orm, the former king of Atlantis. Setting aside their differences, they join forces to protect their kingdom and save the world from irreversible destruction.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aquaman</title>
    <desc>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, the city of Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people -- and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur, Orm's half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne. With help from royal counselor Vulko, Arthur</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>A court psychologist asks Rush to investigate the homicide of a woman who was murdered in front of his client.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>The team gets an anonymous letter saying the 1999 accidental death of a swim coach at a military academy was the result of a carefully orchestrated plot.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>DNA evidence prompts Rush and Valens to reopen the murder case of a beautiful 15-year-old girl who had a number of admirers, young and old.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>Rush revisits her first crime scene when reopening a triple homicide case at a now-condemned restaurant in a blighted part of town.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>A reunion of World War II factory workers stirs up memories of a mysterious death, and a friend of the deceased begs Lilly to investigate the killing.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After two jurors for a high-profile mafia trial are gunned down, the team jumps into an organized crime investigation until it is discovered that the jurors may not have been the intended targets at all.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>As Maggie and the team search for New York's latest serial killer, the copycat method used by the murderer forces Maggie to seek help from Ray DeStefano, the serial slasher she put behind bars.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When an undercover FBI agent is killed in the field, the team makes the unnerving discovery that the identities of multiple undercover agents have been compromised, including Maggie who has been actively working to infiltrate an eco-terrorist group.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a famous rapper and two teen fans are gunned down on his tour bus, the team discovers there may be more to the story than his feud with another rapper; Isobel hits a major milestone that has her contemplating her future at the Bureau.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After two women are brutally murdered via napalm, Maggie and OA are led to a dating site where they discover a group of scorned users who are targeting women who reject them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After a young girl goes missing in Queens, the team discovers the kidnappers used her as leverage to carry out a major explosives heist, sending them on a hunt for the dangerous culprits; Scola and Dani begin working on their footing as partners.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When a CEO is killed by a targeted explosion inside his penthouse, the team must work to figure out how someone accessed the highly secure building; Maggie pumps the brakes on her personal life.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When two IRS special agents are stabbed to death in Brooklyn, the team is thrown into an investigation that leads back to the resurgence of the online conspiracy community of Duke Ducoyle, their suspect from a previous case.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Aquaman and the Lost Kingdom</title>
    <desc>After failing to defeat Aquaman the first time, Black Manta wields the power of the mythic Black Trident to unleash an ancient and malevolent force. Hoping to end his reign of terror, Aquaman forges an unlikely alliance with his brother, Orm, the former king of Atlantis. Setting aside their differences, they join forces to protect their kingdom and save the world from irreversible destruction.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Batman</title>
    <desc>Batman ventures into Gotham City's underworld when a sadistic killer leaves behind a trail of cryptic clues. As the scale of the perpetrator's plans become clear, he must bring justice to the abuse of power and corruption that plagues the metropolis.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624083500 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Road Wars</title>
    <desc>The Thames Valley Police provide a fascinating insight into car crime and its prevention. Plus, shocking video footage captures dangerous drivers in action. Strong language. (S4, ep 8)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>Ho'onani Makuakane (Honor Thy Father): After the attempted murder of a Pearl Harbor veteran at a remembrance ceremony, the team investigate a decades-old crime. (S4, ep 10)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>Pukana (Keepsake): Danger looms when the discovery of a dead body leads Chin onto the trail of a serial killer. Contains violent and distressing scenes. (S4, ep 11)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Cry Foul: When a series of deadly explosions hit oil derricks across Los Angeles, the team must hunt down an activist-turned-terrorist. (S5, ep 17)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Family: When Hicks witnesses the assassination of his longtime friend, the team races to find the shooter and discover the motive. (S5, ep 18)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mornings</title>
    <desc>All the big stories of the morning plus news making interviews, analysis and eyewitness reports from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624133000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mornings</title>
    <desc>All the big stories of the morning plus news making interviews, analysis and eyewitness reports from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mornings with Ridge and Frost</title>
    <desc>All the big stories of the morning plus news making interviews, analysis and eyewitness reports from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624143000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mornings with Ridge and Frost</title>
    <desc>All the big stories of the morning plus news making interviews, analysis and eyewitness reports from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stargate SG-1</title>
    <desc>2010: Ten years have passed since an alien race known as the Aschen saved Earth and cured cancer but Carter discovers the awful truth behind this seemingly infallible race. (S4, ep 16)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Flash</title>
    <desc>Hear No Evil: Barry feels guilty for what happened to Caitlin. Mark comes up with a plan and old friends pay an unexpected visit to STAR Labs. Flashing images. (S9, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>The Birds and the Bees: Grace drags Will along to keep her in check during her first date with Nick, only to leave a heated Will at his table for one. Edward Burns guests stars. (S7, ep 17)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624173000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>The Fabulous Baker Boys: Will agrees to fire Karen's pastry chef until the baker cooks up a delectable love triangle for the three of them. (S7, ep 18)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer tells Bart that either Santa's Little Helper goes to obedience school and learns to listen or they will have to get rid of him. Special guest voice Tracy Ullman. (S2, ep 14)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624183000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer arranges a date between Principal Skinner and Marge's sister Selma. (S2, ep 15)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wildlife ER</title>
    <desc>Into the Sunset: Contend with a flood of abandoned koala joeys while vet nurse Nick goes on a hunt for natural remedies to treat a wallaby's gut ailment. (S2, ep 6)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>Na Hala a ka makua (Sins of the Father): Tensions mount when McGarrett and Danny are kidnapped by a convict desperate to clear his name. Michael Madsen guests. (S4, ep 14)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>Pale 'la (Buried Secrets): A surprise is in store for Danny when his mum (guest star Melanie Griffith) stops by. Contains violent and distressing scenes. (S4, ep 15)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Incoming: When a plane carrying Street and the dangerous prisoner he's transporting is hijacked, the SWAT team races to save the innocent passengers onboard. (S5, ep 19)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Quandary: SWAT discovers an illegal weapons dealer has sold stock to someone targeting a senior politician, and must rush to stop a deadly ambush. (S5, ep 20)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625000000 +0000" stop="20260625003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>While attending a comic book convention Bart finds the very first issue of 'Radio-Active Man' on sale for $100 and talks Milhouse and Martin into sharing in the cost. (S2, ep 21)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625003000 +0000" stop="20260625010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer goes in search of his long-lost brother. Featuring the voice of Danny DeVito. (S2, ep 16)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625010000 +0000" stop="20260625013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Office Olympics: With Michael and Dwight out of the office, Jim and Pam lead the staff in a series of games to stave off boredom. (S2, ep 3)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625013000 +0000" stop="20260625020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>The Fire: As a fire forces the staff to assemble in the car park, Michael tries to become a mentor to young temp Ryan. (S2, ep 4)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer expects a generous gift in return when he donates some of Bart's blood to an ailing Mr Burns. (S2, ep 22)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625023000 +0000" stop="20260625030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Mr Lisa Goes to Washington: When Lisa enters a competition about patriotism, the Simpsons find themselves on an all expenses paid trip to Washington. (S3, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625030000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mean Girls</title>
    <desc>Naive new girl Lindsay Lohan accidentally falls in with catty queen bee Rachel McAdams. Top teen comedy. (2004)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Never Mind The Buzzcocks</title>
    <desc>Pepsi &amp; Shirlie, Martin Fry, Debbie Gibson and Judi Love join the regulars for an 80s special of the pop culture panel show, hosted by Greg Davies. (S5, ep 3)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Ultimate Romcom Movies</title>
    <desc>Film fans Clara Amfo, Ellie Taylor and Russell Kane go head to head as they discuss the essential elements that must feature in the ultimate romcom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Grimm</title>
    <desc>You Don't Know Jack: As Adalind and Rosalee work to help Juliette, Nick investigates a killer labelled by the press as a Jack the Ripper copycat. (S4, ep 20)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Force: North East</title>
    <desc>An emergency dash results in a serious collision between the police van and a taxi. Plus, officers race to save a man threatening to take his own life. (S5, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New: FROM</title>
    <desc>The residents of the town stand at a crossroads unlike any they've faced before as Boyd sets a daring and dangerous plan in motion. (S4, ep 9)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>O kela me keia manawa (Now and Then): McGarrett tries to track down the Captain's friend, who is wanted for murder, while Kono continues her search for Adam. (S4, ep 12)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Incoming: When a plane carrying Street and the dangerous prisoner he's transporting is hijacked, the SWAT team races to save the innocent passengers onboard. (S5, ep 19)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Quandary: SWAT discovers an illegal weapons dealer has sold stock to someone targeting a senior politician, and must rush to stop a deadly ambush. (S5, ep 20)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mornings</title>
    <desc>All the big stories of the morning plus news making interviews, analysis and eyewitness reports from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625133000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mornings</title>
    <desc>All the big stories of the morning plus news making interviews, analysis and eyewitness reports from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mornings with Ridge and Frost</title>
    <desc>All the big stories of the morning plus news making interviews, analysis and eyewitness reports from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625143000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mornings with Ridge and Frost</title>
    <desc>All the big stories of the morning plus news making interviews, analysis and eyewitness reports from around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stargate SG-1</title>
    <desc>Absolute Power: SG-1 notice a change in Daniel Jackson after he is reunited with the Harsesis child, Shifu (Lane Gates). (S4, ep 17)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Flash</title>
    <desc>Rogue of War: Barry and Iris start to put together the pieces of what's happening in Central City - and believe they know just what the Rogues want. (S9, ep 3)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Sour Balls: Jack and Will decide to buy a vacation home in Loudon Falls, an up-and-coming gay community. But they soon find it's not quite the party scene they'd imagined. (S7, ep 19)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>The Blonde Leading the Blind: Will becomes jealous after Grace forms a friendship with his therapist and begins to compete for her attention. Sharon Stone guest stars. (S7, ep 20)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Grampa Simpson feels there is little left to live for, until he falls in love with Beatrice, a beautiful woman at the rest home. (S2, ep 17)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer's boss, Mr Burns, commissions Marge to paint a portrait of him. Featuring the voice of Ringo Starr. (S2, ep 18)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wildlife ER</title>
    <desc>A Summer to Remember: Vet Emily takes the pressure off a gassy koala mum while the team fights a wave of lorikeet paralysis syndrome. (S3, ep 1)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>Hoku Welowelo (Fire In The Sky): Conspiracy theorist Jerry Ortega (returning guest star Jorge Garcia) helps the Five-0 solve a triple homicide. (S4, ep 16)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>Ma Lalo o ka 'ili (Beneath The Surface): Danny forces a reunion between his parents, while Jerry helps McGarrett decipher a code at the bottom of his champ box. (S4, ep 17)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Zodiac: A Los Angeles SWAT lieutenant balances loyalty to the job and to the streets where he grew up. (S5, ep 21)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Farewell: In the season five finale, the SWAT team races to stop a devastating terror attack after control of a university chemistry lab is seized. (S5, ep 22)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>When Flanders Failed: Marge annoys Homer when she tells him that she admires Ned Flanders for working hard and being able to provide his family with the best of everything. (S3, ep 3)</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624080000 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Beast</title>
    <desc>Joe Maxwell's current romantic involvement puts a damper on the celebration marking the anniversary of Catherine and Vincent's first meeting.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghost Whisperer</title>
    <desc>When a student's ghost accuses a police officer of murdering him, Melinda believes that the death was not a mere skateboarding accident.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Strong Medicine</title>
    <desc>Lu takes over for Dana while she is caring for her mother; Dana's genetic test reveals she is pre-disposed to breast cancer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Any Day Now</title>
    <desc>M.E.'s sister (Delta Burke) jolts Collier out of depression and irritates Rene with her prejudice; at a segregated hospital, Catherine insists on medical care for young Rene.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Touched by an Angel</title>
    <desc>The angels urge a politician seeking re-election to acknowledge the existence of slavery in Sudan, but it will jeopardize her career.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>After being subpoenaed to testify at the jury probe of a brokerage house, Jessica is charged with contempt for speaking to a witness who is killed.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>In Japan, Jessica gets involved in the murder of a motorcycle racer, the son of an international CEO (Pat Morita).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica works hard to get her friend's (Tony Plana) Latino band a recording contract, until a murder rocks her plans.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major Crimes</title>
    <desc>The squad investigates a brutal murder and discovers dark secrets at the root of a drug bust gone wrong; Raydor's estranged husband returns to Los Angeles; Jack becomes fast friends with Rusty.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major Crimes</title>
    <desc>The division tries to solve the case of a missing child with gender dysphoria; the squad attempts to connect evidence to a dangerous bully; Jack Raydor tries to make up for years of bad parenting.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major Crimes</title>
    <desc>A case deals with gang violence and social profiling; Sharon offers Jack the opportunity to be a court-appointed attorney in a case; Rusty is worried about meeting Kris' parents.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major Crimes</title>
    <desc>A media frenzy begins when the body of a Latino man is found at the home of a swimming coach; Flynn struggles with an emotional dilemma; Kris' mother visits Raydor to discuss some concerns.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major Crimes</title>
    <desc>Provenza faces possible permanent desk duty; the squad investigates the death of an ICE agent which leads them to the residents of an old apartment complex.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>Jane tries to find a way to get Maura to meet her biological mother; Angela gets involved in a political campaign; a nun from Jane and Frankie Jr.'s past returns.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>A bank robbery leaves a security guard dead and a lot of unanswered questions; Pope gets some news about his chances at becoming the city's police chief.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>After returning home from duty in Afghanistan, three soldiers are gunned down outside a club; Brenda's investigation puts her on a collision course with Maj. Edward Dorset.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625000000 +0000" stop="20260625010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major Crimes</title>
    <desc>Jack Raydor defends a man who is attempting to withdraw a confession in the murder of his wife; the team is alerted to the possibility of a conspiracy; Rusty interviews Slider.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625010000 +0000" stop="20260625020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>A notable county prosecutor is arrested for murder; when Angela hears that Maura is planning to meet Jack's daughter, she sets out to educate Maura about the interests of children today.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Veronica Mars</title>
    <desc>Veronica helps Abel Koontz, the man originally convicted for Lilly's murder, search for his missing daughter.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625030000 +0000" stop="20260625040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Rory kisses Tristan at a party after fighting with Dean; Lorelai impulsively shows up at Max's house for a night of lovemaking.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625040000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Rory's great-grandmother offers Lorelai a trust fund for Rory's education, causing Emily to fear losing her newfound relationship with them.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>After determining a serial killer's identity, the team works with the FBI to apprehend him and protect potential targets.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>Drew Barrymore presents human-interest stories, celebrity guests, lifestyle segments and field pieces, all driven by her infectious brand of humor and optimism.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625063000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Drew Barrymore Show</title>
    <desc>Drew Barrymore presents human-interest stories, celebrity guests, lifestyle segments and field pieces, all driven by her infectious brand of humor and optimism.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Entertainment Tonight</title>
    <desc>News and features about performers, productions and the milieu.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625073000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Inside Edition</title>
    <desc>A syndicated news magazine includes investigative reports, interviews with newsmakers, human interest stories and celebrity and pop-culture features.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beauty and the Beast</title>
    <desc>Catherine gets a new co-worker at the D.A.'s office and soon discovers that he has a connection to the Tunnel World.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghost Whisperer</title>
    <desc>Melinda tries to help Ned stop a ghost out for revenge at the Grandview radio station.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Strong Medicine</title>
    <desc>A young woman's Parkinson's disease may require a controversial form of treatment; Marc's classmate may be an alcoholic.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Any Day Now</title>
    <desc>Mary Elizabeth and Collier use Grandma Otis' legacy to start a construction business; Michael continues to stalk Rene; young M.E. and Rene happen upon a KKK meeting.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Touched by an Angel</title>
    <desc>In the midst of World War II, a bitter American soldier must choose between saving his own life or honoring his fallen comrades.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Seth Hazlitt's benefit concert to save the woods near Cabot Cove is endangered when the lead singer is permanently silenced.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Details in a manuscript convince a young editor (Tracy Middendorf) that the author (Richard Beymer) kidnapped her 11 years earlier, but when the author is found dead, the editor becomes the primary suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>When the producer of a hit twenty-something series is murdered, Jessica does some directing of her own.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>An attraction grows between Rush and FBI agent Ryan Cavanaugh as they investigate the 1969 murder of a soldier; jewelry is stolen from Vera's girlfriend's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the 1989 case of a prom queen who may have been intentionally killed in a hit-and-run; Rush tries to ignore her father's requests to give her sister (Nicki Aycox) another chance.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>Valens helps Rush search for her abducted sister; Jeffries tries to close a case that has haunted him for 17 years.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>Lilly Rush interviews a maid who says she witnessed the beating death of a teenage girl during a party on a luxurious estate more than 25 years ago.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cold Case</title>
    <desc>A woman asks Lilly to investigate the murder of her fiancé's first wife and points a finger at an inmate serving time for an unrelated crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>Jane and Maura investigate when a financier is found in a trash can, wearing a cloak and mask; Maura makes a deeper connection with her biological mother and half-sister.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>Brenda's squad investigates the murder of an aspiring actress who used an online dating service; Brenda prepares for an interview with the mayor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Closer</title>
    <desc>After two paramedics are murdered, the LAPD and the FBI investigate a case that could be the precursor to a terrorist attack.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major Crimes</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a murder during the taping of a reality competition show pitting married couples against each other; Sanchez is reminded of his late wife; Rusty meets Slider's lawyer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624083000 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, smugglers and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorway Patrol</title>
    <desc>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624093000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorway Patrol</title>
    <desc>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder</title>
    <desc>Documentary series charting the exploits of the City of London police, charged with safeguarding the Square Mile at the heart of the crime-ridden capital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>A visitor from Novak's past joins Ambo for a late-night ride-along. Herrmann faces a mountain of records and reports.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team is called in when a chaotic campus protest turns deadly.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After bodies are discovered across the city, the team tracks down a serial killer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Nolan volunteers to guard Professor Fiona Ryan's house overnight, after a series of mysterious notes and the vandalism of her car.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Criminal Intent</title>
    <desc>While investigating the murder of a diver, Goren and Eames learn that he is part of a treasure-hunting team that stumbled onto a wealthy family's dark secret.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624163000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624173000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624183000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624193000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>The Good, the Bad and the Ugly: After losing control of a crime scene, Nolan and Talia debate whether people are fundamentally good or bad.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Matlock</title>
    <desc>The Wellbrexa case reaches its dramatic conclusion as the team makes a final push to bring Senior to justice while fighting for their client.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc</title>
    <desc>A mysterious, fast-acting and extremely deadly virus causes an emergency lockdown on Westside Hospital's sixth floor.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>The team are thrown into the world of true crime docuseries when their case features a celebrity.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625000000 +0000" stop="20260625010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The assassination of a Brooklyn plumber launches the team into an investigation that ruffles feathers with the CIA.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625010000 +0000" stop="20260625020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A tourist is viciously attacked in Times Square. As the squad scours the area for clues, the victim takes the investigation into her own hands.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After a corporate executive is assassinated, the team races to find the leaders of a terrorist organisation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625030000 +0000" stop="20260625040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Road Wars</title>
    <desc>Officers Chris Piggott and Simon Hills are on the receiving end of a load of grief from a violent suspect they think has been trying to break into a car. Strong language.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625040000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">UK Border Force</title>
    <desc>The observational documentary series going behind the scenes of UK immigration continues, as officers at Heathrow Terminal 3's passport control question suspicious travellers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real A &amp; E</title>
    <desc>A day at the beach ends in disaster when a day tripper mysteriously collapses, and a rugby player lands himself in hospital with a dislocated shoulder for the third time.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625053000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Real A &amp; E</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bondi Rescue</title>
    <desc>American Superstar Comedian Conan O'Brien tries his hand at lifeguarding - with hilarious results.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625063000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bondi Rescue</title>
    <desc>A man is reported to have fallen from cliffs, but when Jesse arrives the situation takes an unexpected turn.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Border Patrol</title>
    <desc>Follow the work of the New Zealand Customs agents in their quest to prevent illegal items passing through the country's borders.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625073000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Border Patrol</title>
    <desc>Follow the work of the New Zealand Customs agents in their quest to prevent illegal items passing through the country's borders.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, smugglers and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625083000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, smugglers and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorway Patrol</title>
    <desc>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625093000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Motorway Patrol</title>
    <desc>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder</title>
    <desc>Documentary series charting the exploits of the City of London police, charged with safeguarding the Square Mile at the heart of the crime-ridden capital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Kidd and Severide eagerly await big news, as Pascal searches for the perfect anniversary gift.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team faces their toughest roadblock yet when a string of crimes leads them to discover an online conspiracy theory community.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team entrusts OA's old army buddy Clay to assist them after three customs officers are shot dead in a cargo heist.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Nolan and his ex-wife must come together to help their son when he collapses and is rushed to hospital.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Criminal Intent</title>
    <desc>The murder of a judge's wife reveals a twisted plot involving an FBI agent, an ex-CIA operative, an actress, a director and possibly the judge.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625183000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625193000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>When Nolan and Lopez track down an escaped criminal, they discover a little kindness goes a long way.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After a corporate executive is assassinated, the team races to find the leaders of a terrorist organisation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>Officers Nolan, Harper and Lopez dive into a complex case when the son of a criminal court judge with many enemies is kidnapped.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624080000 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the Ring</title>
    <desc>In the mid '90s, wrestling is rocked by accusations of rampant steroid abuse; with star witness Hulk Hogan, prosecutors set out to prove that Vince McMahon is the one responsible.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the Ring</title>
    <desc>In a culture that celebrates machismo and negative gay stereotypes, wrestling innovator Chris Kanyon keeps his own sexuality a closely guarded secret for decades.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624103000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Natural Blood Pressure Management</title>
    <desc>Cardiologist Dr. Ernst von Schwarz, M.D. shows how to manage your blood pressure naturally and help protect your heart for life with My Best Heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Freedom to Leave the House! Inogen Portable Oxygen</title>
    <desc>Regain independence and enjoy greater mobility with the compact design and long-lasting battery of portable oxygen.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624113000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Was a Teenage Felon</title>
    <desc>At 17, Denise parties with celebrities on the Sunset Strip and transforms herself from a high school drug dealer to an international cocaine queenpin.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Was a Teenage Felon</title>
    <desc>At 15, Peter starts abusing meth and steals to feed his drug habit; his schemes grow from petty crime to grand-theft auto; a final heist lands him in max security prison.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Was a Teenage Felon</title>
    <desc>Fighting, dealing and stealing his way through the city since his first assault charge at age 11, MMA icon Adam eventually earns the moniker of Albuquerque's Most Hated.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Was a Teenage Felon</title>
    <desc>Growing up in England, Shaun dreams of striking it rich; moving to the United States at 19, he makes millions in stocks and then becomes the Arizona rave scene's Ecstasy Kingpin.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Was a Teenage Felon</title>
    <desc>Larry is raised among mobsters in the Bronx, N.Y., starts gambling at 11, steals cars by 16, and ultimately becomes the biggest jewel thief in the U.S.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Was a Teenage Felon</title>
    <desc>At 19, Chin becomes the cocaine kingpin of Nashville, makes millions, and parties with the hottest strippers; on Sunday morning, he attends church listening to his father preach.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Was a Teenage Felon</title>
    <desc>Arrested at 9 and homeless at 10, Jacob learns to survive on the streets of Florida; he soon rises from petty weed sales to helping run a ruthless Mexican drug cartel by age 19.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>In an exclusive prison interview, Barbara Rogers reveals that cult leader Sherry Shriner is the force who brought Steve and Barbara together and ultimately tore them apart.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>When doomsday prepper Steve Mineo is expelled from Sherry Shriner's cult, he tries to protect his girlfriend from online attacks and winds up dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>With Barbara on trial and Sherry exploiting Steve's murder to gain followers, a ballistics expert shows how it's possible that Steve turned the gun on himself.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>An investigation into how Sherry's ministry lives on after her death from a heart attack, as well as the proliferation of her conspiracy theories about the New Age Alien Agenda.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ancient Aliens</title>
    <desc>Joan of Arc's defeat of the English Army; a young boy from India learns advanced mathematical formulas; an American serviceman receives a message while touching an alien aircraft; the ancient astronaut theory.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625000000 +0000" stop="20260625010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ancient Aliens</title>
    <desc>Festivals, coronations, funerals, and other modern rituals could reflect attempts by early humans to emulate ancient alien visitors.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625010000 +0000" stop="20260625020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ancient Aliens</title>
    <desc>An ancient mountaintop fortress in Peru constructed with laser-like tools; temples at Vijayanagara, India harness cosmic energy; an acoustic chamber in Malta enables interplanetary communication.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Proof Is Out There</title>
    <desc>A strange silver object seen in the sky seen over Kansas might be a real UFO.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625023000 +0000" stop="20260625030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Proof Is Out There</title>
    <desc>Discusses whether a bipedal figure that crossed a snowy field is a fabled yeti; also explores the history of UFOs in Italy and if a creature peeking around the corner is a real-life alien.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625030000 +0000" stop="20260625033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Proof Is Out There</title>
    <desc>Recent video of a large, hairy creature and casts of its footprints; a man dodges rush hour traffic with seemingly superhuman reflexes; a woman escapes from her sinking vehicle without opening the doors or windows.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625033000 +0000" stop="20260625040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Proof Is Out There</title>
    <desc>Examining whether a girl whose reflection doesn't match her expression is proof of a simulated reality; suggestion that Mars was colonized centuries ago; a mysterious hum being heard around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625040000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>When doomsday prepper Steve Mineo is expelled from Sherry Shriner's cult, he tries to protect his girlfriend from online attacks and winds up dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>With Barbara on trial and Sherry exploiting Steve's murder to gain followers, a ballistics expert shows how it's possible that Steve turned the gun on himself.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>An investigation into how Sherry's ministry lives on after her death from a heart attack, as well as the proliferation of her conspiracy theories about the New Age Alien Agenda.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>When doomsday prepper Steve Mineo is expelled from Sherry Shriner's cult, he tries to protect his girlfriend from online attacks and winds up dead.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>With Barbara on trial and Sherry exploiting Steve's murder to gain followers, a ballistics expert shows how it's possible that Steve turned the gun on himself.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Devil You Know</title>
    <desc>An investigation into how Sherry's ministry lives on after her death from a heart attack, as well as the proliferation of her conspiracy theories about the New Age Alien Agenda.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Historic Silver Set</title>
    <desc>Add the Set of 20 Truly Historic Morgan Silver Dollars in Brilliant Uncirculated condition to your numismatic collection today; with only about 1% of all Morgan Dollars grading in uncirculated condition, examples like these are Condition Rarities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625103000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Historic Silver Set</title>
    <desc>Add the Set of 20 Truly Historic Morgan Silver Dollars in Brilliant Uncirculated condition to your numismatic collection today; with only about 1% of all Morgan Dollars grading in uncirculated condition, examples like these are Condition Rarities.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1776 Silver Rarities</title>
    <desc>Collect every circulation dual date 1776-2026 denomination struck; each coin in this 10-Coin Silver Set is certified PF70UCAM in coveted First Day of Issue holders; included are some one-year only designs and strikes celebrating America's 250th.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625113000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">1776 Silver Rarities</title>
    <desc>Collect every circulation dual date 1776-2026 denomination struck; each coin in this 10-Coin Silver Set is certified PF70UCAM in coveted First Day of Issue holders; included are some one-year only designs and strikes celebrating America's 250th.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hamilton's Pharmacopeia</title>
    <desc>Haunted by past mistakes, Hamilton embarks on a journey to correct an error in his reporting and identifies the origin of an international toad venom smoking phenomenon.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hamilton's Pharmacopeia</title>
    <desc>Succumbing to viewer requests, Hamilton journeys to Argentina to understand the legend of Anadenanthera, the world's oldest psychedelic.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hamilton's Pharmacopeia</title>
    <desc>With the precise structure of LSD's molecular target identified, Hamilton discusses the new era of psychedelic research and meets pioneers of the field.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hamilton's Pharmacopeia</title>
    <desc>Hamilton traces the multi-billion year history of nitrous oxide on Earth and follows a strange noble gas to the Czech Republic.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Betraying the Badge</title>
    <desc>A New Orleans crack dealer reports cops to the feds, which leads to an elaborate sting involving a warehouse full of cocaine and the murder of an innocent woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Betraying the Badge</title>
    <desc>A bad cop-turned-good in North Carolina helps uncover a pattern of crimes committed by officers in the sheriff's department, which brings down 22 law enforcement officials.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Betraying the Badge</title>
    <desc>A Florida sheriff's deputy investigates rumors that his partner is crooked and uncovers some crimes, including theft and the murder of an innocent businessman.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Betraying the Badge</title>
    <desc>An anonymous tip alleging that La. sheriff's deputies are illegally seizing millions of dollars from drug dealers results in the prosecution of over 35 officers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Betraying the Badge</title>
    <desc>A group of officers in Savannah, Ga., has lucrative off-duty work providing security for diamond shipments; when the diamonds turn out to be drugs, the FBI gets involved.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hells Angels: Ride or Die</title>
    <desc>The Hells Angels are not the world's only outlaw motorcycle club; In the decades since the Angels' formation many challengers have emerged, and one group in particular has threatened their status at the top, The Mongols.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hells Angels: Ride or Die</title>
    <desc>In an outlaw organization that prides itself on secrecy and anonymity, Sonny Barger has held the spotlight as the most famous Hells Angel of all; Barger has represented the Angels in the news and in movies.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hells Angels: Ride or Die</title>
    <desc>Former Angels president George Christie reveals for the first time the debauchery, delights and dangers that go into the club's revelries; These are no-holds-barred accounts of outlaw fun at its most extreme.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">United Gangs of America</title>
    <desc>Nazi Lowriders unleash a shockwave of murder, hate crimes and drug trafficking across California; a former member tells his story.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624083000 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Xzibit, Too $hort, and Michael Blackson battle it out in games, including Pick Up and Kill It, What You Call That, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Xzibit performs "Get Ya Walk On.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Kirk Franklin battle it out in games Alphabet Train, Bless 'Em, Sunday Service, and the Wildstyle battle; Kirk Franklin performs "Bless Me.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624093000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Jason Lee battle it out in games; DC Young Fly performs "Two Shots.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Jay Pharoah and Next battle it out in games: What You Call That, Outgoing Message, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Next performs "Too Close.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624103000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and King Combs battle it out in games: Alphabet Train, Let Me Holla, Kick 'Em Out The Classroom, and the Wildstyle Battle; King Combs performs "Can't Stop.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Lil Meech and Travis Porter battle it out in games, including Got Props, What You Call That, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Travis Porter performs "Ayy Ladies.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624113000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, J. Valentine and Tank battle it out in games Let Me Holla, Sex, Flix and Chill, R&amp;Beef, and the Wildstyle battle; J. Valentine performs "BBL.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Joe Albanese, Jilly Anais, and Michael Blackson battle it out in games: "Got Props", "Let Me Holla", "Kick 'Em Out the Classroom", and the "Wildstyle" battle; Jilly Anais performs "Throwback.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624123000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Sammie, and Bobby V. of RSVP battle it out in games: "Let Me Holla", "Sex", "Flix and Chill", "R&amp;Beef", and the "Wildstyle" battle; Bobby V. performs "Slow Down.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flip Side</title>
    <desc>Mom and daughter, Mona and Jordan challenge BFF's Aaron and Michael.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624133000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flip Side</title>
    <desc>Khemi and Patrice battle Terry and Javi.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and KaMillion battle it out in games: Flow Job, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, Twerk Werk, and the Wildstyle; KaMillion performs "Rich Bitch Walk.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624143000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Ari Fletcher and Rodney Perry battle it out in games Turn Up for What, Talking Spit, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Too $hort performs "Blow the Whistle.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Joey Bada$$ battle it out in games: Pick Up and Kill It, What You Call That, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Joey Bada$$ performs "Zipcodes.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624153000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, DeRay Davis and Jayda Cheaves battle it out in games Alphabet Train, Hood Jeopardy, Talkin' Spit, and the Wildstyle battle; DeRay Davis performs "Right Side of Money.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Bruce Bruce and K Camp battle it out in Little Squad vs. Big Squad, Alphabet Train, Hood Jeopardy, Eat That A... Up, and the Wildstyle battle; K Camp performs "Holy Spirit.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624163000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Jess Hilarious battle it out in games: "Got Props", "Talkin' Spit", "Kick 'Em Out the Classroom", and the "Wildstyle" battle; DW Flame performs "Pop Out.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Hannibal Buress battle it out in games Pick Up and Kill It, What You Call That, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Hannibal Buress performs "Veneers" as Eshe Tune.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624173000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Affion Crockett, Rich Homie Quan and Destanni Henderson battle it out in games Got Props, Thanks for Nothing, Remix, and the Wildstyle battle; Rich Homie Quan performs "Dangerous.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Basketball Wives</title>
    <desc>Evelyn takes on the media after her altercation; Tami tries to convince Evelyn to give the marriage another chance.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Basketball Wives</title>
    <desc>Evelyn's friend meets the ladies; Suzie and Tami's curiosity creates complications.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Jay insists that Michael get a vasectomy so they can feel free to enjoy themselves, but Michael is reluctant to undergo the operation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624203000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Mike worries when Jay wants to put her college degree to good use and enter the workforce.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael is convinced that junior has gotten a tattoo, but Junior won't admit it; Michael is concerned that none of his children are willing to own up to things they've done.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624213000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael and Jay play mind games on Junior after they discover he has been smoking marijuana; Kady wants to spend more time with her big sister.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael has difficulty coping when Junior beats him at basketball; Claire buys a padded bra to impress boys.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624223000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Junior attempts to fool his parents into believing he got an A for his algebra assignment, but the scheme backfires when Janet and Michael treat him like a prodigy.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260624233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael hires an attractive tutor in hopes of invoking Junior's passion for math.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260624233000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael advises Jr. to fight his school bully with words instead of fists; Michael feels Jay is neglecting the family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625000000 +0000" stop="20260625020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Brothers</title>
    <desc>Follows the hilarious path of four African-American men as they take on love, sex, friendship and two of life's most terrifying prospects -- commitment and honesty. Lifelong friends banded together to weather love's innate terrors and occasional triumphs in this brazenly comic yet painfully true exploration of the battle between the sexes. Amidst the career track, basketball and bar hopping, "The </desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Johnson Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Separated from his beautiful wife (Vanessa L. Williams), Nate Johnson (Cedric the Entertainer) wants to make amends with her and spend time with his kids, finding the perfect chance for bonding in a cross-country trip to a family reunion. Convincing them all to join in on the journey, Nate takes the Johnson clan on a trek from California to Missouri, but they encounter various strange situations a</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625040000 +0000" stop="20260625043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>DC Young Fly Hosts, Kid 'n Play, and the Full Force Brothers battle it out in games: Eat That Ass Up, Remix, Family Reunion, and the Wildstyle battle; Kid 'n Play performs "Last Night.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625043000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>DC Young Fly Hosts, Kid 'n Play, and the Full Force Brothers battle it out in games: Eat That Ass Up, Remix, Family Reunion, and the Wildstyle battle; Kid 'n Play performs "Last Night.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>DC Young Fly hosts; Ying Yang Twins and James Kennedy battle it out in games, including Turn Up for What, What You Call That, Remix, and the Wildstyle battle; Ying Yang Twins perform "Get Low.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625053000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Conceited hosts this episode, where Sevyn Streeter battles it out in games: Turn Up for What?, Flow Job, Talkin' Spit, and the Wildstyle battle; Sevyn Streeter performs "23.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Host Justina Valentine, DaniLeigh and Shuba play Battle of the Sexes, Big Ol' Booty, Let Me Holla, Talkin' Spit, and the Wildstyle battle; DaniLeigh performs "I Hate to See It.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625063000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and N.O.R.E. battle it out in games: So Fly, Turn Me Up in the Headphones, Hip Hop History and the Wildstyle battle; N.O.R.E. performs "Nothin'.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and KennyHoopla battle it out in games: Let Me Holla, Roast Roulette, Rock 'N Beef, and the Wildstyle battle; KennyHoopla performs "You Needed a Hit.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625073000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, SWV and Chaotic battle it out in games: So Fly, Family Reunion, R&amp;Beef and the Wildstyle battle; SWV performs "Anything.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and the members of Dru Hill battle it out in games: Hip Hop Potluck, Sex, Flix, and Chill, R&amp;Beef, and the Wildstyle battle; Dru Hill performs "Beauty.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625083000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Lecrae battle it out in games like Pick Up and Kill It, Bless 'Em, Remix and the Wildstyle Battle; Lecrae performs "Spread the Opps.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and NLE Choppa battle it out in games: Pick Up and Kill It, Let Me Holla, Hip Hop History and the Wildstyle battle; NLE Choppa performs "Ain't Gonna Answer.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625093000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Trick Daddy battle it out in games; "Got Props"; "Celebrity Death Battle", "Remix"; "Wildstyle" battle; Famous Dex performs.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Jim Jones and Geena Fontanella battle it out in games; Jim Jones performs "We Fly High".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625103000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Shenseea and Markell Washington battle it out in games: Eat That A... Up, Talking Spit, Remix and the Wildstyle battle; Shenseea performs "Curious.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Scar Lip and OG Parker battle it out in games like Pick Up and Kill It, Got Damned, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom and the Wildstyle Battle; Scar Lip performs "This Is New York.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625113000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Tami Roman, Jazz Anderson and SleazyWorld Go battle it out in games: Got Props, Flow Job, Got Damned and the Wildstyle battle; SleazyWorld Go performs "What You Want 2.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Carla Hall and Klondike Blonde battle it out in games; Klondike Blonde performs "Drip and Moshpit.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625123000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and JD McCrary battle it out in games like R&amp;Beef, Sex, Flix and Chill, Family Reunion and the Wildstyle Battle; JD McCrary performs "Never Too Much.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flip Side</title>
    <desc>Couple Kyle and Anna face off with funny friends Safisha and Jessica.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625133000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Flip Side</title>
    <desc>Father and son Rick and Reed face off with co-workers Tien and Linda.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Da'Vinchi and Icewear Vezzo battle it out in games: Let Me Holla, What You Call That?, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom and the Wildstyle Battle; Icewear Vezzo performs "Up the Scoe.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625143000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Saucy Santana battle, plus Eat That Ass Up, Hood Jeopardy, Greenery Screenery and the Wildstyle battle.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Apryl Jones and Breez Kennedy battle it out in games: Turn Up for What?, Flow Job, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom and the Wildstyle battle; Breez Kennedy performs "Love Crazy (Blowing Up Your Phone).".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625153000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Bobby Shmurda battle it out in games: Hood Jeopardy, Turn Me Up in the Headphones, Plead the Fifth and the Wildstyle battle; Bobby Shmurda performs Shmoney.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and N.O.R.E. battle it out in games: So Fly, Turn Me Up in the Headphones, Hip Hop History and the Wildstyle battle; N.O.R.E. performs "Nothin'.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625163000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Gillie Da King, Wallo267 and Flau'jae battle it out in games: On the Gang, Turn Me Up in the Headphones, Plead the Fifth and the Wildstyle battle; Flau'jae performs "Big 4.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Sukihana battle it out in games like Big Ol' Booty, Talking Spit, Plead the Fifth and the Wildstyle Battle; Sukihana performs "Grinch.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625173000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Justina Valentine and Tonio Skits battle it out in games like Got Props, Let Me Holla, Hip Hop Potluck and the Wildstyle Battle; Justina Valentine performs "Fever.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Basketball Wives</title>
    <desc>The women deal with the fallout from Suzie interrogating Tasha; Tami raises questions within the group when she does not show up at Evelyn's birthday blowout.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Basketball Wives</title>
    <desc>Evelyn talks to a therapist about her issues; Tami is displeased with Shaunie.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael and Jay get a lesson in listening when they try to remember what they asked each other to do.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Claire is upset when Michael continues to pal around with her former boyfriend (Andrew McFarlane); Junior spends too much time in the bathroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Just when Michael is feeling frustrated about his love life, his brother visits with his sexy new girlfriend.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael takes living life to its fullest a little too far after his accountant (Doug Banks) unexpectedly dies.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael is left in charge of the house when Janet leaves to tend to her sick mother, and must contend with multiple problems.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael contends with multiple problems, including a positive pregnancy test, a sad 6-year-old and Jr.'s basketball troubles.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>The household becomes unbearable when Michael decides to let the kids do as they please.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Fed up with Michael's parenting style, the children confront their father with a description of the ideal dad.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Johnson Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Separated from his beautiful wife (Vanessa L. Williams), Nate Johnson (Cedric the Entertainer) wants to make amends with her and spend time with his kids, finding the perfect chance for bonding in a cross-country trip to a family reunion. Convincing them all to join in on the journey, Nate takes the Johnson clan on a trek from California to Missouri, but they encounter various strange situations a</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624083000 +0000" stop="20260624090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>After having a conversation about dealbreakers in relationships with Bow, Dre realizes that he gave up on some of his goals in life and begins tackling them; Junior worries Olivia might leave him after she mentions her dealbreakers.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624090000 +0000" stop="20260624093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>After one of Dre's secrets with Pops is spilled to Ruby, he realizes that his relationships with each of his parents have changed since they got married; Bow surprises Jack and Diane with a brand-new car and tries to teach the twins how to drive.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624093000 +0000" stop="20260624100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>Dre feels pigeonholed to the urban marketing team at Stevens &amp; Lido and realizes he needs to make some big career changes; Boyz II Men stop by the office to help out the team with a campaign pitch; Junior has to deal with the twins.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624100000 +0000" stop="20260624103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>The most popular girl in high school turns J.J. into a one-woman man.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624103000 +0000" stop="20260624110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Florida promises to burst into a full-fledged hurricane unless someone can figure out what triggered the storm.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624110000 +0000" stop="20260624113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Cliff and Russell (Earle Hyman) recall baseball's great old days with two retired Negro League players (Frank Robinson, Joe Black).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624113000 +0000" stop="20260624120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Cliff urges two old friends (Red Buttons, E.G. Marshall) who have not spoken to each other for years to reunite.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624120000 +0000" stop="20260624123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>When Theo counsels at a community center, he gets an unexpected reaction from the kids.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624123000 +0000" stop="20260624130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>In his new job at the counseling center, Theo befriends a boy (Merlin Santana) with a reading problem.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624130000 +0000" stop="20260624133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Regine and Darryl second-guess their relationship after she fails to hit it off with his friends.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624133000 +0000" stop="20260624140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Things heat up for Maxine when she finds out her new boss is her former boyfriend.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624140000 +0000" stop="20260624143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Kyle becomes annoyed with Overton and Synclaire's relationship; Maxine tries to recover a compromising tape of herself.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624143000 +0000" stop="20260624150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Khadijah and Synclaire help Overton get revenge on pool sharks; Kyle has a date with a princess; Maxine goes to New Jersey to get a tattoo.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624150000 +0000" stop="20260624160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Attraction</title>
    <desc>When a young pregnant woman is reported missing, police work quickly to find any sign of her; but as all leads turn up nothing, the investigation is soon back to square one, until a surprising witness comes forward to reveal a devastating secret.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624160000 +0000" stop="20260624170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Attraction</title>
    <desc>A couple stumbles upon the tied body of a man in Atlanta's wealthiest neighborhood; police suspect his death may be related to a love triangle; a mysterious man known as "New York" could be the key to solving the case.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624170000 +0000" stop="20260624180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>A promising young woman with a passion for hip-hop finds her ride-or-die soul mate in a young up-and-coming rapper; when a petty feud turns deadly, she'll have to decide if she's all in for her man or if she's better off taking this ride alone.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624180000 +0000" stop="20260624190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>When a gifted new hip-hop artist takes the Dallas club scene by storm, she falls under the spell of a hot young man who seems to embody the thug life underworld she vividly portrays in her art.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624190000 +0000" stop="20260624200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>A young woman down on her luck falls in love with an older man who swears to protect her; after a deadly encounter leaves a family member in critical condition, his protection may not be enough when his actions lead her down a deadly path.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624200000 +0000" stop="20260624203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Dwayne is in the middle as Whitley and Kinu (Alise Gyse Dickens) compete on rival academic teams.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624203000 +0000" stop="20260624210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Walter is the host for a "Twilight Zone"-type look at students cramming for midterm exams.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624210000 +0000" stop="20260624213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Dwayne's visiting mom (Patti LaBelle) lands in the middle of a melee involving Dwayne, Kinu (Alisa Gyse Dickens) and Whitley.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624213000 +0000" stop="20260624220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Dwayne and Whitley finally commit themselves to a relationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624220000 +0000" stop="20260624223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Cliff and Russell (Earle Hyman) recall baseball's great old days with two retired Negro League players (Frank Robinson, Joe Black).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624223000 +0000" stop="20260624230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Cliff urges two old friends (Red Buttons, E.G. Marshall) who have not spoken to each other for years to reunite.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624230000 +0000" stop="20260624233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>When Theo counsels at a community center, he gets an unexpected reaction from the kids.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260624233000 +0000" stop="20260625000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>In his new job at the counseling center, Theo befriends a boy (Merlin Santana) with a reading problem.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-24</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625000000 +0000" stop="20260625003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Fred has different plans when Lamont and Rollo plan a romantic evening with two girls.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625003000 +0000" stop="20260625010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>A woman with whom Grady had a drunken fling mistakes him for her fiancé, Fred Sanford.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625010000 +0000" stop="20260625013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Grady tries to keep the Sanford home free of Bible meetings and orgies.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625013000 +0000" stop="20260625020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Woodrow moves into the Sanford house when Esther kicks him out.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625020000 +0000" stop="20260625023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Judy makes advances toward Grady to win his support in her scheme to marry Lamont.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625023000 +0000" stop="20260625030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Grady invites cousin Emma to the Sanfords', hoping that she will do the cooking and cleaning.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625030000 +0000" stop="20260625033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Junk dealer Fred Sanford runs roughshod over his son and partner, Lamont, in a groundbreaking sitcom. Fred's moneymaking schemes routinely backfire, and he does just about anything to get out of working -- up to and including faking a heart attack. He's rude, sarcastic, outspoken, overtly prejudiced, and pretty darn nasty to his friends and family.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625033000 +0000" stop="20260625040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>When Fred returns early from a long trip, he spoils a homecoming party Lamont and Grady had planned.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625040000 +0000" stop="20260625043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Uncle George dies, and Lamont will inherit $7,000 if he produces a son within the next 12 months and names him George.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625043000 +0000" stop="20260625050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Fred is sure that the ring Lamont gave him as a present is the one he has heard was stolen from Frank Sinatra.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625050000 +0000" stop="20260625053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Grady's fiancée decrees that after the wedding, he will no longer be spending his evenings with the Sanfords.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625053000 +0000" stop="20260625060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Lamont leaves after Fred refuses to allow a sensitivity group to meet at the Sanford home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625060000 +0000" stop="20260625063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Fred sees the beginning of the end of his junk business when Lamont takes a job in a men's clothing store.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625063000 +0000" stop="20260625070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Uncle George dies, and Lamont will inherit $7,000 if he produces a son within the next 12 months and names him George.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625070000 +0000" stop="20260625080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unsung</title>
    <desc>R &amp; B group, The Sylvers; "Boogie Fever" and "Hot Line.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625080000 +0000" stop="20260625083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>Dre overreacts to Devante leaving the house ashy and Bow intervenes, making the situation worse; Jack makes a bold outfit choice for picture day.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625083000 +0000" stop="20260625090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>Dre calls into a radio show and gets humiliated in front of Diane and tries to redeem himself; Bow tries to bond with a group of young female doctors and learns a hard truth.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625090000 +0000" stop="20260625093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>When Junior's girlfriend, Olivia, gets into Yale, he asks Bow to convince her to stay and attend USC instead; Diane and Jack discover Dre's inspiration for his ads are hitting a little too close to home.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625093000 +0000" stop="20260625100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>When Dre and Bow get a note that Devante may be falling behind at his private school, they expect he is being discriminated against because he is the only Black student in class; Jack and Diane enlist Charlie to cheer Junior up.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625100000 +0000" stop="20260625103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Michael protests when he is chosen to attend a better school as part of a busing program.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625103000 +0000" stop="20260625110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Michael's school assignment sets off a chain reaction of events in the Evans household.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625110000 +0000" stop="20260625113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Vanessa's announcement of her engagement comes as a shock to the family -- but more startling news follows.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625113000 +0000" stop="20260625120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Just as Clair is about to get a room of her own, Elvin (Geoffrey Owens) and Sondra's house plans go awry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625120000 +0000" stop="20260625123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>The air contains hints of romance for Theo; an out-and-out crush for Rudy dashes Kenny's (Deon Richmond) hopes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625123000 +0000" stop="20260625130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Pam's hopes to attend the same college as Charmaine are dashed; Olivia prepares for "show and tell.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625130000 +0000" stop="20260625133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Synclaire's role in a theatrical production is expanded, and she has to decide if she can play the part.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625133000 +0000" stop="20260625140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Khadijah covers a boxing scandal; Maxine helps Regine sue a former beau.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625140000 +0000" stop="20260625143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Regine and Khadijah's mothers go on vacation, leaving the girls to baby-sit Khadijah's grandmother.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625143000 +0000" stop="20260625150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>An appearance on a talk show about "Roommates From Heaven" ends with Regine packing her bags.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625150000 +0000" stop="20260625160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Attraction</title>
    <desc>A devoted and freshly-in-love father goes missing when his girlfriend discovers a scene of carnage in his apartment; with hard evidence in short supply and two suspects each pointing the finger at the other, the case becomes a battle of perception.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625160000 +0000" stop="20260625170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Attraction</title>
    <desc>A simple errand turns deadly when a young mom is shot and later succumbs to her injuries; after pursuing the wrong suspect, detectives face a new twist when a woman comes forward with information that will take the investigation across state lines.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625170000 +0000" stop="20260625180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>A Baltimore mother reconnects with her childhood sweetheart, but she ends up in the middle of a criminal investigation; loyalty to her man may put the blame on her.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625180000 +0000" stop="20260625190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>A young woman dedicated to her boyfriend offers to help with an easy errand, but when the task doesn't go according to plan, her man decides to seek reparations; his plan wraps her into an investigation.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625190000 +0000" stop="20260625200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>When a 26-year-old woman falls for a handsome 28-year-old, she believes she's found a man who will truly love and protect her; but when his protection comes with dire consequences, she'll have to weigh the cost of his security versus her own freedom.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625200000 +0000" stop="20260625203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Dwayne's preoccupation with Whitley affects his grades; Ron and Freddie plan a video.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625203000 +0000" stop="20260625210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Ron considers a career decision; Terrance (Cory Tyler) thinks his father (Glynn Turman) should reject an offer.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625210000 +0000" stop="20260625213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Emotions run high as Dwayne's classmates send their friend Zelmer to the Persian Gulf.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625213000 +0000" stop="20260625220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Whitley consults a counselor (Debbie Allen) for help in coping with her feelings about her ex-fiancé (Dominic Hoffman).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625220000 +0000" stop="20260625223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Vanessa's announcement of her engagement comes as a shock to the family -- but more startling news follows.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625223000 +0000" stop="20260625230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Just as Clair is about to get a room of her own, Elvin (Geoffrey Owens) and Sondra's house plans go awry.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625230000 +0000" stop="20260625233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>The air contains hints of romance for Theo; an out-and-out crush for Rudy dashes Kenny's (Deon Richmond) hopes.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260625233000 +0000" stop="20260626000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Pam's hopes to attend the same college as Charmaine are dashed; Olivia prepares for "show and tell.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-25</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260626000000 +0000" stop="20260627000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Uncensored</title>
    <desc>Tevin Campbell describes growing up in the spotlight as a child star, talks about being only 12 when he signed his record deal, working with star producers like Quincy Jones and Babyface, and releasing hits like "Can We Talk" and "I'm Ready.".</desc>
    <date>2026-06-26</date>
  </programme>
</tv>