<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260720224103 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="464919">
    <display-name lang="US">TLC HD (US)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465208">
    <display-name lang="US">TV ONE HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Sarper braces himself for never-before-seen footage of his confrontation outside the bar; Kara explains her secret hallway conversation with Guillermo; the cast deliberates over who they would eat to survive in the wilderness.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Thais becomes emotional while watching never-before-seen footage of her camp therapy session with Patrick and Dr. Tyrone, while Zied doubles down on wanting Rebecca to be a real wife; inspired by Russ and Pao, the cast plays Mouth Mayhem.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260721010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Tension amongst the couples reaches new heights at wilderness therapy. Guillermo draws a line in the sand with Kara. Pao is tired of waiting for Russ to be the man she wants. Shekinah and Sarper get exiled from the group.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721010000 +0000" stop="20260721020100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>The fallout from Greek Night intensifies as Sammy sides with Krista, leaving Steph blindsided. When Krista overhears Steph calling her a name, tensions explode. As relationships are redefined, Krista wants the apology she feels she's owed to move forward.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721020100 +0000" stop="20260721030100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>The cast reacts to never-before-seen footage from wilderness therapy. Pao reveals she met with a divorce attorney, Thais and Patrick discuss their tent hookup, and Shekinah's frustration over Sarper helping Thais sparks debate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721030100 +0000" stop="20260721040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth drops a shocking ultimatum when Andrei refuses to expand their family; Chloe is pushed to grow up fast with her mother moving away; Ashley and Manuel's explosive fights push their marriage to the breaking point.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721040000 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>Tension amongst the couples reaches new heights at wilderness therapy. Guillermo draws a line in the sand with Kara. Pao is tired of waiting for Russ to be the man she wants. Shekinah and Sarper get exiled from the group.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721060100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>The fallout from Greek Night intensifies as Sammy sides with Krista, leaving Steph blindsided. When Krista overhears Steph calling her a name, tensions explode. As relationships are redefined, Krista wants the apology she feels she's owed to move forward.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721060100 +0000" stop="20260721070100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Last Resort</title>
    <desc>The cast reacts to never-before-seen footage from wilderness therapy; Pao reveals she met with a divorce attorney; Thais and Patrick discuss their tent hookup; Shekinah's frustration over Sarper helping Thais sparks debate.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721070100 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Elizabeth drops a shocking ultimatum when Andrei refuses to expand their family; Chloe is pushed to grow up fast with her mother moving away; Ashley and Manuel's explosive fights push their marriage to the breaking point.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doubling Down with the Derricos</title>
    <desc>With the house close to being ready, the Derricos host a barbecue for their new neighbors in an effort to make a good first impression; Darian anxiously awaits word about her NYU application; GG takes steps to find out why she hasn't been feeling well.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doubling Down with the Derricos</title>
    <desc>Deon and Karen must deal with the children's emotional reaction to leaving their old house; Darian makes some drastic plans for her future; Eric leads the youngest five children on a search for the Easter Bunny; GG learns the results of her MRI.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jennifer Hudson Show</title>
    <desc>Simon Cowell ("America's Got Talent"); Olivia Culpo ("Next Gen Chef"); Jennifer welcomes 6-year-old viral video star Milo Garza.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Mitch and Cam's friend Sal announces she's getting married the next day, and they are in the wedding; Gloria doesn't trust her new nanny; Claire bonds with Haley; Phil helps Luke with a girl.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721113000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Claire and Cam bring in a third party (Wendi McLendon-Covey) when they reach an impasse on a landscaping decision; Phil teaches basic fix-it skills to the kids; Mitch helps Lily with a bully.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>While at the hospital, Claire and Phil see an older version of their family; Manny and Jay visit a private school; Mitch and Cam organize a day for Gloria and Lily.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721123000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Modern Family</title>
    <desc>Phil gets desperate when Cam and Claire's flipped house is more difficult to sell than expected; Javier brings his new girlfriend along to visit Manny.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé</title>
    <desc>Edward struggles to fit in with Marissa's friends; Catie's mom is concerned about her recent behavior; Debby asks Mido for a decision; Anabelle offends Shea's daughter; Ashia seeks her mother-in-law's approval; Rasit makes an unlikely bond.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little and Looking for Love</title>
    <desc>A 19-year-old primordial dwarf, Hannah, journeys through adolescence facing ordinary challenges with an extraordinary condition.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>Krista's roaring 20s birthday bash brings glamour, jealousy, and surprise guests as Sammy and Steph's messy love triangle creates new suspicions; JJ confronts her past, and Krista takes a big climb toward independence.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>Krista's birthday party sparks drama as Sammy distances himself from Steph after their kiss; Anthony pursues Krista, while JJ and John grow closer; after a night of Drag Bingo, John shares a shocking secret that leaves JJ stunned.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Little Singles</title>
    <desc>Steph and John come clean about the secret relationships complicating their lives; Steph's Greek-themed celebration spirals into chaos when Krista confronts Sammy about the messy love triangle threatening to tear the group apart.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jay &amp; Pamela</title>
    <desc>Jay and Pamela brave New York City to make their runway debut during fashion week; they also want to take in all that NYC has to offer, but sightseeing has its challenges; Raphael and Rene are overwhelmed helping Jay and Pamela shop for a new bed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jay &amp; Pamela</title>
    <desc>With Jay turning 30, Pamela plans to celebrate this milestone birthday by giving him the party he always dreamt of as a child. And she has some surprises for him including one that makes him blush!</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jay &amp; Pamela</title>
    <desc>Pamela braces for family drama when she and Jay head to Kansas City for her grandmother's funeral; Rene and Raphael are caught completely off guard when Jay and Pamela reveal plans for the future; a visit to a fertility clinic has Pamela on edge.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>Baylen returns from Kansas City still hurt by Sammi's Bridezilla comment; hoping to lift Baylen's spirits, Colin plans a Valentine's Day surprise while the couple meets a wedding officiant; Colin reveals another surprise she never saw coming.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>After surprising Baylen with a wedding day change, the couple goes to their menu tasting and Colin drops another bombshell; Julie worries the mounting pressure on Sammi to pull off the perfect celebration could further strain her relationship with Baylen.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260722000000 +0000" stop="20260723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>With bonus scenes; Baylen's bridal shower finally arrives, but the celebration takes a turn when she reveals shocking future plans; Baylen and Sammi confront the tension that's been lingering.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260720220000 +0000" stop="20260720223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Denise must convince her parents that she has found the perfect job.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260720223000 +0000" stop="20260720230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>The grandparents are surprised when Sondra gives birth to twins.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260720230000 +0000" stop="20260720233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>The grandparents are surprised when Sondra gives birth to twins.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260720233000 +0000" stop="20260721000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Theo wants a date with Julia (Naomi Campbell) but needs his best friend's (Troy Winbush) help; Rudy owes money to her father.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721000000 +0000" stop="20260721010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Attraction</title>
    <desc>When a hard-working Liberian immigrant is found brutally murdered, her family is left reeling. But Investigators soon uncover a secret that may have led to her death. With the trail going cold will they find the killer before they disappear for good?</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721010000 +0000" stop="20260721020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Attraction</title>
    <desc>When a young sex worker goes missing in Houston, her loved ones believe law enforcement isn't making her case a priority; as days turn to weeks, hope begins to dwindle until a seemingly unrelated 911 call comes in that turns the case on its head.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721020000 +0000" stop="20260721030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>A 19-year-old who spent her life taking care of others falls hard for a reckless man who has a gun, a plan, and no conscience. Her soft heart gives way to blind loyalty-landing her behind the wheel of a deadly crime spree with no escape route.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721030000 +0000" stop="20260721040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>In La Crosse, Brittany Jones' rush to aid her boyfriend after a violent encounter plunges her into a legal nightmare, with loyalty leading to harsh consequences.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721040000 +0000" stop="20260721050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Attraction</title>
    <desc>When a young sex worker goes missing in Houston, her loved ones believe law enforcement isn't making her case a priority; as days turn to weeks, hope begins to dwindle until a seemingly unrelated 911 call comes in that turns the case on its head.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721050000 +0000" stop="20260721060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>A 19-year-old who spent her life taking care of others falls hard for a reckless man who has a gun, a plan, and no conscience. Her soft heart gives way to blind loyalty-landing her behind the wheel of a deadly crime spree with no escape route.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721060000 +0000" stop="20260721070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>When Antonetta Stevens learns her fiancé is cheating, she plots revenge; with her sister-in-law by her side, she lures his lover into a deadly ambush; what she does for her man changes everything.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721070000 +0000" stop="20260721080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unsung</title>
    <desc>Warryn Campbell is joined by Mary Mary, DJ Quik, Mario, Shanice and more to celebrate and share the story of his life and hits.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721080000 +0000" stop="20260721083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>The family is divided over the idea of getting a dog; Bow's brother Johan is in town, and he doesn't get the warm welcome he expects from Ruby.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721083000 +0000" stop="20260721090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>Dre and Bow decide to go back to their therapist, who suggests they make time for a date night; when the bouncy house gets left behind after Devante's birthday party, Jack and Diane take advantage of it in different ways.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721090000 +0000" stop="20260721093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>When Junior decides to run for class president, Dre steps in to be his campaign manager; Pops, Johan and Jack discuss the presidential election; Bow worries Zoey's college essay isn't good enough.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721093000 +0000" stop="20260721100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">black-ish</title>
    <desc>The Johnson kids try to cope when Dre and Bow try taking turns living in the house to give each other space; tensions rise when the family reunites for Junior's high school graduation.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721100000 +0000" stop="20260721103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Denise has a crush on her geology professor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721103000 +0000" stop="20260721110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Jaleesa takes bets on how Dwayne will act when a graduate student tries to seduce him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721110000 +0000" stop="20260721113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>A voice teacher (Betty Carter) helps Vanessa and her friends polish a musical act.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721113000 +0000" stop="20260721120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Clair hires a fitness instructor (Debbie Allen) to get her back into shape.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721120000 +0000" stop="20260721123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>The hamster Rudy is watching for a friend falls ill during the night.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721123000 +0000" stop="20260721130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Vanessa tells a fib so she can rendezvous with her boyfriend.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721130000 +0000" stop="20260721133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Khadijah neglects her roommates when she becomes involved in a new romance.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721133000 +0000" stop="20260721140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Things the roommates confided to Regine surface in a comic's act.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721140000 +0000" stop="20260721143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>When Khadijah's mother visits on Mother's Day, she brings her friend Laverne, Regine's estranged mother.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721143000 +0000" stop="20260721150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Khadijah must choose between Alonzo and her old flame, Terrence, who announces he wants her back.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721150000 +0000" stop="20260721160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Attraction</title>
    <desc>When a woman is found with a single gunshot wound to her head, her family is shocked; a free spirit and devoted mother, she loved life; as detectives dig, they question if her happiness was just a façade, or if her death was by someone else's hand.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721160000 +0000" stop="20260721170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fatal Attraction</title>
    <desc>Detectives uncover a history of abuse and a man out for revenge when a woman is found murdered in her own bed.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721170000 +0000" stop="20260721180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>Jasmine Webb's romance with Doug Heath began in light but ended in darkness. Manipulated by abuse and drugs, she became trapped in his violent spiral-until one night at a barbecue, gunfire claimed an innocent man and shattered families forever.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721180000 +0000" stop="20260721190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>A seasoned correctional officer finds herself drawn to the kind of man she's spent her career keeping the city safe from. And as the relationship quickly heats up, she must choose between the life she's known and the love she's just discovered.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721190000 +0000" stop="20260721200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">For My Man</title>
    <desc>When a single mother in Buffalo, New York feels her man slipping away, she makes a bold move in an attempt to win back his affection. Blinded by passion, her reckless choice has life-altering consequences that reverberate through her entire community.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721200000 +0000" stop="20260721203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Denise has a crush on her geology professor.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721203000 +0000" stop="20260721210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Jaleesa takes bets on how Dwayne will act when a graduate student tries to seduce him.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721210000 +0000" stop="20260721213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Denise volunteers as a school counselor during final exams to get out of writing a major research paper.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721213000 +0000" stop="20260721220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Different World</title>
    <desc>Former Hillman student Lettie Bostic returns and assumes the role of dorm director.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721220000 +0000" stop="20260721223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>A voice teacher (Betty Carter) helps Vanessa and her friends polish a musical act.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721223000 +0000" stop="20260721230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Clair hires a fitness instructor (Debbie Allen) to get her back into shape.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721230000 +0000" stop="20260721233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>The hamster Rudy is watching for a friend falls ill during the night.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260721233000 +0000" stop="20260722000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Vanessa tells a fib so she can rendezvous with her boyfriend.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-21</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260722000000 +0000" stop="20260723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Khadijah neglects her roommates when she becomes involved in a new romance.</desc>
    <date>2026-07-22</date>
  </programme>
</tv>