<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<tv date="20260530111733 " generator-info-name="TV2-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV2-Source-EPG">
  <channel id="470773">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Showcase Television Inc. (Canada)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9191">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Arts HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465259">
    <display-name lang="US">Oprah Winfrey Network HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9583">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Atlantic HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465009">
    <display-name lang="US">Ovation HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470459">
    <display-name lang="Canada">SLICE HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470003">
    <display-name lang="US">WLIW-DT</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464919">
    <display-name lang="US">TLC HD (US)</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="470616">
    <display-name lang="Canada">Silver Screen Classics</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9187">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Comedy HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465053">
    <display-name lang="US">Syfy HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465114">
    <display-name lang="US">TNT HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465006">
    <display-name lang="US">USA Network HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="464987">
    <display-name lang="US">truTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465206">
    <display-name lang="US">VH1 HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="12517">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Max HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="9577">
    <display-name lang="United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland">Sky Witness+1</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465138">
    <display-name lang="US">SundanceTV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465278">
    <display-name lang="US">Start TV Network</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465208">
    <display-name lang="US">TV ONE HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="465234">
    <display-name lang="US">Vice HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260530100000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Mom's Letter From Heaven</title>
    <desc>A rebellious teenager finds a letter from her dead mother.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rookie Blue</title>
    <desc>An inmate escapes during a prisoner transport; Gail and Dov try to help a man with amnesia; Traci and Chris help reconstruct notes missing from a court case.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rookie Blue</title>
    <desc>Andy faces the possibility that her father may have murdered someone during a drunken blackout; Chris and Dov's squad car is robbed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rookie Blue</title>
    <desc>Andy questions her future with the force after the suspicious death of a young girl; the rookies find out if they have passed their evaluations.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rookie Blue</title>
    <desc>An untimely arrest compromises a major drug bust; Andy goes undercover with Swarek; Dov must choose between his girlfriend and his career.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jack Reacher</title>
    <desc>One morning in an ordinary town, five people are shot dead in a seemingly random attack; all evidence points to a single suspect: an ex-military sniper who is quickly brought into custody; Reacher, an enigmatic ex-Army investigator, believes the authorities have the right man but agrees to help the sniper's defense attorney.. However, the more Reacher delves into the case, the less clear-cut it ap</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jack Reacher: Never Go Back</title>
    <desc>Investigator Jack Reacher (Tom Cruise) springs into action after the arrest of Susan Turner (Cobie Smulders), an Army major accused of treason. Suspecting foul play, Jack embarks on a mission to prove that the head of his old unit is innocent. After crossing paths with the law, Reacher must now go on the lam to uncover the truth behind a major government conspiracy that involves the death of U.S. </desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260530213000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jack Ryan: Shadow Recruit</title>
    <desc>CIA recruit Jack Ryan is caught in a dangerous web of intrigue and espionage spun between a shadowy government agent, his unsuspecting fiancée and a fearless Russian power broker. To stop a devastating terrorist plot against the United States, Jack must quickly evolve from soldier to analyst to full-fledged operative.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission: Impossible Rogue Nation</title>
    <desc>With the IMF now disbanded and Ethan Hunt out in the cold, a new threat -- called the Syndicate -- soon emerges. The Syndicate is a network of highly skilled operatives who are dedicated to establishing a new world order via an escalating series of terrorist attacks. Faced with what may be the most impossible mission yet, Ethan gathers his team and joins forces with Ilsa Faust, a disavowed British</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hostage</title>
    <desc>After one of his hostage negotiations goes awry, LAPD officer Jeff Talley (Bruce Willis) quits the force and relocates his family to the suburbs. As the sheriff in a sleepy town, Jeff thinks he has escaped the hustle and bustle -- until an elaborate local heist puts him back in the center of a hostage situation. When his own family is pulled into the fray, Jeff is forced to decide whether he shoul</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531053000 +0000" stop="20260531083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission: Impossible Rogue Nation</title>
    <desc>With the IMF now disbanded and Ethan Hunt out in the cold, a new threat -- called the Syndicate -- soon emerges. The Syndicate is a network of highly skilled operatives who are dedicated to establishing a new world order via an escalating series of terrorist attacks. Faced with what may be the most impossible mission yet, Ethan gathers his team and joins forces with Ilsa Faust, a disavowed British</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531083000 +0000" stop="20260531093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NCIS</title>
    <desc>After NCIS finds a secret government bank account that's funding a nationwide network of vigilante justice, the team must determine who is acting as judge and jury.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531093000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Face to Face With David</title>
    <desc>David Oulton interviews guests from the worlds of entertainment, business, fashion and politics.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Obsession: Escaping My Ex</title>
    <desc>Madison Turner must fight for her life when the man who betrayed her escapes from a prison van and holds her captive.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Private Eyes</title>
    <desc>Angie's mother's new beau hires Everett and Shade, when his clinic's database is hacked.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Private Eyes</title>
    <desc>Shade and Angie investigate a vandalized shop.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Top Gun</title>
    <desc>The Top Gun Naval Fighter Weapons School is where the best of the best train to refine their elite flying skills. When hotshot fighter pilot Maverick (Tom Cruise) is sent to the school, his reckless attitude and cocky demeanor put him at odds with the other pilots, especially the cool and collected Iceman (Val Kilmer). But Maverick isn't only competing to be the top fighter pilot, he's also fighti</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission: Impossible</title>
    <desc>When U.S. government operative Ethan Hunt (Tom Cruise) and his mentor, Jim Phelps (Jon Voight), go on a covert assignment that takes a disastrous turn, Jim is killed, and Ethan becomes the prime murder suspect. Now a fugitive, Hunt recruits brilliant hacker Luther Stickell (Ving Rhames) and maverick pilot Franz Krieger (Jean Reno) to help him sneak into a heavily guarded CIA building to retrieve a</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission: Impossible III</title>
    <desc>Retired from active duty, and training recruits for the Impossible Mission Force, agent Ethan Hunt (Tom Cruise) faces the toughest foe of his career: Owen Davian (Philip Seymour Hoffman), an international broker of arms and information, who is as cunning as he is ruthless. Davian emerges to threaten Hunt and all that he holds dear -- including the woman Hunt loves.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260531213000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission: Impossible III</title>
    <desc>Retired from active duty, and training recruits for the Impossible Mission Force, agent Ethan Hunt (Tom Cruise) faces the toughest foe of his career: Owen Davian (Philip Seymour Hoffman), an international broker of arms and information, who is as cunning as he is ruthless. Davian emerges to threaten Hunt and all that he holds dear -- including the woman Hunt loves.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470773" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mission: Impossible -- Fallout</title>
    <desc>Ethan Hunt and the IMF team join forces with CIA assassin August Walker to prevent a disaster of epic proportions. Arms dealer John Lark and a group of terrorists known as the Apostles plan to use three plutonium cores for a simultaneous nuclear attack on the Vatican, Jerusalem and Mecca, Saudi Arabia. When the weapons go missing, Ethan and his crew find themselves in a desperate race against time</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <desc>A young doctor continues to date a beautiful showgirl in spite of warnings that her three previous marriages ended badly for her past husbands.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Peter O'Toole: Along The Sky Road to Aqaba</title>
    <desc>Feature documentary reflecting on Peter O'Toole's towering theatrical legacy. Includes interviews with Sir Anthony Hopkins, Sir Derek Jacobi and Stephen Fry.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovering: Dirk Bogarde</title>
    <desc>Movie experts reflect on the career of Dirk Bogarde, the great English actor known for his complex roles in the dark films Victim, Death in Venice and The Night Porter.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic Movies: Mulholland...</title>
    <desc>A look at David Lynch's 2001 mystery thriller, defined by the shifting relationship between Betty and Rita.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530171000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Iconic Women Of Country</title>
    <desc>Iconic Women Of Country opens up the music vaults to provide an intimate look at legendary female artists, their stories and songs and why they've stood the test of time.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530171000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Johnny Cash: A Legend in Concert</title>
    <desc>Fantastic collection of recordings from Johnny Cash's early years, including nostalgic performances of I Got Stripes, Don't Take Your Guns To Town and Five Feet High and Rising.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bowie: The Man Who Changed The World</title>
    <desc>Documentary celebrating the life and legacy of David Bowie, one of the 20th century's most influential musical artists. Features interviews with those who knew him best.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Bowie: Serious Moonlight</title>
    <desc>Filmed in Vancouver in 1983 during his legendary Serious Moonlight Tour, David Bowie performs hits including Heroes, Let's Dance, Life on Mars?, Rebel Rebel, and Fame.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530235000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Becoming Madonna</title>
    <desc>Madonna's coming-of-age story is one of the greatest in entertainment history. This immersive documentary traces her transformation from outsider to controversial star. Strong language/sex.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260530235000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bjork: Cornucopia</title>
    <desc>The eponymous concert tour, which debuted as a residency at The Shed in New York City before travelling the world and concluding four years later. Flashing images.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531031500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Women Who Rock</title>
    <desc>Take a trip back to the 1970s, a game-changing decade which brought new sounds and icons like Nancy Wilson and Joan Jett, plus rockers such as Debbie Harry. (2 of.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531031500 +0000" stop="20260531041000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Great Songwriters</title>
    <desc>Ian McCulloch / Echo and the Bunnymen: The Echo and the Bunnymen frontman talks songwriting and his life in music, and performs beloved tracks including The Killing Moon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531041000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Discovering: Elton John</title>
    <desc>Leading figures in the music industry examine the monumental career of Sir Elton John, exploring his greatest hits, as well as his work on The Lion King and Billy Elliot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Turandot</title>
    <desc>At the Vienna State Opera, Claus Guth stages Puccini's last opera as a chamber drama of timeless topicality, with audience favourite Jonas Kaufmann in the leading role.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531073000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tales Of The Unexpected</title>
    <desc>Art dealer Lionel gets an artist to visualise his fiancee Janet nude and paint her accordingly. Janet, however, does not see the funny side.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tales Of The Unexpected</title>
    <desc>When Pamela and Arthur invite a young couple over for the weekend, things take a surprising turn.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531083000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tales Of The Unexpected</title>
    <desc>A dinner party takes a surprising turn when one pretentious guest is challenged to a wine-tasting contest.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tales Of The Unexpected</title>
    <desc>John Mills stars in this twisted tale. A man starts to suffer when he becomes haunted by the memory of the brutal treatment he received in his childhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531093000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tales Of The Unexpected</title>
    <desc>Joan Collins stars in a twisted tale. George has problems with female attention, but when a beautiful woman joins his congregation things are set to change.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <desc>A remorseful detective vows to find the men who murdered his son, who followed in his footsteps and also became a cop.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Alfred Hitchcock Hour</title>
    <desc>A patient at a mental hospital kills the head doctor and takes over, replacing the staff with fellow patients.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531142000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classic FM Live: Summer</title>
    <desc>.Concert 2026. From the Royal Albert Hall, Dan Walker and Myleene Klass lead a powerhouse night with the CBSO and top soloists.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531142000 +0000" stop="20260531154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Portrait Artist Of The Decade</title>
    <desc>In this special, the last nine winners return to the Battersea Arts Centre to paint one of Britain's best-loved personalities - in the space of just four hours.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531154500 +0000" stop="20260531172500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Joseph And The Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat</title>
    <desc>Based on the story of Joseph and his coat of many colours, Tim Rice and Andrew Lloyd Webber's first musical comes to the screen. Starring Donny Osmond.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531172500 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FILM: Agatha Christie's The Seven Dials Mystery</title>
    <desc>In 1925, a country house party prank turns deadly. Lady Caterham and Superintendent Battle assist in solving the country house mystery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Manchurian Candidate</title>
    <desc>An American POW in the Korean War is brainwashed as an unwitting assassin for an international Communist conspiracy. Discriminatory content.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9191" start="20260531223000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Opry Live</title>
    <desc>Prepare to be blown away by performances from Opry member Riley Green, Charles Wesley Godwin and Ashley McBryde.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belle Collective: Birmingham</title>
    <desc>Tiffaney launches her Choosing Line to mixed reviews. Funmi's dreams are crushed when Sam makes a move she didn't see coming. Stormi makes a choice that shifts the group's future. At a Last Supper, the truth is served cold -- and betrayals come to light.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belle Collective: Birmingham</title>
    <desc>At the reunion, lies and betrayals leave the Collective questioning everything. Stormi and Tiffaney revisit the fallout that changed the group dynamic. K'La's character is attacked, Funmi faces an unexpected foe, and Amber reveals her true loyalty.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family or Fiancé</title>
    <desc>A couple who rushed into an engagement now face some serious conversations when they discover that their philosophies on religion, children, and other crucial ideologies are so unaligned that the groom even refuses to get a marriage license.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family or Fiancé</title>
    <desc>A groom desperately wishes to impress his bride's wealthy parents and prove he will be a suitable husband.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Party</title>
    <desc>Play's parents are out of town, and he's planning the house party to end all house parties. His best friend, Kid, wants to go more than anything, knowing Sydney (Tisha Campbell-Martin), the hottest girl in school, is sure to be there. But when Kid gets into a fight at school, his father grounds him. Still determined to go, Kid sneaks out of the house and faces one calamity after another as he make</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530173000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters</title>
    <desc>A Phoenix man is excited to invest in his first property, but while he wants a place that fits his bachelor lifestyle, his mother wants him to settle down in a single-family home; with Mom helping to cover costs, he must consider her two cents.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters</title>
    <desc>Twin sisters search for a home that can accommodate them, one husband and their aging mother in Atlanta; they're looking for a place that will give everyone their own personal space, but pleasing so many big personalities will be a challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530183000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters</title>
    <desc>A family has been staying with parents until they can afford a place of their own in New Rochelle, N.Y.; one doesn't mind spending more on a fully-renovated historic charmer, but the other is determined to find a home in need of fixing up.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters International</title>
    <desc>A couple hope to leave the stress of Los Angeles and start a real estate business in Playa del Carmen, Mexico; one wants to live the dream with a pricey private getaway, while his husband pushes for a practical option so they can focus on business.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530193000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters International</title>
    <desc>After a lengthy long-distance relationship, a married couple searches for their first place in his hometown of South Gloucestershire, England; they're giving up her income to make the move, so they'll have to navigate more than just big expectations.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Funniest Home Videos</title>
    <desc>Kids are stumped by pay phones; dogs react to disappearing owners; soccer mishaps; party fails.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Funniest Home Videos</title>
    <desc>A woman finds out she's going to be a grandma; a little boy tears two $20 bills in half; a boy cuts his hair and glues it to his armpits; senior citizens laugh at themselves.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Marriage: Huntsville</title>
    <desc>Destiny and Nell make nice, for now. Tisha finds a new way to anger Marsau. Destiny questions Tisha's motives. Kimmi casts doubt on Marsau's feelings toward Maurice. Tricia tries to change her story, again. The Scott brothers meet for a serious talk.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Marriage: Huntsville</title>
    <desc>The gang travels to Guntersville for a couples' retreat. Now that Tricia's divorce is finalized, she doesn't seem that happy. Destiny and Tisha attempt to mend their relationship, and Maurice and Martell bump heads over Maurice's DUI story.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Marriage: Huntsville</title>
    <desc>Maurice tries to resolve his beef with Martell. The group enjoys their last days in Guntersville. Kimmi shares a shocking revelation about her relationship. Marsau and Tisha have a very difficult conversation about their future.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531010000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heart &amp; Hustle: Houston</title>
    <desc>The ladies are back, but with the group fractured, La'Torria wonders if they will all show up for her event; Chloe uncovers a shocking revelation about her relationship, while Alaina's estranged husband shares his version of their broken marriage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belle Collective: Birmingham</title>
    <desc>At the reunion, lies and betrayals leave the Collective questioning everything. Stormi and Tiffaney revisit the fallout that changed the group dynamic. K'La's character is attacked, Funmi faces an unexpected foe, and Amber reveals her true loyalty.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Marriage: Huntsville</title>
    <desc>Maurice tries to resolve his beef with Martell. The group enjoys their last days in Guntersville. Kimmi shares a shocking revelation about her relationship. Marsau and Tisha have a very difficult conversation about their future.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heart &amp; Hustle: Houston</title>
    <desc>The ladies are back, but with the group fractured, La'Torria wonders if they will all show up for her event; Chloe uncovers a shocking revelation about her relationship, while Alaina's estranged husband shares his version of their broken marriage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Belle Collective: Birmingham</title>
    <desc>At the reunion, lies and betrayals leave the Collective questioning everything. Stormi and Tiffaney revisit the fallout that changed the group dynamic. K'La's character is attacked, Funmi faces an unexpected foe, and Amber reveals her true loyalty.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Marriage: Huntsville</title>
    <desc>The gang travels to Guntersville for a couples' retreat. Now that Tricia's divorce is finalized, she doesn't seem that happy. Destiny and Tisha attempt to mend their relationship, and Maurice and Martell bump heads over Maurice's DUI story.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Marriage: Huntsville</title>
    <desc>Maurice tries to resolve his beef with Martell. The group enjoys their last days in Guntersville. Kimmi shares a shocking revelation about her relationship. Marsau and Tisha have a very difficult conversation about their future.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">#Somebody's Son</title>
    <desc>The winner of the couples' photo shoot goes on a date with Joshua, leaving the other women plotting their next move; James deepens his bond with Alyssia during a flirtatious dinner, while one woman's jealousy causes her to spiral.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">#Somebody's Son</title>
    <desc>Both houses participate in a vulnerable "bare it all" exercise, revealing hidden truths and stirring emotions; Joshua and James go on massage dates; James grows closer to Sabranae.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Marriage: Huntsville</title>
    <desc>The gang travels to Guntersville for a couples' retreat. Now that Tricia's divorce is finalized, she doesn't seem that happy. Destiny and Tisha attempt to mend their relationship, and Maurice and Martell bump heads over Maurice's DUI story.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love and Marriage: Huntsville</title>
    <desc>Maurice tries to resolve his beef with Martell. The group enjoys their last days in Guntersville. Kimmi shares a shocking revelation about her relationship. Marsau and Tisha have a very difficult conversation about their future.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Heart &amp; Hustle: Houston</title>
    <desc>The ladies are back, but with the group fractured, La'Torria wonders if they will all show up for her event; Chloe uncovers a shocking revelation about her relationship, while Alaina's estranged husband shares his version of their broken marriage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Funniest Home Videos</title>
    <desc>Wedding fails, including a groom who gets a phone call at the altar; a man pranks his girlfriend into thinking motorcycles have seatbelts; a mom challenges her son to eat a spoonful of horseradish.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Funniest Home Videos</title>
    <desc>Parents trick kids into eating caramel-covered onions; a mailman climbs up a pole to escape a dog that is chasing him; kids say funny things.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Funniest Home Videos</title>
    <desc>A woman finds out she's going to be a grandma; a little boy tears two $20 bills in half; a boy cuts his hair and glues it to his armpits; senior citizens laugh at themselves.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Funniest Home Videos</title>
    <desc>Kids are stumped by pay phones; dogs react to disappearing owners; soccer mishaps; party fails.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters</title>
    <desc>A social media influencer is ready to leave public housing and find a home of her own in New Jersey; she's looking for a multi-family property that will build generational wealth, but her long list of must-haves will make her search a challenge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531173000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters</title>
    <desc>A first-time buyer is focused on historic row homes in Philadelphia; however, her college friend and agent struggles to get her to accept what houses actually cost in the current market.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters</title>
    <desc>After a stint in Dallas, a family of seven is moving back to its hometown of Kansas City; she's thrifty and looking for a starter home on the Missouri side, but he's willing to spend more for a bigger home on the Kansas side of town.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531183000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters</title>
    <desc>A buyer has worked hard to get through a lot in life and is now ready to buy her first home outside Washington, D.C.; her sisters have their own ideas about what's best for her in a purchase, and she'll have to struggle to make her own decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters International</title>
    <desc>Wooed by the friendly people, good weather and delicious food, two entrepreneurs are moving their family to Merida, Mexico; while she's pushing for relaxing beachfront living, he wants to be surrounded by convenience in the city's bustling downtown.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531193000 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters International</title>
    <desc>A family of urban homesteaders is leaving their Atlanta home to give their kids a hands-on global experience in Jaco, Costa Rica; Dad has big ideas on how to ease their transition, but world-traveler Mom is focused on the details.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters International</title>
    <desc>A Utah couple with a young baby decides to make the move to New Zealand after finding a career-boosting job in Timaru that promises a practical, family-focused lifestyle.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531203000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters International</title>
    <desc>A mother decides to move overseas and lands a clinical social worker position in Okinawa, Japan; she's resolute on finding a penthouse apartment with an ocean view, but her sensible daughter is determined to keep those wild ideas in check.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters International</title>
    <desc>A recently laid off Arizona woman decides the time is right for a new adventure teaching English abroad; a job in Shenzhen, China, fits the bill, but she struggles to come to terms with how small apartments are in her price range.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531213000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">House Hunters International</title>
    <desc>A newly engaged couple that has never left Philadelphia or lived together decides to take the leap and move to Sydney to pursue a job opportunity; they are challenged to figure out their new country, new home and new set of relationship rules.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260531230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">48 Hours: Hard Evidence</title>
    <desc>In a small Texas town, Darci Bass receives devastating news, someone shot her daughter, Livye Lewis, in her car; investigators find Lewis' ex-boyfriend bloodied and disoriented; he insists he has no recollection of what happened; Peter Van San reports.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260531230000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">48 Hours: Hard Evidence</title>
    <desc>On New Year's 2021 in her Canton, Georgia, home, Morgan Metzer finds herself confronting an intruder; Metzer's ordeal takes a surprising turn when her ex-husband comes to her rescue, but is he a hero or something more sinister?</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465259" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">48 Hours: Hard Evidence</title>
    <desc>A gunman murders a Yale grad student in New Haven. As police investigate, they uncover signs of obsession and premeditation -- revealing a plan masked as chance. What begins as a quick attack unravels into something far more personal and calculated.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deadwood</title>
    <desc>The camp elders hold a meeting to map out a strategy to deal with the dastardly Hearst. But can they outwit the ruthless gold baron.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deadwood</title>
    <desc>Wyatt Earp and his brother ride into town as heroes when they save a sabotaged stagecoach. But is there more to the newcomers than meets the eye.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deadwood</title>
    <desc>Merrick answers for his publication of the Sheriff's letter, and Hearst's muscle terrorize the camp. Can anyone stop his ruthlessness? Gritty drama.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prisoner</title>
    <desc>Prison officer Amber must escort a criminal to court. When the convoy is ambushed, she shackles herself to him and they go on the run.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prisoner</title>
    <desc>Amber forms an uneasy alliance with her prisoner as they're pulled deeper into a dangerous criminal underworld.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prisoner</title>
    <desc>With danger closing in, Amber makes a risky decision as she fights to protect her family.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prisoner</title>
    <desc>Amber reunites with her family while Tibor faces his mother. Olly's actions put them all in danger.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prisoner</title>
    <desc>Separated and under pressure, Amber turns to Tibor for help as a wider threat begins to emerge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prisoner</title>
    <desc>Amber's plan to get Tibor to court is put in jeopardy in London. The fate of her family becomes paramount.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Miniature Wife</title>
    <desc>Gone Into the Heart of Darkness: Lindy's thirst for vengeance against Les turns into all-out war. The battle is on. Contains strong language.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530215500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>As Ava moves on, Deborah opens The Diva and faces her final act. With new roles and big choices, her legacy takes shape in the final chapter. Contains upsetting themes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530215500 +0000" stop="20260530230500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True Detective</title>
    <desc>As they deal with family crises, Liz and Navarro zone in on the site of Annie's murder. Language/distressing scenes. (S4, ep 4 of.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260530230500 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Succession</title>
    <desc>Amid rising tensions, Shiv tries to reposition herself within a new political landscape, while Kendall rallies supporters. (S4, ep 9 of.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531002500 +0000" stop="20260531012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Homicide: Life On The Street</title>
    <desc>A girl is found with a broken rib which punctured her lung and 26 belt buckle marks on her body.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531012000 +0000" stop="20260531021500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Homicide: Life On The Street</title>
    <desc>An Asian store owner, a war hero, tried to forbid dope dealers from operating outside his store. His killing leads detectives to Mahoney.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531021500 +0000" stop="20260531031000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Homicide: Life On The Street</title>
    <desc>Pembleton and Lewis are assigned to the brutal murder of a wealthy woman, as each focus on a different suspect.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531031000 +0000" stop="20260531040500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Guest Wing</title>
    <desc>At Chillingham Castle, the staff manage their relationship with eccentric baronet Sir Humphry Wakefield, while Carlton Towers welcomes the Afghan Hound Dog Show. (Episode 3 of.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531040500 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Guest Wing</title>
    <desc>Carlton Towers hosts a British culinary weekend for eager tourists, while a group of budding wine connoisseurs arrive at Chillingham Castle for a tasting weekend. (Episode 4 of.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fish Town</title>
    <desc>Dreams become a reality when 17-year-old Logan takes to the high seas as an apprentice deck hand. Plus, landlady Pat enjoys a trip down memory lane, recalling the old days.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Fish Town</title>
    <desc>Competition is fierce as local merchant Robert and wife Kelly open up a fish and chip restaurant. Plus, follow the journey of the turbot as it goes from sea to the dinner plate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531075000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deadwood</title>
    <desc>An attempt on Alma's life prompts Swearengen to take her into protective custody. But who is responsible for the attempted murder? Gritty drama.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531075000 +0000" stop="20260531084500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deadwood</title>
    <desc>Trixie decides to take the Hearst matter into her own hands, leaving the rest of the camp to deal with what she's done... Gritty drama.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531084500 +0000" stop="20260531094500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catherine The Great</title>
    <desc>Oscar winner Helen Mirren stars in an epic Sky Original about the power, politics and passions of Russian empress Catherine the Great. (1 of.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531094500 +0000" stop="20260531104500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catherine The Great</title>
    <desc>Potemkin returns, only to discover that Catherine has a new lover. Prince Paul grows more frustrated by his lack of power. (2 of.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531104500 +0000" stop="20260531115000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catherine The Great</title>
    <desc>Catherine struggles to deal with Potemkin's jealousy. Then, tragedy strikes for Paul, forcing her to resort to extreme measures. (3 of.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531115000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Catherine The Great</title>
    <desc>Mistrust pushes Catherine and Potemkin's relationship to breaking point. Following a tragedy, a despotic Catherine makes a decision. (4 of.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531134000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>After returning from Singapore to a career further smeared by Bob Lipka, Deborah decides to shift the narrative and focus on achieving EGOT status.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531134000 +0000" stop="20260531142000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>Deborah rallies her fanbase to help secure Madison Square Garden for her next stand-up show. Meanwhile, Jimmy pitches an idol and Ava meets a fan.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531142000 +0000" stop="20260531150500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>Deborah hits it off with the Palmetto's new artist in residence. Marcus sets out to save a historic casino and Marty has uninvited wedding guests.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531150500 +0000" stop="20260531154500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>Ava finds inspiration at a 50th anniversary event for Who's Making Dinner? While Deborah is reminded of painful memories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531154500 +0000" stop="20260531162500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>Deborah fulfils a lifelong promise to DJ, while Ava attempts to secure the rights for her 'Who's Making Dinner?' reboot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531162500 +0000" stop="20260531170500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>As The Diva goes over budget, Deborah seeks an investor while Jimmy and Kayla try to secure a comic in residence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531170500 +0000" stop="20260531174500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>Determined to wear an esteemed suit for her MSG show, Deborah finds herself on an unexpected couple's weekend in Montecito.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531174500 +0000" stop="20260531182500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>Deborah gets creative when she's asked to promote her on-sale ticket date. Meanwhile, Kayla and Jimmy are at odds after being served with a lawsuit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531182500 +0000" stop="20260531190500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>Determined to wear an esteemed suit for her MSG show, Deborah finds herself on an unexpected couple's weekend in Montecito.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531190500 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hacks</title>
    <desc>As Ava moves on, Deborah opens The Diva and faces her final act. With new roles and big choices, her legacy takes shape in the final chapter. Contains upsetting themes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Prisoner</title>
    <desc>Separated and under pressure, Amber turns to Tibor for help as a wider threat begins to emerge.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531223500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Euphoria</title>
    <desc>If you can heal your past, you can transform your mistakes into blessings. Contains strong language, nudity, violence and sexual images.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9583" start="20260531223500 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Atomic</title>
    <desc>In Casablanca, Max and JJ try to win back the uranium. But as the cartel closes in, the pair face a choice. (S1, epof.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Song by Song</title>
    <desc>One of the biggest hits of Cash's career stayed at No. 1 for seven weeks; written by his future wife June Carter and first recorded by her sister Anita.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530113000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Song by Song</title>
    <desc>Written by Broadway Legend Jerry Lieber, "Jackson" tells the story of a married couple trying to re-ignite their passion; Johnny and June were married one year after recording the song.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murdoch Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Murdoch's investigation of a mysterious death may be linked to a new automat diner Higgins and Roberts have invested in.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murdoch Mysteries</title>
    <desc>After a would-be Catholic assassin is killed, Murdoch contends with the powerful Protestant leader who was the target.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murdoch Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Murdoch and Brackenreid are stunned when an actor in a performance of "Hamlet" dies on stage before their eyes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murdoch Mysteries</title>
    <desc>Murdoch's investigation of a plane crash that killed the pilot reveals a nefarious plot linked to James Pendrick.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murdoch Mysteries</title>
    <desc>After a prison break and a bank heist, Murdoch and Crabtree contend with reports of a mechanical man with a cannon arm.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murdoch Mysteries</title>
    <desc>When a lawyer's murder is staged like a dog attack, Murdoch suspects the culprits are after a dog bequeathed a fortune.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Leverage</title>
    <desc>The team infiltrates the high school reunion of a software magnate who is involved with the Axis of Evil.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Leverage</title>
    <desc>When Parker is trapped in an unknown location while working a theft for her mentor, the team must race the clock to find and free her.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Leverage</title>
    <desc>In order to rob a Boston vault, the team must time their heist to a nearby symphony concert.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Leverage</title>
    <desc>Nate and the team try to take down a corrupt CEO before he can release a drug that will kill thousands.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Leverage</title>
    <desc>In order to take down a corrupt record executive, the team must infiltrate the world of country and western music.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Leverage</title>
    <desc>After targeting a greedy debt collector, the crew discovers that their target is also a domestic terrorist who is funding an armed militia.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531010000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Leverage</title>
    <desc>The team enters the world of master car thieves in order to take down a crooked car dealer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Leverage</title>
    <desc>When small businessmen are blackmailed into committing crimes, the team's investigation reveals an unlikely foe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>Barnaby and Winter investigate a new brewery located in a supposedly cursed Abbey when a body appears inside one of the vats.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>An old friend must help Barnaby and Winter solve the death of a butterfly collector before more bodies follow in his wake.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Risk-Free Hearing Aid!</title>
    <desc>Call today to try the high quality, low-price Audien hearing aid, risk-free! No doctor or fittings necessary.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531073000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tired of Pain? Go Drug-Free</title>
    <desc>See how a drug-free patch is helping people find relief-without medication.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NEW! Shark PowerDetect with DuoClean Detect Technology</title>
    <desc>Meet the new Shark PowerDetect Upright Vacuum with features like DuoClean Detect Technology, self-cleaning brush roll and odor neutralizing, and you will be cleaning faster, smarter and better!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531083000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bathroom Makeover</title>
    <desc>Transform your bath affordably in just one day!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531093000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NECTAR TRI-PILLOW -Cooler, Comfy, Better Sleep! Buy One Get One FREE!</title>
    <desc>Discover the Nectar Tri-Comfort Cooling Pillow for the ultimate sleep experience! Adjustable to three firmness levels to provide customized support and cooling all night long. Order NOW to get a second pillow FREE, plus a 30-night home trial!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Song by Song</title>
    <desc>Johnny Cash wasn't sure about this quirky tune so he tested it on a "captive" audience during his concert at San Quentin prison.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531103000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Song by Song</title>
    <desc>The original hangover anthem was written and recorded by Kris Kristofferson in 1969; Kris reveals why Cash wanted to cover this song that was already a hit and how Johnny came to perform it during an episode of "Columbo.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Song by Song</title>
    <desc>One of Cash's final and most unlikely hits, this painful ballad was written and first performed by superstar Trent Reznor; the "Nine-Inch Nails" frontman explains why he was reluctant to allow Johnny to record the song.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531113000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Song by Song</title>
    <desc>Dolly has described this autobiographical song as her favorite among all those she's written.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Natural Blood Pressure Management</title>
    <desc>Cardiologist Dr. Ernst von Schwarz, M.D. shows how to manage your blood pressure naturally and help protect your heart for life with My Best Heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Death in Paradise</title>
    <desc>Jack and the team investigate the death of a zoo owner, murdered by a tranquilizer dart.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531143000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Death in Paradise</title>
    <desc>Jack and the team are puzzled when the presenter of a holiday television program is found drowned, and the spotlight falls on the crew.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Death in Paradise</title>
    <desc>In order to find the truth beneath the lies, Jack and the team must navigate the tempestuous waters of a family divided after a wealthy coffee magnate is shot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531173000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Death in Paradise</title>
    <desc>A shadow is cast over a small fishing community when their festival queen is murdered in baffling circumstances.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Death in Paradise</title>
    <desc>Jack and his team struggle with one of the toughest challenges they have faced in their lives when tragedy strikes close to home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531203000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Death in Paradise</title>
    <desc>Saint Marie mourns when radio legend Dezzie Dixon is murdered live on air, and Jack must unravel a complex mystery in order to find the culprit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260531233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Death in Paradise</title>
    <desc>A horse-trekking expedition comes to an abrupt end when Jack finds the dead body of a rider in the police station.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465009" start="20260531233000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Death in Paradise</title>
    <desc>New Year's Eve celebrations are cut short when a masked man stabs a woman in her own home; Jack and the team must uncover the identity of the mystery murderer before he strikes again.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Property Brothers: Buying &amp; Selling</title>
    <desc>Dana and Andy ripped apart their home for an all-out overhaul, but then Andy got a new job, the huge project stalled, and now they're stuck; Jonathan steps in to finish the job, but soon uncovers a host of scary and expensive fixes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Debbie, Kevin, and their three children are a newly-blended family; to bring this new family together, Brian and Sarah build an irresistible treehouse village in their backyard.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530123000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Marc &amp; Mandy Show</title>
    <desc>Topics include home décor, parenting, food, fashion, fitness and wellness.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Property Brothers: Buying &amp; Selling</title>
    <desc>Two suburbanites are ready to move back downtown with their daughters; Jonathan helps transform the family's lackluster home into a showpiece, but he must rework the design when the budget takes a major hit; Drew leads the hunt for a dreamy downsize.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Brian and Sarah build a sports bar in a couple's backyard to give them a place of their own.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530143000 +0000" stop="20260530163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Evan Almighty</title>
    <desc>Newscaster Evan Baxter (Steve Carell) leaves Buffalo behind when he wins a seat in Congress. Moving his wife (Lauren Graham) and family to northern Virginia, he seems to have it made, then God (Morgan Freeman) throws a crisis of biblical proportions at his feet: The Lord wants him to build an ark and line up all the animals two-by-two in preparation for a flood.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530163000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bruce Almighty</title>
    <desc>Bruce Nolan's career in TV has been stalled for a while, and when he's passed over for a coveted anchorman position, he loses it, complaining that God is treating him poorly. Soon after, God actually contacts Bruce and offers him all of his powers if he thinks he can do a better job. Bruce accepts and goes on a spree, using his new-found abilities for selfish, personal use until he realizes that t</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Wild West</title>
    <desc>When President Ulysses S. Grant (Kevin Kline) learns that diabolical inventor Dr. Arliss Loveless (Kenneth Branagh) is planning to assassinate him, he orders Civil War hero James West (Will Smith) and U.S. Marshal Artemus Gordon (also Kline) to arrest him. West's trigger-happy personality doesn't always mesh well with that of the thoughtful Gordon, but they manage to work together. And with the he</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530213000 +0000" stop="20260530233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Evan Almighty</title>
    <desc>Newscaster Evan Baxter (Steve Carell) leaves Buffalo behind when he wins a seat in Congress. Moving his wife (Lauren Graham) and family to northern Virginia, he seems to have it made, then God (Morgan Freeman) throws a crisis of biblical proportions at his feet: The Lord wants him to build an ark and line up all the animals two-by-two in preparation for a flood.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260530233000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bruce Almighty</title>
    <desc>Bruce Nolan's career in TV has been stalled for a while, and when he's passed over for a coveted anchorman position, he loses it, complaining that God is treating him poorly. Soon after, God actually contacts Bruce and offers him all of his powers if he thinks he can do a better job. Bruce accepts and goes on a spree, using his new-found abilities for selfish, personal use until he realizes that t</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baywatch</title>
    <desc>When a dangerous crime wave hits the beach, the legendary Mitch Buchannon leads his elite squad of lifeguards on a mission to prove that you don't have to wear a badge to save the bay. Joined by a trio of hotshot recruits, including former Olympian Matt Brody, they ditch the surf and go deep under cover to take down a ruthless businesswoman whose devious plans threaten the future of the bay.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531043000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Wild West</title>
    <desc>When President Ulysses S. Grant (Kevin Kline) learns that diabolical inventor Dr. Arliss Loveless (Kenneth Branagh) is planning to assassinate him, he orders Civil War hero James West (Will Smith) and U.S. Marshal Artemus Gordon (also Kline) to arrest him. West's trigger-happy personality doesn't always mesh well with that of the thoughtful Gordon, but they manage to work together. And with the he</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baywatch</title>
    <desc>When a dangerous crime wave hits the beach, the legendary Mitch Buchannon leads his elite squad of lifeguards on a mission to prove that you don't have to wear a badge to save the bay. Joined by a trio of hotshot recruits, including former Olympian Matt Brody, they ditch the surf and go deep under cover to take down a ruthless businesswoman whose devious plans threaten the future of the bay.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531093000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Backyard Builds</title>
    <desc>Brian and Sarah build a sports bar in a couple's backyard to give them a place of their own.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love It or List It</title>
    <desc>Phil and Kelly's fourth child is on the way, and they are outgrowing their two-story home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love It or List It</title>
    <desc>Joe is looking for a new house after living in a condo.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love It or List It</title>
    <desc>A space that has both character and function.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love It or List It</title>
    <desc>A home to accommodate three generations.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Italian Job</title>
    <desc>After a heist in Venice, Steve turns on his partners in crime, killing safecracker John Bridger and keeping all the gold for himself; the rest of the team, including leader Charlie Croker, driver Handsome Rob, explosives man Left Ear and tech geek Lyle, vows revenge; they enlist the help of Bridger's daughter, Stella and plot to recover the gold from Steve's Los Angeles mansion.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lara Croft: Tomb Raider</title>
    <desc>This live action feature is inspired by the most successful interactive video-game character in history -- Lara Croft. Beautiful and brainy, Lara is the heroine of Eidos Interactive's phenomenally successful "Tomb Raider" game series. It is one woman's fearless quest crisscrossing the globe, in an amazing attempt to save the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lara Croft Tomb Raider: The Cradle of Life</title>
    <desc>Fearless explorer Lara Croft (Angelina Jolie) tries to locate Pandora's box before criminals Jonathan Reiss (Ciarán Hinds) and Chen Lo (Simon Yam) use it for evil. According to myth, the box holds deadly organisms that could kill millions of people. With her old partner, Terry (Gerard Butler), Croft goes on a hunt that takes her from Europe to Asia to Africa, where pal Kosa (Djimon Hounsou) helps </desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260531213000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Italian Job</title>
    <desc>After a heist in Venice, Steve turns on his partners in crime, killing safecracker John Bridger and keeping all the gold for himself; the rest of the team, including leader Charlie Croker, driver Handsome Rob, explosives man Left Ear and tech geek Lyle, vows revenge; they enlist the help of Bridger's daughter, Stella and plot to recover the gold from Steve's Los Angeles mansion.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470459" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lara Croft: Tomb Raider</title>
    <desc>This live action feature is inspired by the most successful interactive video-game character in history -- Lara Croft. Beautiful and brainy, Lara is the heroine of Eidos Interactive's phenomenally successful "Tomb Raider" game series. It is one woman's fearless quest crisscrossing the globe, in an amazing attempt to save the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Kratts</title>
    <desc>While looking at shapes in nature, the Wild Kratts discover a sphere shaped "rock" that turns out to be a 3-banded armadillo; Zach challenges everyone to a bowling match.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530113000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Weather Hunters</title>
    <desc>Benny's toy penguin is swept away by melting snow, transforming a day of sledding into an urgent rescue mission.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lyla in the Loop</title>
    <desc>Luke plays doctor with Stu as a nurse and Lyla pretends to be different patients; Lyla, Everett, Luke and Stu build an elaborate track to get a tennis ball down to the lobby.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530123000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Carl the Collector</title>
    <desc>When Nico teases Carl about bikes being for babies, he sets out to prove Nico wrong; Carl and his Fuzzytown friends can't wait to build a tree fort, but Carl has a hard time working as a team.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Air Supply: 50th Anniversary Concert</title>
    <desc>Graham Russell and Russell Hitchcock celebrate Air Supply's 50th anniversary with a concert packed with romantic hits including "Lost in Love," "All Out of Love" and "Every Woman in the World.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530143000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Deconstructing the Beatles</title>
    <desc>A look at milestone albums of The Beatles and the stories that accompanied them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Visions of Italy: Southern Style</title>
    <desc>An aerial view of the landscape of southern Italy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530173000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Spatchcock Funk</title>
    <desc>The team pays respect to the South by bringing the people and fixin's for a low country boil.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lucky Chow</title>
    <desc>The deep, lived fusion between Chinese and Italian cultures, from Milan's Chinatown to Prato's working class dumpling shops and Florence's street food.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530183000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christopher Kimball's Milk Street Television</title>
    <desc>German apple cake; Belgian spice cookies; Danish dream cake with a buttery coconut-brown sugar topping that caramelizes under the broiler.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christina Cooks: Back to the Cutting Board</title>
    <desc>How Italian cooking traditions are passed down to newer generations.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530193000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">America's Test Kitchen</title>
    <desc>Macarons with raspberry buttercream; gougeres.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Travels With Darley</title>
    <desc>Revolutionary War history in North Carolina; Greensboro's transformed Revolution Mill and its denim legacy; Dolley Madison; the Battle of Alamance; Guilford Courthouse National Military Park; Bentonville Battlefield.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530203000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Family to the Rescue</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">This Old House</title>
    <desc>Visiting a factory that makes engineered plank flooring; installing some board and batten wall paneling in the new mudroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530213000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ask This Old House</title>
    <desc>The perfect tech setup for an outdoor movie night; breaking down the basics of a homeowner's insurance policy; rebuilding a picnic table.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">GZERO World With Ian Bremmer</title>
    <desc>Harvard economist Gita Gopinath examines what comes next after the Iran war upends an already shaky global economy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530223000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Compass Points From PBS News</title>
    <desc>Experts analyze prominent international affairs topics and America's role in a shifting world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260530233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Consuelo Mack WealthTrack</title>
    <desc>Investment tips in stocks, bonds, real estate and collectibles.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260530233000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Firing Line With Margaret Hoover</title>
    <desc>Margaret Hoover leads interviews and debates.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531013500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>A couple is murdered near a house that is said to be haunted.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531013500 +0000" stop="20260531023200 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Seaside Hotel</title>
    <desc>The hotel is taken over by strangers who want to change it completely; is it the end of an era?; or is it time to make one last attempt to save the Seaside Hotel?</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531023200 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cinema Nomad</title>
    <desc>Photographer-turned-director Alejandro; film premieres, ceremonial dances and the cultural landscape of Bolivia's Indigenous population.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ireland in Music</title>
    <desc>Robert &amp; Gemma Bradley rock out at Giant's Causeway.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531033000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tradfest: The Fingal Sessions</title>
    <desc>Aoife O'Donovan, Ultan O'Brien and Ultan Conlon share songs and stories.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago &amp; Friends: Live at 55</title>
    <desc>Chicago performs their greatest hits with special guests Steve Vai, Chris Daughtry, Robert Randolph, Robin Thicke, VoicePlay, Judith Hill and Christone "Kingfish" Ingram.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531053000 +0000" stop="20260531063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Austin City Limits</title>
    <desc>Grammy Award-winning singer-songwriter Brittany Howard showcases new numbers from "What Now" as well as other hits.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531063000 +0000" stop="20260531073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live From the Artists Den: Reprise</title>
    <desc>The Swell Season -- led by Glen Hansard and backed by Markéta Irglová on piano and two of Hansard's bandmates from The Frames on bass and violin -- perform their melodic, original songs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531073000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Music With Rhiannon Giddens</title>
    <desc>Lyrical guitarist Joy Clark, a rising singer-songwriter on the Americana music scene.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago &amp; Friends: Live at 55</title>
    <desc>Chicago performs their greatest hits with special guests Steve Vai, Chris Daughtry, Robert Randolph, Robin Thicke, VoicePlay, Judith Hill and Christone "Kingfish" Ingram.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531093000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">MotorWeek</title>
    <desc>Subaru Outback Wilderness; Audi RS3.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Antiques Roadshow</title>
    <desc>A Hawaiian kou bowl; a Gandhi presentation spinning wheel; an 1888 Joseph Nawahi painting.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Asian Americans</title>
    <desc>Asian Americans fight for equality in the fields, on campuses and in the culture.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">27Speaks Headlines</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531123000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Upstate Attractions</title>
    <desc>The Wild Center, a combined zoo-aquarium, museum and education center in the Adirondack Mountains.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">WLIW Arts Beat</title>
    <desc>In this edition of Arts Beat, a musician who plays an instrument with a one-of-a-kind sound; an artist pursues her love of tintype photography; a ceramic artist who connects with her Nigerian ancestors.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531133000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Washington Week With The Atlantic</title>
    <desc>A panel of journalists provides reporting and analysis of the major stories emanating from the United States capital.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New York Now</title>
    <desc>Journalists discuss New York state politics and government.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531143000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Your Fantastic Mind</title>
    <desc>The next phase of the ENRICH stroke trial; a personal story of psychedelic therapy for depression; Atlanta's pre-arrest diversion facility.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Weekends With Yankee</title>
    <desc>Filmmaker and environmentalist Tomas Koeck discusses New Hampshire's iconic loons; a late-summer garden party at Groundswell with founder David Fierabend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531153000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wild Foods</title>
    <desc>Exploring the Haudenosaunee Nation's history in New York's Adirondacks; an adventure to the headwaters of the Hudson River.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cook's Country</title>
    <desc>Alcapurrias; the story of Coco López and pina coladas; coquito cocktails.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lidia's Kitchen</title>
    <desc>Cream of fava soup with rice; homemade chocolate cherry panettone; eggplant rollatini.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Life of Loi: Mediterranean Secrets</title>
    <desc>Diving into the vibrant flavor of the Emirates; chef Abu Halab prepares Kamoon Tower and a quick baba ghanoush; traditional lamb stew called thareed; skewered grilled chicken.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531173000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Indian as Apple Pie</title>
    <desc>Masala dabba; spice blends used most frequently; how to make eggplant and potatoes, raita yogurt and a kachumber salad; organizing and storing spices.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Visions of Italy: Southern Style</title>
    <desc>An aerial view of the landscape of southern Italy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531193000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago &amp; Friends: Live at 55</title>
    <desc>Chicago performs their greatest hits with special guests Steve Vai, Chris Daughtry, Robert Randolph, Robin Thicke, VoicePlay, Judith Hill and Christone "Kingfish" Ingram.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Great Performances</title>
    <desc>Exploring the role of Jewish composers and lyricists in the creation of the modern American musical; narrator Joel Grey.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470003" start="20260531230000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Billy Joel: The 100th -- Live at Madison Square Garden</title>
    <desc>Billy Joel's record-breaking 100th consecutive performance at Madison Square Garden; special appearances by Sting and Jerry Seinfeld.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Four Weddings</title>
    <desc>Tulisa and her garden nuptials; Crystal's rockabilly beach party; Erica splurges on wine; Alli's chicken fingers and fries.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Face Doctors</title>
    <desc>Terry consults experts about the flesh-eating eye infection stemming from a simple toothache; Anita makes the heartbreaking decision to have one of her eyes removed.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Face Doctors</title>
    <desc>Kamil seeks prosthetist Nigel's help after losing half of his nose; Surgeon Vijay pieces together Dean's shattered jaw and cheekbone.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Day in My Body</title>
    <desc>There are only two foods that won't send Caroline into anaphylaxis; touching almost anything causes Ariana's butterfly skin to blister and tear; Aleazia's cystic hygroma caused his jaw and tongue to swell, permanently freezing his mouth open.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Day in My Body</title>
    <desc>Zahra is housebound by a rare condition, but new prosthetics may be her ticket to freedom; Mahogany's leg weighs nearly 100 pounds due to lymphedema. Joseph was born without a jaw but won't let it stop him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Day in My Body</title>
    <desc>Twenty-seven-year-old Taffy presents physically as a 4-year-old; Adrienne's rare disorder has left both her eyes completely covered by skin; Baby Brody undergoes a procedure to fix a severe cleft palate.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Jasmine's plans to host the perfect Thanksgiving gets off to a rocky start; Loren makes choices for the kids that Alex doesn't agree with; Ari dives back into the dating scene, after a long hiatus.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Matt's mom threatens Jasmine's peace during Thanksgiving dinner; Armando hits a speed bump during his visa process; Josh attempts to rekindle things with an old flame.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Kalani grows suspicious when her boyfriend repeatedly goes missing in the middle of the night; Emily and Kobe reveal some big changes for their family; Cleo undergoes a major transformation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Single Life</title>
    <desc>The singles dive deep into their dating journeys; Sophie gets to the bottom of Pedro's avoidance, Colt and Jamal face off, and Kim feels betrayed when Liz reveals a secret that threatens the future of their friendship.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jay &amp; Pamela</title>
    <desc>Jay and Pamela may have bitten off more than they can chew; they've decided they want to prioritize their health, plan a wedding and move out of their parent's basement apartment in the next three months.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jay &amp; Pamela</title>
    <desc>Pamela has been living in the same house with Jay's parents for the last years; she and his dad have never bonded; when he invites Pamela to a cooking lesson, it's time to clear the air; Jay and Pamela's first meeting with a realtor is thwarted.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>With less than seven months to their big day, Baylen and Colin are still struggling to make major wedding decisions; Baylen and maid of honor Sammi are at odds over the planning of Baylen and Colin's joint bachelor and bachelorette weekend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531010000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>When Sammi fails to show up to their joint Bach weekend, Baylen has an honest conversation with Sammi about her role; after Julie raises concerns about how remote the venue is, Baylen proposes a plan that might put the entire wedding day in jeopardy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Neighborhood Watch</title>
    <desc>If you can't laugh at the ones you love, who can you laugh at? They say a good sense of humor and not taking yourself too seriously are cornerstones of any loving relationship; these families know how to have a good time at each other's expense.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531023000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Neighborhood Watch</title>
    <desc>Whether it's husbands and wives, parents and kids, grandparents, or even pets, failing is fun for the whole family; these neighbors know that families who fail together laugh together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Single Life</title>
    <desc>Your 90 Day favorites are back for the final night of the Tell All; Ashley asks if Ed will be invited to Liz's wedding; Kenny and Armando keep the cocktails flowing; Darcey and Stacey spill tea on each other, and Robert and Anny roast everyone nonstop.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>With less than seven months to their big day, Baylen and Colin are still struggling to make major wedding decisions; Baylen and maid of honor Sammi are at odds over the planning of Baylen and Colin's joint bachelor and bachelorette weekend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Baylen Out Loud</title>
    <desc>When Sammi fails to show up to their joint Bach weekend, Baylen has an honest conversation with Sammi about her role; after Julie raises concerns about how remote the venue is, Baylen proposes a plan that might put the entire wedding day in jeopardy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Neighborhood Watch</title>
    <desc>If you can't laugh at the ones you love, who can you laugh at? They say a good sense of humor and not taking yourself too seriously are cornerstones of any loving relationship; these families know how to have a good time at each other's expense.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531063000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Neighborhood Watch</title>
    <desc>Whether it's husbands and wives, parents and kids, grandparents, or even pets, failing is fun for the whole family; these neighbors know that families who fail together laugh together.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day: The Single Life</title>
    <desc>Your 90 Day favorites are back for the final night of the Tell All; Ashley asks if Ed will be invited to Liz's wedding; Kenny and Armando keep the cocktails flowing; Darcey and Stacey spill tea on each other, and Robert and Anny roast everyone nonstop.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé: Before the 90 Days</title>
    <desc>After seven years, Meisha and Nicola finally meet; Christian and Cleo hope opposites attract; Razvan tests Amanda's jealousy; Gino suggests a prenup, and Jasmine explodes; Riley and Violet have their first date; David meets his honey babe, Sheila.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Do You Think You Are?</title>
    <desc>Actress Liv Tyler unravels the mystery of her father Steven Tyler's maternal family line, uncovering ancestors who took part in famous American battles.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Who Do You Think You Are?</title>
    <desc>Jessica Biel hunts for the truth behind family lore about the death of an ancestor, and also makes two shocking discoveries that shake everything she knows about her heritage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Say Yes to the Dress</title>
    <desc>Jamie and fiancée Lisa are shopping together, and to keep the brides from seeing each other's looks, the consultants plan a wild surprise; wedding planner Michelle tries to let go and enjoy being the bride; Shay confronts Randy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Say Yes to the Dress</title>
    <desc>Randy's mom visits for her 93rd birthday, and she's happy to share her fiery opinions with everyone; timid bride Courtney's appointment gets hijacked by her provocative mother; Katie needs a gown suitable for two big secrets.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Say Yes to the Dress</title>
    <desc>Omarosa, of "The Apprentice," is determined to find a colorful, dramatic gown for her big day; jet-setting bride Valerie wants a dress fit for her lavish Ibiza wedding; Randy rescues bride Magaly who needs a dress for her underwater ceremony.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Plathville</title>
    <desc>Moriah gives a glimpse into her life in Montana; Isaac looks for a reconciliation with Kaylynn; Ethan hopes his rather complicated plan to surprise Teegan doesn't backfire; Barry learns what people are saying about him in town.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Plathville</title>
    <desc>Ethan returns to Cairo for Thanksgiving before officially moving to Wisconsin to be closer to his ex-girlfriend, Teegan; Kim makes a surprising admission to the family, Barry hunts for Bigfoot, and Zac inserts himself into Ethan's situationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Plathville</title>
    <desc>After a tense start in Montana, Ethan sets out to repair his relationship with Teegan but is met with the cold shoulder; meanwhile, Lydia and Zac navigate feeling like outsiders as everyone vacations in Montana; Barry gets serious about Bigfoot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Welcome to Plathville</title>
    <desc>Ethan continues to try to win back Teegan's heart, but Moriah, Isaac and Kaylynn worry it's too little too late; Ken confronts Kim about her weight, and a worried Kim drives to Wisconsin to check on Ethan.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Jasmine's plans to host the perfect Thanksgiving gets off to a rocky start; Loren makes choices for the kids that Alex doesn't agree with; Ari dives back into the dating scene, after a long hiatus.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Matt's mom threatens Jasmine's peace during Thanksgiving dinner; Armando hits a speed bump during his visa process; Josh attempts to rekindle things with an old flame.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Diaries</title>
    <desc>Kalani grows suspicious when her boyfriend repeatedly goes missing in the middle of the night; Emily and Kobe reveal some big changes for their family; Cleo undergoes a major transformation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé</title>
    <desc>Debby anxiously awaits news of Mido's arrival; Marissa's ex hopes Edward won't try to take over the role of Dad; Josh confronts Catie about her party girl ways; Rasit's family asks him to send money; Paula manifested her American fiancé, Thomas.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464919" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">90 Day Fiancé</title>
    <desc>Using a unique visa, couples embark on a 90-day journey; their foreign mates will travel to the US and have 90 days to marry or leave the country.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lux Radio Theatre</title>
    <desc>Lux Radio Theater presents "The Petrified Forest"; starring Ronald Colman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classroom Classics</title>
    <desc>"The Good Loser" and "Family Life.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530123000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Retrola: Canada's Time Machine</title>
    <desc>Images of Canadians doing various activities throughout history.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Postcards From Canada</title>
    <desc>Images of the East Coast and Canadian Winters.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530133000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr. Ho Talks</title>
    <desc>Dr. Ho discusses getting relief from pain and tension in the comfort of one's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trending Now</title>
    <desc>Taking a daily dive into the most talked about stories on the minds (and screens) of people everywhere.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530143000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr. Ho Talks</title>
    <desc>Dr. Ho discusses getting relief from pain and tension in the comfort of one's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wanted: Dead or Alive</title>
    <desc>A widowed mother, threatened with the loss of her son through a court order, proposes to Josh.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530153000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trending Now</title>
    <desc>Taking a daily dive into the most talked about stories on the minds (and screens) of people everywhere.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Hustler</title>
    <desc>The story follows Fast Eddie Felsen (Paul Newman) and his adventures in the world of professional pool. Fast Eddie is a young hopeful on his way to challenging Minnesota Fats (Jackie Gleason) for his world title. When he starts getting feelings for a woman he gets into a dilemma.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Guadalcanal Diary</title>
    <desc>Filmed just months after the actual allied invasion of Guadalcanal late in 1942, this patriotic feature follows a ragtag group of Marines sent to fight in the South Pacific. As steely Sgt. Malone (Lloyd Nolan), Brooklyn wise guy Potts (William Bendix) and the teenaged Anderson (Richard Jaeckel) prepare for battle, they are taken aback when they initially meet no resistance. Rattled by stealthy Jap</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Matter of Life and Death</title>
    <desc>British Air Force pilot Peter Carter (David Niven) is on his way home to England from a World War II bombing mission in a badly damaged aircraft. Before he bails out of the plane into the ocean, he contacts June (Kim Hunter), an Allied radio operator with whom he shares what he believes to be his final moments on Earth. But Peter survives, finds June and they fall in love. A problem arises when a </desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">State Fair</title>
    <desc>The small-town Frake family attend the Iowa State Fair, the annual highlight of their summer. Son Wayne (Dick Haymes) plots revenge on a midway barker (Henry Morgan) who had embarrassed him the summer before and falls for the beautiful singer Emily (Vivian Blaine), while his melancholy sister Margie (Jeanne Crain) becomes smitten with slick city-boy reporter Pat (Dana Andrews). Meanwhile, mother M</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531010000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Me Tender</title>
    <desc>Confederate soldiers led by Vance Reno (Richard Egan) rob a Union train of its payroll money. But because the Civil War officially ended the day before, their theft was not a legitimate act of war. Now an outlaw, Vance takes his share and heads home, where he intends to marry his fiancée, Cathy (Debra Paget). But upon arrival he discovers that she has already married his youngest brother, Clint (E</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Titanic</title>
    <desc>Stuck in an unloving marriage, rich socialite Julia Sturges boards the Titanic with her two young children with the intent of divorcing her husband, Richard, when she arrives in the States. At the last minute, Richard discovers her plan and manages to get on board the ship in an attempt to convince her to stay with him. Their marital problems take a backseat, however, when the Titanic collides wit</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Commando Cody: Sky Marshal of the Universe</title>
    <desc>Masked super-scientist Commando Cody investigates the dangerous climate changes ravaging Earth, and discovers the disasters are being caused by space-alien forces led by a mysterious ruler.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True North Classics</title>
    <desc>The best in short film from the 1930s to 1960s.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531063000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Postcards From Canada</title>
    <desc>Images of the East Coast and Canadian Winters.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Retrola: Canada's Time Machine</title>
    <desc>Images of Canadians doing various activities throughout history.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531073000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classroom Classics</title>
    <desc>"Understanding Your Emotions" and "Are You Popular?".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lux Radio Theatre</title>
    <desc>An alcoholic lawyer's free-spirited daughter falls for a notorious gambler he defended for murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lux Radio Theatre</title>
    <desc>A man falsely accused of murder attempts to stop a spy ring which is trying to steal top secret information; starring Robert Montgomery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lux Radio Theatre</title>
    <desc>In 1921, an Irish rebel and a beautiful aristocratic Englishwoman fall in love; starring Madeline Carroll.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lux Radio Theatre</title>
    <desc>The misadventures of two social-climbing women in small town America.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Classroom Classics</title>
    <desc>"The Facts About Nuclear Weapons.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531123000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Retrola: Canada's Time Machine</title>
    <desc>Images of cottage life and people's own backyard.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Postcards From Canada</title>
    <desc>Images of the East Coast and Canadian Winters.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531133000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">True North Classics</title>
    <desc>The best in short film from the 1930s to 1960s.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Commando Cody: Sky Marshal of the Universe</title>
    <desc>Masked super-scientist Commando Cody investigates the dangerous climate changes ravaging Earth, and discovers the disasters are being caused by space-alien forces led by a mysterious ruler.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr. Ho Talks</title>
    <desc>Dr. Ho discusses getting relief from pain and tension in the comfort of one's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531153000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Trending Now</title>
    <desc>Taking a daily dive into the most talked about stories on the minds (and screens) of people everywhere.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dr. Ho Talks</title>
    <desc>Dr. Ho discusses getting relief from pain and tension in the comfort of one's home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kaeshammer's Kitchen</title>
    <desc>Blues-rock dynamo Jesse Roper brings his laid-back vibes, killer guitar skills and cooking chops to the kitchen before performing "Cool Whip" and "Turn it Up".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">State Fair</title>
    <desc>The small-town Frake family attend the Iowa State Fair, the annual highlight of their summer. Son Wayne (Dick Haymes) plots revenge on a midway barker (Henry Morgan) who had embarrassed him the summer before and falls for the beautiful singer Emily (Vivian Blaine), while his melancholy sister Margie (Jeanne Crain) becomes smitten with slick city-boy reporter Pat (Dana Andrews). Meanwhile, mother M</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love Me Tender</title>
    <desc>Confederate soldiers led by Vance Reno (Richard Egan) rob a Union train of its payroll money. But because the Civil War officially ended the day before, their theft was not a legitimate act of war. Now an outlaw, Vance takes his share and heads home, where he intends to marry his fiancée, Cathy (Debra Paget). But upon arrival he discovers that she has already married his youngest brother, Clint (E</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Titanic</title>
    <desc>Stuck in an unloving marriage, rich socialite Julia Sturges boards the Titanic with her two young children with the intent of divorcing her husband, Richard, when she arrives in the States. At the last minute, Richard discovers her plan and manages to get on board the ship in an attempt to convince her to stay with him. Their marital problems take a backseat, however, when the Titanic collides wit</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="470616" start="20260531230000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Outlaw</title>
    <desc>The life of legendary outlaw Billy the Kid, including his partnership with Doc Holliday and his clashes with lawman Pat Garrett. The film was notorious in its day because of producer/director Howard Hughes concentration on newcomer Jane Russell's cleavage, and national release in America was delayed by some years.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Jeff's plan to get chicken fingers from the cafeteria for the group evolves into a mafia movie-style endeavour with Abed calling all the shots.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530113000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Shirley gets Pierce kicked out of the study group, as Jeff and Britta plot revenge on a group of high schoolers who make fun of them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Greendale Community College is transformed into an apocalyptic war zone when the dean promises the winner of a paintball competition priority registration.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530123000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Annie uses inside information about Chang to get him fired so that the study group will be forced to stay together and take Spanish again.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Britta and Professor Slater fight for the affection of Jeff. Meanwhile, Troy is confused when Abed doesn't invite him to move into his dorm room.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530133000 +0000" stop="20260530141000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Trip</title>
    <desc>Rob and Steve begin in Piemonte at the Trattoria Della Posta, before stopping in Genova on their way to the Cenobio dei Dogi in Camogli.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530141000 +0000" stop="20260530145000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Trip</title>
    <desc>After depressing calls from home, Rob and Steve get a ride on a magnificent yacht, where Rob charms attractive crew member Lucy with his impressions.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530145000 +0000" stop="20260530153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Trip</title>
    <desc>Rob wakes up in bed with Lucy and feels rather guilty though he keeps it from Steve. Then, they move on to the seaside resort of Viareggio.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530153000 +0000" stop="20260530161000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Trip</title>
    <desc>Rob Brydon and Steve Coogan's journey continues. They meet Emma and photographer Yolanda before they arrive in Rome and visit the Keats museum.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530161000 +0000" stop="20260530165000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Trip</title>
    <desc>Steve and Rob visit Pompeii and have lunch at Relais Blu on the Sorrento coast, overlooking the isle of Capri.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530165000 +0000" stop="20260530173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Trip</title>
    <desc>Steve and Rob are joined by Steve's son Joe and his assistant Emma. They sail from Naples to Capri where they have lunch at Il Riccio.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530173000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Andy pays a price when he tries to help Pam, while Dwight prepares an ambitious presentation for the opening of the store.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Jim tries to protect Dwight from being fired and Andy discovers Erin's full intentions in Florida.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530183000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Andy heads to Florida to tell Erin that he loves her, while Nellie comes to Scranton with big plans for the office.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Andy tries to figure out how to break up with Jessica, while the Scranton staff attempt to sabotage Nellie's welcome party.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530193000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Andy releases his angry side as he fights to get his job back from Nellie, while Pam finds Kelly a potential new boyfriend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530211500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rob Beckett: Wallop</title>
    <desc>Rob Beckett is back - the Mouth of the South has had a busy few years and now returns to tour to fill audiences in. Live stand-up.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530211500 +0000" stop="20260530223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nikki Glaser: Good Clean...</title>
    <desc>Nikki Glaser dishes the dirt about dating, sex and not-so-private parts in this raucous stand-up special in front of Denver's sold-out Paramount Theater.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530223000 +0000" stop="20260530233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ellie Taylor: Palavering</title>
    <desc>Comedian, presenter and actor Ellie Taylor performs at the Bloomsbury Theatre, covering everything from how to keep the spark alive in marriage to her stint on Strictly.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260530233000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Comeback</title>
    <desc>Valerie is offered a role in a new multi-cam sitcom but is hesitant to accept when she learns it will be written by AI.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531001000 +0000" stop="20260531005000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Comeback</title>
    <desc>Valerie meets her human showrunners and tries to convince a TV vet to direct the pilot.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531005000 +0000" stop="20260531012500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Comeback</title>
    <desc>Valerie discovers being back on a soundstage makes her miss her old sitcom team of one.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531012500 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Comeback</title>
    <desc>When AI churns out an unusable script, Valerie is forced to lean into her executive producer role to do damage control.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sort Of</title>
    <desc>As Sabi braces for their father's return, Deenzie drops world-shaking news. Strong language/mature themes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531023000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sort Of</title>
    <desc>Sabi has an awkward first day on the job with Imran. Bessy struggles to make sense of her life. Strong language/mature themes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sort Of</title>
    <desc>Sabi needs to get paid. Paul is blindsided when Bessy makes a big decision without telling anyone. Strong language/mature themes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531033000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sort Of</title>
    <desc>Sabi and the family do their best to get used to the new rhythm, while Paul pretends to be Bessy in order to text with Penny.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping 2026</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531043000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping 2026</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531053000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping 2026</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531063000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Teleshopping</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531072500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sort Of</title>
    <desc>With the help of Sabi and friends, Aqsa and Izzy sort of take the next step. Paul and Bessy reconnect over a shared experience.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531072500 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sort Of</title>
    <desc>BRLiN prepares for an important installation as Deenzie takes Sabi on a field trip. Meanwhile, Paul joins a support group.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sort Of</title>
    <desc>A medical emergency forces Sabi to go to the ER, while Wolf cracks when pressured to reveal secrets to Raffo.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531083000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Jeff's plan to get chicken fingers from the cafeteria for the group evolves into a mafia movie-style endeavour with Abed calling all the shots.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Shirley gets Pierce kicked out of the study group, as Jeff and Britta plot revenge on a group of high schoolers who make fun of them.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531093000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Grace's delight in having a bright intern soon turns to horror when the young woman re-makes herself in the image of the sassy Karen.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Convinced their relationship is going nowhere, Grace must resist temptation and break up with Ben. Jack works an unwilling Will into his cabaret act too.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531103000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>The normally conservative Grace throws caution to the wind and embarks on an exciting romantic escapade. Will helps out a newly employed Jack.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Jeff and Britta engage in a game of relationship one-upsmanship in response to Britta's embarrassing moment at the end of the previous school year.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531113000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Jeff blows off the study group to hang out with his old co-workers at the law firm, but Annie believes one of them got him fired.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Pierce's religion convinces him that the spirit of his dead mother is captured in a cheap lava lamp and Jeff has a crisis of faith about his body.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531123000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Everyone in the study group except Abed is stuck in a crude 1980s space simulator as it is towed off campus, and Abed leads the team home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Community</title>
    <desc>Shirley asks Abed to make a film about Jesus, but he quickly angers Shirley by turning it into a self-indulgent mess.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531133000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>When Grace gets a shock at a medical check-up, she learns that her emergency contact is not Will but her ex Leo. Jack takes a temp job as a drama teacher.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Jack unexpectedly learns that he is a grandfather, but his grandson is being shipped off to an anti-gay therapy camp. Grace and Karen behave badly.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531143000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>How to Succeed in Business Without Really Crying: Grace gets a job decorating a string of boutique hotels. Will is surprised at his reaction to becoming senior partner.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Karen faces her darkest hour when her maid Rosario suffers a heart attack. Will and Grace's new business relationship begins to show signs of stress.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531153000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Will, Grace, Karen and Jack wish they could have experienced Christmas in old New York, but realise the past was not quite as romantic as they pictured.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Will and Grace try to convince themselves they are okay with dating the same man. Jack and Karen get an annoying commercial jingle stuck in their heads.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Will and Grace's old friend Larry decides he's in love with Will. Jack's first day as a Lyft driver doesn't go as planned.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>At Vince's wedding, Grace tries to stop Will making a scene. Jack fends off the advances of an amorous cop and Karen plays a high-society treasure hunt.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531173000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Jack celebrates his one-month-anniversary with Drew, who is still married to Angela. Meanwhile, Grace gets a spot on QVC selling her bedsheets.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Will &amp; Grace</title>
    <desc>Grace is horrified to realise she's dated three men from the same family. Will and Karen get on each other's nerves, but bond over their own little telenovela.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531183000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Andy tries to confront Robert at a silent charity auction, while Oscar bonds with Angela's husband, Senator Robert Lipton.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Dwight and Jim fight a nearby branch for a big client, Andy makes a plan to get his old job back and Pam learns more about Nellie.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531193000 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Dwight offers free family portraits to the office staff with the hope of getting closer to Angela's baby. Season finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Hill New Bits &amp; Greatest Hits</title>
    <desc>Harry Hill kicks off with new material and classic sketches, offering surreal takes on everyday topics while revisiting some of his most memorable moments.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531213000 +0000" stop="20260531225000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ricky Gervais - Politics</title>
    <desc>Recorded live in London in 2004, Ricky Gervais delivers another smash-hit show covering everything from being mistaken for Johnny Vegas to politics and beyond. Strong language/adult humour.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9187" start="20260531225000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kevin Hart: Reality Check</title>
    <desc>Kevin Hart is as funny as ever in his first stand-up special for three years in front of a sold-out crowd at Resort World in Las Vegas. Contains strong language and adult humour.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">RateEscape: Stop Overpaying For Cellular</title>
    <desc>Cut up to half the cost of your monthly cell phone bill; same towers, same coverage, but a lot less money; it sounds great but is it too good to be true?; join myth-busting legend Kari Byron as she takes on Big Wireless to save you money.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260530113000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rare Silver &amp; Gold Coins</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone</title>
    <desc>Adaptation of the first of J.K. Rowling's popular children's novels about Harry Potter, a boy who learns on his eleventh birthday that he is the orphaned son of two powerful wizards and possesses unique magical powers of his own. He is summoned from his life as an unwanted child to become a student at Hogwarts, an English boarding school for wizards. There, he meets several friends who become his </desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260530153000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets</title>
    <desc>The follow-up to "Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone" finds young wizard Harry Potter and his friends, Ron and Hermione, facing new challenges during their second year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry as they try to discover a dark force that is terrorizing the school.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban</title>
    <desc>Harry Potter's third year at Hogwarts starts off badly when he learns deranged killer Sirius Black has escaped from Azkaban prison and is bent on murdering the teenage wizard. While Hermione's cat torments Ron's sickly rat, causing a rift among the trio, a swarm of nasty Dementors is sent to protect the school from Black. A mysterious new teacher helps Harry learn to defend himself, but what is hi</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire</title>
    <desc>During Harry's fourth year at Hogwarts a competition will be held between three schools of wizardry, and contestants will be magically chosen for the very dangerous event.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531013000 +0000" stop="20260531043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix</title>
    <desc>Now in his fifth year at Hogwarts, Harry learns that many in the wizarding community do not know the truth of his encounter with Lord Voldemort. Cornelius Fudge, Minister of Magic, appoints his toady, Dolores Umbridge, as Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher, for he fears that professor Dumbledore will take his job. But her teaching is deficient and her methods, cruel, so Harry prepares a group o</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531043000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince</title>
    <desc>As Death Eaters wreak havoc in both Muggle and Wizard worlds, Hogwarts is no longer a safe haven for students. Though Harry suspects there are new dangers lurking within the castle walls, Dumbledore is more intent than ever on preparing the young wizard for the final battle with Voldemort. Teenage hormones run rampant through Hogwarts, presenting a different sort of danger. Love may be in the air,</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyond Sherwood Forest</title>
    <desc>The Sheriff of Nottingham uses a shape-shifting monster to destroy Robin Hood (Robin Dunne).</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NECTAR TRI-PILLOW -Cooler, Comfy, Better Sleep! Buy One Get One FREE!</title>
    <desc>Discover the Nectar Tri-Comfort Cooling Pillow for the ultimate sleep experience! Adjustable to three firmness levels to provide customized support and cooling all night long. Order NOW to get a second pillow FREE, plus a 30-night home trial!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531103000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paid Programming</title>
    <desc>Paid programming.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531113000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NEW! Shark PowerDetect with DuoClean Detect Technology</title>
    <desc>Meet the new Shark PowerDetect Upright Vacuum with features like DuoClean Detect Technology, self-cleaning brush roll and odor neutralizing, and you will be cleaning faster, smarter and better!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire</title>
    <desc>During Harry's fourth year at Hogwarts a competition will be held between three schools of wizardry, and contestants will be magically chosen for the very dangerous event.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531153000 +0000" stop="20260531183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix</title>
    <desc>Now in his fifth year at Hogwarts, Harry learns that many in the wizarding community do not know the truth of his encounter with Lord Voldemort. Cornelius Fudge, Minister of Magic, appoints his toady, Dolores Umbridge, as Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher, for he fears that professor Dumbledore will take his job. But her teaching is deficient and her methods, cruel, so Harry prepares a group o</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531183000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince</title>
    <desc>As Death Eaters wreak havoc in both Muggle and Wizard worlds, Hogwarts is no longer a safe haven for students. Though Harry suspects there are new dangers lurking within the castle walls, Dumbledore is more intent than ever on preparing the young wizard for the final battle with Voldemort. Teenage hormones run rampant through Hogwarts, presenting a different sort of danger. Love may be in the air,</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465053" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 1</title>
    <desc>Without the guidance and protection of their professors, Harry (Daniel Radcliffe), Ron (Rupert Grint) and Hermione (Emma Watson) begin a mission to destroy the Horcruxes, the sources of Voldemort's immortality. Though they must rely on one another more than ever, dark forces threaten to tear them apart. Voldemort's Death Eaters have seized control of the Ministry of Magic and Hogwarts, and they ar</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260530100000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Roland-Garros Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Roland Garros Stadium in Paris, France.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Roland-Garros Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Roland Garros Stadium in Paris, France.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live at Roland Garros</title>
    <desc>Jim Courier, Caroline Wozniacki, Lindsay Davenport, Sam Querrey, and others will be live in Paris to break down the top moments and matches of Roland-Garros.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260530213000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom</title>
    <desc>Three years after the destruction of the Jurassic World theme park, Owen Grady and Claire Dearing return to the island of Isla Nublar to save the remaining dinosaurs from a volcano that's about to erupt. They soon encounter terrifying new breeds of gigantic dinos while uncovering a conspiracy that threatens the entire planet.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: All Elite Wrestling: Collision</title>
    <desc>The all new matches, more stories and more action, featuring the world-class All Elite Wrestling roster.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531044500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom</title>
    <desc>Three years after the destruction of the Jurassic World theme park, Owen Grady and Claire Dearing return to the island of Isla Nublar to save the remaining dinosaurs from a volcano that's about to erupt. They soon encounter terrifying new breeds of gigantic dinos while uncovering a conspiracy that threatens the entire planet.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531044500 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Central Intelligence</title>
    <desc>Bullied as a teen for being overweight, Bob Stone shows up to his high school reunion looking fit and muscular. While there, he finds Calvin Joyner, a fast-talking accountant who misses his glory days as a popular athlete. Stone is now a lethal CIA agent who needs Calvin's number skills to help him save the compromised U.S. spy satellite system. Together, the former classmates encounter shootouts,</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>The team is called in to track down a serial killer after the bodies of multiple women with the same physical description are found scattered across the city; Maggie juggles her roles as a guardian to Ella and an FBI agent.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>After a park ranger is shot dead by a masked assailant on Governors Island, the team discovers a string of connected crimes that leads them to their toughest roadblock yet: an online conspiracy theory community.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Roland-Garros Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Roland Garros Stadium in Paris, France.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Roland-Garros Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Roland Garros Stadium in Paris, France.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Roland-Garros Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Roland Garros Stadium in Paris, France.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live at Roland Garros</title>
    <desc>Jim Courier, Caroline Wozniacki, Lindsay Davenport, Sam Querrey, and others will be live in Paris to break down the top moments and matches of Roland-Garros.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531213000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Foul Play With Anthony Davis</title>
    <desc>NHL forward Wyatt Johnston and Howie Mandel set up NHL defenseman Lian Bichsel at a restaurant where a romantic proposal meltdown turns him into the unwitting villain.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260531230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">FBI</title>
    <desc>When an alt-right provocateur is murdered after giving a speech at a university in New York City, Maggie and OA investigate the school's more extreme political groups and rely on OA's sister, a student, for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260531230000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NHL on TNT Face Off</title>
    <desc>Wayne Gretzky, Liam McHugh, Anson Carter, and Paul Bissonnette present pregame coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465114" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NHL Hockey</title>
    <desc>Eastern Conference Final, Game 6. (If necessary).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Following the devastating fire at the Nash home, Bobby's fate remains uncertain; Athena embarks on a mission to uncover the truth; Hen and Karin engage in a heated custody battle; Christopher grapples with forgiving Eddie.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>A trailer with millions of bees crashes on the streets of Los Angeles, unleashing a swarm.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena is tasked with safely delivering a prisoner to testify on a high-profile case; a light plane is hit by a swarm of bees and careens into a passenger plane.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena's only chance of surviving and saving everyone on the flight is to attempt to land the plane before it crashes and call on the 118 for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>When it finally looks like Hen and Karen may get their foster license back, they are hit with another obstacle; the 118 races to the aid of a cheerleader involved in an infield collision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 is once again working on the spookiest night of the year and missing out on all the tricks and treats; Buck's Halloween decorations become a little scarier than he had hoped.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>When a toddler falls down a pipe and becomes trapped, the 118 must rely on more than their skills to rescue him; old wounds are opened when members of the 118 race to the aid of a man dealing with a divorce.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>When Athena is assigned a rookie to mentor, she begins to question her own abilities.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Things get messy for the 118 following a massive pipe explosion; Athena investigates the brutal beating of a man found behind a grocery store.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to a fire at a local animal shelter and races to evacuate all the animals; Maddie takes a 9-1-1 call that sets her on a quest for answers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Following Maddie's mysterious 911 call, Chimney returns home to find his daughter alone and Maddie nowhere to be found.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 responds to a call at a megachurch, where Bobby runs into his estranged mother; Buck is looking to expand his social circle now that Eddie has left.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Maddie's return to work proves to be more triggering than expected, as she may have returned too soon; Eddie struggles to adapt to his new surroundings.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>After the 118 responds to several calls from the same person, Hen steps in to offer them advice; Eddie confronts his parents and takes a big step in his relationship with his son.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531010000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118 is called to a research lab that has been set on fire and becomes a biohazard.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Athena and Buck are in a race against time to rescue the rest of the 118 following the fire in the biolab.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Following the tragic events at the lab, the 118 must come together to lay their fallen hero to rest; despite her own grief, Athena re-investigates the death of a child to help a grieving mother.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>Following an earthquake, the 118 races to the scene of several unusual fires and must figure out their cause before anyone else is hurt.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">9-1-1</title>
    <desc>The 118, still reeling from their recent loss, is dispatched to a mass casualty event after a high-rise apartment building collapses; Athena and Chimney have to work together to save a familiar face.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler investigate a successful woman's suspicious death and find themselves in the world of sadomasochism.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>Benson and Stabler encounter problems when the prime suspect in a sexual assault cannot be identified by the shaken victim.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The shooting death of a school student by a 7-year-old classmate leads to new information on an unsolved slaying.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The question of patients' rights surfaces when a mentally ill man electing not to take his medication is a suspect in the stabbing death of psychiatric doctoral student.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives investigate a series of sexual attacks happening on subways; Benson begins dating a crime reporter.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a baby is kidnapped from a grocery store, detectives Benson and Stabler discover it is part of a black-marketing of infants.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>After a man's mutilation on the subway, detectives discover he has been abducting women for years and forcing them to live in his dungeon.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The death of a wealthy senior citizen leads to an investigation that uncovers a serial killer who targets the elderly.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a Chinese woman's daughter is held for ransom by smugglers, the detectives turn to her sister for help.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>While searching for a child molester who has abducted three young children orphaned by Hurricane Katrina, detectives learn that the suspect also possesses a deadly strain of anthrax.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman believes her young son was molested by her husband; an online pedophile site is investigated.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A nanny's Internet love interest (Steven Bauer) is the obvious suspect when she is found murdered, but detectives look more closely at her employers (Mark Valley, Anastasia Griffith) when skeletons are found in their closet.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When the corpse of a famous astronaut is found floating in the waters of Battery Park, Detectives Benson and Stabler think the murder may be connected to a string of serial rapes; at a dead end, Stabler seeks advice from an old mentor (James Brolin).</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>DNA evidence points to Benson as the prime suspect when the sexually mutilated body of a member of a biker gang is found in the park; Stabler fights to prove his partner's innocence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The detectives are called to investigate when a hotel maid reports being assaulted by a powerful Italian diplomat.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>When a dancer is raped by a man with a unique tattoo, details of the case remind Rollins of a serial rapist she was tracking in Atlanta.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260531230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A woman claims that Brian Cassidy (Dean Winters) raped her while he was working undercover; when Cassidy and his lawyer utilize surprising defense methods, Detective Amaro is affected.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260531230000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>The already frantic search for a missing diabetic boy becomes more urgent when he is spotted with a couple known for child endangerment and pornography.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465006" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit</title>
    <desc>A feud between a famous author (Robert Vaughn) and his sixth wife, Charmaine (Marcia Cross), turns into a criminal case when Charmaine is faced with allegations of abuse; Barba winds up dealing with family drama of his own.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260530100000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: The Rally at Roland-Garros</title>
    <desc>Live look-in coverage from all courts at Roland-Garros, highlighting the most exciting action of the day.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Roland-Garros Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Roland Garros Stadium in Paris, France.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live at Roland Garros</title>
    <desc>Jim Courier, Caroline Wozniacki, Lindsay Davenport, Sam Querrey, and others will be live in Paris to break down the top moments and matches of Roland-Garros.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260530213000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland-Garros Match of the Day</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260530233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">PowerHouse: The Rise of Czech Women in Professional Tennis</title>
    <desc>Documenting the influx of female Czech tennis players on the international stage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260530233000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Savannah Bananas Pre-Game</title>
    <desc>A pregame look at the wild antics and trick plays used by the Savannah Bananas baseball team.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Banana Ball World Tour</title>
    <desc>From Kauffman Stadium in Kansas City, Mo.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Giro d'Italia</title>
    <desc>Coverage of the annual multiple-stage bicycle race held in Italy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland-Garros Match of the Day</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531043000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys provide a false sense of security to some sassy shoppers, and the competition reaches new heights during a rematch of their balloon challenge in the grocery store.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys cannonball into an uncomfortable poolside encounter, and convince strangers to press send on their absurd e-mails; tonight's loser presents a shocking senior citizen initiative to a community planning board.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531053000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys work stadium security and contaminate evidence during a crime scene investigation class; tonight's loser develops multiple personality disorder when opening for Legends in Concert.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys team up for a complex guessing game in the park and polish strangers' footwear to an imperfect shine; tonight's loser takes a pounding on the mound at a Brooklyn Cyclone's game.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531063000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>The guys ham it up behind the counter of a famous NYC deli, and then break the ice with bizarre behavior while selling popsicles; tonight's loser wishes Bingo wasn't his name-o in a humiliating and cringe-worthy punishment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Impractical Jokers</title>
    <desc>Joe, Sal, Q and Murr are trying to land a job at a mobile company; the guys head to the ferry where they piggyback one insane gesture on top of another; tonight's loser bears witness to a matrimony that's anything but holy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531073000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland-Garros Match of the Day</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Roland-Garros Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Roland Garros Stadium in Paris, France.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: 2026 Roland-Garros Tennis</title>
    <desc>From Roland Garros Stadium in Paris, France.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live at Roland Garros</title>
    <desc>Jim Courier, Caroline Wozniacki, Lindsay Davenport, Sam Querrey, and others will be live in Paris to break down the top moments and matches of Roland-Garros.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531213000 +0000" stop="20260531230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Roland-Garros Match of the Day</title>
    <desc />
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260531230000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NHL on TNT Face Off</title>
    <desc>Wayne Gretzky, Liam McHugh, Anson Carter, and Paul Bissonnette present pregame coverage.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464987" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: NHL Hockey</title>
    <desc>Eastern Conference Final, Game 6. (If necessary).</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Tye Tribbett, and Amir and Amari O'Neil battle it out in games: Turn Up for What?, Bless 'Em, Sunday Service, and the Wildstyle battle; Tye Tribbett performs New.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530113000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Melii, Rickey Smiley, and Javon WannaWalton and Jaden Walton battle it out in games: Turn Up for What, Greenery Screenery, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Melii performs Cartier.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Vedo, and Kai Cenat battle it out in games: Alphabet Train, Sex, Flix, and Chill, R&amp;Beef, and the Wildstyle battle; Vedo performs "Soon as I Get Home.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530123000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Bryce Vine, Tamar Braxton and Keith L. Williams battle it out in games; Bryce Vine performs "Gold Rush.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Pheelz, Bianca Belair &amp; The Street Profits battle it out in the games Alphabet Train, Greenery Screenery, Eat That A** Up, and the Wildstyle battle; Pheelz performs "Finesse.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530133000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Sidney Starr battle it out in games; Bobb'e J Thompson performs "Pressure.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>GloRilla brings the energy and bars as the New School captain in games of It's My Birthday, Talking Spit, Twerk Werk and Wildstyle before performing her song "F.N.F. (Let's Go).".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530143000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Ms. Pat and Armani White battle it out in games Turn Up for What, Thanks for Nothing, Kick 'em Out the Classroom and The Wildstyle Battle; Armani White performs "Billie Eilish.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Robert Williams III, and Sean Kingston battle it out in games: What You Call That?, Plead the Fifth, Remix, and the Wildstyle battle; Sean Kingston performs "Ocean Drive.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530153000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, DJ Quik and Jahi Winston battle it out in games Pick Up and Kill It, Hip Hop Auction, Hip Hop History, and the Wildstyle battle; DJ Quik performs "Tonite.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael and Jay get a lucrative offer from a large company; Kady and Claire bicker over who gets to spend more time in the bathroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530163000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Mike worries when Jay wants to put her college degree to good use and enter the workforce.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Junior attempts to fool his parents into believing he got an A for his algebra assignment, but the scheme backfires when Janet and Michael treat him like a prodigy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530173000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Claire is upset when Michael continues to pal around with her former boyfriend (Andrew McFarlane); Junior spends too much time in the bathroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael and Janet's romantic overtures are seen on the Internet after Jr. gets new computer equipment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530183000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>The war between the Tylers and Kyles continues in the restaurant, with everyone nearly going at it with each other.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Janet and Michael are astounded when their often dim-witted son shines on an IQ test, ranking him as a genius.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530193000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>After the children tease him about getting old, Michael pretends to injure his back playing Twister so they will have to cater to his every whim.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>An encounter with Michael's ex-girlfriend prompts Janet to get a makeover; on a dare, Junior tries to steal a bra from the girls' locker room.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530203000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>After getting his driver's license, Jr. buys a clunker instead of the practical car Michael picked out for him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Janet thinks Michael plans to golf on their anniversary, but he arranges to have Brian McKnight sing for them at a surprise ceremony to renew their vows.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530213000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>In order to save money, Michael books a 43-hour flight to Hawaii with several layovers; Michael chastises Janet for packing too many clothes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paul Blart: Mall Cop</title>
    <desc>A single suburban father works at a mall as a security guard to make ends meet. He takes his job very seriously, even though most of his colleagues and customers don't. As the holidays approach, Paul gets his moment to shine when Santa's little helpers shut down the mall down and take hostages, including his daughter and girlfriend. He realizes no one knows the place better than he does and he mou</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Paul Blart: Mall Cop 2</title>
    <desc>Six years after he saved the day at his beloved New Jersey shopping mall, security guard Paul Blart (Kevin James) is taking a well-deserved vacation. In recognition for his hard work, he's won an all-expenses-paid trip to a security convention in Las Vegas, and decides to take his teenage daughter, Maya (Raini Rodriguez), with him. True to form, however, Paul just can't relax and take it easy, so </desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531023000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Love You, Beth Cooper</title>
    <desc>Nerdy teenager Denis Cooverman (Paul Rust) harbors a secret crush on Beth Cooper (Hayden Panettiere), the hottest girl in high school. During his graduation speech, Denis lets the cat out of the bag and declares his love for Beth, who, instead of dissing Denis, shows up at his house later that day and promises to show him the time of his life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Chet Hanks, and Young Dro battle it out in the games Flow Job, Let Me Holla, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Young Dro performs "Yessir.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531053000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, EarthGang, and Arnez J. battle it out in games: Alphabet Train, Hood Jeopardy, Kick 'Em out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; EarthGang performs "Billi.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Pi'erre Bourne battle it out; Pi'erre Bourne performs "Good Movie.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531063000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and TraeTwoThree battle it out in games; TraeTwoThree performs "Watch It Grow.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Katt Williams, Mark Curry and Michael Blackson battle it out in games: Got Damned, On the Gang, Plead the Fifth, Wildstyle Battle; Justina Valentine performs "Mouth Go Crazy.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Kevin Hart, and Berner battle it out in games: Got Damned, Got Props, On the Gang, Wildstyle battle; Berner performs "20 Joints.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531083000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Chance the Rapper, and Taylor Bennett battle it out in games: Got Props, Let Me Holla, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, Wildstyle Battle; Taylor Bennett performs "Kick Back.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Xzibit, Too $hort, and Michael Blackson battle it out in games, including Pick Up and Kill It, What You Call That, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Xzibit performs "Get Ya Walk On.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531093000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Kirk Franklin battle it out in games Alphabet Train, Bless 'Em, Sunday Service, and the Wildstyle battle; Kirk Franklin performs "Bless Me.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Jason Lee battle it out in games; DC Young Fly performs "Two Shots.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531103000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Jay Pharoah and Next battle it out in games: What You Call That, Outgoing Message, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Next performs "Too Close.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and King Combs battle it out in games: Alphabet Train, Let Me Holla, Kick 'Em Out The Classroom, and the Wildstyle Battle; King Combs performs "Can't Stop.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531113000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Lil Meech and Travis Porter battle it out in games, including Got Props, What You Call That, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Travis Porter performs "Ayy Ladies.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, J. Valentine and Tank battle it out in games Let Me Holla, Sex, Flix and Chill, R&amp;Beef, and the Wildstyle battle; J. Valentine performs "BBL.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531123000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Joe Albanese, Jilly Anais, and Michael Blackson battle it out in games: "Got Props", "Let Me Holla", "Kick 'Em Out the Classroom", and the "Wildstyle" battle; Jilly Anais performs "Throwback.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Sammie, and Bobby V. of RSVP battle it out in games: "Let Me Holla", "Sex", "Flix and Chill", "R&amp;Beef", and the "Wildstyle" battle; Bobby V. performs "Slow Down.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531133000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, and KaMillion battle it out in games: Flow Job, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, Twerk Werk, and the Wildstyle; KaMillion performs "Rich Bitch Walk.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Ari Fletcher and Rodney Perry battle it out in games Turn Up for What, Talking Spit, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Too $hort performs "Blow the Whistle.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531143000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon and Joey Bada$$ battle it out in games: Pick Up and Kill It, What You Call That, Kick 'Em Out the Classroom, and the Wildstyle battle; Joey Bada$$ performs "Zipcodes.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, DeRay Davis and Jayda Cheaves battle it out in games Alphabet Train, Hood Jeopardy, Talkin' Spit, and the Wildstyle battle; DeRay Davis performs "Right Side of Money.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531153000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nick Cannon Presents: Wild 'n Out</title>
    <desc>Nick Cannon, Bruce Bruce and K Camp battle it out in Little Squad vs. Big Squad, Alphabet Train, Hood Jeopardy, Eat That A... Up, and the Wildstyle battle; K Camp performs "Holy Spirit.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>In Hawaii, Michael and Janet are pursued by two attractive strangers (Nicole Scherzinger, Tyson C. Beckford); Claire goes on a shopping spree.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Janet learns that Claire is thinking about having sex with her boyfriend; Jr. is an irresponsible driver.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael's sister (Vivica A. Fox) visits and sparks a rivalry with Jay.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531173000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael takes too many hair-growth pills and suffers unusual side effects.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>As the boss' son, Jr. convinces other employees at Kyle Trucking to do his work for him; Claire arranges a secret date with a guy she met on the Internet.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531183000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Vanessa's parents try to bully Michael and Jay into buying things that will benefit them, not the baby.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael and Jay get a lucrative offer from a large company; Kady and Claire bicker over who gets to spend more time in the bathroom.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531193000 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Michael and Janet's romantic overtures are seen on the Internet after Jr. gets new computer equipment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>The war between the Tylers and Kyles continues in the restaurant, with everyone nearly going at it with each other.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531203000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>Janet thinks Michael plans to golf on their anniversary, but he arranges to have Brian McKnight sing for them at a surprise ceremony to renew their vows.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">My Wife and Kids</title>
    <desc>In order to save money, Michael books a 43-hour flight to Hawaii with several layovers; Michael chastises Janet for packing too many clothes.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260531213000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">I Love You, Beth Cooper</title>
    <desc>Nerdy teenager Denis Cooverman (Paul Rust) harbors a secret crush on Beth Cooper (Hayden Panettiere), the hottest girl in high school. During his graduation speech, Denis lets the cat out of the bag and declares his love for Beth, who, instead of dissing Denis, shows up at his house later that day and promises to show him the time of his life.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465206" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Titanic</title>
    <desc>Two young lovers from different backgrounds meet and fall in love on the ill-fated maiden voyage of the unsinkable R.M.S. Titanic.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>3 Seventeen Year Olds: Hondo, his father and his teen charge confront LA's history of racial tension between the Black community and the police. Season premiere. (S4, ep 1)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Stakeout: The SWAT team works with the CIA to confirm whether an international crime lord has resurfaced in LA after being off grid for years. (S4, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>Hookman: The team track a sniper targeting the police in a must-see remake of a standout episode from the original series. Peter Weller (Robocop) guest stars and directs. (S3, ep 15)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>Kekoa (Warrior): The team investigate the brutal murder of a traditional fighting master. Plus, McGarrett gets more than he bargained for while keeping tabs on his mother. (S3, ep 16)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hawaii Five-0</title>
    <desc>Pa'ani (The Game): Five-0 need the help of American football star Arian Foster (guesting as himself) to solve the murder of an executive whose drink was spiked. (S3, ep 17)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Africa's Hunters</title>
    <desc>Kimba's Rise: In the Mwamba pride, hunting is left to the females as the males lurk in other territories with the intention of taking over other prides. (S3, ep 1)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Africa's Hunters</title>
    <desc>Pride and Prejudice: Milo's sibling is taken by a predator, so the males leave to find new females. Meanwhile, the animals find themselves threatened. (S3, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Africa's Hunters</title>
    <desc>The Misfits Come of Age: The Misfit is a charismatic cub who has had a rough ride as he was bullied by his big brothers and rejected by his mother. (S3, ep 3)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Police 24/7</title>
    <desc>A stolen truck leads police on a dangerous high-speed chase, a speeder gives the police an earful, and a disgruntled mom picks up her drunk son. Flashing images. (S1, ep 1)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Police 24/7</title>
    <desc>Get an intimate look at the men and women working in law enforcement across the country as they attempt to keep the streets safe from crime. Flashing images. (S1, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Police 24/7</title>
    <desc>A call to a shooting leads to a scuffle and a lost gun and an officer must clear squatters from an abandoned house. Flashing images. (S1, ep 3)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Bartless: When Bart's latest prank leads to chaos at Springfield Elementary, Marge and Homer dream of a world in which their rambunctious son was never a Simpson. (S34, ep 15)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530223000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Hostile Kirk Place: Kirk goes on a crusade to censor and control the school curriculum in response to a history lesson that paints one of his ancestors in a bad light. (S34, ep 16)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260530232500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Pin Gal: A mysterious figure from Marge's past returns to coach her for a bowling tournament. (S34, ep 17)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530232500 +0000" stop="20260530235000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Fan-Ily Feud: Homer publicly disparages a pop singer and faces the wrath of her vengeful fans. (S34, ep 18)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260530235000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Write Off This Episode: Marge is seduced by the money and prestige of Big Charity fundraising when she and Lisa launch a charity together. (S34, ep 19)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531001500 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicken Run</title>
    <desc>Top animation from the makers of Wallace and Gromit. A tale of battery hens and freedom, with star voices including Mel Gibson. (2000)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sport's Funniest Moments</title>
    <desc>From football to F1 and cricket to golf, enjoy some of the funniest and most farcical moments from the sporting world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Beekeeper</title>
    <desc>Jason Statham stings the enemy in a brutal hunt for vengeance, which escalates after he is revealed to be part of a powerful organisation. Action-packed Sky Original film. (2024)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531071500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Josh Widdicombe: Bit Much...</title>
    <desc>Recorded live at The London Palladium, Josh Widdicombe performs his hit stand-up, tackling hot comedy topics such as advent calendars, weddings and the closing time of his local park.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531071500 +0000" stop="20260531081000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Force: North East</title>
    <desc>As the documentary returns for a fifth season, officers race to a stabbing outside a pub in Newcastle and there is a raid on a cannabis farm. (S5, ep 1)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531081000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Force: North East</title>
    <desc>An emergency dash results in a serious collision between the police van and a taxi. Plus, officers race to save a man threatening to take his own life. (S5, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New: La Brea</title>
    <desc>Pilot: A massive sinkhole opens and splits the Harris family in two, with Eve and Josh sent to a mysterious primeval world... (S1, ep 1)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">New: La Brea</title>
    <desc>Day Two: With Josh's life on the line, Eve traverses the dangerous wilderness to save him. Gavin and Izzy work to prove survivors are alive inside the sinkhole. (S1, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Road Wars</title>
    <desc>Officers raid a huge cannabis plantation with over 650 plants, enough to harvest £25,000 of weed a week, while cops hunt down two burglars on the run in Ascot. Strong language. (S5, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway Patrol</title>
    <desc>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers. (S9, ep 3)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531123000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Highway Patrol</title>
    <desc>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers. (S9, ep 4)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Gunpowder Treason: A search for an abducted teenager leads the team to a member of the Witness Protection Program, and a decades-old political extremist group. (S3, ep 16)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Hotel LA: The SWAT team must protect a hotel full of civilians when a joint task force mission with the LAPD Gang Division goes badly wrong. (S3, ep 17)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>Stigma: When their former unit leader Buck goes off the grid, Hondo and the team confront their emotional difficulties as they race to save him. (S3, ep 18)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Last Day In Florida: Jim tries to protect Dwight from being fired and Andy discovers Erin's full intentions in Florida. (S8, ep 18)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Get The Girl: Andy heads to Florida to tell Erin that he loves her, while Nellie comes to Scranton with big plans for the office. (S8, ep 19)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Welcome Party: Andy tries to figure out how to break up with Jessica, while the Scranton staff attempt to sabotage Nellie's welcome party. (S8, ep 20)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531173000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Office (US)</title>
    <desc>Angry Andy: Andy releases his angry side as he fights to get his job back from Nellie, while Pam finds Kelly a potential new boyfriend. (S8, ep 21)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>The Very Hungry Caterpillars: When a plague of insects shuts down Springfield, the Simpsons face their greatest challenge yet - spending time in lockdown with each other. (S34, ep 20)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531183000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Clown V. Board of Education: Krusty opens a school for clowning, and it becomes the most successful thing he's ever done. (S34, ep 21)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Homer's Adventure Through the Windshield Glass: After Homer crashes his car and flies through the windshield, a magical friend reveals a secret truth about his marriage. (S34, ep 22)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531193000 +0000" stop="20260531195500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Lard of the Dance: Homer thinks he can make a fortune by recycling grease and Lisa helps to organise a school dance. Featuring the guest voice of Lisa Kudrow. (S10, ep 1)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531195500 +0000" stop="20260531202000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>The Wizard of Evergreen Terrace: Homer experiences a mid-life crisis and is inspired to become an inventor. Featuring the voice of William Daniels as Kit the Car. (S10, ep 2)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531202000 +0000" stop="20260531204500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Simpsons</title>
    <desc>Bart the Mother: Bart tends to a nest filled with eggs after he inadvertently kills a bird with an air rifle. With the guest voice of the late Phil Hartman. (S10, ep 3)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531204500 +0000" stop="20260531214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Attenborough's Global...</title>
    <desc>...Adventure: To celebrate Sir David Attenborough's 100th birthday, we look back to when he went on a seven-year journey. From the stunning Great Barrier Reef to the rainforests of Borneo.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531214500 +0000" stop="20260531224500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Attenborough's Global...</title>
    <desc>...Adventure - Home Planet: To celebrate David Attenborough's 100th birthday, join him when he embarked on a seven-year journey. From the Great Barrier Reef to the jungles of Borneo.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531224500 +0000" stop="20260531234500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">David Attenborough's Global...</title>
    <desc>...Adventure: The Rise of Nature. Mark Sir David Attenborough's 100th birthday as he explores life on our planet, starting from seabeds hundreds of millions of years ago to life today.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="12517" start="20260531234500 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The BFG</title>
    <desc>An orphan girl befriends a gentle giant who takes her to Giant Country, where they attempt to stop evil tyrants from invading the human world. Fantasy fun from Steven Spielberg. (2016)</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught On Dashcam</title>
    <desc>From distracted drivers to animals on the attack and an unmissable heroic rescue - join us for a brand-new episode of Caught on Dashcam.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530124000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught Red Handed</title>
    <desc>A couple on holiday get a nasty shock when their phone shows a burglar on the prowl back home. A gang of men get caught in a trap while stealing cheese from a factory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530124000 +0000" stop="20260530132000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught Red Handed</title>
    <desc>A shopkeeper gets a surprise when his regular customer suddenly becomes an armed robber. An elderly man falls victim to a thieving carer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530132000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught Red Handed</title>
    <desc>A city unites to take down small-business thieves, a couple use their baby buggy to steal beer, and a jeweller thinks on his feet when he's targeted by armed robbers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Documentary series following Australian Customs and Border Protection officers as they attempt to enforce the country's customs, quarantine and immigration laws.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530143000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Documentary series following Australian Customs and Border Protection officers as they attempt to enforce the country's customs, quarantine and immigration laws.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Documentary series following Australian Customs and Border Protection officers as they attempt to enforce the country's customs, quarantine and immigration laws.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530153000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Documentary series following Australian Customs and Border Protection officers as they attempt to enforce the country's customs, quarantine and immigration laws.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Documentary series following Australian Customs and Border Protection officers as they attempt to enforce the country's customs, quarantine and immigration laws.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530163000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530173000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530183000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530193000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught On Dashcam</title>
    <desc>From blockbuster smashes and explosive road rage, to crazy police chases and thieving animals - it's all Caught on Dashcam in this epic series finale.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Blue Bloods</title>
    <desc>Frank faces a dilemma when a veteran who became a local celebrity asks him to make an exception to the NYPD recruitment age limit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Doc</title>
    <desc>Richard seeks redemption after a hostile reception, helping an exhausted worker. Meanwhile, Amy and TJ treat a lawyer, leading to unexpected complications.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chicago Fire</title>
    <desc>Severide and Violet clash with Paramedic Chief Robinson. Capp and Tony attempt to break a world record.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Equalizer</title>
    <desc>McCall's quest to prove that a famous rapper is innocent of murdering a fellow artist drags her into a deadly battle between rival rap crews.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531010000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Good Doctor</title>
    <desc>Dr Shaun Murphy unknowingly creates a competition when he introduces a new performance rating system.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Watson</title>
    <desc>Respect the Quirks: Watson examines a case with a mentally unstable mother whose delusions reflect his own recently discovered hallucinations.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Brit Cops: Rapid Response</title>
    <desc>Action-packed documentary following rapid response officers, the fastest cops in Britain, as they crack down on crime. Time is of the essence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A1: Highway Patrol</title>
    <desc>A suspected stolen vehicle leads police to pull a driver who is found to be over the drink drive limit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Road Wars</title>
    <desc>This observational documentary returns for a fifth series following the Thames Valley Police. Officers hit the jackpot in Slough's biggest ever drugs raid. Strong language.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531064000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught Red Handed</title>
    <desc>A couple on holiday get a nasty shock when their phone shows a burglar on the prowl back home. A gang of men get caught in a trap while stealing cheese from a factory.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531064000 +0000" stop="20260531072000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught Red Handed</title>
    <desc>A shopkeeper gets a surprise when his regular customer suddenly becomes an armed robber. An elderly man falls victim to a thieving carer.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531072000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught Red Handed</title>
    <desc>A city unites to take down small-business thieves, a couple use their baby buggy to steal beer, and a jeweller thinks on his feet when he's targeted by armed robbers.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A1: Highway Patrol</title>
    <desc>Police race to the scene of a head-on collision and a milk lorry overturns, bringing rush hour chaos to the A1.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Send In The Dogs UK</title>
    <desc>Documentary following the work of Britain's police dogs in real operations, sniffing out everything from drugs and weapons to counterfeit money. Ken Stott narrates.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Border Patrol</title>
    <desc>New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531103000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Border Patrol</title>
    <desc>New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Border Patrol</title>
    <desc>New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531113000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Border Patrol</title>
    <desc>New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Border Security USA</title>
    <desc>Documentary exploring the extreme measures people take to break US security laws and America's desperate fight against drugs, illegal immigration and terrorism.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Stop Search Seize</title>
    <desc>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531143000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531153000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531173000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531183000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531193000 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Nothing To Declare</title>
    <desc>Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Caught On Dashcam</title>
    <desc>Buckle up! It's time for a new series of Caught on Dashcam. The show that brings you the thrills and spills from the world of driving - all caught on camera.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Watson</title>
    <desc>Respect the Quirks: Watson examines a case with a mentally unstable mother whose delusions reflect his own recently discovered hallucinations.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="9577" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Rookie</title>
    <desc>The team works together after Nolan and Celina discover a possible suicide that spirals into a conspiracy.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530113000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530123000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530133000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530143000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530153000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Andy Griffith Show</title>
    <desc>Andy Taylor is the widower sheriff of the small, sleepy North Carolina town of Mayberry. Andy and son Opie live with Aunt Bee, who takes care of the family. Andy's deputy is his bumbling but neurotically hilarious cousin, Barney Fife. Among Andy's Mayberry friends is the town's resident barber, Floyd.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530163000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Patriot Games</title>
    <desc>When former CIA agent Jack Ryan (Harrison Ford) hampers an IRA terrorist attack in London, he kills one of the terrorists. The dead man's brother, another member of the group named Sean Miller (Sean Bean), is arrested but quickly escapes. Vowing revenge against Ryan, Miller travels to the United States, where he forces Ryan's wife (Anne Archer) and daughter (Thora Birch) into a car accident that b</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Clear and Present Danger</title>
    <desc>Agent Jack Ryan (Harrison Ford) becomes acting deputy director of the CIA when Admiral Greer (James Earl Jones) is diagnosed with cancer. When an American businessman, and friend of the president, is murdered on a yacht, Ryan starts discovering links between the man and drug dealers. As CIA agent John Clark (Willem Dafoe) is sent to Colombia to kill drug kingpins in retaliation, Ryan must fight th</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beverly Hills Cop</title>
    <desc>After his childhood buddy is murdered while visiting Detroit, rebellious cop Axel Foley (Eddie Murphy) follows the leads to Beverly Hills, Calif., under the auspices of a vacation. He checks in with old friend Jenny Summers (Lisa Eilbacher) and starts to believe her boss, art dealer Victor Maitland (Steven Berkoff), might somehow be involved in the murder. However, Lt. Bogomil (Ronny Cox) of the B</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531001500 +0000" stop="20260531021500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beverly Hills Cop II</title>
    <desc>The hard-nosed Detroit cop returns to Los Angeles to help solve another case. This time he must direct his efforts towards unraveling the Alphabet Crimes, a series of robberies committed by leather-jacketed punks. The investigation puts him on the trail of an illegal arms dealer and his hit lady.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531021500 +0000" stop="20260531044500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Road House</title>
    <desc>The Double Deuce is the meanest, loudest and rowdiest bar south of the Mason-Dixon Line, and Dalton (Patrick Swayze) has been hired to clean it up. He might not look like much, but the Ph.D.-educated bouncer proves he's more than capable -- busting the heads of troublemakers and turning the roadhouse into a jumping hot-spot. But Dalton's romance with the gorgeous Dr. Clay (Kelly Lynch) puts him on</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531044500 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Outlaw Josey Wales</title>
    <desc>Josey Wales watches helplessly as his wife and child are murdered by Union men led by Capt. Terrill. Seeking revenge, Wales joins the Confederate Army. He refuses to surrender when the war ends, but his fellow soldiers go to hand over their weapons -- and are massacred by Terrill. Wales guns down some of Terrill's men and flees to Texas, where he tries to make a new life for himself, but the bount</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Warriors</title>
    <desc>A turf battle between New York City street gangs that rages from Coney Island to the Bronx. The Warriors are mistakenly fingered for the killing of a gang leader. Soon they have every gang in the city out to get revenge, and they must make their way across the city to their own turf.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531121500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Rocky Balboa</title>
    <desc>Now long-retired, Rocky (Sylvester Stallone) runs a Philadelphia eatery and mourns the loss of his beloved wife, Adrian. Yearning to recapture a bit of his glory days, he plans to re-enter the ring for a few low-profile, local matches. All that changes when Rocky accepts a challenge to fight the world's reigning heavyweight champion, Mason "the Line" Dixon (Antonio Tarver).</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531121500 +0000" stop="20260531143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beverly Hills Cop</title>
    <desc>After his childhood buddy is murdered while visiting Detroit, rebellious cop Axel Foley (Eddie Murphy) follows the leads to Beverly Hills, Calif., under the auspices of a vacation. He checks in with old friend Jenny Summers (Lisa Eilbacher) and starts to believe her boss, art dealer Victor Maitland (Steven Berkoff), might somehow be involved in the murder. However, Lt. Bogomil (Ronny Cox) of the B</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531143000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beverly Hills Cop II</title>
    <desc>The hard-nosed Detroit cop returns to Los Angeles to help solve another case. This time he must direct his efforts towards unraveling the Alphabet Crimes, a series of robberies committed by leather-jacketed punks. The investigation puts him on the trail of an illegal arms dealer and his hit lady.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Road House</title>
    <desc>The Double Deuce is the meanest, loudest and rowdiest bar south of the Mason-Dixon Line, and Dalton (Patrick Swayze) has been hired to clean it up. He might not look like much, but the Ph.D.-educated bouncer proves he's more than capable -- busting the heads of troublemakers and turning the roadhouse into a jumping hot-spot. But Dalton's romance with the gorgeous Dr. Clay (Kelly Lynch) puts him on</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Black Hawk Down</title>
    <desc>In 1993, the U.S. sends special forces into Somalia to destabilize the government and bring food and humanitarian aid to the starving population. Using Black Hawk helicopters to lower the soldiers onto the ground, an unexpected attack by Somalian forces brings two of the helicopters down immediately. From there, the U.S. soldiers must struggle to regain their balance while enduring heavy gunfire.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465138" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Iron Eagle</title>
    <desc>When Col. Ted Masters' (Tim Thomerson) plane goes down in an Arab country, and he's sentenced to death for trespassing, his 18-year-old son, Doug (Jason Gedrick), is determined to save him. Unfortunately, Doug isn't the best fighter pilot -- he wasn't accepted into the Air Force because he needs to listen to music in order to hit a target. So he enlists the help of Col. Chappy (Louis Gossett Jr.) </desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Any Day Now</title>
    <desc>M.E. is in the crossfire of a school shooting; René has heart palpitations; bullies pressure young Collier to end his friendship with René.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Touched by an Angel</title>
    <desc>Monica and Tess must prevent a jealous widower from destroying his son's friendship with the town eccentric.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>While traveling with her publisher's assistant in Amish country, Jessica's involvement in a traffic mishap leads her to a murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica comes to the aid of a small-town diner's owner (Dee Wallace Stone), who becomes an outcast when she is blamed for three arsenic poisoning deaths.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A writer is murdered after sending Jessica a manuscript exposing a kidnapping scam, and Jessica's friend, private investigator Harry McGraw (Jerry Orbach) is caught near the body.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>A monk (Clyde Kusatsu) teaches Billie how to use her power of projection to find her sister; Phoebe celebrates her independence by throwing a housewarming party that gets out of control.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>When Henry gets too involved in her magical world, Paige begins to realize the difficulties of dating a mortal; Billie finds her missing sister, Christy (Marnette Patterson), whom demons have held captive for years.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Piper organizes an engagement party for Paige and Henry, but the couple begin to get cold feet.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Phoebe goes on a journey through her past loves to try to revive her excitement for romance; a group of magical teens comes to the manor seeking refuge from demons.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Coop realizes that he has fallen for Phoebe, but she yearns to be with a mortal; Piper tracks down killer demons.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Phoebe and Piper plot to get Leo back; Paige saves her new charge from two Darklighters; Billie must make an important decision.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>Billie and Christy use magic in an effort to destroy the reputations of the Charmed Ones.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Charmed</title>
    <desc>The Charmed Ones are stuck in the Underworld; Leo's ghost appears to Piper and offers demonic approval; a large battle ensues.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Lorelai and Sookie are thrilled when author Norman Mailer and a young reporter make return visits to the inn's dining room, but Sookie's awe turns to annoyance when the writer fails to order any food.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531010000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Logan brings Rory to an event staged by his secret society, where she finds herself participating in a thrilling and dangerous stunt.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Rory is touched when Emily and Richard throw a party to introduce her to their Yale alumni friends; when Dean arrives at the party to pick up Rory, it is clear to him that he has no place in her privileged world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Rory and Lorelai decide to confront Richard and Emily, individually, about their separation, but when Emily announces her plans to start dating again, they have no chance.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gilmore Girls</title>
    <desc>Rory is delighted that her former headmaster asks her to host a girl who is thinking of applying to Yale; Lorelai and Luke have their first fight when she buys an old boat that had belonged to his father.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghost Whisperer</title>
    <desc>When a fire breaks out at Rockland University, Jim saves a professor, Eli, who has a near-death experience; Melinda befriends Eli and realizes he shares her ability.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghost Whisperer</title>
    <desc>Melinda reconnects with old high-school friends after one of their classmates dies mysteriously.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ghost Whisperer</title>
    <desc>Melinda tracks down a ghost who is targeting girls on a social-networking Website.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Medium</title>
    <desc>When Allison buys a camcorder for Joe's birthday, she begins to see images that seem to be linked to a murder that may or may not have happened.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Medium</title>
    <desc>Allison has visions that contradict the findings of an FBI profiler helping on a potential serial-killer case, causing him to question the source of her information.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Strong Medicine</title>
    <desc>A boy has a heart attack after being shot with a stun gun at school; Dylan gambles on a patient's treatment for a rare form of MS; a patient comes in after being exposed to ricin.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Any Day Now</title>
    <desc>M.E. writes about the importance of the Confederate flag; René handles a case involving nursing-home residents; René and Judge "Turk" Terhune try to figure out where their relationship is going; young René and M.E. explore feminism.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Journey With Dylan Dreyer</title>
    <desc>Dylan tours South Africa's Wild Coast to discover one of the last great ocean wildernesses and witness the amazing animals drawn here from around the globe.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531123000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Recipe Rehab</title>
    <desc>Chef Richard answers questions, reveals kitchen tricks, market essentials and how to prepare healthy meals quickly.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica takes a teaching position in New York, gets an apartment and finds its previous tenant murdered.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A policeman-turned-professor challenges Jessica to solve a series of campus muggings that soon escalates to murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>A friend (Bradford Dillman) is suspected of killing the author (Jessica Walter) who was writing an unauthorized biography of his wife.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Sheriff Metzger assumes his younger brother, the black sheep of the family, is guilty of murder, as charged.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>New computer owner Jessica discovers hackers gathering information for blackmail, a crime that leads to murder.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica probes a 20-year-old unsolved murder after attending the funeral of a New Orleans jazz great.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica attempts to prove a battered wife innocent of killing her husband after failing to convince the woman to defend herself.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>Jessica tries to disprove charges against her friend's boyfriend, suspected of murdering a Las Vegas casino manager.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Murder, She Wrote</title>
    <desc>After Jessica speaks at an exclusive men's club, they ask her to investigate when one of their members is murdered, and they are all suspects.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260531230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elementary</title>
    <desc>Joan tackles her first solo case when a woman disappears after leaving a tearful breakup video for her husband.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260531230000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elementary</title>
    <desc>Sherlock and Joan try to prevent a robbery during a snow storm; Sherlock tries to help a transgender woman who recently went through a breakup.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465278" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Elementary</title>
    <desc>Joan and Sherlock search for a murdered blackmailer's accomplice; Sherlock doesn't want to celebrate his first year of sobriety.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jeffersons</title>
    <desc>Louise and George each try to duck out of celebrating their wedding anniversary.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530113000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jeffersons</title>
    <desc>Harry wants to get rid of his lady house-guest.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jeffersons</title>
    <desc>A new clause in George's will upsets Louise.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530123000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jeffersons</title>
    <desc>A highly successful but unconventional stockbroker fascinates George.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jeffersons</title>
    <desc>George tries to make points with a local banker while Allan tries to make points with the banker's daughter.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530133000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Jeffersons</title>
    <desc>Billy Dee Williams can't convince Florence that he really is who he says he is.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Raising Fame</title>
    <desc>Four-time NBA champion and NBA Hall of Famer, Shaquille O'Neal, sits down with Mom Lucille to tell the story about how he overcame a difficult childhood to become the icon in sports, business and entertainment that he is today.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Unsung</title>
    <desc>Portraits of trailblazing athletes, from Jesse Owens and Bill Russell to Venus Williams and Laila Ali, who helped change the game -- and the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>James is determined to press charges in court after J.J. receives a flesh wound in a gang war.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530163000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Thelma catches her cousin nipping at the family liquor supply.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>James is sure that the new job he has been promised is the answer to the family's troubles.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530173000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Florida's dream of finally getting her high-school diploma is clouded by James' opposition to the idea.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Florida and James are torn between letting J.J. do a portrait and their misgivings about the prospective model.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530183000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>The Evans family risks eviction to open a fix-it shop in their apartment.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>J.J. finds out that his date has snobbish parents that disapprove of him.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530193000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>The Evanses are afraid they may be eating dog food when an elderly neighbor brings the main course for dinner.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>James suspects that there's more than meets the eye when an old friend pays a visit.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530203000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>J.J. announces that his immediate future could include matrimony.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>The Evans family faces an economic crisis after both James and J.J. lose their jobs.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530213000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Thelma gets a scholarship offer from an exclusive girls school.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260530223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>A small-fry extortionist bullies Michael into handing over his milk money on a daily basis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530223000 +0000" stop="20260530230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>James buys a gun to protect the family from a rash of crimes in the neighborhood.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530230000 +0000" stop="20260530233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>The family discovers that the high-paying job James has been offered has one major drawback.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260530233000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>James insists that Florida stay in a private hospital instead of the clinic for a minor operation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531000000 +0000" stop="20260531003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>James is miserable to be around, and money -- or the lack of it -- is responsible.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531003000 +0000" stop="20260531010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>The family is divided when James and Florida support rival candidates in a local election.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531010000 +0000" stop="20260531013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Thelma receives unexpected support for her engagement to "Mr. Right.".</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531013000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Florida and James go off to a mountain cabin for a romantic celebration of their 20th wedding anniversary.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Florida gets the biggest surprise when she gives a surprise baby shower.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531023000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Florida fears the worst when a change in school causes a change in Michael.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>The fact that Willona's new boyfriend has a physical disability creates a very awkward problem.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531033000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Good Times</title>
    <desc>Florida pickets the neighborhood supermarket after a roast from the store makes everyone sick.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Girlfriends' Getaway 2</title>
    <desc>Chaos strikes when a gushing bride (Garcelle Beauvais) and her three friends (Essence Atkins, Terri J. Vaughn) travel to San Juan, Puerto Rico, for an exotic wedding.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>To save Flavor, Khadijah sells a partial interest to a conglomerate; Synclaire attempts to cheer up Regine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531063000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Regine becomes a juror in a high-profile case; Synclaire helps an unemployed actor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Behind the Movement</title>
    <desc>Rosa Parks' refusal to give up her seat launched the history-making Montgomery Bus Boycott.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531092000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love That Girl</title>
    <desc>Jasmine's investment idea backfires after Imunique inducts her into an investment club; the group gets scammed and must call Pookie and Nem to retrieve their funds.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531092000 +0000" stop="20260531094000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love That Girl</title>
    <desc>Bridget had a pregnancy scare; Latrell takes advantage of Imunique and Fabian.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531094000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Love That Girl</title>
    <desc>Latrell and Imunique find a lot of money; Delroy has been kidnapped.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>To save Flavor, Khadijah sells a partial interest to a conglomerate; Synclaire attempts to cheer up Regine.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531103000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Regine becomes a juror in a high-profile case; Synclaire helps an unemployed actor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Kyle attends his high-school reunion and confronts the school bully, who is leading a rather grim existence.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531113000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Regine helps a couple plan a graveyard wedding; Khadijah dates her anesthesiologist.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Quarterback Jeff Blake mistakenly attends Max and Gary's dinner party.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531123000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Synclaire realizes her true talent when she stands in as the lead in a play.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Khadijah and her new beau attend a holiday event with the snobbish medical elite.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531133000 +0000" stop="20260531140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Regine coordinates her ex-boyfriend's wedding and becomes convinced he is marrying the wrong woman.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531140000 +0000" stop="20260531143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Regine's mother dates a debonair gentleman; Synclaire avoids Overton's new car.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531143000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Synclaire gets a job as a clown on a children's cable program but soon has problems with the show's star.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>Kyle and Maxine take off for some privacy; Synclaire and Overton decide to live together for the weekend.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531153000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Living Single</title>
    <desc>During a night out on the town, the women meet some interesting characters when they visit a gay bar.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Cliff asks his stuffy former English professor to be his partner in a pinochle game.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531163000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Cliff is determined to settle a score with a former track rival.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Clair puts Cliff on a diet after a friend suffers a mild heart attack.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531173000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Cliff and the gang comb the house in search of an elusive snake.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Grandma and Grandpa Huxtable celebrate their 50th wedding anniversary with the Count Basie Orchestra.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531183000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Theo is torn between two women; Cliff joins Rudy for a spot of tea.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Friends urge Vanessa to wear makeup even though Clair doesn't allow it.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531193000 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Theo is disappointed after he gets an average grade on a history paper that he was sure would get an A.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Theo is inspired by a school speaker and asks his parents for flying lessons.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531203000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Vanessa is labeled a conceited rich girl after two girls visit her home.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Denise tries to explain to her parents why she received a below-average grade on an English paper.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531213000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Cosby Show</title>
    <desc>Rudy finds a lost dog, but has trouble letting go when its owner comes to get it.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260531223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Fred thinks that Lamont's African dress and customs are ludicrous until he hears what they include.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531223000 +0000" stop="20260531230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Fred is aghast when Lamont dates the sister of their Puerto Rican neighbor.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531230000 +0000" stop="20260531233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Fred is upset about Lamont spending a lot of time with Julio and ignoring him, so he tries to make his son feel guilty by discussing burial insurance with a funeral home agent.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260531233000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Lamont is upset when Fred announces that he plans to marry a young woman he has just met.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465208" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sanford &amp; Son</title>
    <desc>Fred moves to a senior citizens home when Lamont decides to travel around the world.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530110000 +0000" stop="20260530113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic Platinum Rarity</title>
    <desc>Get the first and only American coin honoring the Declaration of Independence today! This specially minted 2026 Platinum Eagle graded PF70UCAM celebrates 250 years of America with a design featuring the quill used by the Founding Fathers in 1776!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530113000 +0000" stop="20260530120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Epic Platinum Rarity</title>
    <desc>Get the first and only American coin honoring the Declaration of Independence today! This specially minted 2026 Platinum Eagle graded PF70UCAM celebrates 250 years of America with a design featuring the quill used by the Founding Fathers in 1776!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530120000 +0000" stop="20260530130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Gamble, No Future</title>
    <desc>Pacheco's top pair is rivered by Robl but then holds on the next hand. Gavri wins with pocket queens but then loses a huge pot with pocket aces.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530130000 +0000" stop="20260530140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Gamble, No Future</title>
    <desc>Phil Hellmuth headlines and is joined by Jennifer Tilly, Randy "3Coin" Sadler, Luiz "Brazil God" Rizental, Pink, and Pedro Velasco Adnet. Freddy Hamad and Alex Aqel debut.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530140000 +0000" stop="20260530150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Verdict</title>
    <desc>Deciding the greatest tennis player in history, Federer, Nadal or Djokovic.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530150000 +0000" stop="20260530160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Verdict</title>
    <desc>Who is the best two sport athlete in history, Bo Jackson vs Deion Sanders? The Verdict decides.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530160000 +0000" stop="20260530170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Verdict</title>
    <desc>Who is the greatest golfer of all time, Jack Nicklaus vs Tiger Woods? The Verdict decides.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530170000 +0000" stop="20260530180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Verdict</title>
    <desc>Could prime Mike Tyson defeat Prime Muhammad Ali? The Verdict decides.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530180000 +0000" stop="20260530190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Verdict</title>
    <desc>Has Shohei Ohtani become a greater baseball player than Babe Ruth?</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530190000 +0000" stop="20260530200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the Cage</title>
    <desc>On the verge of financial ruin, the UFC bets everything on an MMA reality television show; the result gives rise to a juggernaut and helps create the Dana White people know today.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530200000 +0000" stop="20260530210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MotoAmerica Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Road America in Elkhart Lake, Wis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530210000 +0000" stop="20260530220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the Cage</title>
    <desc>When UFC pioneer Evan Tanner is found dead of heat exposure alone in the California desert, the MMA world wonders what led to his passing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260530220000 +0000" stop="20260531000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: Arena Football One</title>
    <desc>From AMSOIL Arena in Duluth, Minn.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531010000 +0000" stop="20260531020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the Cage</title>
    <desc>When UFC pioneer Evan Tanner is found dead of heat exposure alone in the California desert, the MMA world wonders what led to his passing.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531020000 +0000" stop="20260531030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the Cage</title>
    <desc>When Japan's PRIDE Fighting Championships' president commits suicide, questions arise about its ties to organized crime.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531030000 +0000" stop="20260531040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the Cage</title>
    <desc>Dark clouds circle over PRIDE, a worldwide popular MMA promotion, when rival Yakuza gangs collide and shadowy secrets come out into the open.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531040000 +0000" stop="20260531050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Gamble, No Future</title>
    <desc>Jennifer Tilly dominates with a straight, doubles up with ace-queen, stacks an opponent with aces, and wins the final pot of the night with two pair.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531050000 +0000" stop="20260531060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Gamble, No Future</title>
    <desc>Freddy Hamad begins by turning two massive hands and then dragging a few more pots. Luis "Brazil God" Rizental finds pocket queens before the Stand-Up Game begins.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531060000 +0000" stop="20260531063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">That's Delicious</title>
    <desc>Concert in Alaska; fly-fishing; eating with an Eskimo; emergency surgery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531063000 +0000" stop="20260531070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">That's Delicious</title>
    <desc>Action and Meyhem have spent their lives eating Jamaican food in Queens, but now they head to Jamaica for some real jerk chicken; music video for Meyhem's new single.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531070000 +0000" stop="20260531080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Gamble, No Future</title>
    <desc>Jennifer Tilly dominates with a straight, doubles up with ace-queen, stacks an opponent with aces, and wins the final pot of the night with two pair.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531080000 +0000" stop="20260531090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">No Gamble, No Future</title>
    <desc>Freddy Hamad begins by turning two massive hands and then dragging a few more pots. Luis "Brazil God" Rizental finds pocket queens before the Stand-Up Game begins.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531090000 +0000" stop="20260531093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">That's Delicious</title>
    <desc>Concert in Alaska; fly-fishing; eating with an Eskimo; emergency surgery.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531093000 +0000" stop="20260531100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">That's Delicious</title>
    <desc>Action and Meyhem have spent their lives eating Jamaican food in Queens, but now they head to Jamaica for some real jerk chicken; music video for Meyhem's new single.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531100000 +0000" stop="20260531103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Aging Brain</title>
    <desc>Learn what's behind mental decline with age, and how to improve memory, focus and concentration with NeuroQ's Darrin Peterson and Dale Bredesen MD.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531103000 +0000" stop="20260531110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531110000 +0000" stop="20260531113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">NECTAR TRI-PILLOW -Cooler, Comfy, Better Sleep! Buy One Get One FREE!</title>
    <desc>Discover the Nectar Tri-Comfort Cooling Pillow for the ultimate sleep experience! Adjustable to three firmness levels to provide customized support and cooling all night long. Order NOW to get a second pillow FREE, plus a 30-night home trial!</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531113000 +0000" stop="20260531120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Natural Blood Pressure Management</title>
    <desc>Cardiologist Dr. Ernst von Schwarz, M.D. shows how to manage your blood pressure naturally and help protect your heart for life with My Best Heart.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531120000 +0000" stop="20260531130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">King of the Road</title>
    <desc>Element skates a real tank with Louie; Zion gets a very special surprise on P-Stone day; Foundation's run in San Francisco ends with a stomach-turning prank on Nick.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531130000 +0000" stop="20260531150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Major League Fishing</title>
    <desc>Four teams compete in Florida for Elimination Match 2 to advance to the Knockout Rounds. From Nov. 17-22, 2024 in Indian River County, Fla.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531150000 +0000" stop="20260531160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Soccer's American Dream</title>
    <desc>The success of World Cup '94 spawns a new men's pro-league, the MLS. But major startup problems and a fractured men's national team make headlines heading into the new millennium.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531160000 +0000" stop="20260531170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Soccer's American Dream</title>
    <desc>In the late 80s, the newly formed US women's national team faces an uphill fight for recognition. But a winning formula brings home two World Cups and Olympic Gold in just 10 years.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531170000 +0000" stop="20260531180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Soccer's American Dream</title>
    <desc>By the mid-80s pro-soccer had collapsed and the US men's national team hadn't made a World Cup in decades. So what better time to launch a bid to bring the 1994 edition to America.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531180000 +0000" stop="20260531190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Soccer's American Dream</title>
    <desc>The North American Soccer League was supposed to light to fuse on pro-soccer in 70s America, so what went wrong?; meanwhile, the country's women are just trying to get on the field.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531190000 +0000" stop="20260531200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the 90s</title>
    <desc>The Viper Room was a refuge for young Hollywood to hide from the prying eyes of the press, until one fateful night when the death of a rising star instantly made it headline news.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531200000 +0000" stop="20260531210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Live: MotoAmerica Superbike Championship</title>
    <desc>From Road America in Elkhart Lake, Wis.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531210000 +0000" stop="20260531220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the 90s</title>
    <desc>For almost 50 years, SNL has launched comedy careers, but if one's lucky enough to get in, one may never get out alive.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531220000 +0000" stop="20260531230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the 90s</title>
    <desc>Robert Downey Jr. turns his troubled backstory into a superpower; while battling a string of addictions, Downey reinvents himself into one of the most celebrated actors today.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260531230000 +0000" stop="20260601000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the 90s</title>
    <desc>The Southern California sun, action and laser-focus on beauty make "Baywatch" appeal to more than a billion people worldwide.</desc>
    <date>2026-05-31</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="465234" start="20260601000000 +0000" stop="20260602000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Dark Side of the 90s</title>
    <desc>The story of how the upstart Fox Network forever changed television, and continues to have prevalence decades later.</desc>
    <date>2026-06-01</date>
  </programme>
</tv>