<tv date="20260407125034 " generator-info-name="TV5-Multi-XML-Processor" generator-info-url="https://github.com/r56wdvm6d5-cloud/epguk" source-info-name="TV5-Source-EPG"><channel id="464105">
    <display-name lang="India">SET HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="463922">
    <display-name lang="India">SONY SAB</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="463918">
    <display-name lang="India">STAR PLUS</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <channel id="441340">
    <display-name lang="India">ZEE TV HD</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="464105" start="20260407124000 +0000" stop="20260407133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Best of Crime Patrol</title>
    <desc>A compilation of the best cases investigated in 'Crime Patrol' showcases people from different walks of life falling victim to the vices of others or their own.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464105" start="20260407133000 +0000" stop="20260407140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mere Sai - Shraddha Aur Saburi</title>
    <desc>The British officers follow Mansingh to Shirdi with the intention to arrest him. In the meantime, Sai offers to help Mansingh but Mansingh remains sceptical.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464105" start="20260407140000 +0000" stop="20260407143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mere Sai - Shraddha Aur Saburi</title>
    <desc>Mansingh breaks down when he remembers the massacre of his community. In the meantime, the British officers frantically search for Mansingh.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464105" start="20260407143000 +0000" stop="20260407150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mere Sai - Shraddha Aur Saburi</title>
    <desc>The residents of Shirdi face a lot of inconveniences when the British officers interfere. On the other hand, Mansingh gets into trouble because of his impulsive decisions.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464105" start="20260407150000 +0000" stop="20260407153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mere Sai - Shraddha Aur Saburi</title>
    <desc>The youngsters of Shirdi express their disapproval of Mansingh's presence in their town. On the other hand, Kulkarni fumes with rage when the British officers refuse to listen to him.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="464105" start="20260407153000 +0000" stop="20260408000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Wheel of Fortune</title>
    <desc>Contestants put their minds to solving word puzzles after spinning a giant wheel that determines the monetary value they are playing for.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="463922" start="20260407123000 +0000" stop="20260407130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah</title>
    <desc>Jethalal tries to impress Babita with his knowledge about foreign countries, but Daya ends up embarrassing him. Babita implores Iyer to buy a new fridge.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463922" start="20260407130000 +0000" stop="20260407133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah</title>
    <desc>Babita and Iyer select a fridge for their house from Jethalal's shop. Jethalal begins to panic when Nattu Kaka accidentally sells the model to someone else.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463922" start="20260407133000 +0000" stop="20260407140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah</title>
    <desc>Jethalal ends up with multiple pieces of the same refrigerator to please Babita. Iyer refuses to buy a refrigerator from him.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463922" start="20260407140000 +0000" stop="20260407143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah</title>
    <desc>Jethalal is irked at Iyer over the refrigerator fiasco. Everyone looks forward to Diwali, and Tapu demands toys and clothes from Jethalal.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463922" start="20260407143000 +0000" stop="20260407150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Hui Gumm Yaadein Ek Doctor, Do Zindagiyaan</title>
    <desc>This is TV Show - Drama Category.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463922" start="20260407150000 +0000" stop="20260407153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Taarak Mehta Ka Ooltah Chashmah</title>
    <desc>The residents of a housing society help each other find solutions when they face common real-life challenges and get involved in sticky situations.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463922" start="20260407153000 +0000" stop="20260408000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Itti Si Khushi</title>
    <desc>Anvita shoulders the burden of raising her five siblings amidst their father's alcoholism.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="463918" start="20260407110000 +0000" stop="20260407133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Yeh Rishta Kya Kehlata Hai</title>
    <desc>Dr Abhimanyu, a misogamist, finds himself getting attracted to Akshara, Kartik and Naira's daughter. Things take a tricky turn when Akshara's half-sister, Arohi, falls in love with him.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463918" start="20260407133000 +0000" stop="20260407140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tod Kar Dil Mera</title>
    <desc>Raushni supports her husband's dream of becoming an IAS officer. However, will a betrayal change her life and aspirations?</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463918" start="20260407140000 +0000" stop="20260407143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Taara</title>
    <desc>Taara, a gifted singer, and Yuvraaj, a wealthy heir, are bound by deep love. However, as class and family honour collide, the couple must confront relentless opposition to keep their love alive.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463918" start="20260407143000 +0000" stop="20260407150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Advocate Anjali Awasthi</title>
    <desc>Anjali Awasthi is a lawyer that struggles to achieve recognition in her field. But this desire to be recognised leads her to take on a challenging case that could help her achieve her dreams.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463918" start="20260407150000 +0000" stop="20260407152000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Mr &amp; Mrs Parshuram</title>
    <desc>Shivprasad lives a quiet life as a devoted husband and father, but he harbors a massive secret. Unknown to his family, he is also Parshuram, a highly skilled spy on dangerous missions.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="463918" start="20260407152000 +0000" stop="20260408000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Udne Ki Aasha</title>
    <desc>Though they get off to a bad start, an aspirational Saili and an unmotivated Sachin end up getting married. Saili then tries to turn her husband into a competent person.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
<programme channel="441340" start="20260407123000 +0000" stop="20260407130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tum Se Tum Tak</title>
    <desc>Anu thinks about her ring before seeing Aryavardhan, but Gayatri tells Jhende to keep them separated until Gopal and Pushpa come back. Meanwhile, at the temple, a mystery person helps out.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="441340" start="20260407130000 +0000" stop="20260407133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ganga Mai Ki Betiyaan</title>
    <desc>Sneha helps a nervous Ganga regain her confidence. Meanwhile, Vimla tries to gather evidence of Sneha and Siddhu's relationship.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="441340" start="20260407133000 +0000" stop="20260407140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Saru</title>
    <desc>Urmila restarts Bhola's vengeance against Saru and instructs him to kill her at Tara and Ramesh's anniversary party. Later, Anika invites Rajat to the party to widen the discord between Saru and Ved.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="441340" start="20260407140000 +0000" stop="20260407150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Lakshmi Nivas</title>
    <desc>A family drama exploring love, loyalty, and personal conflicts in a traditional household.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="441340" start="20260407150000 +0000" stop="20260407153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Tum Se Tum Tak</title>
    <desc>Aryavardhan attempts to see Anu, and Mansi's opposition causes concern for Harshvardhan. Later, Raghupati schemes against Anu and Aryavardhan while Gopal and Pushpa look for the unknown individual.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="441340" start="20260407153000 +0000" stop="20260408000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Ganga Mai Ki Betiyaan</title>
    <desc>Siddhu stands with Ganga before Bhaskar's review. Soon, berated for her lack of training, she rises to the occasion with Sneha's faith and Shantanu's counsel and impresses Bhaskar with exotic cuisine.</desc>
    <date>2026-04-07</date>
  </programme>
</tv>